<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>courier on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/courier/</link>
    <description>Recent content in courier on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/courier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MOL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mol/</guid>
      <description> MOL is a Japanese transport company headquartered in Toranomon, Minato, Tokyo, Japan. It is one of the largest shipping companies in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DHL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dhl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dhl/</guid>
      <description>DHL (Dalsey, Hillblom and Lynn) International GmbH is an American-founded German company which is now the international courier, parcel, and express mail division of the German logistics company Deutsche Post DHL. Deutsche Post DHL is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest logistics company, particularly in sea and air mail. The company delivers over 1.3 billion parcels per year
  Sourcel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FedEx</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fedex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fedex/</guid>
      <description>FedEx Corporation is an American multinational courier delivery services company headquartered in Memphis, Tennessee. The name &amp;ldquo;FedEx&amp;rdquo; is a syllabic abbreviation of the name of the company&amp;rsquo;s original air division, Federal Express (now FedEx Express), which was used from 1973 until 2000. The company is known for its overnight shipping service and pioneering a system that could track packages and provide real-time updates on package location (to help in finding lost packages), a feature that has now been implemented by most other carrier services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ups/</guid>
      <description> United Parcel Service (UPS) is an American multinational package delivery and supply chain management company.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>