<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Al Jazeera</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/al-jazeera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/al-jazeera/</guid>
      <description> Al Jazeera is a state-funded broadcaster in Doha, Qatar, owned by the Al Jazeera Media Network. Initially launched as an Arabic news and current-affairs satellite TV channel, Al Jazeera has since expanded into a network with several outlets, including the Internet and specialty television channels in multiple languages.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC News is an operational business division of the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) responsible for the gathering and broadcasting of news and current affairs. The department is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest broadcast news organisation and generates about 120 hours of radio and television output each day, as well as online news coverage. The service maintains 50 foreign news bureaux with more than 250 correspondents around the world. Fran Unsworth has been Director of News and Current Affairs since January 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC World News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC World News is the BBC&amp;rsquo;s international news and current affairs television channel. It has the largest audience of any channel, with an estimated 121 million viewers weekly in 2016&amp;frasl;2017, part of the estimated 372 million weekly audience of the BBC&amp;rsquo;s four main international news services. Launched on 11 March 1991 as BBC World Service Television outside Europe, its name was changed to BBC World on 16 January 1995 and to BBC World News on 21 April 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</guid>
      <description>CBC News is the division of the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation responsible for the news gathering and production of news programs on the corporation&amp;rsquo;s English-language operations, namely CBC Television, CBC Radio, CBC News Network, and CBC.ca. Founded in 1941, CBC News is the largest news broadcaster in Canada and has local, regional and national broadcasts and stations. It frequently collaborates with its French-language counterpart, Radio-Canada Info, although the two are organizationally separate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cna/</guid>
      <description> CNA is an English language news channel based in Singapore. It broadcasts free-to-air domestically and as a subscription network to 29 territories across Asia and Australia.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc/</guid>
      <description>CNBC is an American pay television business news channel that is owned by NBCUniversal Broadcast, Cable, Sports and News, a division of NBCUniversal, with both being ultimately owned by Comcast. Headquartered in Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey, the network primarily carries business day coverage of U.S. and international financial markets; following the end of the business day and on non-trading days, CNBC primarily carries financial and business-themed documentaries and reality shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn/</guid>
      <description> Cable News Network (CNN) is an American news-based pay television channel owned by AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. CNN was founded in 1980 by American media proprietor Ted Turner as a 24-hour cable news channel. Upon its launch, CNN was the first television channel to provide 24-hour news coverage, and was the first all-news television channel in the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN Airport</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport/</guid>
      <description> CNN Airport is an American out-of-home television network operated by CNN. The service broadcasts general news, weather, stock market updates, entertainment, and travel content to airports across the United States. The founding management was led by Jon Petrovich and Scott Weiss. Deborah Cooper was the inaugural vice president/general manager, and continues in the role today.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN en Espanol</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol/</guid>
      <description> CNN en Español (stylized as CN͠N) is a Pan-American Spanish-language news channel, owned by WarnerMedia. It was launched on pay television, on 17 March 1997.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNNplus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</guid>
      <description> CNN+ (CNN Plus) was a Spanish 24-hour television news channel. Launched in 1999 as a joint venture by Sogecable and Turner Broadcasting, a unit of Time Warner that owns CNN, it went off the air at the end of 28 December 2010. The management announced that CNN+ would be closed on 31 December 2010.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv/</guid>
      <description> CTV News Channel is a Canadian discretionary service that is owned by Bell Media (a wholly owned subsidiary of Bell Canada). It broadcasts national and international news headlines, breaking news, and information. The channel is headquartered at 9 Channel Nine Court in the Agincourt neighbourhood of Scarborough in the city of Toronto.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/echo-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/echo-tv/</guid>
      <description> Echo TV was a christian-conservative Hungarian television channel owned and operated by Echo Hungária TV Zrt , and founded in 2005 to cover business news. Later focusing on news broadcasting and public affairs, it was known as a supporter of Fidesz and KDNP.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Business</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-business/</guid>
      <description>Fox Business Network (also known as Fox Business) is an American pay television business news channel that is owned by the Fox News Group division of Fox Corporation. The network discusses business and financial news. Day-to-day operations are run by Kevin Magee, executive vice president of Fox News; Neil Cavuto manages content and business news coverage. As of February 2015, Fox Business Network is available to approximately 74,224,000 pay television households (63.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-news/</guid>
      <description>Fox News (officially Fox News Channel and abbreviated FNC) is an American pay television news channel. It is owned by the Fox News Group, which itself was owned by News Corporation from 1996–2013, 21st Century Fox from 2013–2019, and Fox Corporation since 2019. The channel broadcasts primarily from studios at 1211 Avenue of the Americas in New York City. Fox News is provided in 86 countries or overseas territories worldwide, with international broadcasts featuring Fox Extra segments during ad breaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France 24</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</guid>
      <description> France 24 (pronounced &amp;ldquo;France vingt-quatre&amp;rdquo;) is a state-owned international news and current affairs television network based in Paris. Its channels broadcast in French, English, Arabic, and Spanish and are aimed at the overseas market, similar to DD News, BBC World News, DW and RT.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HKBN</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn/</guid>
      <description> HKBN Limited (Chinese: 香港寬頻有限公司), commonly known for its subsidiary Hong Kong Broadband Network Limited (Chinese: 香港寬頻網絡), is a Hong Kong-based telecommunication company. Hong Kong Broadband Network Limited was established on 23 August 1999, is one of the largest residential broadband and telecommunications service providers in Hong Kong. HKBN operates in both Hong Kong and Guangzhou, and employs about 2,900 personnel
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i24 News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/i24-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/i24-news/</guid>
      <description> i24NEWS is an Israeli international 24-hour news and current affairs television channel located in Jaffa Port, Tel Aviv, Israel. It broadcasts in French, English and Arabic. The channel&amp;rsquo;s owner is Patrick Drahi, and the CEO is Frank Melloul.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>