<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel App</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</guid>
      <description>Marvel is a design, prototyping an collaboration application based in London, UK.
 Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailchimp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mailchimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mailchimp/</guid>
      <description>Mailchimp is a marketing automation platform and an email marketing service. The platform is a trading name of its operator, Rocket Science Group, an American company founded in 2001 by Ben Chestnut and Mark Armstrong with Dan Kurzius joining at a later date.Mailchimp began as a paid service and added a freemium option in 2009. Within a year its user base had grown from 85,000 to 450,000. By June 2014, it was sending over 10 billion emails per month on behalf of its users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rambler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</guid>
      <description> Rambler (Russian: Рамблер) is a Russian search engine and one of the biggest Russian web portals. It is owned by the Rambler Media Group and Prof-Media since 2006. It was launched in 1996 by Stack Ltd, including Sergey Lysakov, Dmitry Kryukov, Vladimir Samoylov and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutterfly</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shutterfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shutterfly/</guid>
      <description> Shutterfly, Inc. is an American Internet-based company, headquartered in Redwood City, California, and specializing in image-publishing services. Shutterfly&amp;rsquo;s flagship product is its photo book line. The company, founded in 1999, is currently led by Christopher North. The company went public in 2006. The Shutterfly customer base is heavily skewed toward women, who accounted for 80% of customers as reported in 2013.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripadvisor</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tripadvisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tripadvisor/</guid>
      <description> TripAdvisor, Inc. is an American travel and restaurant website company that shows hotel and restaurant reviews, accommodation bookings and other travel-related content. It also includes interactive travel forums.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</guid>
      <description>Yandex N.V. is a Russian multinational corporation specializing in Internet-related products and services, including search and information services, eCommerce, transportation, navigation, mobile applications, and online advertising. Yandex provides over 70 services in total. Incorporated in the Netherlands, Yandex primarily serves audiences in Russia and the Commonwealth of Independent States. The company founders and most of the team members are located in Russia. The company has 18 commercial offices worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon/</guid>
      <description>History of the Amazon Logo (from logomyway.com and 1000logos.net) The Amazon logo has had three different iterations over the years, but neither of the first two stuck around for very long. The company’s first logo was simply the word Amazon.com spelled out in black font with a larger, yellow font used for the “o”. This design was later replaced with a logo that featured the company name with a near-straight yellow line beneath it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/google/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/google/</guid>
      <description>About Google Google is an American multinational technology company that specializes in Internet-related services and products. These include online advertising technologies, search, cloud computing, software, and hardware. Google was founded in 1998 by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while they were Ph.D. students at Stanford University in California.
The current Google logo was released on Sept 1 2015. A sans serif logotype retains google’s distinct multi-color sequence, and a compact version of the Google icon works in small contexts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-web-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:21:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-web-services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>