<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>e on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/e/</link>
    <description>Recent content in e on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/e/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EFF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eff/</guid>
      <description> The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is an international non-profit digital rights group based in San Francisco, California. The foundation was formed in July 1990 by John Gilmore, John Perry Barlow and Mitch Kapor to promote Internet civil liberties.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expedia Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia-group/</guid>
      <description> Expedia Group is an American global travel technology company. Its websites, which are primarily travel fare aggregators and travel metasearch engines, include CarRentals.com, CheapTickets, Expedia.com, HomeAway, Hotels.com, Hotwire.com, Orbitz, Travelocity, trivago, and Venere.com.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emirates Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Emirates is an airline based in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. The airline is a subsidiary of The Emirates Group, which is wholly owned by the government of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Investment Corporation of Dubai. It is the largest airline in the Middle East, operating over 3,600 flights per week from its hub at Dubai International Airport, to more than 150 cities in 80 countries across six continents. Cargo activities are undertaken by Emirates SkyCargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ebay/</guid>
      <description>eBay Inc. (/ˈiːˌbeɪ/ EE-bay) is an American multinational e-commerce corporation based in San Jose, California that facilitates consumer-to-consumer and business-to-consumer sales through its website. eBay was founded by Pierre Omidyar in the autumn of 1995, and became a notable success story of the dot-com bubble. eBay is a multibillion-dollar business with operations in about 30 countries, as of 2011. The company manages the eBay website, an online auction and shopping website in which people and businesses buy and sell a wide variety of goods and services worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eno</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eno/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:04:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eno/</guid>
      <description>Abour Eno by Capital One Eno is your Capital One assistant that looks out for you and your money. Eno works 24&amp;frasl;7 to help you protect your money, shop safer online, and manage your Capital One accounts.
Eno helps you protect your money. When Eno spots unusual and suspicious activity, such as fraud, duplicate charges, and generous tips, Eno gives you a heads up through automated alerts and helps you resolve the issues on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>