<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>e on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/e/</link>
    <description>Recent content in e on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/e/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Electronic Arts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/electronic-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/electronic-arts/</guid>
      <description>Electronic Arts Inc. (EA) is an American video game company headquartered in Redwood City, California. It is the second-largest gaming company in the Americas and Europe by revenue and market capitalization after Activision Blizzard and ahead of Take-Two Interactive and Ubisoft as of March 2018.
 Founded and incorporated on May 27, 1982, by Apple employee Trip Hawkins, the company was a pioneer of the early home computer games industry and was notable for promoting the designers and programmers responsible for its games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Games</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games/</guid>
      <description>Epic Games, Inc. is an American video game and software developer and publisher based in Cary, North Carolina. The company was founded by Tim Sweeney as Potomac Computer Systems in 1991, originally located in his parents&amp;rsquo; house in Potomac, Maryland. Following his first commercial video game release, ZZT (1991), the company became Epic MegaGames, Inc. in early 1992 and brought on Mark Rein, who is the company&amp;rsquo;s vice president to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/espn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/espn/</guid>
      <description>ESPN (originally an initialism for Entertainment and Sports Programming Network) is an American basic cable sports channel owned by ESPN Inc., owned jointly by The Walt Disney Company (80%) and Hearst Communications (20%). The company was founded in 1979 by Bill Rasmussen along with his son Scott Rasmussen and Ed Egan.
 ESPN broadcasts primarily from studio facilities located in Bristol, Connecticut. The network also operates offices in Miami, New York City, Seattle, Charlotte, and Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etihad Airways</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/etihad-airways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/etihad-airways/</guid>
      <description>Etihad Airways (Arabic: شَرِكَة ٱلْاِتِّحَاد لِلطَّيْرَان‎, romanized: sharikat al-ittiḥād li-ṭ-ṭayarān) is the flag carrier of the UAE and the second-largest airline in the country (after Emirates). Its head office is in Khalifa City, Abu Dhabi, near Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s International Airport. Etihad commenced operations in November 2003.
 The airline operates more than 1,000 flights per week to over 120 passenger and cargo destinations in the Middle East, Africa, Europe, Asia, Australia, and North America, with a fleet of 102 Airbus and Boeing aircraft as of February 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expedia.com</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia.com/</guid>
      <description>Expedia.com is an American online travel agency and metasearch engine. The website and mobile app can be used to book airline tickets, hotel reservations, car rentals, cruise ships, and vacation packages.
 It is owned and operated by Expedia Group, ranked first on the list of top earning travel companies.
Source About Expedia.com Expedia Group is the world’s travel platform, with an extensive brand portfolio that includes some of the world’s leading online travel brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flix/</guid>
      <description>Flix is an American premium cable and satellite television network that is owned by Showtime Networks, a subsidiary of ViacomCBS through its domestic networks division. Its programming consists solely of theatrically released feature films released from the 1970s to the present day, interspersed with some films from the 1950s and 1960s.
 It is the only premium television service in the United States that does not operate any multiplex channels that provide additional programming alongside the main service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freddie Mac</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/freddie-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/freddie-mac/</guid>
      <description>The Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corporation (FHLMC), known as Freddie Mac, is a public government-sponsored enterprise (GSE), headquartered in Tysons Corner, Virginia.[3][4] Freddie Mac is ranked No. 38 on the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.
 The FHLMC was created in 1970 to expand the secondary market for mortgages in the US. Along with the Federal National Mortgage Association (Fannie Mae), Freddie Mac buys mortgages on the secondary market, pools them, and sells them as a mortgage-backed security to investors on the open market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eda/</guid>
      <description> Egg Donor America, a leading center for egg donation. EDA primary goal is to make the process of selecting an egg donor as easy and as comfortable as possible. Egg Donor America was founded by fertility expert Dr. Pierre Asmar. Dr. Asmar oversees every aspect of the egg donor program.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus/</guid>
      <description> Exodus is a multi-cryptocurrency wallet that boasts an easy-to-use UI. You can keep your Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), DASH, Decred (DCR), Ethereum Classic (ETC), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Bitcoin Gold (BTG) and Vertcoin (VTC), along with a continuously increasing number of Ethereum tokens, all in one place and easily calculate and organize your savings with their pie chart portfolio.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</guid>
      <description> Ethereum is an open source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform and operating system featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It supports a modified version of Nakamoto consensus via transaction-based state transitions. Ether is a cryptocurrency generated by the Ethereum platform and used to compensate mining nodes for computations performed. Each Ethereum account has an ether balance and ether may be transferred from one account to another.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Classic</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum Classic is an open-source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It provides a decentralized Turing-complete virtual machine, the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), which can execute scripts using an international network of public nodes. Ethereum Classic and Ethereum have a value token called &amp;ldquo;ether&amp;rdquo;, which can be transferred between participants, stored in a cryptocurrency wallet and is used to compensate participant nodes for computations performed in the Ethereum Platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/echo-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/echo-tv/</guid>
      <description> Echo TV was a christian-conservative Hungarian television channel owned and operated by Echo Hungária TV Zrt , and founded in 2005 to cover business news. Later focusing on news broadcasting and public affairs, it was known as a supporter of Fidesz and KDNP.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eni</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</guid>
      <description>Eni S.p.A. is an Italian multinational oil and gas company headquartered in Rome. Considered one of the global supermajors, it has operations in 79 countries, and is currently world&amp;rsquo;s 11th largest industrial company with a market capitalization of 68 billion euros (US$ 90 billion), as of August 14, 2013 The Italian government owns a 30.303% golden share in the company, 3.934% held through the state Treasury and 26.369% held through the Cassa Depositi e Prestiti.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</guid>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is an independent agency[dubious – discuss] of the United States federal government for environmental protection. President Richard Nixon proposed the establishment of EPA on July 9, 1970 and it began operation on December 2, 1970, after Nixon signed an executive order. The order establishing the EPA was ratified by committee hearings in the House and Senate. The agency is led by its Administrator, who is appointed by the President and approved by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equinor</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor/</guid>
      <description>Equinor ASA (OSE: EQNR, formerly Statoil and StatoilHydro) is a Norwegian multinational energy company headquartered in Stavanger, Norway. It is a petroleum and wind energy company with operations in thirty-six countries. By revenue, while under Statoil name, Equinor was ranked by Forbes Magazine (2013) as the world&amp;rsquo;s eleventh largest oil and gas company and the twenty-sixth largest company, regardless of industry, by profit in the world. The company has about 20,200 employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etsy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/etsy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/etsy/</guid>
      <description>Etsy is an e-commerce website (etsy.com) focused on handmade or vintage items and craft supplies. These items fall under a wide range of categories, including jewelry, bags, clothing, home décor and furniture, toys, art, as well as craft supplies and tools. All vintage items must be at least 20 years old. The site follows in the tradition of open craft fairs, giving sellers personal storefronts where they list their goods for a fee of US$0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ExxonMobil</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/exxonmobil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/exxonmobil/</guid>
      <description>Exxon Mobil Corporation, doing business as ExxonMobil, is an American multinational oil and gas corporation headquartered in Irving, Texas. It is the largest direct descendant of John D. Rockefeller&amp;rsquo;s Standard Oil Company, and was formed on November 30, 1999 by the merger of Exxon (formerly the Standard Oil Company of New Jersey) and Mobil (formerly the Standard Oil Company of New York). ExxonMobil&amp;rsquo;s primary brands are Exxon, Mobil, Esso, and ExxonMobil Chemical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edmonton Oilers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/edmonton-oilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/edmonton-oilers/</guid>
      <description> The Edmonton Oilers are a professional ice hockey team based in Edmonton, Alberta. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</guid>
      <description> Enel S.p.A., or the Enel Group, is an Italian multinational energy company that is active in the sectors of electricity generation and distribution, as well as in the distribution of natural gas.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eff/</guid>
      <description> The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is an international non-profit digital rights group based in San Francisco, California. The foundation was formed in July 1990 by John Gilmore, John Perry Barlow and Mitch Kapor to promote Internet civil liberties.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expedia Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia-group/</guid>
      <description> Expedia Group is an American global travel technology company. Its websites, which are primarily travel fare aggregators and travel metasearch engines, include CarRentals.com, CheapTickets, Expedia.com, HomeAway, Hotels.com, Hotwire.com, Orbitz, Travelocity, trivago, and Venere.com.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ebay/</guid>
      <description>eBay Inc. (/ˈiːˌbeɪ/ EE-bay) is an American multinational e-commerce corporation based in San Jose, California that facilitates consumer-to-consumer and business-to-consumer sales through its website. eBay was founded by Pierre Omidyar in the autumn of 1995, and became a notable success story of the dot-com bubble. eBay is a multibillion-dollar business with operations in about 30 countries, as of 2011. The company manages the eBay website, an online auction and shopping website in which people and businesses buy and sell a wide variety of goods and services worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emirates Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Emirates is an airline based in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. The airline is a subsidiary of The Emirates Group, which is wholly owned by the government of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Investment Corporation of Dubai. It is the largest airline in the Middle East, operating over 3,600 flights per week from its hub at Dubai International Airport, to more than 150 cities in 80 countries across six continents. Cargo activities are undertaken by Emirates SkyCargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eno</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eno/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:04:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eno/</guid>
      <description>Abour Eno by Capital One Eno is your Capital One assistant that looks out for you and your money. Eno works 24/7 to help you protect your money, shop safer online, and manage your Capital One accounts.
Eno helps you protect your money. When Eno spots unusual and suspicious activity, such as fraud, duplicate charges, and generous tips, Eno gives you a heads up through automated alerts and helps you resolve the issues on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>