<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>automotive on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/automotive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in automotive on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/automotive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AMG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amg/</guid>
      <description> Mercedes-AMG GmbH, commonly known as AMG, is the high-performance brand used by Mercedes-Benz. AMG independently hires engineers and contracts with manufacturers to customize Mercedes-Benz AMG vehicles. Mercedes-AMG is headquartered in Affalterbach, Baden-Württemberg, Germany.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acura</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</guid>
      <description>Acura (/ˈækjʊrə/) is the American luxury vehicle marque of Japanese automaker Honda. The brand was launched in the United States and Canada on 27 March 1986, marketing luxury, performance, and high-performance vehicles. It was introduced to Hong Kong in 1991, Mexico in 2004, China in 2006, Russia in 2014 (no longer available in Russia) and Kuwait in 2015, and is also sold in Ukraine. Honda&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce Acura to the Japanese domestic market (JDM) in 2008 was delayed, due to economic reasons,[4] and later withheld as a result of the 2008 financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpina</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</guid>
      <description>Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners. For instance, the Alpina B7 is produced at the same assembly line in Dingolfing, Germany (BMW Plant Dingolfing), as BMW&amp;rsquo;s own 7 Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aston-Martin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</guid>
      <description>Aston Martin Lagonda Global Holdings plc is a British independent manufacturer of luxury sports cars and grand tourers. It was founded in 1913 by Lionel Martin and Robert Bamford. Steered from 1947 by David Brown, it became associated with expensive grand touring cars in the 1950s and 1960s, and with the fictional character James Bond following his use of a DB5 model in the 1964 film Goldfinger. Their sports cars are regarded as a British cultural icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/audi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/audi/</guid>
      <description>Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMW</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</guid>
      <description> BMW AG (German originally an initialism for Bayerische Motoren Werke in German, or Bavarian Motor Works in English) is a German multinational company which currently produces automobiles and motorcycles, and also produced aircraft engines until 1945.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bentley</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</guid>
      <description> Bentley Motors Limited is a British manufacturer and marketer of luxury cars and SUVs—and a subsidiary of the Volkswagen Group since 1998.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buick</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buick/</guid>
      <description>Buick is a division of the American automobile manufacturer General Motors (GM). It was among the first American marques of automobiles, and was the company that established General Motors in 1908. Before the establishment of General Motors, GM founder William C. Durant had served as Buick&amp;rsquo;s general manager and major investor. Buick was the first production automobile maker in the world to equip its cars with overhead valve engines, which it did in 1904.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadillac</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac/</guid>
      <description> Cadillac /ˈkædɪlæk/ is a division of the American automobile manufacturer General Motors (GM) that designs and builds luxury vehicles. Its major markets are the United States, Canada, and China. Cadillac vehicles are distributed in 34 additional markets worldwide. Cadillac automobiles are at the top of the luxury field within the United States. In 2017, Cadillac&amp;rsquo;s U.S. sales were 156,440 vehicles and its global sales were 356,467 vehicles.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrysler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chrysler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chrysler/</guid>
      <description>Chrysler is one of the &amp;ldquo;Big Three&amp;rdquo; automobile manufacturers in the United States, headquartered in Auburn Hills, Michigan. The original Chrysler Corporation was founded in 1925 by Walter Chrysler from the remains of the Maxwell Motor Company. In 1998, it was acquired by Daimler-Benz, and the holding company was renamed DaimlerChrysler. After Daimler divested Chrysler in 2007, the company existed as Chrysler LLC (2007–2009) and Chrysler Group LLC (2009–2014) before merging in 2014 with Italian holding company Fiat S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citroen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</guid>
      <description> Citroën is a French automobile manufacturer, part of the PSA Peugeot Citroën group since 1976, founded in 1919 by French industrialist André-Gustave Citroën (1878–1935). In 1934, the firm established its reputation for innovative technology with the Traction Avant. This car was the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass-produced front wheel drive car, and also one of the first to feature a unitary type body, with no chassis supporting the mechanical components.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daimler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</guid>
      <description> Daimler AG is a German multinational automotive corporation, headquartered in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. Daimler-Benz was formed with the merger of Benz &amp;amp; Cie and Daimler Motoren Gesellschaft in 1926. The company was renamed DaimlerChrysler upon acquiring the American automobile manufacturer Chrysler Corporation in 1998, and was again renamed Daimler upon divesting of Chrysler in 2007.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</guid>
      <description> Dodge is an American brand of automobile manufactured by FCA US LLC (formerly known as Fiat Chrysler Group LLC), based in Auburn Hills, Michigan. Dodge vehicles currently include performance cars, though for much of its existence Dodge was Chrysler&amp;rsquo;s mid-priced brand above Plymouth.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/f1/</guid>
      <description>Formula One (also Formula 1 or F1) is the highest class of single-seater auto racing sanctioned by the Fédération Internationale de l&amp;rsquo;Automobile (FIA) and owned by the Formula One Group. The FIA Formula One World Championship has been one of the premier forms of racing around the world since its inaugural season in 1950. The word &amp;ldquo;formula&amp;rdquo; in the name refers to the set of rules to which all participants&amp;rsquo; cars must conform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fiat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fiat/</guid>
      <description> Fiat Automobiles is an Italian automobile manufacturer, a subsidiary of FCA Italy S.p.A., which is part of Fiat Chrysler Automobiles (previously Fiat S.p.A.). Fiat Automobiles was formed in January 2007 when Fiat reorganized its automobile business, and traces its history back to 1899 when the first Fiat automobile, the Fiat 4 HP, was produced.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ford</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ford/</guid>
      <description>Ford Motor Company is an American multinational automaker that has its main headquarter in Dearborn, Michigan, a suburb of Detroit. It was founded by Henry Ford and incorporated on June 16, 1903. The company sells automobiles and commercial vehicles under the Ford brand and most luxury cars under the Lincoln brand. Ford also owns Brazilian SUV manufacturer Troller, an 8% stake in Aston Martin of the United Kingdom and a 32% stake in Jiangling Motors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gm/</guid>
      <description>General Motors Company, is an American multinational corporation headquartered in Detroit that designs, manufactures, markets, and distributes vehicles and vehicle parts, and sells financial services, with global headquarters in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Renaissance Center. It was originally founded by William C. Durant on September 16, 1908 as a holding company. The company is the largest American automobile manufacturer, and one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest. As of 2018, General Motors is ranked #10 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</guid>
      <description> Honda Motor Company, Ltd. is a Japanese public multinational conglomerate corporation primarily known as a manufacturer of automobiles, motorcycles, and power equipment.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hummer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</guid>
      <description> Hummer was a brand of trucks and SUVs, first marketed in 1992 when AM General began selling a civilian version of the M998 Humvee. In 1998, General Motors (GM) purchased the brand name from AM General and marketed three vehicles: the original Hummer H1, based on the military Humvee, as well as the new H2 and H3 models that were based on smaller, civilian-market GM platforms.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</guid>
      <description> The Hyundai Motor Company, is a South Korean multinational automotive manufacturer headquartered in Seoul. The company was founded in 1967 and, along with its 32.8% owned subsidiary, Kia Motors, and its 100% owned luxury subsidiary Genesis Motor, altogether comprise the Hyundai Motor Group. It is the third largest vehicle manufacturer in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaguar</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jaguar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jaguar/</guid>
      <description> Jaguar is the luxury vehicle brand of Jaguar Land Rover, a British multinational car manufacturer with its headquarters in Whitley, Coventry, England. Jaguar Cars was the company that was responsible for the production of Jaguar cars until its operations were fully merged with those of Land Rover to form Jaguar Land Rover on 1 January 2013.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeep</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jeep/</guid>
      <description> Jeep is a brand of American automobile and division of FCA US LLC (formerly Chrysler Group, LLC), a wholly owned subsidiary of the Italian-American corporation Fiat Chrysler Automobiles. Jeep has been a part of Chrysler since 1987, when Chrysler acquired the Jeep brand, along with remaining assets, from its previous owner American Motors Corporation (AMC).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kia/</guid>
      <description>Kia Motors Corporation, headquartered in Seoul, is South Korea&amp;rsquo;s second-largest automobile manufacturer, following the Hyundai Motor Company, with sales of over 3.3 million vehicles in 2015. As of December 2015, the Kia Motor Corporation is minority owned by Hyundai, which owns a 33.88% stake valued at just over US$6 billion. Kia in turn is a minority owner of more than twenty Hyundai subsidiaries ranging from 4.9% up to 45.37%, totaling more than US$8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamborghini</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini/</guid>
      <description> Automobili Lamborghini is an Italian brand and manufacturer of luxury sports cars and SUVs based in Sant&amp;rsquo;Agata Bolognese and tractors Lamborghini Trattori in Pieve di Cento, Italy. The company is owned by the Volkswagen Group through its subsidiary Audi.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lincoln</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lincoln/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lincoln/</guid>
      <description> Lincoln, formally the Lincoln Motor Company, is a luxury vehicle brand of the American manufacturer Ford Motor Company. Marketed among the top luxury brands in the United States, Lincoln has competed closely against Cadillac for nearly its entire existence. Lincoln has the distinction of establishing the personal luxury car segment, with the entry of the Lincoln Continental into mass production in 1940.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mazda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mazda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mazda/</guid>
      <description> Mazda Motor Corporation (Japanese: マツダ株式会社 Hepburn: Matsuda Kabushiki-gaisha), commonly referred to as simply Mazda, is a Japanese multinational automaker based in Fuchū, Aki District, Hiroshima Prefecture, Japan.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</guid>
      <description> Mercedes-Benz is a German global automobile marque and a division of Daimler AG. The brand is known for luxury vehicles, buses, coaches, and trucks. The headquarters is in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. The name first appeared in 1926 under Daimler-Benz. In 2018, Mercedes-Benz was the biggest selling premium vehicle brand in the world, having sold 2.31 million passenger cars.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mini/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mini/</guid>
      <description>Mini (stylised as MINI) is a British automotive marque, owned by BMW since 2000, and used by them for a range of small cars. The word Mini has been used in car model names since 1959, and in 1969 it became a marque in its own right when the name &amp;ldquo;Mini&amp;rdquo; replaced the separate &amp;ldquo;Austin Mini&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Morris Mini&amp;rdquo; car model names. BMW acquired the marque in 1994 when it bought Rover Group (formerly British Leyland), which owned Mini, among other brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/opel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opel/</guid>
      <description> Opel is a German automobile manufacturer, a subsidiary of French automaker Groupe PSA since August 2017. From 1929 until 2017, Opel was owned by American automaker General Motors. Opel vehicles are sold in England under the Vauxhall brand. Some Opel vehicles are badge-engineered in Australasia under the Holden brand, and in North America and China under the Buick brand.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porsche</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/porshe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/porshe/</guid>
      <description> Dr.-Ing. h.c. F. Porsche AG, usually shortened to Porsche AG, is a German automobile manufacturer specializing in high-performance sports cars, SUVs and sedans. Porsche AG is headquartered in Stuttgart, and is owned by Volkswagen AG, which is itself majority-owned by Porsche Automobil Holding SE. Porsche&amp;rsquo;s current lineup includes the 718 Boxster/Cayman, 911, Panamera, Macan and Cayenne.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Royce Motors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</guid>
      <description>Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited is a British luxury automobile maker. A wholly owned subsidiary of German group BMW, it was established in 1998 after BMW was licensed the rights to the Rolls-Royce brand name and logo from Rolls-Royce plc and acquired the rights to the Spirit of Ecstasy and Rolls-Royce grill shape trademarks from Volkswagen AG. Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited operates from purpose-built administrative and production facilities opened in 2003 across from the historic Goodwood Circuit in Goodwood, West Sussex, England, United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skoda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/skoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/skoda/</guid>
      <description> ŠKODA AUTO is a Czech automobile manufacturer founded in 1895 as Laurin &amp;amp; Klement. Its headquarters are in Mladá Boleslav, Czech Republic.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</guid>
      <description> Smart (stylized as smart) is a German automotive brand and division of Daimler AG. The company is based in Böblingen, Germany. It produces microcars and subcompacts, primarily the Fortwo and Forfour. The primary assembly plants is the Smartville in Hambach, France. A second plant exists in Novo Mesto, Slovenia. Marketed in 46 countries around the world, production of the Fortwo had surpassed 1.7 million units by early 2015.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subaru</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</guid>
      <description> Subaru is the automobile manufacturing division of Japanese transportation conglomerate Subaru Corporation (formerly known as Fuji Heavy Industries), the twenty-second largest automaker by production worldwide in 2012.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesla/</guid>
      <description>Tesla, Inc. (formerly Tesla Motors, Inc.) is an American automotive and energy company based in Palo Alto, California. The company specializes in electric car manufacturing and, through its SolarCity subsidiary, solar panel manufacturing. It operates multiple production and assembly plants, notably Gigafactory 1 near Reno, Nevada, and its main vehicle manufacturing facility at Tesla Factory in Fremont, California. As of March 2019, Tesla sells the Model S, Model X, and Model 3 automobiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/volkswagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volkswagen/</guid>
      <description> Volkswagen is a German automaker founded on 28 May 1937 by the German Labour Front, a Nazi labour union, and headquartered in Wolfsburg. It is the flagship marque of the Volkswagen Group, the largest automaker by worldwide sales in 2016 and 2017. The group&amp;rsquo;s biggest market is in China, which delivers 40% of its sales and profits.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volvo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</guid>
      <description> The Volvo Group (Swedish: Volvokoncernen; legally Aktiebolaget Volvo, shortened to AB Volvo) (stylized as VOLVO) is a Swedish multinational manufacturing company headquartered in Gothenburg. While its core activity is the production, distribution and sale of trucks, buses and construction equipment, Volvo also supplies marine and industrial drive systems and financial services. In 2016, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest manufacturer of heavy-duty trucks.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</guid>
      <description>About the Toyota logo   The Toyota brand represents our tenets of quality, reliability and durability. It also stands as a symbol to inspire people around the world to go to the places and do the things they’ve always dreamed of.
 The staging platform is how we refer to the Toyota emblem when shown in the red surround. The staging platform allows the emblem to be anchored and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota F1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scion</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>