<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>newspaper on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/newspaper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in newspaper on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/newspaper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deseret News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</guid>
      <description>The Deseret News is a newspaper published in Salt Lake City, Utah, United States. It is Utah&amp;rsquo;s oldest continuously published daily newspaper and has the largest Sunday circulation in the state and the second largest daily circulation behind The Salt Lake Tribune. The News is owned by Deseret News Publishing Company, a subsidiary of Deseret Management Corporation, a holding company owned by The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-tribune/</guid>
      <description> The Chicago Tribune is a daily newspaper based in Chicago, Illinois, United States, owned by Tribune Publishing. Founded in 1847, and formerly self-styled as the &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Newspaper&amp;rdquo; (for which WGN radio and television are named), it remains the most-read daily newspaper of the Chicago metropolitan area and the Great Lakes region. It had the 6th highest circulation for American newspapers in 2017.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Hampshire Gazette</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette/</guid>
      <description> The Daily Hampshire Gazette is a six-day morning daily newspaper based in Northampton, Massachusetts, and covering all of Hampshire County and southern towns of Franklin County, Massachusetts. The newspaper prints Monday through Saturday, with the latter labeled &amp;ldquo;Weekend Edition&amp;rdquo;.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligencer Journal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligencer Journal, known locally as the Intell, was the daily, morning newspaper published by Lancaster Newspapers, Inc in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. It is the 7th oldest newspaper in the United States and was one of the oldest newspapers to be continually published under the same name. The Intelligencer Journal&amp;rsquo;s editorial page generally leaned to the Democratic/liberal perspective. The Intelligencer merged with its sister newspaper, the Lancaster New Era, in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Post</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</guid>
      <description> The New York Post (sometimes abbreviated as NY Post) is a daily newspaper in New York City. The Post also operates the celebrity gossip site PageSix.com, the entertainment site Decider.com, and co-produces the television show Page Six TV.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsday</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday/</guid>
      <description> Newsday is an American daily newspaper that primarily serves Nassau and Suffolk counties and the New York City borough of Queens on Long Island, although it is also sold throughout the New York metropolitan area. In 2012, Newsday expanded to include Rockland and Westchester county news on its website.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Globe</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-globe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-globe/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Globe (sometimes abbreviated as The Globe) is an American daily newspaper founded and based in Boston, Massachusetts, since its creation by Charles H. Taylor in 1872. The newspaper has won a total of 26 Pulitzer Prizes as of 2016, and with a total paid circulation of 245,824 from September 2015 to August 2016, it is the 25th most read newspaper in the United States. The Boston Globe is the oldest and largest daily newspaper in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Journal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wall-street-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wall-street-journal/</guid>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal is a U.S. business-focused, English-language international daily newspaper based in New York City. The Journal, along with its Asian and European editions, is published six days a week by Dow Jones &amp;amp; Company, a division of News Corp. The newspaper is published in the broadsheet format and online. The Journal has been printed continuously since its inception on July 8, 1889, by Charles Dow, Edward Jones, and Charles Bergstresser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-post/</guid>
      <description> The Washington Post (sometimes abbreviated as WaPo) is a major American daily newspaper published in Washington, D.C., with a particular emphasis on national politics and the federal government. It has the largest circulation in the Washington metropolitan area. Its slogan &amp;ldquo;Democracy Dies in Darkness&amp;rdquo; began appearing on its masthead in 2017. Daily broadsheet editions are printed for the District of Columbia, Maryland, and Virginia.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>