<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>newspaper on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/newspaper/</link><description>Recent content in newspaper on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/newspaper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-new-york-times//file/the-new-york-times.svg</url><title>The New York Times Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">The New York Times</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/the-new-york-times/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-new-york-times/</guid><description turbo="true">The New York Times (NYT), is an American newspaper based in New York City with worldwide influence and readership. Nicknamed &amp;ldquo;the Gray Lady&amp;rdquo;, the Times has long been regarded within the industry as a national &amp;ldquo;newspaper of record&amp;rdquo;. The paper&amp;rsquo;s motto, &amp;ldquo;All the News That&amp;rsquo;s Fit to Print&amp;rdquo;, appears in the upper left-hand corner of the front page. Founded in 1851, the paper has won 130 Pulitzer Prizes, more than any other newspaper.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news//file/deseret-news.svg</url><title>Deseret News Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Deseret News</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</guid><description turbo="true">The Deseret News is a newspaper published in Salt Lake City, Utah, United States. It is Utah&amp;rsquo;s oldest continuously published daily newspaper and has the largest Sunday circulation in the state and the second largest daily circulation behind The Salt Lake Tribune. The News is owned by Deseret News Publishing Company, a subsidiary of Deseret Management Corporation, a holding company owned by The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church).</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-tribune//file/chicago-tribune.svg</url><title>Chicago Tribune Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Tribune</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-tribune/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-tribune/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Chicago Tribune is a daily newspaper based in Chicago, Illinois, United States, owned by Tribune Publishing. Founded in 1847, and formerly self-styled as the &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Newspaper&amp;rdquo; (for which WGN radio and television are named), it remains the most-read daily newspaper of the Chicago metropolitan area and the Great Lakes region. It had the 6th highest circulation for American newspapers in 2017.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette//file/daily-hampshire-gazette.svg</url><title>Daily Hampshire Gazette Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Daily Hampshire Gazette</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Daily Hampshire Gazette is a six-day morning daily newspaper based in Northampton, Massachusetts, and covering all of Hampshire County and southern towns of Franklin County, Massachusetts. The newspaper prints Monday through Saturday, with the latter labeled &amp;ldquo;Weekend Edition&amp;rdquo;.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal//file/intelligencer-journal.svg</url><title>Intelligencer Journal Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Intelligencer Journal</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal/</guid><description turbo="true">The Intelligencer Journal, known locally as the Intell, was the daily, morning newspaper published by Lancaster Newspapers, Inc in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. It is the 7th oldest newspaper in the United States and was one of the oldest newspapers to be continually published under the same name. The Intelligencer Journal&amp;rsquo;s editorial page generally leaned to the Democratic/liberal perspective. The Intelligencer merged with its sister newspaper, the Lancaster New Era, in 2009.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday//file/newsday.svg</url><title>Newsday Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Newsday</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday/</guid><description turbo="true"> Newsday is an American daily newspaper that primarily serves Nassau and Suffolk counties and the New York City borough of Queens on Long Island, although it is also sold throughout the New York metropolitan area. In 2012, Newsday expanded to include Rockland and Westchester county news on its website.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post//file/ny-post.svg</url><title>NY Post Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NY Post</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</guid><description turbo="true"> The New York Post (sometimes abbreviated as NY Post) is a daily newspaper in New York City. The Post also operates the celebrity gossip site PageSix.com, the entertainment site Decider.com, and co-produces the television show Page Six TV.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-globe//file/the-globe.svg</url><title>The Globe Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">The Globe</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/the-globe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-globe/</guid><description turbo="true">The Boston Globe (sometimes abbreviated as The Globe) is an American daily newspaper founded and based in Boston, Massachusetts, since its creation by Charles H. Taylor in 1872. The newspaper has won a total of 26 Pulitzer Prizes as of 2016, and with a total paid circulation of 245,824 from September 2015 to August 2016, it is the 25th most read newspaper in the United States. The Boston Globe is the oldest and largest daily newspaper in Boston.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/wall-street-journal//file/wall-street-journal.svg</url><title>Wall Street Journal Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Wall Street Journal</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/wall-street-journal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wall-street-journal/</guid><description turbo="true">The Wall Street Journal is a U.S. business-focused, English-language international daily newspaper based in New York City. The Journal, along with its Asian and European editions, is published six days a week by Dow Jones &amp;amp; Company, a division of News Corp. The newspaper is published in the broadsheet format and online. The Journal has been printed continuously since its inception on July 8, 1889, by Charles Dow, Edward Jones, and Charles Bergstresser.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-post//file/washington-post.svg</url><title>Washington Post Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Washington Post</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-post/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Washington Post (sometimes abbreviated as WaPo) is a major American daily newspaper published in Washington, D.C., with a particular emphasis on national politics and the federal government. It has the largest circulation in the Washington metropolitan area. Its slogan &amp;ldquo;Democracy Dies in Darkness&amp;rdquo; began appearing on its masthead in 2017. Daily broadsheet editions are printed for the District of Columbia, Maryland, and Virginia.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune//file/san-diego-union-tribune.svg</url><title>San Diego Union Tribune Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">San Diego Union Tribune</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</guid><description turbo="true">About San Diego Union Tribune The San Diego Union-Tribune is San Diego’s largest media company and its oldest business, dating back to the founding of the Union in 1868.
Today, Union-Tribune publications reach more than 96 percent of San Diego County households each week. The company portfolio includes its Pulitzer Prize-winning newspaper, The San Diego Union-Tribune; the region’s leading website, SanDiegoUnionTribune.com; weekly entertainment guide Night + Day; lifestyle magazine Pacific San Diego; Spanish-language weekly Hoy San Diego; and nine community newspapers: the La Jolla Light; Del Mar Times; Encinitas Advocate; Solana Beach Sun; Carmel Valley Times; Poway News Chieftain; Rancho Santa Fe Review; Ramona Sentinel and Rancho Bernardo News Journal.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine//file/new-england-journal-of-medicine.svg</url><title>New England Journal of Medicine Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">New England Journal of Medicine</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:31 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine/</guid><description turbo="true">About NEJM The New England Journal of Medicine is a weekly medical journal published by the Massachusetts Medical Society. It is among the most prestigious peer-reviewed medical journals as well as the oldest continuously published one.
The New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM) is the world’s leading medical journal and website. Published continuously for over 200 years, NEJM delivers high-quality, peer-reviewed research and interactive clinical content to physicians, educators, and the global medical community.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine//file/boston-magazine.svg</url><title>Boston Magazine Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Boston Magazine</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:55 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine/</guid><description turbo="true">About Boston Magazine Boston is a magazine concerning life in the Greater Boston area and has been in publication since the 1960s.
Sophisticated, intellectual, and full of charm, Boston is a world center of higher education, medicine, finance, and biotechnology, with some of the nation’s leading cultural institutions, best restaurants, trendiest shopping, top universities, and smartest people. Then there’s the other Boston: a city of power struggles, politics, expensive real estate, and cutting-edge music and arts.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item></channel></rss>