<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chermayeff &amp; Geismar &amp; Haviv on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/chermayeff-geismar-haviv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chermayeff &amp; Geismar &amp; Haviv on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/chermayeff-geismar-haviv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</guid>
      <description> Animal Planet is an American pay television channel owned by Discovery, Inc. First established on October 1, 1996, the network is primarily devoted to series and documentaries about wild animals and domestic pets.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Ashe Stadium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</guid>
      <description> Arthur Ashe Stadium is a tennis stadium at Flushing Meadows-Corona Park in Queens, New York City. Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center, it is the main stadium of the US Open tennis tournament, and the largest tennis stadium in the world, with a capacity of 23,771.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>The National Aquarium - also known as National Aquarium in Baltimore and formerly known as Baltimore Aquarium - is a non-profit public aquarium located at 501 East Pratt Street on Pier 3 in the Inner Harbor area of downtown Baltimore, Maryland, in the United States. Constructed during a period of urban renewal in Baltimore, the aquarium opened on August 8, 1981. The aquarium has an annual attendance of 1.5 million visitors and is the largest tourism attraction in the State of Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beko</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beko/</guid>
      <description> Beko /bɛkoʊ/ (sometimes stylized as beko) is a Turkish domestic appliance and consumer electronics brand of Arçelik A.Ş. controlled by Koç Holding.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bemis Company</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</guid>
      <description> Bemis Company, Inc. is a global manufacturer of flexible packaging products (ranging from self-venting cook-in-bag packaging and retort packaging for shelf-stable products, to vacuum packaging for meat products and puncture-resistant, sterile medical packaging) and pressure-sensitive materials. Bemis is headquartered in Neenah, Wisconsin in the United States. Its divisions are located in 12 countries and its films for packaging products and adhesive materials are distributed worldwide.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</guid>
      <description> Brown University is a private Ivy League research university in Providence, Rhode Island. Founded in 1764 as the College in the English Colony of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, it is the seventh-oldest institution of higher education in the United States and one of the nine colonial colleges chartered before the American Revolution.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBRE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</guid>
      <description> CBRE Group, Inc., is an American commercial real estate services and investment firm. The abbreviation CBRE stands for Coldwell Banker Richard Ellis. As of 2018, it is the largest commercial real estate services company in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</guid>
      <description> The organization offers the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) designation, the Certificate in Investment Performance Measurement (CIPM) designation, and the Investment Foundations Certificate. It provides continuing education conferences, seminars, webcasts, and publications to allow members and other participants to stay current on developments in the investment industry. CFA Institute also oversees the CFA Institute Research Challenge for university students and the Research Foundation of CFA Institute.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</guid>
      <description> Conservation International (CI) is an American nonprofit environmental organization headquartered in Arlington, Virginia. Its goal is to protect nature as a source of food, fresh water, livelihoods and a stable climate.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conduent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</guid>
      <description> Conduent Inc. is a technology-led business process services company headquartered in New Jersey. It was formed in 2017 as a divestiture from Xerox.The company offers digital platforms for businesses and governments. It has 85,000 employees in more than 40 countries.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cornell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</guid>
      <description>Cornell University (/kɔːrˈnɛl/ kor-NEL) is a private and statutory Ivy League research university in Ithaca, New York. Founded in 1865 by Ezra Cornell and Andrew Dickson White, the university was intended to teach and make contributions in all fields of knowledge—from the classics to the sciences, and from the theoretical to the applied. These ideals, unconventional for the time, are captured in Cornell&amp;rsquo;s founding principle, a popular 1868 Ezra Cornell quotation: &amp;ldquo;I would found an institution where any person can find instruction in any study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Hero</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</guid>
      <description>Course Hero is an education technology website company based in Redwood City, California, which operates an online learning platform for students to access course-specific study resources contributed by a community of students and educators. The crowdsourced learning platform contains practice problems, study guides, infographics, class notes, step-by-step explanations, essays, lab reports, videos, user-submitted questions paired with answers from tutors, and original materials created and uploaded by educators. Users either buy a subscription or upload original documents to receive unlocks that are used to view and download full Course Hero documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominion Energy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</guid>
      <description> Dominion Energy, Inc., commonly referred to as Dominion, is an American power and energy company headquartered in Richmond, Virginia that supplies electricity in parts of Virginia, North Carolina, and South Carolina and supplies natural gas to parts of West Virginia, Ohio, Pennsylvania, North Carolina, South Carolina, and Georgia. Dominion also has generation facilities in Indiana, Illinois, Connecticut, and Rhode Island.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</guid>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is an independent agency[dubious – discuss] of the United States federal government for environmental protection. President Richard Nixon proposed the establishment of EPA on July 9, 1970 and it began operation on December 2, 1970, after Nixon signed an executive order. The order establishing the EPA was ratified by committee hearings in the House and Senate. The agency is led by its Administrator, who is appointed by the President and approved by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flatiron Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</guid>
      <description> Flatiron is a healthcare technology company providing software and data analytics services to the FDA, cancer researchers, and care providers. Flatiron’s Learning Oncology Platform supports over 260 community oncology practices across the U.S, 10 of the top 12 life science companies and three major academic research centers. Early investors include Google Ventures, First Round Capital, Roche and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins/</guid>
      <description>HarperCollins Publishers L.L.C. is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest publishing companies and is one of the Big Five English-language publishing companies, alongside Penguin Random House, Simon &amp;amp; Schuster, Hachette and Macmillan. The company is headquartered in New York City and is a subsidiary of News Corp. The name is a combination of several publishing firm names: Harper &amp;amp; Row, an American publishing company acquired in 1987 (whose own name was the result of an earlier merger of Harper &amp;amp; Brothers (founded 1817) and Row, Peterson &amp;amp; Company), together with UK publishing company William Collins, Sons (founded 1819), acquired in 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard University Press</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press/</guid>
      <description> Harvard University Press (HUP) is a publishing house established on January 13, 1913, as a division of Harvard University, and focused on academic publishing. It is a member of the Association of American University Presses. After the retirement of William P. Sisler in 2017, the university appointed as Director George Andreou.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthPartners</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</guid>
      <description> HealthPartners is an integrated, nonprofit health care provider and health insurance company located in Bloomington, Minnesota offering care, coverage, research and education to its members, patients and the community.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</guid>
      <description> Grupo Imagen is a Mexican media conglomerate, part of Grupo Empresarial Ángeles
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetpack/</guid>
      <description> Jetpack is the ultimate toolkit for WordPress. It gives you everything you need to design, secure, and grow your site in one bundle.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>