<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chermayeff &amp; Geismar &amp; Haviv on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/chermayeff-geismar-haviv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chermayeff &amp; Geismar &amp; Haviv on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/chermayeff-geismar-haviv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</guid>
      <description> Animal Planet is an American pay television channel owned by Discovery, Inc. First established on October 1, 1996, the network is primarily devoted to series and documentaries about wild animals and domestic pets.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Ashe Stadium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</guid>
      <description> Arthur Ashe Stadium is a tennis stadium at Flushing Meadows-Corona Park in Queens, New York City. Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center, it is the main stadium of the US Open tennis tournament, and the largest tennis stadium in the world, with a capacity of 23,771.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avery</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/avery/</guid>
      <description> Avery Products Corporation is one of the world’s leading manufacturers of self-adhesive labels, labeling software, binders, dividers and other products, and markets under the well-known Avery® brand. Throughout our history, Avery has built a solid reputation as the trusted brand and leading resource for organization and identification solutions.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>The National Aquarium - also known as National Aquarium in Baltimore and formerly known as Baltimore Aquarium - is a non-profit public aquarium located at 501 East Pratt Street on Pier 3 in the Inner Harbor area of downtown Baltimore, Maryland, in the United States. Constructed during a period of urban renewal in Baltimore, the aquarium opened on August 8, 1981. The aquarium has an annual attendance of 1.5 million visitors and is the largest tourism attraction in the State of Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beko</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beko/</guid>
      <description> Beko /bɛkoʊ/ (sometimes stylized as beko) is a Turkish domestic appliance and consumer electronics brand of Arçelik A.Ş. controlled by Koç Holding.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bemis Company</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</guid>
      <description> Bemis Company, Inc. is a global manufacturer of flexible packaging products (ranging from self-venting cook-in-bag packaging and retort packaging for shelf-stable products, to vacuum packaging for meat products and puncture-resistant, sterile medical packaging) and pressure-sensitive materials. Bemis is headquartered in Neenah, Wisconsin in the United States. Its divisions are located in 12 countries and its films for packaging products and adhesive materials are distributed worldwide.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</guid>
      <description> Brown University is a private Ivy League research university in Providence, Rhode Island. Founded in 1764 as the College in the English Colony of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, it is the seventh-oldest institution of higher education in the United States and one of the nine colonial colleges chartered before the American Revolution.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBRE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</guid>
      <description> CBRE Group, Inc., is an American commercial real estate services and investment firm. The abbreviation CBRE stands for Coldwell Banker Richard Ellis. As of 2018, it is the largest commercial real estate services company in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</guid>
      <description> The organization offers the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) designation, the Certificate in Investment Performance Measurement (CIPM) designation, and the Investment Foundations Certificate. It provides continuing education conferences, seminars, webcasts, and publications to allow members and other participants to stay current on developments in the investment industry. CFA Institute also oversees the CFA Institute Research Challenge for university students and the Research Foundation of CFA Institute.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</guid>
      <description> Conservation International (CI) is an American nonprofit environmental organization headquartered in Arlington, Virginia. Its goal is to protect nature as a source of food, fresh water, livelihoods and a stable climate.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conduent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</guid>
      <description> Conduent Inc. is a technology-led business process services company headquartered in New Jersey. It was formed in 2017 as a divestiture from Xerox.The company offers digital platforms for businesses and governments. It has 85,000 employees in more than 40 countries.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cornell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</guid>
      <description>Cornell University (/kɔːrˈnɛl/ kor-NEL) is a private and statutory Ivy League research university in Ithaca, New York. Founded in 1865 by Ezra Cornell and Andrew Dickson White, the university was intended to teach and make contributions in all fields of knowledge—from the classics to the sciences, and from the theoretical to the applied. These ideals, unconventional for the time, are captured in Cornell&amp;rsquo;s founding principle, a popular 1868 Ezra Cornell quotation: &amp;ldquo;I would found an institution where any person can find instruction in any study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Hero</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</guid>
      <description>Course Hero is an education technology website company based in Redwood City, California, which operates an online learning platform for students to access course-specific study resources contributed by a community of students and educators. The crowdsourced learning platform contains practice problems, study guides, infographics, class notes, step-by-step explanations, essays, lab reports, videos, user-submitted questions paired with answers from tutors, and original materials created and uploaded by educators. Users either buy a subscription or upload original documents to receive unlocks that are used to view and download full Course Hero documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominion Energy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</guid>
      <description> Dominion Energy, Inc., commonly referred to as Dominion, is an American power and energy company headquartered in Richmond, Virginia that supplies electricity in parts of Virginia, North Carolina, and South Carolina and supplies natural gas to parts of West Virginia, Ohio, Pennsylvania, North Carolina, South Carolina, and Georgia. Dominion also has generation facilities in Indiana, Illinois, Connecticut, and Rhode Island.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</guid>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is an independent agency[dubious – discuss] of the United States federal government for environmental protection. President Richard Nixon proposed the establishment of EPA on July 9, 1970 and it began operation on December 2, 1970, after Nixon signed an executive order. The order establishing the EPA was ratified by committee hearings in the House and Senate. The agency is led by its Administrator, who is appointed by the President and approved by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flatiron Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</guid>
      <description> Flatiron is a healthcare technology company providing software and data analytics services to the FDA, cancer researchers, and care providers. Flatiron’s Learning Oncology Platform supports over 260 community oncology practices across the U.S, 10 of the top 12 life science companies and three major academic research centers. Early investors include Google Ventures, First Round Capital, Roche and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins/</guid>
      <description>HarperCollins Publishers L.L.C. is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest publishing companies and is one of the Big Five English-language publishing companies, alongside Penguin Random House, Simon &amp;amp; Schuster, Hachette and Macmillan. The company is headquartered in New York City and is a subsidiary of News Corp. The name is a combination of several publishing firm names: Harper &amp;amp; Row, an American publishing company acquired in 1987 (whose own name was the result of an earlier merger of Harper &amp;amp; Brothers (founded 1817) and Row, Peterson &amp;amp; Company), together with UK publishing company William Collins, Sons (founded 1819), acquired in 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard University Press</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press/</guid>
      <description> Harvard University Press (HUP) is a publishing house established on January 13, 1913, as a division of Harvard University, and focused on academic publishing. It is a member of the Association of American University Presses. After the retirement of William P. Sisler in 2017, the university appointed as Director George Andreou.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthPartners</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</guid>
      <description> HealthPartners is an integrated, nonprofit health care provider and health insurance company located in Bloomington, Minnesota offering care, coverage, research and education to its members, patients and the community.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</guid>
      <description> Grupo Imagen is a Mexican media conglomerate, part of Grupo Empresarial Ángeles
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetpack/</guid>
      <description> Jetpack is the ultimate toolkit for WordPress. It gives you everything you need to design, secure, and grow your site in one bundle.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBTA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mbta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mbta/</guid>
      <description>The Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority is the public agency responsible for operating most public transportation services in Greater Boston, Massachusetts. Earlier modes of public transportation in Boston were independently owned and operated; many were first folded into a single agency with the formation of the Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA) in 1947. The MTA was replaced in 1964 with the present-day MBTA, which was established as an individual department within the Commonwealth of Massachusetts before becoming a division of the Massachusetts Department of Transportation (MassDOT) in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MOCA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/moca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/moca/</guid>
      <description>The Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles (MOCA) is a contemporary art museum with three locations in greater Los Angeles, California. The main branch is located on Grand Avenue in Downtown Los Angeles, near the Walt Disney Concert Hall. MOCA&amp;rsquo;s original space, initially intended as a &amp;ldquo;temporary&amp;rdquo; exhibit space while the main facility was built, is now known as the Geffen Contemporary, in the Little Tokyo district of downtown Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magirus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/magirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/magirus/</guid>
      <description> Magirus GmbH is a truck manufacturer based in Ulm, Germany, founded by Conrad Dietrich Magirus (1824–1895). The parent company was Klöckner Humboldt Deutz AG, maker of the well-known Deutz engines, so the brand commonly used was Magirus Deutz, and for a short time Klöckner. The logo of Magirus Deutz was a stylised M with a sharp, long centre point to represent the spire of Ulm Cathedral.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merck</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/merck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/merck/</guid>
      <description> Merck KGaA (also called as the Merck Group), branded and commonly known as Merck, is a German multinational pharmaceutical, chemical and life sciences company headquartered in Darmstadt, with around 50,000 employees in around 70 countries. Merck was founded in 1668 and is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest operating chemical and pharmaceutical company, as well as one of the largest pharmaceutical companies in the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mercy For Animals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercy-for-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercy-for-animals/</guid>
      <description> Mercy For Animals (MFA) is an international nonprofit animal protection organization founded in 1999 by Milo Runkle. MFA’s mission is to “prevent cruelty to farmed animals and promote compassionate food choices and policies.”
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoMA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/moma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/moma/</guid>
      <description> The Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) is an art museum located in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, on 53rd Street between Fifth and Sixth Avenues. The museum will be temporarily closed to expand its galleries from June 16 through October 21, 2019. MoMA PS1 will remain open on its regular schedule.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ng/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ng/</guid>
      <description>National Geographic (formerly the National Geographic Magazine and branded also as NAT GEO) is the official magazine of the National Geographic Society. It has been published continuously since its first issue in 1888, nine months after the Society itself was founded. It primarily contains articles about science, geography, history, and world culture. The magazine is known for its thick square-bound glossy format with a yellow rectangular border and its extensive use of dramatic photographs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYU</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu/</guid>
      <description> New York University (NYU) is a private research university based in New York City. Founded in 1831, NYU&amp;rsquo;s historical campus is in Greenwich Village, Lower Manhattan. NYU also has degree-granting campuses in Abu Dhabi and Shanghai, and academic centers in Accra, Berlin, Buenos Aires, Florence, London, Los Angeles, Madrid, Paris, Prague, Sydney, Tel Aviv, and Washington, D.C.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Visions</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-visions/</guid>
      <description>Launched in 1989, New Visions for Public Schools has become one of New York City’s largest educational nonprofits, supporting schools, training teachers, and operating a growing network of charter schools. The three bars of the new visual identity suggest growth, dynamism, the letter V, and climbing steps. It is simple enough to work everywhere, while standing out from the field of educational logos. To underscore the organization’s commitment to working within the public school system, Chermayeff &amp;amp; Geismar &amp;amp; Haviv gave all the words in the name equal emphasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oceano Azul Foundation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oceano-azul-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oceano-azul-foundation/</guid>
      <description>The Oceano Azul Foundation is an international organization founded by the Sociedade Francisco Manuel dos Santos and based in Portugal with the mission of contributing to the sustainability of a healthy and productive ocean. Combining scientific study, political and economic activism, together with a deep ethical commitment, the Foundation integrates many human perspectives to “look at the planet’s sustainability from the ocean’s point of view.” The Oceano Azul Foundation manages the Oceanário de Lisboa, for which Chermayeff &amp;amp; Geismar &amp;amp; Haviv designed the visual identity, as well as major tile murals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open English</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/open-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/open-english/</guid>
      <description> Open English is an online English school with headquarters in Coconut Grove, Florida. In 2014, the school had 100,000 students in the Spanish speaking world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimism Brewing</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/optimism-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/optimism-brewing/</guid>
      <description>Optimism is a brewery founded by husband and wife Troy Hakala and Gay Gilmore in 2013. It took more than a year to secure a location for the brewery and rehabilitation on the 100 year old warehouse took almost two years. Optimism is located in the Capitol Hill neighborhood of Seattle at the corner of Broadway and E Union Street (Map). The brewery opened and we served our first beers on December 5, 2015 (the anniversary of the Repeal of Prohibition).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pbs/</guid>
      <description>The Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) is an American public broadcaster and television program distributor. It is a nonprofit organization and the most prominent provider of educational television programming to public television stations in the United States, distributing series such as American Experience, America&amp;rsquo;s Test Kitchen, Antiques Roadshow, Arthur, Barney &amp;amp; Friends, Clifford the Big Red Dog, Downton Abbey, Finding Your Roots, Frontline, The Magic School Bus, Masterpiece, Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood, Nature, Nova, the PBS NewsHour, Sesame Street, Teletubbies, and This Old House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prague Zoo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo/</guid>
      <description>Prague Zoological Garden is a zoo in Prague, Czech Republic. It was opened in 1931 with the goal to &amp;ldquo;advance the study of zoology, protect wildlife, and educate the public&amp;rdquo; in the district of Troja in the north of Prague. In 2013, the zoo occupied 58 hectares (140 acres) with 50 hectares (120 acres) in use for exhibits, and housed around 5,000 animals from just 676 species, including 132 species listed as threatened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princeton University Press</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/princeton-university-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/princeton-university-press/</guid>
      <description> Princeton University Press is an independent publisher with close connections to Princeton University. Its mission is to disseminate scholarship within academia and society at large.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RatPac</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac/</guid>
      <description> RatPac Entertainment is an American motion picture production and financing company owned by producer-director Brett Ratner. RatPac was founded by Ratner and billionaire James Packer. RatPac is a partner in RatPac-Dune Entertainment with Dune Entertainment.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Gems</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</guid>
      <description> Screen Gems, Inc. is an American film production and distribution studio that is a division of Sony Pictures&amp;rsquo;s Motion Picture Group, a subsidiary of Japanese multinational conglomerate Sony.[1] It has served several different purposes for its parent companies over the decades since its incorporation. The label currently specializes in genre films, mainly horror.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinsegae</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</guid>
      <description> Shinsegae (Korean: 신세계, KRX: 004170) is a South Korean department store franchise, along with several other businesses, headquartered in Seoul, South Korea. The name Shinsegae literally means &amp;ldquo;New World&amp;rdquo; in Korean. Its flagship store in Centum City, Busan, was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest department store at 3,163,000 square feet (293,900 m2), surpassing Macy&amp;rsquo;s flagship Herald Square in New York City in 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showtime</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime/</guid>
      <description> Showtime Networks Inc. (SNI) is an American entertainment company that oversees the company&amp;rsquo;s premium cable television channels, including its flagship service Showtime. It is a subsidiary of media conglomerate CBS Corporation.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smithsonian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smithsonian/</guid>
      <description>The Smithsonian Institution (/smɪθˈsoʊniən/ smith-SOH-nee-ən), also known simply as the Smithsonian, is a group of museums and research centers administered by the Government of the United States. It was founded on August 10, 1846, &amp;ldquo;for the increase and diffusion of knowledge&amp;rdquo;.[= The institution is named after its founding donor, British scientist James Smithson. It was originally organized as the &amp;ldquo;United States National Museum&amp;rdquo;, but that name ceased to exist as an administrative entity in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNDP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</guid>
      <description> The United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) is the United Nations&amp;rsquo; global development network. It advocates for change and connects countries to knowledge, experience and resources to help people build a better life for themselves. It provides expert advice, training and grants support to developing countries, with increasing emphasis on assistance to the least developed countries. It promotes technical and investment cooperation among nations.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNH</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</guid>
      <description> The University of New Hampshire (UNH) is a public research university with its main campus in Durham, New Hampshire. It was founded and incorporated in 1866 as a land grant college in Hanover in connection with Dartmouth College. In 1893, UNH moved to Durham.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Bicentennial</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-bicentennial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-bicentennial/</guid>
      <description> The United States Bicentennial was a series of celebrations and observances during the mid-1970s that paid tribute to historical events leading up to the creation of the United States of America as an independent republic. It was a central event in the memory of the American Revolution. The Bicentennial culminated on Sunday, July 4, 1976, with the 200th anniversary of the adoption of the Declaration of Independence.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Open</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-open/</guid>
      <description> The United States Open Tennis Championships is a hard court tennis tournament. The tournament is the modern version of one of the oldest tennis championships in the world, the U.S. National Championship, for which men&amp;rsquo;s singles and men&amp;rsquo;s doubles were first played in 1881.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universidad Tecmilenio</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</guid>
      <description>The Universidad TecMilenio (UTM) (TecMilenio University) is a private institution of higher education. The institution is part of Monterrey Institute of Technology and Higher Education TecMilenio University ITESM System, an educational system with national and international levels, through 30 campus and an online campus with a unique and innovative educational model that forms professionals with the skills needed by modern businesses and organizations. For-profit schools that have entered the country in recent years, the university serves some 21,000 students on its own at high school, undergraduate and postgraduate level, frequently through distance learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Univision Networks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/univision-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/univision-networks/</guid>
      <description> The graphic identification for this large Spanish-language television network features a bold abstract letter “U”, which, with the upper left quadrant turned, also suggests an exuberantly colorful bird.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wta/</guid>
      <description> The Women&amp;rsquo;s Tennis Association (WTA) is the principal organizing body of women&amp;rsquo;s professional tennis. It governs the WTA Tour which is the worldwide professional tennis tour for women and was founded to create a better future for women&amp;rsquo;s tennis. The WTA&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters is in St. Petersburg, Florida, with its European headquarters in London and its Asia-Pacific headquarters in Beijing.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoshinoya</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</guid>
      <description> Yoshinoya is a Japanese multinational fast food chain, and the second-largest chain of gyūdon (beef bowl) restaurants. The chain was established in Japan in 1899. Its motto is &amp;ldquo;Tasty, low-priced, and quick&amp;rdquo;.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>