<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>white on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/colors/white/</link>
    <description>Recent content in white on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/colors/white/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk 123D</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk-123d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk-123d/</guid>
      <description>Autodesk 123D was a suite of hobbyist CAD and 3D modelling tools created by Autodesk. It is similar in scope to Trimble SketchUp and is based on Autodesk Inventor. As well as the more basic drawing and modelling capabilities it also has assembly and constraint support and STL export. Available for the software is also a library of ready-made blocks and objects.
 Autodesk is also working in collaboration with three companies (Ponoko, Techshop and 3D Systems) to enable users of 123D to create physical objects from their designs using 3D printing technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avast</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/avast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/avast/</guid>
      <description>Avast Software s.r.o. is a Czech multinational cybersecurity software company headquartered in Prague, Czech Republic that researches and develops computer security software, machine learning and artificial intelligence. Avast has more than 435 million monthly active users and the second largest market share among anti-malware application vendors worldwide as of April 2020. The company has approximately 1,700 employees across its 25 offices worldwide.
 Avast was founded by Pavel Baudiš and Eduard Kučera in 1988 as a cooperative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C-sharp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/c-sharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/c-sharp/</guid>
      <description>C# is a general-purpose, multi-paradigm programming language encompassing strong typing, lexically scoped, imperative, declarative, functional, generic, object-oriented (class-based), and component-oriented programming disciplines. It was developed around 2000 by Microsoft as part of its .NET initiative and later approved as an international standard by Ecma (ECMA-334) in 2002 and ISO (ISO/IEC 23270) in 2003. Mono is the name of the free and open-source project to develop a compiler and runtime for the language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doosan Bears</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan-bears/</guid>
      <description> The Doosan Bears (Korean: 두산 베어스) are a professional baseball team of the KBO League and are based in Seoul, South Korea. They have won six Korean Series titles (1982, 1995, 2001, 2015, 2016, and 2019) and play their home games at Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Jamsil Baseball Stadium; sharing the stadium with their rivals, the LG Twins.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eslint</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eslint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eslint/</guid>
      <description>ESLint is a static code analysis tool for identifying problematic patterns found in JavaScript code. It was created by Nicholas C. Zakas in 2013. Rules in ESLint are configurable, and customized rules can be defined and loaded. ESLint covers both code quality and coding style issues. ESLint supports current standards of ECMAScript, and experimental syntax from drafts for future standards. Code using JSX or TypeScript can also be processed when a plugin or transpiler is used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanshin Tigers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanshin-tigers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanshin-tigers/</guid>
      <description>The Hanshin Tigers (Japanese: 阪神タイガース Hanshin Taigāsu) are a Nippon Professional Baseball team playing in the Central League. The team is based in Nishinomiya, Hyōgo Prefecture, Japan, and are owned by Hanshin Electric Railway Co., Ltd., a subsidiary of Hankyu Hanshin Holdings Inc.
 The Hanshin Tigers are one of the oldest professional clubs in Japan. They played their first season in 1936 as the Osaka Tigers and assumed their current team name in 1961.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JCB</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb/</guid>
      <description>JCB is a manufacturer of equipment for construction, agriculture, waste handling, and demolition, based in Rocester, Staffordshire, England. It produces over 300 types of machines, including diggers (backhoes), excavators, tractors, and diesel engines, across 22 factories spanning Asia, Europe, North America, and South America; its products are sold in over 150 countries.
 Joseph Cyril Bamford Excavators Ltd. was founded in 1945 by Joseph Cyril Bamford and continues to be owned by the Bamford family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KT Wiz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kt-wiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kt-wiz/</guid>
      <description> KT Wiz (Korean: 케이티 위즈) is a South Korean professional baseball team founded in 2013. Their home stadium is Suwon Baseball Stadium in Suwon.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sega</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sega/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sega/</guid>
      <description>Sega Corporation is a Japanese multinational video game developer and publisher headquartered in Shinagawa, Tokyo. Its international branches, Sega of America and Sega Europe, are respectively headquartered in Irvine, California, and London. Sega&amp;rsquo;s arcade division existed as Sega Interactive Co., Ltd. from 2015 to 2020 before it merged with Sega Games to create Sega Corporation with Sega Games as the surviving entity. Sega is a subsidiary of Sega Group Corporation, which is, in turn, a part of Sega Sammy Holdings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sina Weibo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sina-weibo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sina-weibo/</guid>
      <description>Sina Weibo is a Chinese microblogging (weibo) website. Launched by Sina Corporation on 14 August 2009, it is one of the biggest social media platforms in China, with over 445 million monthly active users as of Q3 2018. The platform has been a huge financial success, with surging stocks, lucrative advertising sales and high revenue and total earnings per quarter. At the start of 2018, it surpassed the US$30 billion market valuation mark for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/skype/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/skype/</guid>
      <description>Skype (/skaɪp/) is a telecommunications application that specializes in providing video chat and voice calls between computers, tablets, mobile devices, the Xbox One console, and smartwatches over the Internet. Skype also provides instant messaging services. Users may transmit text, video, audio and images. Skype allows video conference calls.
 At the end of 2010, there were over 660 million worldwide users, with over 300 million estimated active each month as of August 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Pictures</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Sony Pictures Entertainment Inc. (Sony Pictures or SPE) is an American entertainment company that produces, acquires, and distributes filmed entertainment (theatrical motion pictures, television programs, and recorded videos) through multiple platforms. Through an intermediate holding company called Sony Film Holding Inc., it is operated as a subsidiary of Sony Entertainment Inc., which is itself a subsidiary of the Japanese multinational technology and media conglomerate Sony Corporation. Based at the former Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer lot in Culver City, California, it encompasses Sony&amp;rsquo;s motion picture, television production and distribution units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/supreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/supreme/</guid>
      <description>Supreme is an American skateboarding shop and clothing brand established in New York City in April 1994.
 The brand caters to the skateboarding and hip hop cultures as well as to youth culture in general. The brand produces clothes and accessories and also manufactures skateboards. Its shoes, clothing, and accessories are sold extensively in the secondary market.
The distinctive red box logo with &amp;ldquo;Supreme&amp;rdquo; in white Futura Heavy Oblique is largely based on Barbara Kruger&amp;rsquo;s propaganda art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swatch</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/swatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/swatch/</guid>
      <description>Swatch (stylized as swatch) is a Swiss watchmaker founded in 1983 by Ernst Thomke, Elmar Mock, and Jacques Müller, and a flagship subsidiary of The Swatch Group. The Swatch product line was developed as a response to the &amp;ldquo;quartz crisis&amp;rdquo; of the 1970s and 1980s, in which Asian-made digital watches were competing against traditional European-made mechanical watches.
 The name Swatch is a contraction of &amp;ldquo;second watch&amp;rdquo;, as the watches were intended as casual, disposable accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tidal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tidal/</guid>
      <description>Tidal (stylized in all caps) is a subscription-based music, podcast and video streaming service that combines lossless audio and high-definition music videos with exclusive content and special features on music. Tidal was launched in 2014 by Norwegian public company Aspiro and is now owned by Project Panther Bidco.
 With distribution agreements with all three major record labels and many independent labels, Tidal claims to offer access to more than 60 million tracks and 240,000 music videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tmall.com</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tmall-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tmall-com/</guid>
      <description>Tmall.com (Chinese: 天猫; pinyin: Tiānmāo), formerly Taobao Mall, is a Chinese-language website for business-to-consumer (B2C) online retail, spun off from Taobao, operated in China by Alibaba Group. It is a platform for local Chinese and international businesses to sell brand name goods to consumers in mainland China, Hong Kong, Macau and Taiwan. It has over 500 million monthly active users, as of February 2018. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s third most visited website according to Alexa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkcell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkcell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkcell/</guid>
      <description> Turkcell is the leading mobile phone operator of Turkey, based in Istanbul. The company has 34.4 million subscribers as of September 30, 2011. In 2015, the company&amp;rsquo;s number of subscribers climbed to 68.9 million, in nine countries Largest shareholder is Telia Finland Oyj with 51% ownership. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest companies (Fortune 2000) list published by Fortune.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft/</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft Entertainment is a French video game company headquartered in Montreuil with several development studios across the world. It publishes games for several video game franchises, including Rayman, Raving Rabbids, Prince of Persia, Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed, Far Cry, Just Dance, and the Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s series. As of March 2018, Ubisoft is the fifth largest publicly traded game company in the Americas and Europe in terms of revenue and market capitalisation, after Activision Blizzard, Electronic Arts, Take-Two Interactive and CD Projekt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unity/</guid>
      <description>Unity is a cross-platform game engine developed by Unity Technologies, first announced and released in June 2005 at Apple Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Developers Conference as a Mac OS X-exclusive game engine. As of 2018, the engine had been extended to support more than 25 platforms. The engine can be used to create three-dimensional, two-dimensional, virtual reality, and augmented reality games, as well as simulations and other experiences. The engine has been adopted by industries outside video gaming, such as film, automotive, architecture, engineering and construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engine</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unreal-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unreal-engine/</guid>
      <description>The Unreal Engine is a game engine developed by Epic Games, first showcased in the 1998 first-person shooter game Unreal. Although initially developed for first-person shooters, it has been used in a variety of other genres, including platformers, fighting games, MMORPGs, and other RPGs. Written in C++, the Unreal Engine features a high degree of portability, supporting a wide range of platforms.
 The latest release is Unreal Engine 4, which launched in 2014 under a subscription model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Network</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-network/</guid>
      <description>USA Network (on-air simply as USA, stylized as usa since 2005) is an American basic cable channel owned by the NBCUniversal Television and Streaming division of NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast. It was originally launched in 1977 as Madison Square Garden Sports Network, one of the first national sports cable television channels, before being relaunched as USA Network in 1980. Once a minor player in basic-tier pay television, USA has steadily gained popularity due to its original programming; it is one of four major subscription-television networks (with TBS, TNT and FX) that also broadcasts syndicated reruns of current and former network television series and theatrically-released feature films, as well as limited sports programming and WWE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whole Foods</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/whole-foods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/whole-foods/</guid>
      <description>Whole Foods Market Inc. is an American multinational supermarket chain headquartered in Austin, Texas, which sells products free from hydrogenated fats and artificial colors, flavors, and preservatives. A USDA Certified Organic grocer in the United States, the chain is popularly known for its organic selections. Whole Foods has 500 stores in North America and seven in the United Kingdom as of March 4, 2019.
 On August 23, 2017, it was reported that the Federal Trade Commission had approved a merger between Amazon and Whole Foods Market; the deal was closed on August 28, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WWF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wwf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wwf/</guid>
      <description>The World Wide Fund for Nature (WWF) is an international non-governmental organization founded in 1961 that works in the field of wilderness preservation and the reduction of human impact on the environment. It was formerly named the World Wildlife Fund, which remains its official name in Canada and the United States.
 WWF is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest conservation organization, with over five million supporters worldwide, working in more than 100 countries and supporting around 3,000 conservation and environmental projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DreamWorks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamworks/</guid>
      <description>DreamWorks Animation LLC (also simply known as DreamWorks, and later rebranded as such since 2018) is an American animation studio that is a subsidiary of Universal Pictures, itself a subsidiary of NBCUniversal, which is owned by Comcast. It is based in Glendale, California, and produces animated feature films, television programs, and online virtual games. The studio has currently released a total of 38 feature films, beginning with Antz (1998); its most recent film was Trolls World Tour (2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Games</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games/</guid>
      <description>Epic Games, Inc. is an American video game and software developer and publisher based in Cary, North Carolina. The company was founded by Tim Sweeney as Potomac Computer Systems in 1991, originally located in his parents&amp;rsquo; house in Potomac, Maryland. Following his first commercial video game release, ZZT (1991), the company became Epic MegaGames, Inc. in early 1992 and brought on Mark Rein, who is the company&amp;rsquo;s vice president to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etihad Airways</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/etihad-airways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/etihad-airways/</guid>
      <description>Etihad Airways (Arabic: شَرِكَة ٱلْاِتِّحَاد لِلطَّيْرَان‎, romanized: sharikat al-ittiḥād li-ṭ-ṭayarān) is the flag carrier of the UAE and the second-largest airline in the country (after Emirates). Its head office is in Khalifa City, Abu Dhabi, near Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s International Airport. Etihad commenced operations in November 2003.
 The airline operates more than 1,000 flights per week to over 120 passenger and cargo destinations in the Middle East, Africa, Europe, Asia, Australia, and North America, with a fleet of 102 Airbus and Boeing aircraft as of February 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferrari</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ferrari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ferrari/</guid>
      <description>Ferrari is an Italian luxury sports car manufacturer based in Maranello. Founded by Enzo Ferrari in 1939 out of Alfa Romeo&amp;rsquo;s race division as Auto Avio Costruzioni, the company built its first car in 1940. However, the company&amp;rsquo;s inception as an auto manufacturer is usually recognized in 1947, when the first Ferrari-badged car was completed.
 In 2014 Ferrari was rated the world&amp;rsquo;s most powerful brand by Brand Finance. In June 2018, the 1964 250 GTO became the most expensive car in history, setting an all-time record selling price of $70 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity Investments</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fidelity-investments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fidelity-investments/</guid>
      <description>Fidelity banking &amp;amp; finances Inc., commonly referred to as Fidelity, earlier as Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research or FMR, is an American multinational financial services corporation based in Boston, Massachusetts.
 It is one of the largest asset managers in the world with $2.46 trillion in assets under management as of March 2018 and a combined total customer asset value number of $6.7 trillion. Fidelity banking &amp;amp; finances operates a brokerage firm, manages a large family of mutual funds, provides fund distribution and investment advice, retirement services, Index funds, wealth management, cryptocurrency, securities execution and clearance, and life insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flix/</guid>
      <description>Flix is an American premium cable and satellite television network that is owned by Showtime Networks, a subsidiary of ViacomCBS through its domestic networks division. Its programming consists solely of theatrically released feature films released from the 1970s to the present day, interspersed with some films from the 1950s and 1960s.
 It is the only premium television service in the United States that does not operate any multiplex channels that provide additional programming alongside the main service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Locker</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker/</guid>
      <description>Foot Locker Retail, Inc. is an American sportswear and footwear retailer, with its headquarters in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, and operating in 28 countries.
 Although established in 1974, and founded as a separate company in 1988, Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s roots date to 1879, as it is a successor corporation to the F. W. Woolworth Company (“Woolworth&amp;rsquo;s”), as many of its freestanding stores were originally Kinney Shoes and Woolworth&amp;rsquo;s locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite/</guid>
      <description>Fortnite is an online video game developed by Epic Games and released in 2017. It is available in three distinct game mode versions that otherwise share the same general gameplay and game engine: Fortnite: Save the World, a cooperative shooter-survival game for up to four players to fight off zombie-like creatures and defend objects with fortifications they can build; Fortnite Battle Royale, a free-to-play battle royale game where up to 100 players fight to be the last person standing; and Fortnite Creative, where players are given complete freedom to create worlds and battle arenas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freddie Mac</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/freddie-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/freddie-mac/</guid>
      <description>The Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corporation (FHLMC), known as Freddie Mac, is a public government-sponsored enterprise (GSE), headquartered in Tysons Corner, Virginia.[3][4] Freddie Mac is ranked No. 38 on the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.
 The FHLMC was created in 1970 to expand the secondary market for mortgages in the US. Along with the Federal National Mortgage Association (Fannie Mae), Freddie Mac buys mortgages on the secondary market, pools them, and sells them as a mortgage-backed security to investors on the open market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heinz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz/</guid>
      <description>The H. J. Heinz Company, better known as Heinz, is an American food processing company headquartered at One PPG Place in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, part of the Kraft Heinz Company. The company was founded by Henry John Heinz in 1869. Heinz manufactures thousands of food products in plants on six continents, and markets these products in more than 200 countries and territories. The company claims to have 150 number-one or number-two brands worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel-Osco</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jewel-osco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jewel-osco/</guid>
      <description>Jewel-Osco is a supermarket chain in the Greater Chicago area, headquartered in Itasca, a western suburb. Jewel-Osco currently has 188 stores across northern, central, and western Illinois; eastern Iowa; and portions of northwest Indiana. Jewel-Osco and Jewel are currently wholly owned subsidiaries of Boise, Idaho-based Albertsons. The company originally started as a door-to-door coffee delivery service before it expanded into delivering non-perishable groceries and later into grocery stores, and supermarkets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kayak</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kayak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kayak/</guid>
      <description>Kayak.com, sometimes styled as KAYAK, is a travel agency and metasearch engine owned and operated by Booking Holdings. The company also runs travel search engines checkfelix, Mundi, Hotels Combined, and swoodoo.
 Kayak&amp;rsquo;s website and mobile apps are currently available in over 18 languages and more than 30 countries, including the United States, the United Kingdom, India, China, France, Germany, Italy, Spain, Russia, Switzerland, Norway, Sweden, Finland, the Netherlands, Australia, Ireland, Mexico, New Zealand, Belgium, Hong Kong, Taiwan, Korea, Japan, and Singapore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lacoste</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</guid>
      <description>Lacoste is a French company, founded in 1933 by tennis player René Lacoste and André Gillier. It sells clothing, footwear, sportswear, eyewear, leather goods, perfume, towels and watches. The company can be recognised by its green crocodile logo. René Lacoste, the company&amp;rsquo;s founder, was nicknamed &amp;ldquo;the Crocodile&amp;rdquo; by fans because of his tenacity on the tennis court. In November 2012 Lacoste was bought outright by Swiss family-held group Maus Frères.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lenovo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lenovo/</guid>
      <description>Lenovo Group Limited, often shortened to Lenovo (/lɛˈnoʊvoʊ/ leh-NOH-voh), is a Chinese multinational technology company that is headquartered in Beijing. The company designs, develops, manufactures, and sells personal computers, tablet computers, smartphones, workstations, servers, electronic storage devices, IT management software, and smart televisions. Lenovo is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest personal computer vendor by unit sales, as of March 2019. It markets the ThinkPad and ThinkBook business lines of notebook computers; IdeaPad, Yoga, and Legion consumer lines of notebook laptops; and the IdeaCentre and ThinkCentre lines of desktops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberty Media</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media/</guid>
      <description>Liberty Media Corporation (commonly referred to as Liberty Media or just Liberty) is an American mass media company controlled by chairman John C. Malone. The company has three divisions, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s ownership stakes in Formula One, SiriusXM, and the Atlanta Braves.
  Source About Liberty Media Liberty Media Corporation owns interests in a broad range of media, communications and entertainment businesses. Those interests are attributed to three tracking stock groups: the Liberty SiriusXM Group, the Braves Group and the Formula One Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Underground</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground/</guid>
      <description>The London Underground (also known simply as the Underground, or by its nickname the Tube) is a public rapid transit system serving London region, England and some parts of the adjacent counties of Buckinghamshire, Essex and Hertfordshire in the United Kingdom.
 The Underground has its origins in the Metropolitan Railway, the world&amp;rsquo;s first underground passenger railway. Opened in January 1863, it is now part of the Circle, Hammersmith &amp;amp; City and Metropolitan lines; the first line to operate underground electric traction trains, the City &amp;amp; South London Railway in 1890, is now part of the Northern line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lowe’s</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes/</guid>
      <description>Lowe&amp;rsquo;s Companies, Inc. (/loʊz/), doing business as Lowe&amp;rsquo;s, is an American retail company specializing in home improvement. Headquartered in Mooresville, North Carolina, the company operates a chain of retail stores in the United States and Canada. As of November 2018, Lowe&amp;rsquo;s and its related businesses operate 2,015 home improvement and hardware stores in North America.
 Lowe&amp;rsquo;s is the second-largest hardware chain in the United States behind rival The Home Depot and ahead of Menards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Studios</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-studios/</guid>
      <description>Marvel Studios, LLC (originally known as Marvel Films from 1993 to 1996) is an American film and television studio that is a subsidiary of The Walt Disney Studios. Marvel Studios is known for the production of the Marvel Cinematic Universe films, based on characters that appear in Marvel Comics publications.
 Marvel Studios has released 23 films since 2008 within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, from Iron Man (2008) to Spider-Man: Far From Home (2019).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mattel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mattel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mattel/</guid>
      <description>Mattel, Inc. (/məˈtɛl/) is an American multinational toy manufacturing and entertainment company founded in 1945 with headquarters in El Segundo, California. The products and brands it produces include Fisher-Price, Barbie, Monster High, Ever After High, Polly Pocket, Hot Wheels, Matchbox, Masters of the Universe, American Girl, Thomas &amp;amp; Friends, and WWE. In the early 1980s, Mattel produced video game systems, under its own brands and under license from Nintendo. The company has presence in 40 countries and territories and sells products in more than 150 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/michelin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/michelin/</guid>
      <description>Michelin (/ˈmɪʃəlɪn, -læ̃/; full name: Compagnie Générale des Établissements Michelin SCA) is a French multinational tyre manufacturer based in Clermont-Ferrand in the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes région of France. It is the second largest tyre manufacturer in the world after Bridgestone and larger than both Goodyear and Continental. In addition to the Michelin brand, it also owns the Kléber tyres company, Uniroyal-Goodrich Tire Company, SASCAR, Bookatable and Camso brands. Michelin is also notable for its Red and Green travel guides, its roadmaps, the Michelin stars that the Red Guide awards to restaurants for their cooking, and for its company mascot Bibendum, colloquially known as the Michelin Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mtv/</guid>
      <description>MTV (originally an initialism of Music Television) is an American cable channel, launched on August 1, 1981. Based in New York City, it serves as the flagship property of the ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division of ViacomCBS, also headquartered in New York City.
 MTV originally aired music videos as guided by television personalities known as &amp;ldquo;video jockeys&amp;rdquo; (VJs), but in the years since its inception, the network significantly toned down its focus on music in favor of original reality programming targeting teenagers and young adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nasa/</guid>
      <description>The National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA; /ˈnæsə/) is an independent agency of the United States Federal Government responsible for the civilian space program, as well as aeronautics and space research. NASA was established in 1958, succeeding the National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics (NACA). The new agency was to have a distinctly civilian orientation, encouraging peaceful applications in space science. Since its establishment, most US space exploration efforts have been led by NASA, including the Apollo Moon landing missions, the Skylab space station, and later the Space Shuttle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nat Geo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nat-geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nat-geo/</guid>
      <description>National Geographic (formerly the National Geographic Magazine and branded also as NAT GEO) is the official magazine of the National Geographic Society. It has been published continuously since its first issue in 1888, nine months after the Society itself was founded. It primarily contains articles about science, geography, history, and world culture. The magazine is known for its thick square-bound glossy format with a yellow rectangular border and its extensive use of dramatic photographs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nissan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissan/</guid>
      <description>Nissan Motor Co., Ltd. (Japanese: 日産自動車株式会社, Hepburn: Nissan Jidōsha Kabushiki-gaisha), usually shortened to Nissan is a Japanese multinational automobile manufacturer headquartered in Nishi-ku, Yokohama. The company sells its cars under the Nissan, Infiniti, and Datsun brands with in-house performance tuning products labelled Nismo. The company traces its name to the Nissan zaibatsu, now called Nissan Group.
 Since 1999, Nissan has been part of the Renault–Nissan–Mitsubishi Alliance (Mitsubishi joining in 2016), a partnership between Nissan of Japan, Mitsubishi Motors of Japan and Renault of France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oculus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oculus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oculus/</guid>
      <description>Oculus is a division of Facebook Technologies, LLC, a subsidiary of Facebook Inc. Founded by Palmer Luckey, Brendan Iribe, Michael Antonov and Nate Mitchell in July 2012 in Irvine, California, now based in Menlo Park. It specializes in virtual reality hardware and software products.
 In April 2012, Luckey announced the Rift, a virtual reality headset designed for video gaming, and launched a Kickstarter campaign in August to make virtual reality headsets available to developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paramount</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount/</guid>
      <description>Paramount Pictures Corporation (also known simply as Paramount) is an American film studio and subsidiary of ViacomCBS. It is the fifth oldest film studio in the world, the second oldest film studio in the United States, and the sole member of the &amp;ldquo;Big Five&amp;rdquo; film studios still located in Los Angeles.
 In 1916, film producer Adolph Zukor put 22 actors and actresses under contract and honored each with a star on the logo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Network</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount-network/</guid>
      <description>Paramount Network is an American pay television channel owned by ViacomCBS. The network&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are located at the Paramount Pictures studio lot in Los Angeles.
 The channel was originally founded by a partnership between radio station WSM and Westinghouse Broadcasting as The Nashville Network (TNN) and began broadcasting March 7, 1983. It initially featured programming catering towards the culture of the Southern United States, including country music, variety shows, outdoors programming, and motor racing coverage (such as NASCAR).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinduoduo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pinduoduo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pinduoduo/</guid>
      <description>Pinduoduo Inc. (Chinese: 拼多多; Pinyin: Pīn duōduō) is the largest interactive e-commerce platform in China and in the world. It is the second-largest online marketplace in China by number of users and number of orders. It is also one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest internet companies. It has pioneered several new trends including social e-commerce, team purchase and consumer-to-manufacturer (C2M) that have revolutionized online shopping in China. Pinduoduo ranks just behind Alibaba Group with close to 600 million users and recorded 1 trillion yuan in GMV in under five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ResearchGate</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/researchgate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/researchgate/</guid>
      <description>ResearchGate is a European commercial social networking site for scientists and researchers to share papers, ask and answer questions, and find collaborators. According to a 2014 study by Nature and a 2016 article in Times Higher Education, it is the largest academic social network in terms of active users, although other services have more registered users, and a 2015–2016 survey suggests that almost as many academics have Google Scholar profiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockstar</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rockstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rockstar/</guid>
      <description>Rockstar Games, Inc. is an American video game publisher based in New York City. The company was established in December 1998 as a subsidiary of Take-Two Interactive, using the assets Take-Two had previously acquired from BMG Interactive. Founding members of the company were Sam and Dan Houser, Terry Donovan and Jamie King, who worked for Take-Two at the time, and of which the Houser brothers were previously executives at BMG Interactive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/safeway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/safeway/</guid>
      <description>Safeway is an American supermarket chain founded in April 1915 in American Falls, Idaho by Marion Barton Skaggs. It is a subsidiary of Albertsons after being acquired by private equity investors led by Cerberus Capital Management in January 2015. Safeway&amp;rsquo;s primary base of operations is in the west [1] with some stores located in the Mid-Atlantic region of the Eastern Seaboard. The subsidiary is headquartered in Pleasanton, California, with its parent company headquartered in Boise, Idaho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shopify/</guid>
      <description>Shopify Inc. is a Canadian multinational e-commerce company headquartered in Ottawa, Ontario. It is also the name of its proprietary e-commerce platform for online stores and retail point-of-sale systems. Shopify offers online retailers a suite of services &amp;ldquo;including payments, marketing, shipping and customer engagement tools to simplify the process of running an online store for small merchants.&amp;rdquo;
 The company reported that it had more than 1,000,000 businesses in approximately 175 countries using its platform as of June 2019, with total gross merchandise volume exceeding $41.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Softbank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/softbank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/softbank/</guid>
      <description>SoftBank Group Corp. is a Japanese multinational conglomerate holding company headquartered in Tokyo. The company owns stakes in Softbank Corp. (ja), Softbank Vision Fund (ja), Arm Holdings, Fortress Investment Group, Boston Dynamics, Sprint (85%), Alibaba (29.5%), Yahoo Japan (48.17%), Brightstar (87.1%), Uber (15%), Didi Chuxing (ca.20%), Ola (ca.30%), Renren (42.9%), InMobi (45%), Hike (25.8%), Snapdeal (ca.30%), Fanatics (ca.22%), Improbable Worlds (ca.50%), Paytm (ca.20%), OYO (42%), Ping An Insurance (7.41%), Slack Technologies (ca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACME</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acme/</guid>
      <description> Acme Markets Inc. is a supermarket chain operating 164 stores throughout Connecticut, Delaware, Maryland, New Jersey, New York, and Pennsylvania and, as of 1999, is a subsidiary of Albertsons, and part of its presence in the Northeast. It is headquartered in East Whiteland Township, Pennsylvania, near Malvern, a Philadelphia suburb.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advance Auto Parts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts/</guid>
      <description>Advance Auto Parts, Inc. (Advance) is an American automotive aftermarket parts provider. Headquartered in Raleigh, North Carolina, it serves both professional installer and do-it-yourself (DIY) customers. As of July 13, 2019, Advance operated 4,912 stores and 150 Worldpac branches in the United States and Canada. The Company also serves 1,250 independently owned Carquest branded stores across these locations in addition to Mexico, the Bahamas, Turks and Caicos and British Virgin Islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AirAsia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/airasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/airasia/</guid>
      <description>AirAsia Berhad is a Malaysian low-cost airline headquartered near Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. It is the largest airline in Malaysia by fleet size and destinations. AirAsia Group operates scheduled domestic and international flights to more than 165 destinations spanning 25 countries. Its main hub is klia2, the low-cost carrier terminal at Kuala Lumpur International Airport (KLIA) in Sepang, Selangor, Malaysia. Its affiliate airlines Thai AirAsia, Indonesia AirAsia, Philippines AirAsia, AirAsia India and AirAsia Japan have hubs in Bangkok-Don Mueang, Jakarta-Soekarno–Hatta , Manila-Ninoy Aquino, Bengaluru (Bangalore)-Kempegowda and Nayoga-Chübu Centair airports respectively, while its sister airline, AirAsia X, focuses on long-haul routes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asahi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi/</guid>
      <description>Asahi Group Holdings, Ltd. is a global beer, spirits, soft drinks and food business group headquartered in Tokyo, Japan.
 In 2018, the group had a revenue JPY 2.1 trillion. Asahi&amp;rsquo;s revenue can be segmented as follows: alcoholic beverage business (41.3%), overseas business (32%), soft drinks business (16.6%), food business (5.2%) and &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; business (4.9%). Asahi, with a 37% market share, is the largest of the four major beer brewers in Japan followed by Kirin Beer with 34% and Suntory with 16%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barcelona-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barcelona-fc/</guid>
      <description> Futbol Club Barcelona (Catalan pronunciation: [fubˈbɔl ˈklub bəɾsəˈlonə] (About this soundlisten)), commonly referred to as Barcelona and colloquially known as Barça , is a Spanish professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</guid>
      <description>The British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) is a British public service broadcaster. Its headquarters are at Broadcasting House in Westminster, London. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest national broadcaster, and the largest broadcaster in the world by number of employees. It employs over 22,000 staff in total, more than 16,000 of whom are in public sector broadcasting. The total number of staff is 35,402 when part-time, flexible, and fixed-contract staff are included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bertelsmann Music Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bertelsmann-music-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bertelsmann-music-group/</guid>
      <description>Bertelsmann Music Group (BMG) was a division of German media company Bertelsmann before its completion of sale of the majority of its assets to Sony Corporation of America on 1 October 2008. Although it was established in 1987, the music company was formed as RCA/Ariola International in 1985 as a joint venture to combine the music label activities of RCA Corporation&amp;rsquo;s RCA Records division and Bertelsmann&amp;rsquo;s Ariola Records and its associated labels which include Arista Records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-dynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-dynamics/</guid>
      <description> Boston Dynamics is an American engineering and robotics design company founded in 1992 as a spin-off from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Headquartered in Waltham, Massachusetts, Boston Dynamics is a wholly owned subsidiary of the Japanese conglomerate SoftBank Group.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bravo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo/</guid>
      <description>Bravo is an American pay television network, launched on December 1, 1980. It is owned by NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast. The channel originally focused on programming related to fine arts and film. It currently broadcasts several reality television series targeted at 25–54-year-old women as well as the gay community, along with acquired and original dramas, and mainstream theatrically released feature films.
 As of January 2016, approximately 89,824,000 American households (77.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridgestone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bridgestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bridgestone/</guid>
      <description> Bridgestone Corporation is a Japanese multinational auto and truck parts manufacturer founded in 1931 by Shojiro Ishibashi (石橋正二郎, Ishibashi Shōjirō) in the city of Kurume, Fukuoka, Japan. The name Bridgestone comes from a calque translation and transposition of ishibashi, meaning &amp;ldquo;stone bridge&amp;rdquo; in Japanese.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/broadcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/broadcom/</guid>
      <description> Broadcom Inc. is an American designer, developer, manufacturer and global supplier of a wide range of semiconductor and infrastructure software products, Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio serves the data center, networking, software, broadband, wireless, and storage and industrial markets.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bugatti</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</guid>
      <description> Automobiles Ettore Bugatti was a French car manufacturer of high-performance automobiles, founded in 1909 in the then-German city of Molsheim, Alsace by the Italian-born industrial designer Ettore Bugatti. The cars were known for their design beauty and for their many race victories. Famous Bugattis include the Type 35 Grand Prix cars, the Type 41 &amp;ldquo;Royale&amp;rdquo;, the Type 57 &amp;ldquo;Atlantic&amp;rdquo; and the Type 55 sports car.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Network</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network/</guid>
      <description>Cartoon Network is an American pay television channel owned by Warner Bros. Entertainment, a division of AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. The channel was launched on October 1, 1992, and primarily broadcasts animated television series, mostly children&amp;rsquo;s programming, ranging from action to animated comedy. It operates usually from 6:00 AM to 8:00 PM (ET/PT) and is targeted at children between ages 7 and 15. Its overnight daypart block Adult Swim is aimed at adults and is treated as a separate entity for promotional purposes and as a separate channel by Nielsen for ratings purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs/</guid>
      <description>CBS (an initialism of the network&amp;rsquo;s former name, the Columbia Broadcasting System) is an American English-language commercial broadcast television and radio network that is the flagship property of the CBS Entertainment Group division of ViacomCBS. The company is headquartered at the CBS Building in New York City with major production facilities and operations in New York City (at the CBS Broadcast Center) and Los Angeles (at CBS Television City and the CBS Studio Center).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/claro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/claro/</guid>
      <description> Claro Americas is a Brazilian company part of América Móvil, a Mexican telecom group. Claro serves clients in Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, the Dominican Republic, Ecuador, El Salvador, Guatemala, Honduras, Nicaragua, Panama, Paraguay, Peru, Puerto Rico and Uruguay. The company&amp;rsquo;s name means &amp;ldquo;bright&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;clear&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo; in Portuguese and Spanish.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC Defenders</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-defenders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-defenders/</guid>
      <description>The DC Defenders are a professional American football team based in Washington, D.C. The team is an owned-and-operated member of the new XFL founded by Vince McMahon’s Alpha Entertainment and plays its home games at Audi Field, a soccer-specific stadium owned and originally built by Major League Soccer&amp;rsquo;s D.C. United, who leases the land from the District of Columbia. At 20,000 seats, Audi Field is the smallest stadium in the XFL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dogecoin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dogecoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dogecoin/</guid>
      <description> Dogecoin (DOGE, symbol: Ð and D) is a Litecoin-derived cryptocurrency featuring a Shiba Inu from the Doge Internet meme on its logo. The users themselves call it “joky”. One of the most popular uses of the coin is the reward of Internet users for interesting and quality content created or shared by them. It was introduced on December 8, 2013.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DQ</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</guid>
      <description> Dairy Queen (DQ) is an American multinational chain of soft serve ice cream and fast-food restaurants owned by International Dairy Queen, Inc., a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway. International Dairy Queen, Inc., also owns Orange Julius, and formerly owned Karmelkorn and Golden Skillet Fried Chicken.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lotte</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte/</guid>
      <description> Lotte Corporation (Korean: 롯데 그룹 lotte geurup) is a South Korean multinational conglomerate. Lotte began its history on June 28, 1948, by Korean businessman Shin Kyuk-ho in Tokyo. Shin expanded Lotte to his ancestral country, South Korea, with the establishment of Lotte Confectionery in Seoul on April 3, 1967. Lotte eventually grew to become South Korea&amp;rsquo;s fifth largest business conglomerate.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marui</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marui/</guid>
      <description> Marui Co., Ltd. (株式会社丸井, Kabushiki-gaisha Marui) (TYO: 8252) is a Japanese retail company which operates a chain of department stores in Tokyo as well in other major Japanese cities. They are best known for their women&amp;rsquo;s fashion and accessories, which are aimed at the 25–35 age range.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sshc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sshc/</guid>
      <description>At The Spine &amp;amp; Sports Health Center, SSHC top interventional pain management physicians will take the time to understand your pain, listen and focus on what matters most to you. SSHC use the latest diagnostic technology (and good old-fashioned listening and observation) to develop an accurate diagnosis. And, SSHC&amp;rsquo;ll develop a personalized treatment plan combining the most effective and least invasive options to fit your needs &amp;ndash;without the risks or complications of surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Peter University</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-peter-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-peter-university/</guid>
      <description> Saint Peter&amp;rsquo;s University is a private Jesuit university in Jersey City, New Jersey. It was founded as Saint Peter&amp;rsquo;s College in 1872 by the Society of Jesus. It offers over 60 undergraduate and graduate programs to more than 2,600 undergraduate and 800 graduate students. Its college mascot is the Peacock and its sports teams play in the Metro Atlantic Athletic Conference, of which it is a founding member.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webhelp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/webhelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/webhelp/</guid>
      <description>Established in 2000, Webhelp is a global leader in customer experience, contact centers, and business solutions, helping clients manage their customer interactions at every stage possible. Headquartered in Paris, France, Webhelp has grown exponentially since 2011 through acquisitions in other parts of the world and is now present in more than 140 locations in over 35 countries, employing more than 50,000 people, and serving over 500 clients. Recently, Webhelp introduced a new identity designed by the Paris office of Futurebrand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yelp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yelp/</guid>
      <description> Yelp is a business directory service and crowd-sourced review forum, and a public company of the same name that is headquartered in San Francisco, California. The company develops, hosts, and markets the Yelp.com website and the Yelp mobile app, which publish crowd-sourced reviews about businesses. It also operates an online reservation service called Yelp Reservations.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beats</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beats/</guid>
      <description> Beats Electronics LLC (also known as Beats by Dr. Dre, or simply Beats by Dre) is a subsidiary of Apple Inc. that produces audio products. Headquartered in Culver City, California, the company was founded by music producer and rapper Dr. Dre and Interscope Records co-founder Jimmy Iovine.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Western</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-western/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-western/</guid>
      <description> Best Western International, Inc. owns the Best Western Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts brand, which it licenses to over 4,500 hotels worldwide. The franchise, with its corporate headquarters in Phoenix, Arizona, includes more than 2,000 hotels in North America. The brand was founded by M.K. Guertin in 1946. As of May 2019, David Kong is the president and CEO of Best Western and Dorothy Dowling is the chief marketing officer.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Cash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017. In 2018 Bitcoin Cash subsequently split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash, and Bitcoin SV. Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Apron</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</guid>
      <description> Blue Apron Inc. is an American ingredient-and-recipe meal kit service. It exclusively operates in the United States. The weekly boxes contain ingredients and also include suggested recipes that must be cooked by hand by the customer using the pre-ordered ingredients.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crown Audio</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-audio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-audio/</guid>
      <description> Crown International, or Crown Audio, is an American manufacturer of audio electronics, and is a subsidiary of Harman International Industries, which has been part of South Korea-based Samsung Electronics since 2017. Today, the company is known primarily for its power amplifiers, but has also manufactured microphones, a line of commercial audio products as well as digital audio networking products.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dazzler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dazzler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dazzler/</guid>
      <description> Featuring sleek decor and exceptional service, Dazzler Hotels represent an exciting synthesis of comfort and functional aesthetics. Centrally located in some of Latin America’s most vibrant neighborhoods, Dazzler offers easy access to local hotspots and top attractions.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deseret News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</guid>
      <description>The Deseret News is a newspaper published in Salt Lake City, Utah, United States. It is Utah&amp;rsquo;s oldest continuously published daily newspaper and has the largest Sunday circulation in the state and the second largest daily circulation behind The Salt Lake Tribune. The News is owned by Deseret News Publishing Company, a subsidiary of Deseret Management Corporation, a holding company owned by The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DigiTech</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/digitech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/digitech/</guid>
      <description> DigiTech is an American company which manufactures digital effects units.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolce</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dolce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dolce/</guid>
      <description> Dolce Hotels and Resorts’ awe-inspiring locations provide imaginative environments for guests to connect, create, and discover. State-of-the-art meeting spaces with advanced technology paired with Dolce sophisticated food and beverage program, offer an ideal combination for stimulating creativity. Whether it’s an award-winning golf courses, rejuvenating spas, or close proximity to the world’s most famous wineries, guests are drawn to Dolce for meetings, celebrations, and memory-making getaways.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DXT</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</guid>
      <description> DXC Technology is an American multinational corporation that provides B2B IT services.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearing Australia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</guid>
      <description> Hearing Australia is a statutory authority constituted under the Australian Hearing Services Act 1991, reporting to the Minister for Human Services, and is within the Department of Human Services portfolio. Hearing Australia is the largest Australian government-funded hearing aid dispensing company providing hearing care and technologies. One of their areas of interest is hearing testing and rehabilitation of children under the age of 26.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Appeal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</guid>
      <description> Human Appeal is a British international development and relief charity based in Manchester. It was established in 1991. It runs targeted poverty relief programmes in emergency response and sustainable development. In the past, the charity was known as Human Appeal International but was restyled in 2018. It is now known as Human Appeal.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetlines/</guid>
      <description> Canada Jetlines, Ltd. (TSX-V : JET) or simply Jetlines, is a planned Canadian ultra low-cost airline headquartered in Vancouver, British Columbia. Jetlines aims to meet the market demand in Canada for low-fare air travel. Jetlines plans to establish a main base at Vancouver International Airport in British Columbia.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Inn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/knights-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/knights-inn/</guid>
      <description> Knights Inn (officially Knights Franchise Systems, Inc.) is a full-limited service hotel chain owned by Red Lion Hotels Corporation and based in Denver, Colorado. Knights Inns used to be built with all-exterior corridors and medieval-inspired architecture, but the chain now has updated options for all Knights Inn properties.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Quinta</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-quinta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-quinta/</guid>
      <description> Thanks to the exclusive Bright Morning Bed,® free Bright Side Breakfast® and spacious in-room work areas, La Quinta Hotels are a bright spot in every traveler’s journey.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ledger</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</guid>
      <description> Ledger is a fast paced, growing company developing security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies as well as blockchain applications for individuals and companies, by leveraging a distinctive, proprietary technology.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litecoin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</guid>
      <description> Litecoin (LTC or Ł) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency and open-source software project released under the MIT/X11 license. Creation and transfer of coins is based on an open source cryptographic protocol and is not managed by any central authority.[citation needed] Litecoin was an early bitcoin spinoff or altcoin, starting in October 2011. In technical details, litecoin is nearly identical to Bitcoin.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macys</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/macys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/macys/</guid>
      <description>Macy&amp;rsquo;s (originally R. H. Macy &amp;amp; Co., stylized as macy*s) is an American department store chain founded in 1858 by Rowland Hussey Macy. It became a division of the Cincinnati-based Federated Department Stores in 1994 (later renamed as Macy&amp;rsquo;s, Inc. in 2007), as a Bloomingdale&amp;rsquo;s department store chain affiliate. As of 2015, Macy&amp;rsquo;s was the largest U.S. department store company by retail sales. As of February 2019, there were 584 full-line stores with the Macy&amp;rsquo;s nameplate in operation throughout the United States, Puerto Rico, and Guam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monero</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</guid>
      <description> Monero is an open-source cryptocurrency created in April 2014 that focuses on fungibility, privacy and decentralization. Monero uses an obfuscated public ledger, meaning anybody can broadcast or send transactions, but no outside observer can tell the source, amount or destination. Monero uses a Proof of Work mechanism to issue new coins and incentivize miners to secure the network and validate transactions.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shure</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shure/</guid>
      <description> Shure Incorporated is an American audio products corporation. It was founded by Sidney N. Shure in Chicago, Illinois in 1925 as a supplier of radio parts kits. The company became a consumer and professional audio-electronics manufacturer of microphones, wireless microphone systems, phonograph cartridges, discussion systems, mixers, and digital signal processing. The company also manufactures listening products, including headphones, high-end earphones, and personal monitor systems.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steam</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/steam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/steam/</guid>
      <description>Steam is a video game digital distribution service platform developed by Valve Corporation. It was launched in September 2003 as a way for Valve to provide automatic updates for their games, but eventually expanded to include games from third-party publishers. Initially launched as a software client component to help keep Valve&amp;rsquo;s games up-to-date, the Steam service has expanded to include web- and mobile-based interfaces for consumers and developers for third-party games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super 8</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</guid>
      <description> With more than 2,800 hotels on four continents, the newly redesigned Super 8 offers affordable, innovative lodging on the open road. As your ultimate roadside companion, every location also offers free WiFi and a complimentary SuperStart Breakfast to get you recharged and refueled for the day ahead.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tether</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</guid>
      <description> Tether is a controversial cryptocurrency with tokens issued by Tether Limited. It formerly claimed that each token was backed by one United States dollar, but on 14 March 2019 changed the backing to include loans to affiliate companies. The Bitfinex exchange was accused by the New York Attorney General of using Tether&amp;rsquo;s funds to cover up $850 million in funds missing since mid-2018.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Hilfiger</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tommy-hilfiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tommy-hilfiger/</guid>
      <description>Tommy Hilfiger, formerly known as Tommy Hilfiger Corporation and Tommy Hilfiger Inc., is an American premium clothing company, manufacturing apparel, footwear, accessories, fragrances and home furnishings. The company was founded in 1985, and today is sold in department stores and over 1400 free-standing retail stores in 90 countries. In 2006, private equity firm Apax Partners acquired Tommy Hilfiger for approximately $1.6 billion, and in May 2004, PVH Corp. (NYSE: PVH) (then known as Philips van Heusen) bought the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelodge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/travelodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/travelodge/</guid>
      <description> With many of Travelodge hotels conveniently located near national parks and landmarks, Travelodge provides a basecamp for adventure. Travelodge’s friendly service, affordable rates and free continental breakfasts ensure that guests are rested and refueled for their next expedition.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tryp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tryp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tryp/</guid>
      <description> Powered By The City. Tucked in the heart of the world’s greatest cities, TRYP by Wyndham is on the pulse of local hotspots and must-see sites— from the best restaurants, the coolest spots and the best ways to tap directly into the pulse of whatever city – big or small – you’re exploring.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Cambridge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</guid>
      <description>The University of Cambridge (legally The Chancellor, Masters, and Scholars of the University of Cambridge) is a collegiate public research university in Cambridge, United Kingdom. Founded in 1209 and granted a royal charter by King Henry III in 1231, Cambridge is the second-oldest university in the English-speaking world and the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-oldest surviving university. The university grew out of an association of scholars who left the University of Oxford after a dispute with the townspeople.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valve</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/valve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/valve/</guid>
      <description> Valve Corporation is an American video game developer, publisher and digital distribution company headquartered in Bellevue, Washington. It is the developer of the software distribution platform Steam and the Half-Life, Counter-Strike, Portal, Day of Defeat, Team Fortress, Left 4 Dead, and Dota series.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Atlantic</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-atlantic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-atlantic/</guid>
      <description>Virgin Atlantic, a trading name of Virgin Atlantic Airways Limited and Virgin Atlantic International Limited, is a British airline with its head office in Crawley, England. The airline was established in 1984 as British Atlantic Airways, and was originally planned by its co-founders Randolph Fields and Alan Hellary to fly between London and the Falkland Islands. Soon after changing the name to Virgin Atlantic Airways, Fields sold his shares in the company after disagreements with Sir Richard Branson over the management of the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldmark</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/worldmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/worldmark/</guid>
      <description> WorldMark by Wyndham (formerly Trendwest) is the developer and marketer of WorldMark, The Club, a vacation ownership program and part of the Wyndham Worldwide Corporation. The original development partner of the Club was Trendwest International (TWI), a subsidiary of Jeld-Wenn Industries, a privately held door and window manufacturer.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wyndham</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wyndham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wyndham/</guid>
      <description>Simply Comfortable. With locations worldwide, each aspect of a Wyndham hotel or resort is designed with one thing in mind – your comfort. Wyndham enthusiastic staff strives to meet your needs with a warm smile and can-do attitude make sure each and every one has a great stay. From welcoming lobbies, to thoughtfully designed, homey guest rooms with incredible sleep experiences, to well-equipped fitness centers, each space is carefully considered to ensure you feel right at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wyndham Grand</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wyndham-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wyndham-grand/</guid>
      <description> Wyndham Grand’s beautiful destinations around the world combine premium amenities, restaurants, and spas with sophisticated architectural design to leave a lasting impression. From little luxuries that surprise and delight to friendly staff who go above and beyond, Wyndham Grand transforms ordinary experiences into unforgettable memories.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! is an American web services provider headquartered in Sunnyvale, California, and owned by Verizon Media. The original Yahoo! company was founded by Jerry Yang and David Filo in January 1994 and was incorporated on March 2, 1995. Yahoo was one of the pioneers of the early Internet era in the 1990s.
 About new Yahoo! logo  With its new products, Yahoo will empower users to better sift out irrelevant parts of the digital world, giving them more control of what they see and when they see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air New Zealand</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-new-zealand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-new-zealand/</guid>
      <description> Air New Zealand Limited is the flag carrier airline of New Zealand. Based in Auckland, the airline operates scheduled passenger flights to 20 domestic and 31 international destinations in 19 countries around the Pacific Rim and the United Kingdom. The airline has been a member of the Star Alliance since 1999.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Ashe Stadium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</guid>
      <description> Arthur Ashe Stadium is a tennis stadium at Flushing Meadows-Corona Park in Queens, New York City. Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center, it is the main stadium of the US Open tennis tournament, and the largest tennis stadium in the world, with a capacity of 23,771.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>The National Aquarium - also known as National Aquarium in Baltimore and formerly known as Baltimore Aquarium - is a non-profit public aquarium located at 501 East Pratt Street on Pier 3 in the Inner Harbor area of downtown Baltimore, Maryland, in the United States. Constructed during a period of urban renewal in Baltimore, the aquarium opened on August 8, 1981. The aquarium has an annual attendance of 1.5 million visitors and is the largest tourism attraction in the State of Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC News is an operational business division of the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) responsible for the gathering and broadcasting of news and current affairs. The department is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest broadcast news organisation and generates about 120 hours of radio and television output each day, as well as online news coverage. The service maintains 50 foreign news bureaux with more than 250 correspondents around the world. Fran Unsworth has been Director of News and Current Affairs since January 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC World News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC World News is the BBC&amp;rsquo;s international news and current affairs television channel. It has the largest audience of any channel, with an estimated 121 million viewers weekly in 2016/2017, part of the estimated 372 million weekly audience of the BBC&amp;rsquo;s four main international news services. Launched on 11 March 1991 as BBC World Service Television outside Europe, its name was changed to BBC World on 16 January 1995 and to BBC World News on 21 April 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</guid>
      <description> BJ&amp;rsquo;s Wholesale Club Holdings, Inc., commonly referred as BJ&amp;rsquo;s, is an American membership-only warehouse club chain operating on the East Coast of the United States and the state of Ohio.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</guid>
      <description>BP plc (formerly The British Petroleum Company plc and BP Amoco plc) is a British multinational oil and gas company headquartered in London, United Kingdom. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s seven oil and gas &amp;ldquo;supermajors&amp;rdquo;, whose performance in 2012 made it the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth-largest oil and gas company, the sixth-largest energy company by market capitalization and the company with the world&amp;rsquo;s 12th-largest revenue (turnover). It is a vertically integrated company operating in all areas of the oil and gas industry, including exploration and production, refining, distribution and marketing, petrochemicals, power generation and trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</guid>
      <description> Brown University is a private Ivy League research university in Providence, Rhode Island. Founded in 1764 as the College in the English Colony of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, it is the seventh-oldest institution of higher education in the United States and one of the nine colonial colleges chartered before the American Revolution.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BU</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bu/</guid>
      <description> Boston University (commonly referred to as BU) is a private research university in Boston, Massachusetts. The university is nonsectarian, but has been historically affiliated with the United Methodist Church.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</guid>
      <description>CBC News is the division of the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation responsible for the news gathering and production of news programs on the corporation&amp;rsquo;s English-language operations, namely CBC Television, CBC Radio, CBC News Network, and CBC.ca. Founded in 1941, CBC News is the largest news broadcaster in Canada and has local, regional and national broadcasts and stations. It frequently collaborates with its French-language counterpart, Radio-Canada Info, although the two are organizationally separate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBRE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</guid>
      <description> CBRE Group, Inc., is an American commercial real estate services and investment firm. The abbreviation CBRE stands for Coldwell Banker Richard Ellis. As of 2018, it is the largest commercial real estate services company in the world.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</guid>
      <description> The organization offers the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) designation, the Certificate in Investment Performance Measurement (CIPM) designation, and the Investment Foundations Certificate. It provides continuing education conferences, seminars, webcasts, and publications to allow members and other participants to stay current on developments in the investment industry. CFA Institute also oversees the CFA Institute Research Challenge for university students and the Research Foundation of CFA Institute.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cna</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cna/</guid>
      <description> CNA is an English language news channel based in Singapore. It broadcasts free-to-air domestically and as a subscription network to 29 territories across Asia and Australia.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN Airport</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport/</guid>
      <description> CNN Airport is an American out-of-home television network operated by CNN. The service broadcasts general news, weather, stock market updates, entertainment, and travel content to airports across the United States. The founding management was led by Jon Petrovich and Scott Weiss. Deborah Cooper was the inaugural vice president/general manager, and continues in the role today.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN en Espanol</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol/</guid>
      <description> CNN en Español (stylized as CN͠N) is a Pan-American Spanish-language news channel, owned by WarnerMedia. It was launched on pay television, on 17 March 1997.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNNplus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</guid>
      <description> CNN+ (CNN Plus) was a Spanish 24-hour television news channel. Launched in 1999 as a joint venture by Sogecable and Turner Broadcasting, a unit of Time Warner that owns CNN, it went off the air at the end of 28 December 2010. The management announced that CNN+ would be closed on 31 December 2010.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conrad Hotels</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels/</guid>
      <description>Conrad Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is an international brand of luxury hotels and resorts owned and operated by Hilton Worldwide. Conrad was considered the luxury flagship brand in the Hilton Family of Brands, named after company founder Conrad Hilton, until being supplanted by The Waldorf-Astoria Collection in 2006. As of December 31, 2018, it as 33 locations with 10,625 rooms, including two that are owned or leased with 778 rooms, 29 that are managed with 8,874 rooms, and two that are franchised with 973 rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Hero</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</guid>
      <description>Course Hero is an education technology website company based in Redwood City, California, which operates an online learning platform for students to access course-specific study resources contributed by a community of students and educators. The crowdsourced learning platform contains practice problems, study guides, infographics, class notes, step-by-step explanations, essays, lab reports, videos, user-submitted questions paired with answers from tutors, and original materials created and uploaded by educators. Users either buy a subscription or upload original documents to receive unlocks that are used to view and download full Course Hero documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSU</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/csu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/csu/</guid>
      <description> Colorado State University (also referred to as Colorado State, State, and CSU) is a public research university in Fort Collins, Colorado. The university is the state&amp;rsquo;s land grant university and the flagship university of the Colorado State University System.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/docker/</guid>
      <description> Docker is a set of platform-as-a-service (PaaS) products that use OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers. Containers are isolated from one another and bundle their own software, libraries and configuration files; they can communicate with each other through well-defined channels. All containers are run by a single operating-system kernel and are thus more lightweight than virtual machines.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/echo-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/echo-tv/</guid>
      <description> Echo TV was a christian-conservative Hungarian television channel owned and operated by Echo Hungária TV Zrt , and founded in 2005 to cover business news. Later focusing on news broadcasting and public affairs, it was known as a supporter of Fidesz and KDNP.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eni</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</guid>
      <description>Eni S.p.A. is an Italian multinational oil and gas company headquartered in Rome. Considered one of the global supermajors, it has operations in 79 countries, and is currently world&amp;rsquo;s 11th largest industrial company with a market capitalization of 68 billion euros (US$ 90 billion), as of August 14, 2013 The Italian government owns a 30.303% golden share in the company, 3.934% held through the state Treasury and 26.369% held through the Cassa Depositi e Prestiti.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/forbes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/forbes/</guid>
      <description>Forbes is an American business magazine. Published bi-weekly, it features original articles on finance, industry, investing, and marketing topics. Forbes also reports on related subjects such as technology, communications, science, politics, and law. Its headquarters is located in Jersey City, New Jersey. Primary competitors in the national business magazine category include Fortune and Bloomberg Businessweek. The magazine is well known for its lists and rankings, including of the richest Americans (the Forbes 400), of the world&amp;rsquo;s top companies (the Forbes Global 2000), and The World&amp;rsquo;s Billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-news/</guid>
      <description>Fox News (officially Fox News Channel and abbreviated FNC) is an American pay television news channel. It is owned by the Fox News Group, which itself was owned by News Corporation from 1996–2013, 21st Century Fox from 2013–2019, and Fox Corporation since 2019. The channel broadcasts primarily from studios at 1211 Avenue of the Americas in New York City. Fox News is provided in 86 countries or overseas territories worldwide, with international broadcasts featuring Fox Extra segments during ad breaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports is the brand name for a number of sports channels, broadcast divisions, programming, and other media around the world that are either controlled or partially owned by the family of Rupert Murdoch. These assets are held mainly by Fox Corporation, with the exceptions of the operations in Australia, which are part of News Corp Australia and rest of the international Fox Sports channels and Fox Sports Networks which are owned by The Walt Disney Company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</guid>
      <description> Fox Television Stations, LLC (FTS; alternately Fox Television Stations Group, LLC), is a group of television stations located within the United States which are owned-and-operated by the Fox Broadcasting Company, a subsidiary of the Fox Corporation.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France 24</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</guid>
      <description> France 24 (pronounced &amp;ldquo;France vingt-quatre&amp;rdquo;) is a state-owned international news and current affairs television network based in Paris. Its channels broadcast in French, English, Arabic, and Spanish and are aimed at the overseas market, similar to DD News, BBC World News, DW and RT.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports 1 (FS1) is an American pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation.[1] FS1 replaced the motorsports network Speed on August 17, 2013, at the same time that its companion channel Fox Sports 2 replaced Fuel TV.[2] Both FS1 and FS2 absorbed most of the sports programming from its predecessors, as well as content from Fox Soccer, which was replaced by the entertainment-based channel FXX on September 2, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS2</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</guid>
      <description> Fox Sports 2 (FS2) is an American sports-oriented pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation. The channel is based at the Fox Sports division&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in the Westwood section of Los Angeles, California.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gazprom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom/</guid>
      <description>Public Joint Stock Company Gazprom is a large Russian company founded in 1989, which carries on the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of natural gas. The company is majority owned by the Government of Russia, via the Federal Agency for State Property Management and Rosneftegaz. The remaining shares are listed on public stock markets of Moscow, London and Frankfurt. The Gazprom name is a portmanteau of the Russian words Gazovaya Promyshlennost (Russian: га́зовая промы́шленность - gas industry).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoPro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gopro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gopro/</guid>
      <description> GoPro, Inc. (marketed as GoPro and sometimes stylised as GoPRO) is an American technology company founded in 2002 by Nick Woodman. It manufactures action cameras and develops its own mobile apps and video-editing software. Founded as Woodman Labs, Inc, the company eventually focused on the connected sports genre, developing its line of action cameras and, later, video editing software.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</guid>
      <description> GlaxoSmithKline plc (GSK) is a British multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Brentford, London. Established in 2000 by a merger of Glaxo Wellcome and SmithKline Beecham, GSK was the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth largest pharmaceutical company as of 2015, after Pfizer, Novartis, Merck, Hoffmann-La Roche and Sanofi.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guinness</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/guinness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/guinness/</guid>
      <description>Guinness is a dark Irish dry stout that originated in the brewery of Arthur Guinness at St. James&amp;rsquo;s Gate, Dublin, Ireland, in 1759. It is one of the most successful beer brands worldwide, brewed in almost 50 countries, and available in over 120. Sales in 2011 amounted to 850 million litres (220,000,000 US gal). It is popular with the Irish, both in Ireland and abroad. In spite of declining consumption since 2001, it is still the best-selling alcoholic drink in Ireland where Guinness &amp;amp; Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Inn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</guid>
      <description> Holiday Inn is a British-owned American brand of hotels, and a subsidiary of InterContinental Hotels Group. Founded as a U.S. motel chain, it has grown to be one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest hotel chains, with 1,173 active hotels and over 214,000 bedrooms as of September 30, 2018. The hotel chain&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Denham, Buckinghamshire.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i24 News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/i24-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/i24-news/</guid>
      <description> i24NEWS is an Israeli international 24-hour news and current affairs television channel located in Jaffa Port, Tel Aviv, Israel. It broadcasts in French, English and Arabic. The channel&amp;rsquo;s owner is Patrick Drahi, and the CEO is Frank Melloul.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetpack/</guid>
      <description> Jetpack is the ultimate toolkit for WordPress. It gives you everything you need to design, secure, and grow your site in one bundle.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuwait Petroleum</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kuwait-petroleum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kuwait-petroleum/</guid>
      <description>Kuwait Petroleum Corporation (Arabic: مؤسسة البترول الكويتية‎) is Kuwait&amp;rsquo;s national oil company, headquartered in Kuwait City. The activities of Kuwait Petroleum Corporation (KPC) are focused on petroleum exploration, production, petrochemicals, refining, marketing, and transportation. KPC produces about 7% of the world&amp;rsquo;s total crude oil. KPC plans are to achieve crude oil production capacities in Kuwait of 3.0 million barrels per day by 2010, 3.5 million barrels per day by 2015 and 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leonard Bernstein</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein/</guid>
      <description> The 100th birthday of composer, conductor, and music educator Leonard Bernstein will be celebrated from August 2017 to August 2019. The symbol joins the Bernstein name with the concept of music for new generations of audiences who may not be as familiar with this luminary’s impact and legacy. Major events, concerts, and festivities are planned around the world—1,000 events taking place on six continents.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lukoil</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</guid>
      <description>The PJSC Lukoil Oil Company is a Russian multinational energy corporation headquartered in Moscow, specializing in the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of petroleum, natural gas, and petroleum products. It was formed in 1991 when three state-run, western Siberian companies named after the respective town in Khanty–Mansi Autonomous Okrug that each was based in, Langepasneftegaz, Urayneftegaz, and Kogalymneftegaz, merged. Its name is the combination of the acronym LUK (initials of the oil-producing cities of Langepas, Uray, Kogalym) and the English word &amp;ldquo;oil&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBTA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mbta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mbta/</guid>
      <description>The Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority is the public agency responsible for operating most public transportation services in Greater Boston, Massachusetts. Earlier modes of public transportation in Boston were independently owned and operated; many were first folded into a single agency with the formation of the Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA) in 1947. The MTA was replaced in 1964 with the present-day MBTA, which was established as an individual department within the Commonwealth of Massachusetts before becoming a division of the Massachusetts Department of Transportation (MassDOT) in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merck</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/merck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/merck/</guid>
      <description> Merck KGaA (also called as the Merck Group), branded and commonly known as Merck, is a German multinational pharmaceutical, chemical and life sciences company headquartered in Darmstadt, with around 50,000 employees in around 70 countries. Merck was founded in 1668 and is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest operating chemical and pharmaceutical company, as well as one of the largest pharmaceutical companies in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mixer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mixer/</guid>
      <description> Mixer is a Seattle-based video game live streaming platform owned by Microsoft. The service officially launched on January 5, 2016, as Beam but was renamed Mixer in May 2017.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MOCA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/moca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/moca/</guid>
      <description>The Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles (MOCA) is a contemporary art museum with three locations in greater Los Angeles, California. The main branch is located on Grand Avenue in Downtown Los Angeles, near the Walt Disney Concert Hall. MOCA&amp;rsquo;s original space, initially intended as a &amp;ldquo;temporary&amp;rdquo; exhibit space while the main facility was built, is now known as the Geffen Contemporary, in the Little Tokyo district of downtown Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoMA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/moma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/moma/</guid>
      <description> The Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) is an art museum located in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, on 53rd Street between Fifth and Sixth Avenues. The museum will be temporarily closed to expand its galleries from June 16 through October 21, 2019. MoMA PS1 will remain open on its regular schedule.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MyNetworkTV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv/</guid>
      <description>MyNetworkTV (unofficially abbreviated as MyTV, MyNet, MNT or MNTV), is an American television network/syndication service that is owned by Fox Corporation, operated by its Fox Television Stations division, and distributed through the syndication structure of 20th Television. MyNetworkTV began operations on September 5, 2006 with an initial affiliate lineup covering about 96% of the country, most of which consisted of stations that were former affiliates of The WB and UPN that did not join the successor of those two networks, The CW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk/</guid>
      <description> NHK World-Japan is the international broadcasting service of NHK (Nippon Hōsō Kyōkai - Japan Broadcasting Corporation), Japan&amp;rsquo;s public broadcaster. The service is aimed at the overseas market, similar to BBC World News, DW, France 24, CGTN, and RT, and broadcast through satellite and cable operators throughout the world as well as online and through its mobile apps. The channel is based in Tokyo, Japan.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nissay</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissay/</guid>
      <description> Nippon Life Insurance Company is the largest Japanese life insurance company by revenue. The company was founded in 1889 as the Nippon Life Assurance Co., Inc. In structure it is a mutual company. It first paid policyholder dividends in 1898.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northface</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/northface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/northface/</guid>
      <description> The North Face is an American outdoor recreation product company. The North Face produces clothing, footwear, and outdoor equipment.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Post</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</guid>
      <description> The New York Post (sometimes abbreviated as NY Post) is a daily newspaper in New York City. The Post also operates the celebrity gossip site PageSix.com, the entertainment site Decider.com, and co-produces the television show Page Six TV.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oceano Azul Foundation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oceano-azul-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oceano-azul-foundation/</guid>
      <description>The Oceano Azul Foundation is an international organization founded by the Sociedade Francisco Manuel dos Santos and based in Portugal with the mission of contributing to the sustainability of a healthy and productive ocean. Combining scientific study, political and economic activism, together with a deep ethical commitment, the Foundation integrates many human perspectives to “look at the planet’s sustainability from the ocean’s point of view.” The Oceano Azul Foundation manages the Oceanário de Lisboa, for which Chermayeff &amp;amp; Geismar &amp;amp; Haviv designed the visual identity, as well as major tile murals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/one-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/one-news/</guid>
      <description> One News is a Philippine pay television news channel that was launched on May 2018 exclusively on satellite provider Cignal. One News is the first Cignal channel launched under the One branding, along with the sports channel One Sports and Filipino-language news channel One PH.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONGC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ongc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ongc/</guid>
      <description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) is an Indian multinational oil and gas company. Its registered office is now at New Delhi, India. It is a Public Sector Undertaking (PSU) of the Government of India, under the administrative control of the Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas. It is India&amp;rsquo;s largest oil and gas exploration and production company. It produces around 70% of India&amp;rsquo;s crude oil (equivalent to around 30% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total demand) and around 62% of its natural gas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panera Bread</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/panera-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/panera-bread/</guid>
      <description> Panera Bread Company is an American chain store of bakery-café fast casual restaurants with over 2,000 locations, all of which are in the United States and Canada. Its headquarters are in Sunset Hills, Missouri, a suburb of St. Louis. The company operates as Saint Louis Bread Company in Greater St. Louis, where it has over 100 locations Offerings include soups, salads, pasta, sandwiches, specialty drinks, and bakery items.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pbs/</guid>
      <description>The Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) is an American public broadcaster and television program distributor. It is a nonprofit organization and the most prominent provider of educational television programming to public television stations in the United States, distributing series such as American Experience, America&amp;rsquo;s Test Kitchen, Antiques Roadshow, Arthur, Barney &amp;amp; Friends, Clifford the Big Red Dog, Downton Abbey, Finding Your Roots, Frontline, The Magic School Bus, Masterpiece, Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood, Nature, Nova, the PBS NewsHour, Sesame Street, Teletubbies, and This Old House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pemex</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pemex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pemex/</guid>
      <description>Petróleos Mexicanos, which translates to Mexican Petroleum, but is trademarked and better known as Pemex, is the Mexican state-owned petroleum company, created in 1938 by nationalization or expropriation of all private, foreign, and domestic oil companies at that time. Pemex had total assets worth $415.75 billion, and was the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest non-publicly listed company by total market value (in December 2005), and Latin America&amp;rsquo;s second-largest enterprise by annual revenue as of 2009, surpassed only by Petrobras (the Brazilian National Oil Company).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pfizer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pfizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pfizer/</guid>
      <description>Pfizer Inc. is an American multinational pharmaceutical corporation headquartered in New York City, with its research headquarters in Groton, Connecticut. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest pharmaceutical companies. It is listed on the New York Stock Exchange, and its shares have been a component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average since 2004. Pfizer ranked No. 57 on the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phillips 66</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/phillips-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/phillips-66/</guid>
      <description>The Phillips 66 Company is an American multinational energy company headquartered in Westchase, Houston, Texas. It debuted as an independent energy company when ConocoPhillips executed a spin-off of its downstream and midstream assets. Taking its name from the 1927 &amp;ldquo;Phillips 66&amp;rdquo; trademark of ConocoPhillips predecessor Phillips Petroleum Company, Phillips 66 began trading on the New York Stock Exchange on May 1, 2012, under the ticker PSX. The company is engaged in producing natural gas liquids (NGL) and petrochemicals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RatPac</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac/</guid>
      <description> RatPac Entertainment is an American motion picture production and financing company owned by producer-director Brett Ratner. RatPac was founded by Ratner and billionaire James Packer. RatPac is a partner in RatPac-Dune Entertainment with Dune Entertainment.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ril/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ril/</guid>
      <description>Reliance Industries Limited (RIL) is an Indian multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. Reliance owns businesses across India engaged in energy, petrochemicals, textiles, natural resources, retail, and telecommunications. Reliance is one of the most profitable companies in India, the largest publicly traded company in India by market capitalization, and the largest company in India as measured by revenue after recently surpassing the government-controlled Indian Oil Corporation. On 18 October 2007, Reliance Industries became the first Indian company to breach $100 billion market capitalization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RMA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma/</guid>
      <description> Reproductive Medicine Associates of New York is dedicated to providing patients the highest quality care in a compassionate and supportive manner. Helping couples successfully achieve their family-building goals has been RMA of New York’s focus since 2001.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia 24</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/russia-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/russia-24/</guid>
      <description> Russia-24 is a state-owned Russian-language news channel from Russia. It covers major national and international events as well as focuses on domestic issues. It is owned by VGTRK
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinsegae</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</guid>
      <description> Shinsegae (Korean: 신세계, KRX: 004170) is a South Korean department store franchise, along with several other businesses, headquartered in Seoul, South Korea. The name Shinsegae literally means &amp;ldquo;New World&amp;rdquo; in Korean. Its flagship store in Centum City, Busan, was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest department store at 3,163,000 square feet (293,900 m2), surpassing Macy&amp;rsquo;s flagship Herald Square in New York City in 2009.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siberia Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</guid>
      <description> S7 Airlines, legally JSC Siberia Airlines (Russian: АО «Авиакомпания &amp;ldquo;Сибирь&amp;rdquo;», &amp;ldquo;АО Aviakompania Sibir&amp;rdquo;), is an airline headquartered in Ob, Novosibirsk Oblast, Russia, with offices in Moscow. As of 2008, it is Russia&amp;rsquo;s biggest domestic airline, with its main bases at Domodedovo International Airport and Tolmachevo Airport
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telegram</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</guid>
      <description> Telegram is a cloud-based instant messaging and voice over IP service. Telegram client apps are available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any type.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-aquarium/</guid>
      <description> The Tennessee Aquarium is a non-profit public aquarium located in Chattanooga, Tennessee, United States. It opened in 1992 on the banks of the Tennessee River in downtown Chattanooga, with a major expansion added in 2005. The Aquarium, which has been accredited by the Association of Zoos and Aquariums (AZA) since 1993, is home to more than 12,000 animals representing almost 800 species.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiktok</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tiktok/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tiktok/</guid>
      <description>TikTok is an iOS and Android social media video app for creating and sharing short lip-sync, comedy, and talent videos. The app was launched in 2017 by ByteDance, for markets outside of China. ByteDance has previously launched Douyin (Chinese: 抖音) for the China market in September 2016. TikTok and Douyin are the same, but run on different servers to comply with Chinese censorship restrictions. The application allows users to create short music and lip-sync videos of 3 to 15 seconds and short looping videos of 3 to 60 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tufts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts/</guid>
      <description>Tufts University is a private research university in Medford and Somerville, Massachusetts. A charter member of the New England Small College Athletic Conference (NESCAC), Tufts College was founded in 1852 by Christian universalists who worked for years to open a nonsectarian institution of higher learning. It was a small New England liberal arts college until its transformation into a larger research university in the 1970s. The university emphasizes active citizenship and public service in all its disciplines, and is known for its internationalism and study abroad programs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitch</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/twitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/twitch/</guid>
      <description>Twitch (stylized as twitch) is a live streaming video platform owned by Twitch Interactive, a subsidiary of Amazon. Introduced in June 2011 as a spin-off of the general-interest streaming platform, Justin.tv, the site primarily focuses on video game live streaming, including broadcasts of eSports competitions, in addition to music broadcasts, creative content, and more recently, &amp;ldquo;in real life&amp;rdquo; streams. Content on the site can be viewed either live or via video on demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNDP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</guid>
      <description> The United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) is the United Nations&amp;rsquo; global development network. It advocates for change and connects countries to knowledge, experience and resources to help people build a better life for themselves. It provides expert advice, training and grants support to developing countries, with increasing emphasis on assistance to the least developed countries. It promotes technical and investment cooperation among nations.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNH</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</guid>
      <description> The University of New Hampshire (UNH) is a public research university with its main campus in Durham, New Hampshire. It was founded and incorporated in 1866 as a land grant college in Hanover in connection with Dartmouth College. In 1893, UNH moved to Durham.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universidad Tecmilenio</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</guid>
      <description>The Universidad TecMilenio (UTM) (TecMilenio University) is a private institution of higher education. The institution is part of Monterrey Institute of Technology and Higher Education TecMilenio University ITESM System, an educational system with national and international levels, through 30 campus and an online campus with a unique and innovative educational model that forms professionals with the skills needed by modern businesses and organizations. For-profit schools that have entered the country in recent years, the university serves some 21,000 students on its own at high school, undergraduate and postgraduate level, frequently through distance learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</guid>
      <description> VK (short for its original name VKontakte; Russian: ВКонта́кте, meaning InContact) is a Russian online social media and social networking service based in Saint Petersburg. VK is available in numerous languages but it is especially used by Russian-speakers. VK allows users to message each other publicly or privately; create groups, public pages, and events; share and tag images, audio, and video; and play browser-based games.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather Channel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/weather-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/weather-channel/</guid>
      <description>The Weather Channel (TWC) is an American pay television channel owned by The Weather Group, LLC, a subsidiary of Entertainment Studios. The channel&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are located in Atlanta, Georgia. Launched on May 2, 1982, the channel broadcasts weather forecasts and weather-related news and analysis, along with documentaries and entertainment programming related to weather. A sister network, Weatherscan, is a digital cable and satellite service that offers 24-hour automated local forecasts and radar imagery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp Messenger is a freeware, cross-platform messaging and Voice over IP (VoIP) service owned by Facebook. It allows users to send text messages and voice messages, make voice and video calls, and share images, documents, user locations, and other media. WhatsApp&amp;rsquo;s client application runs on mobile devices, but is also accessible from Windows and Mac desktop computers, as long as the user&amp;rsquo;s mobile device remains connected to the Internet while they use the desktop app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wta/</guid>
      <description> The Women&amp;rsquo;s Tennis Association (WTA) is the principal organizing body of women&amp;rsquo;s professional tennis. It governs the WTA Tour which is the worldwide professional tennis tour for women and was founded to create a better future for women&amp;rsquo;s tennis. The WTA&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters is in St. Petersburg, Florida, with its European headquarters in London and its Asia-Pacific headquarters in Beijing.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XBOX</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/xbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/xbox/</guid>
      <description>Xbox is a video gaming brand created and owned by Microsoft. It represents a series of video game consoles developed by Microsoft, with three consoles released in the sixth, seventh, and eighth generations, respectively. The brand also represents applications (games), streaming services, an online service by the name of Xbox Live, and the development arm by the name of Xbox Game Studios. The brand was first introduced in the United States in November 2001, with the launch of the original Xbox console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y Combinator</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/y-combinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/y-combinator/</guid>
      <description> Y Combinator is an American seed accelerator which was launched in March 2005. Y Combinator is consistently ranked at the top of U.S. accelerators.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>76ers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/76ers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/76ers/</guid>
      <description>The Philadelphia 76ers (also commonly known as the Sixers) are an American professional basketball team based in the Philadelphia metropolitan area. The 76ers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Atlantic Division and play at Wells Fargo Center. Founded in 1946 and originally known as the Syracuse Nationals, they are one of the oldest franchises in the NBA, and one of only eight (out of 23) to survive the league&amp;rsquo;s first decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Hawks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-hawks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-hawks/</guid>
      <description> The Atlanta Hawks are an American professional basketball team based in Atlanta, Georgia. The Hawks compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Southeast Division. The team plays its home games at State Farm Arena.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Austin FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/austin-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/austin-fc/</guid>
      <description> Austin FC is a professional soccer franchise based in Austin, Texas. Austin FC will compete in Major League Soccer in 2021, and will open a new stadium on McKalla Place in north central Austin the same year.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AW Restaurants</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants/</guid>
      <description>A&amp;amp;W Restaurants, Inc. is a chain of fast-food restaurants distinguished by its draft root beer, root beer floats and burgers. Its origins date back to 1919 when Roy W. Allen opened a walk-up root beer stand in Lodi, California. Allen&amp;rsquo;s employee Frank Wright partnered with him and they founded their first restaurant in Sacramento, California, in 1923. The company name was taken respectively from the initials of their last names—Allen and Wright.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AW Root Beer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</guid>
      <description> A&amp;amp;W Root Beer is a root beer brand primarily available in the United States and Canada, started in 1919 by Roy W. Allen. In 1922, Allen partnered with Frank Wright. They combined their initials to create the brand &amp;ldquo;A&amp;amp;W&amp;rdquo; and inspired a restaurant chain, founded in 1922. Originally, A&amp;amp;W root beer drinks sold for five cents.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Celtics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-celtics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-celtics/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Celtics are an American professional basketball team based in Boston, Massachusetts. The Celtics compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Atlantic Division. Founded in 1946 as one of the league&amp;rsquo;s original eight teams, the team play their home games at TD Garden, which they share with the National Hockey League (NHL)&amp;rsquo;s Boston Bruins. The Celtics are one of the most successful teams in NBA history; the franchise has won the most championships in the NBA with 17, accounting for 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Nets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brooklyn-nets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brooklyn-nets/</guid>
      <description>The Brooklyn Nets are an American professional basketball team based in the New York City borough of Brooklyn. The Nets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference. The team plays its home games at Barclays Center. They are one of two NBA teams located in New York City; the other is the New York Knicks. The team was established in 1967 as a charter franchise of the NBA&amp;rsquo;s rival league, the American Basketball Association (ABA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sabres</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-sabres/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-sabres/</guid>
      <description>The Buffalo Sabres are a professional ice hockey team based in Buffalo, New York. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was established in 1970, along with the Vancouver Canucks, when the league expanded to 14 teams. They have played at KeyBank Center since 1996. Prior to that, the Buffalo Sabres played at the Buffalo Memorial Auditorium from the start of the franchise in 1970.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carolina Hurricanes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-hurricanes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-hurricanes/</guid>
      <description> The Carolina Hurricanes are a professional ice hockey team based in Raleigh, North Carolina. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Hurricanes play their home games at the 18,680-seat PNC Arena.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Blackhawks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-blackhawks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-blackhawks/</guid>
      <description>The Chicago Blackhawks (spelled Black Hawks until 1986, and known colloquially as the Hawks) are a professional ice hockey team based in Chicago, Illinois. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). They have won six Stanley Cup championships since their founding in 1926. The Blackhawks are one of the &amp;ldquo;Original Six&amp;rdquo; NHL teams along with the Detroit Red Wings, Montreal Canadiens, Toronto Maple Leafs, Boston Bruins and New York Rangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Bulls</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bulls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bulls/</guid>
      <description> The Chicago Bulls are an American professional basketball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The Bulls compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division. The team was founded on January 16, 1966. The team plays its home games at the United Center, an arena shared with the Chicago Blackhawks of the National Hockey League (NHL).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Rapids</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rapids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rapids/</guid>
      <description> The Colorado Rapids are an American professional soccer club based in the Denver suburb of Commerce City, Colorado. The Rapids compete in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the Western Conference. The franchise began play in 1996 as one of the charter clubs in MLS.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Columbus Crew SC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-crew-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-crew-sc/</guid>
      <description>Columbus Crew Soccer Club is an American professional soccer club based in Columbus, Ohio. The Crew competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference and began play in 1996 as one of the ten charter clubs of the league. The team is currently being operated by an ownership group led by the Haslam family and former team doctor Pete Edwards. The Haslam/Edwards group is the third owner in club history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAngelo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dangelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dangelo/</guid>
      <description> D&amp;rsquo;Angelo Grilled Sandwiches is a chain of sandwich shops located throughout New England. It serves various kinds of hot and cold subs, wraps, and salads.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC United</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-united/</guid>
      <description>D.C. United is an American professional soccer club based in Washington, D.C. The club competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS), the top level of professional American soccer. The franchise began play in 1996 as one of the ten charter clubs of the league. The club was one of the most successful clubs in the early years of MLS, winning eight of its thirteen titles between 1996 and 1998 under then head coach Bruce Arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Pistons</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-pistons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-pistons/</guid>
      <description>The Detroit Pistons are an American professional basketball team based in Detroit, Michigan. The Pistons compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division and plays its home games at Little Caesars Arena. The team was founded in Fort Wayne, Indiana as the Fort Wayne (Zollner) Pistons in 1941, a member of the National Basketball League (NBL) where it won two NBL championships: in 1944 and 1945.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Red Wings</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-red-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-red-wings/</guid>
      <description>The Detroit Red Wings are a professional ice hockey team based in Detroit. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL) and are one of the Original Six teams of the league. Founded in 1926, the team was known as the Detroit Cougars until 1930. For the 1930–31 and 1931–32 seasons the team was called the Detroit Falcons, and in 1932 changed their name to the Red Wings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edmonton Oilers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/edmonton-oilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/edmonton-oilers/</guid>
      <description> The Edmonton Oilers are a professional ice hockey team based in Edmonton, Alberta. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FC Cincinnati</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-cincinnati/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-cincinnati/</guid>
      <description>FC Cincinnati is an American professional soccer club based in Cincinnati, Ohio that plays in the Eastern Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The team succeeded the lower-division team of the same name and was announced on May 29, 2018, when MLS awarded an expansion franchise to Cincinnati. The team began MLS play on March 2, 2019 with its first match against Seattle Sounders FC. The club&amp;rsquo;s ownership group is led by Carl H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FC Dallas</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-dallas/</guid>
      <description> FC Dallas is an American professional soccer club based in the Dallas suburb of Frisco, Texas. The club competes as a member of Major League Soccer (MLS). The franchise began play in 1996 as a charter club of the league. The club was founded in 1995 as the Dallas Burn before adopting its current name in 2004.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Dynamo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo/</guid>
      <description>Houston Dynamo are an American professional soccer club based in Houston, Texas. The franchise competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), as a member of the Western Conference. The Dynamo had first played their home games at Robertson Stadium on the University of Houston campus until 2011. Since 2012, the Dynamo has played home matches at BBVA Stadium, a soccer-specific stadium located in Houston. The team&amp;rsquo;s head coach is Wilmer Cabrera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Rockets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-rockets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-rockets/</guid>
      <description>The Houston Rockets are an American professional basketball team based in Houston, Texas. The Rockets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The team plays its home games at the Toyota Center, located in downtown Houston. The Rockets have won two NBA championships and four Western Conference titles. The team was established in 1967 as the San Diego Rockets, an expansion team originally based in San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Clippers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers/</guid>
      <description>The Los Angeles Clippers (branded as the LA Clippers) are an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles. The Clippers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of Pacific Division of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference. The Clippers play their home games at the Staples Center, an arena they share with fellow NBA team the Los Angeles Lakers, as well as the Los Angeles Sparks of the Women&amp;rsquo;s National Basketball Association (WNBA) and the Los Angeles Kings of the National Hockey League (NHL).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Galaxy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-galaxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-galaxy/</guid>
      <description> The LA Galaxy, also known as the Los Angeles Galaxy, is an American professional soccer franchise based in the Los Angeles suburb of Carson, California, that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), as a member of the Western Conference. The club began play in 1996 as one of the league&amp;rsquo;s eight charter members.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Kings</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings/</guid>
      <description>The Los Angeles Kings are a professional ice hockey team based in Los Angeles. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was founded on June 5, 1967, after Jack Kent Cooke was awarded an NHL expansion franchise for Los Angeles on February 9, 1966, becoming one of the six teams that began play as part of the 1967 NHL expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montreal Canadiens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/montreal-canadiens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/montreal-canadiens/</guid>
      <description> The Montreal Canadiens[note 3] (French: Les Canadiens de Montréal) are a professional ice hockey team based in Montreal, Quebec. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montreal Impact</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/montreal-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/montreal-impact/</guid>
      <description> The Montreal Impact is a Canadian professional soccer team based in Montreal, Quebec. The Impact competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS). The team began play in 2012 as an expansion team of the league, being the league&amp;rsquo;s third Canadian club, and replaced the North American Soccer League team of the same name.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Predators</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators/</guid>
      <description> The Nashville Predators are a professional ice hockey team based in Nashville, Tennessee. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Predators&amp;rsquo; television broadcasting rights are held by Fox Sports Tennessee, whereas radio broadcasting rights are held by WPRT-FM. The Predators have played their home games at Bridgestone Arena since 1998.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville SC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-sc/</guid>
      <description> Nashville Soccer Club is an American professional soccer team based in Nashville, Tennessee. Founded in 2016, the team made its debut in the United Soccer League in 2018.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NE Revolution</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ne-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ne-revolution/</guid>
      <description> The New England Revolution is an American professional soccer club based in the Greater Boston area that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), in the Eastern Conference of the league. It is one of the ten charter clubs of MLS, having competed in the league since its inaugural season.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey Devils</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-jersey-devils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-jersey-devils/</guid>
      <description>The New Jersey Devils are a professional ice hockey team based in Newark, New Jersey. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The club was founded as the Kansas City Scouts in Kansas City, Missouri, in 1974. The Scouts moved to Denver, Colorado in 1976 and became the Colorado Rockies. In 1982, they moved to East Rutherford, New Jersey and took their current name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Islanders</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-islanders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-islanders/</guid>
      <description>The New York Islanders are a professional ice hockey team based in the New York metropolitan area. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team splits its home games between Barclays Center in the borough of Brooklyn and Nassau Coliseum in Uniondale, New York. The Islanders are one of three NHL franchises in the New York metropolitan area, along with the New Jersey Devils and New York Rangers, and their fan base resides primarily on Long Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Rangers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-rangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-rangers/</guid>
      <description>The New York Rangers are a professional ice hockey team based in New York City. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team plays its home games at Madison Square Garden in the borough of Manhattan, an arena they share with the New York Knicks of the National Basketball Association (NBA). They are one of three NHL teams located in the New York metropolitan area; the others being the New Jersey Devils and New York Islanders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Red Bulls</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-red-bulls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-red-bulls/</guid>
      <description>The New York Red Bulls are an American professional soccer club based in Harrison, New Jersey. The Red Bulls compete as a member of the Eastern Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The club was established in October 1994 and began play in the league&amp;rsquo;s inaugural season in 1996 as the New York/New Jersey MetroStars. In 2006, the team was sold to Red Bull GmbH and re-branded as part of the company&amp;rsquo;s global network of football clubs, leading to the team&amp;rsquo;s current name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-fc/</guid>
      <description> New York City Football Club is an American professional soccer club based in New York City that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), the highest level of American soccer, as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONE FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/one-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/one-fc/</guid>
      <description>ONE Championship (formerly known as ONE Fighting Championship or ONE FC) is a Singapore-based mixed martial arts (MMA), Muay Thai, kickboxing, boxing, and grappling promotion which was launched on 14 July 2011 by entrepreneur Chatri Sityodtong and former ESPN Star Sports senior executive Victor Cui. ONE Championship broadcasts to over 1.7 billion potential viewers in 136 countries. ONE Championship is backed by Sequoia Capital, GIC, Temasek Holdings, Iconiq Capital, Mission Holdings, and Greenoaks Capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oral-B</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oral-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oral-b/</guid>
      <description> Oral-B is a brand of oral hygiene products, including toothpastes, toothbrushes, electric toothbrushes, and mouthwashes. The brand has been in business since the invention of the Hutson toothbrush in 1950. It has been owned by American multinational Procter &amp;amp; Gamble (P&amp;amp;G) since 2006.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orlando City SC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/orlando-city-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/orlando-city-sc/</guid>
      <description> Orlando City Soccer Club is an American professional soccer club in Orlando, Florida, that competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS). Orlando City SC began play in 2015 as an expansion team and is the first MLS franchise in the state since Miami Fusion and Tampa Bay Mutiny folded following the 2001 season. The team plays at Exploria Stadium in Downtown Orlando.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ottawa Senators</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ottawa-senators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ottawa-senators/</guid>
      <description> The Ottawa Senators (French: Sénateurs d&amp;rsquo;Ottawa) are a professional ice hockey team based in Ottawa, Ontario. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Senators play their home games at the 18,652-seat Canadian Tire Centre, which opened in 1996 as the Palladium.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pelicans</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pelicans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pelicans/</guid>
      <description> The New Orleans Pelicans are an American professional basketball team based in New Orleans, Louisiana. The Pelicans compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The team plays their home games in the Smoothie King Center.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Flyers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-flyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-flyers/</guid>
      <description> The Philadelphia Flyers are a professional ice hockey team based in Philadelphia. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). Part of the 1967 NHL Expansion, the Flyers were the first expansion team in the post–Original Six era to win the Stanley Cup, victorious in 1973–74 and again in 1974–75.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Penguins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-penguins/</guid>
      <description>The Pittsburgh Penguins (colloquially known as the Pens) are a professional ice hockey team based in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Penguins are one of two NHL franchises in Pennsylvania, the other being the Philadelphia Flyers. The cities&amp;rsquo; proximity has led to a rivalry known as the &amp;ldquo;Battle of Pennsylvania&amp;rdquo;. The club is owned by Mario Lemieux and Ronald Burkle, who purchased the Penguins in 1999 and brought the club out of bankruptcy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland Timbers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/portland-timbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/portland-timbers/</guid>
      <description> The Portland Timbers are an American professional soccer club based in Portland, Oregon. The Timbers compete in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference. The Timbers have played their home games at Providence Park since 2011, when the team began play as an expansion team in the league.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland Trail Blazers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/portland-trail-blazers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/portland-trail-blazers/</guid>
      <description>The Portland Trail Blazers, commonly known as the Blazers, are an American professional basketball team based in Portland, Oregon. The Trail Blazers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Northwest Division. The team played its home games in the Memorial Coliseum before moving to Moda Center in 1995 (called the Rose Garden until 2013). The franchise entered the league as an expansion team in 1970, and has enjoyed a strong following: from 1977 through 1995, the team sold out 814 consecutive home games, the longest such streak in American major professional sports at the time, and only since surpassed by the Boston Red Sox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rsl/</guid>
      <description> Real Salt Lake is an American professional soccer franchise that competes as a member club of Major League Soccer (MLS) Western Conference. RSL began play in 2005 as an expansion team of the league. The club was founded in 2004 when the club&amp;rsquo;s first owner and founder was awarded an expansion berth in Major League Soccer.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Sounders FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-sounders-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-sounders-fc/</guid>
      <description>Seattle Sounders FC is an American professional soccer club based in Seattle, Washington. The Sounders compete as a member of the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The club was established on November 13, 2007, and began play in 2009 as an MLS expansion team. The Sounders are a phoenix club, carrying the same name as the original franchise that competed in the North American Soccer League from 1974 to 1983.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SJ Earthquakes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes/</guid>
      <description>The San Jose Earthquakes are an American professional soccer team based in San Jose, California, United States, that competes as a member of the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The franchise began play in 1996 (originally as the San Jose Clash) as one of the charter clubs of the league. The Earthquakes took part in the first game in MLS history, defeating D.C. United 1–0. The Earthquakes have won two MLS Cup titles, in 2001 and 2003, and two Supporters&amp;rsquo; Shields in 2005 and 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sporting KC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc/</guid>
      <description> Sporting Kansas City is an American professional soccer club in Kansas City, Kansas, with its main office and historic location in Kansas City, Missouri. The club competes as a member of the Western Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS), having returned in 2015 after spending ten seasons in the Eastern Conference.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis Blues</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-blues/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Blues are a professional ice hockey team based in St. Louis, Missouri. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The franchise was founded in 1967 as one of the six teams from the 1967 NHL expansion and is named after the W. C. Handy song &amp;ldquo;Saint Louis Blues&amp;rdquo;. The Blues play their home games at the 19,150-seat Enterprise Center in downtown St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Bay Lightning</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-lightning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-lightning/</guid>
      <description>The Tampa Bay Lightning are a professional ice hockey team based in Tampa, Florida. The Lightning compete as a member of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The club has won one Stanley Cup championship in their history, in 2003–04. The team is often referred to as the Bolts, and the nickname was used on the former third jerseys. The Lightning plays home games in Amalie Arena in Tampa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tampax</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampax/</guid>
      <description> Tampax is a brand of tampon currently owned by Procter &amp;amp; Gamble and sold in over 100 countries. Both the brand and the product were invented by Dr. Earle Haas, who filed a patent in 1931. The original product was designed from the start as flushable and biodegradeable.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timberwolves</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/timberwolves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/timberwolves/</guid>
      <description>The Minnesota Timberwolves (also commonly known as the Wolves) are an American professional basketball team based in Minneapolis, Minnesota. The Timberwolves compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Northwest Division. Founded in 1989, the team is owned by Glen Taylor who also owns the WNBA&amp;rsquo;s Minnesota Lynx. The Timberwolves play their home games at Target Center, their home since 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-fc/</guid>
      <description> Toronto Football Club is a Canadian professional soccer team based in Toronto, Ontario. The team competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the Eastern Conference. The team plays its home matches at BMO Field, located at Exhibition Place on Toronto&amp;rsquo;s shoreline. Toronto FC joined MLS in 2007 as an expansion team and was the first Canadian-based franchise in the league.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Maple Leafs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-maple-leafs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-maple-leafs/</guid>
      <description>The Toronto Maple Leaf Hockey Club, commonly referred to as the Toronto Maple Leafs or simply the Leafs, are a professional ice hockey team based in Toronto, Ontario. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The club is owned by Maple Leaf Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment, Ltd. and are represented by Chairman Larry Tanenbaum. The Maple Leafs&amp;rsquo; broadcasting rights are split between BCE Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Raptors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-raptors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-raptors/</guid>
      <description>The Toronto Raptors are a Canadian professional basketball team based in Toronto, Ontario. The Raptors compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Atlantic Division. They play their home games at the Scotiabank Arena, which they share with the Toronto Maple Leafs of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was founded in 1995 as part of the NBA&amp;rsquo;s expansion into Canada, along with the Vancouver Grizzlies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Canucks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-canucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-canucks/</guid>
      <description> The Vancouver Canucks are a professional ice hockey team based in Vancouver, British Columbia. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Canucks play their home games at Rogers Arena, formerly known as General Motors Place, which has an official capacity of 18,910. Travis Green is the head coach and Jim Benning is the general manager.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Whitecaps FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-whitecaps-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-whitecaps-fc/</guid>
      <description>Vancouver Whitecaps FC is a Canadian professional soccer team based in Vancouver, British Columbia that competes in the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The Whitecaps were the 17th team to enter Major League Soccer and replaced the USSF Division 2 team of the same name in the city. The club has been owned and managed by the same group since their USSF days, having graduated to MLS after the conclusion of the USSF&amp;rsquo;s 2010 season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Capitals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-capitals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-capitals/</guid>
      <description>The Washington Capitals (colloquially known as the Caps) are a professional ice hockey team based in Washington, D.C. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Capitals are owned by Monumental Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment, headed by Ted Leonsis. From 1974 to 1997 the Capitals played their home games at the Capital Centre, in Landover, Maryland (a suburb in the Washington metropolitan area).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Wizards</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-wizards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-wizards/</guid>
      <description> The Washington Wizards are an American professional basketball team based in Washington, D.C. The Wizards compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Southeast Division. The team plays its home games at the Capital One Arena, in the Chinatown neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winnipeg Jets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wnnipeg-jets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wnnipeg-jets/</guid>
      <description> The Winnipeg Jets are a professional ice hockey team based in Winnipeg, Manitoba. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team is owned by True North Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment and plays its home games at Bell MTS Place.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yum! Brands</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yum-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yum-brands/</guid>
      <description> Yum! Brands, Inc., or Yum! and formerly Tricon Global Restaurants, Inc., is an American fast food company. A Fortune 500 corporation, Yum! operates the brands Taco Bell, KFC, Pizza Hut, and WingStreet worldwide, except in China, where the brands are operated by a separate company, Yum China. Prior to 2011, Yum! owned Long John Silver&amp;rsquo;s and A&amp;amp;W Restaurants.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Braves</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-braves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-braves/</guid>
      <description>The Atlanta Braves are an American professional baseball franchise based in the Atlanta metropolitan area. The franchise competes in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the National League (NL) East division. The Braves played home games at Atlanta–Fulton County Stadium from 1966 to 1996, and Turner Field from 1997 to 2016. Since 2017, their home stadium has been SunTrust Park, located 10 miles (16 km) northwest of downtown Atlanta in Cumberland, Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Orioles</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-orioles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-orioles/</guid>
      <description>The Baltimore Orioles are an American professional baseball team based in Baltimore, Maryland. As one of the American League&amp;rsquo;s eight charter teams in 1901, this particular franchise spent its first year as a major league club in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, as the Milwaukee Brewers (not related to the second current Brewers franchise there) before moving to St. Louis, Missouri, to become the St. Louis Browns. After 52 often-beleaguered years in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boots UK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boots-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boots-uk/</guid>
      <description> Boots UK Ltd., trading as Boots, is a health and beauty Retail and pharmacy chain in the United Kingdom and other territories including Ireland and Thailand
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Red Sox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-red-sox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-red-sox/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Red Sox are an American professional baseball team based in Boston, Massachusetts. The Red Sox compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) East division. The Red Sox have won nine World Series championships, tied for the third-most of any MLB team, and they have played in 13. Their most recent appearance and win was in 2018. In addition, they won the 1904 American League pennant, but were not able to defend their 1903 World Series championship when the New York Giants refused to participate in the 1904 World Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Bills</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-bills/</guid>
      <description>The Buffalo Bills are a professional American football team based in the Buffalo–Niagara Falls metropolitan area. The Bills compete in the National Football League (NFL), as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team plays their home games at New Era Field in Orchard Park, New York. The Bills are the only NFL team that plays its home games in the state of New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Cubs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-cubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-cubs/</guid>
      <description>The Chicago Cubs are an American professional baseball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The Cubs compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. The team plays its home games at Wrigley Field, located on the city&amp;rsquo;s North Side. The Cubs are one of two major league teams in Chicago; the other, the Chicago White Sox, is a member of the American League (AL) Central division.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago White Sox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox/</guid>
      <description>The Chicago White Sox are an American professional baseball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The White Sox compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) Central division. The White Sox are owned by Jerry Reinsdorf, and play their home games at Guaranteed Rate Field, located on the city&amp;rsquo;s South Side. They are one of two major league clubs in Chicago; the other is the Chicago Cubs, who are a member of the National League (NL) Central division.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Reds</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-reds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-reds/</guid>
      <description> The Cincinnati Reds are an American professional baseball team based in Cincinnati, Ohio. The Reds compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. They were a charter member of the American Association in 1882 and joined the NL in 1890.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland Browns</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns/</guid>
      <description>The Cleveland Browns are a professional American football team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Browns compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) North division. The Browns play their home games at FirstEnergy Stadium, which opened in 1999, with administrative offices and training facilities in Berea, Ohio. The Browns&amp;rsquo; official colors are brown, orange, and white. They are unique among the 32 member franchises of the NFL in that they do not have a logo on their helmets</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland Indians</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians/</guid>
      <description>The Cleveland Indians are an American professional baseball team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Indians compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) Central division. Since 1994, they have played at Progressive Field. The team&amp;rsquo;s spring training facility is at Goodyear Ballpark in Goodyear, Arizona. Since their establishment as a major league franchise in 1901, the Indians have won two World Series championships: in 1920 and 1948, along with 10 Central Division titles and six American League pennants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Cowboys</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>The Dallas Cowboys are a professional American football team based in the Dallas–Fort Worth metroplex. The Cowboys compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) East division. The team is headquartered in Frisco, Texas, and plays its home games at AT&amp;amp;T Stadium in Arlington, Texas, which opened for the 2009 season. The stadium took its current name prior to the 2013 season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denver Broncos</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-broncos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-broncos/</guid>
      <description>The Denver Broncos are a professional American football franchise based in Denver, Colorado. The Broncos compete as a member club of the National Football League (NFL)&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) West division. The team began play in 1960 as a charter member of the American Football League (AFL) and joined the NFL as part of the merger in 1970. The Broncos are owned by the Pat Bowlen trust and currently play home games at Broncos Stadium at Mile High (formerly known as Invesco Field at Mile High from 2001–2010 and Sports Authority Field at Mile High from 2011–2017).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Tigers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-tigers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-tigers/</guid>
      <description>The Detroit Tigers are an American professional baseball team based in Detroit, Michigan. The Tigers compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the American League (AL) Central division. The club was founded as one of the AL&amp;rsquo;s eight charter franchises in 1901. The Tigers have won four World Series championships (1935, 1945, 1968, and 1984), 11 AL pennants (1907, 1908, 1909, 1934, 1935, 1940, 1945, 1968, 1984, 2006, 2012), and four AL Central division championships (2011, 2012, 2013, and 2014).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>The Green Bay Packers are a professional American football team based in Green Bay, Wisconsin. The Packers compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) North division. It is the third-oldest franchise in the NFL, dating back to 1919, and is the only non-profit, community-owned major league professional sports team based in the United States. Home games have been played at Lambeau Field since 1957.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Astros</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros/</guid>
      <description> The Houston Astros are an American professional baseball team based in Houston, Texas. The Astros compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West division, having moved to the division in 2013 after spending their first 51 seasons in the National League (NL). The Astros have played their home games at Minute Maid Park since 2000.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Texans</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-texans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-texans/</guid>
      <description> The Houston Texans are a professional American football team based in Houston, Texas. The Texans compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) South division. The team plays its home games at NRG Stadium.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indianapolis Colts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indianapolis-colts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indianapolis-colts/</guid>
      <description>The Indianapolis Colts are an American football team based in Indianapolis, Indiana. The Colts compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) South division. Since the 2008 season, the Colts have played their games in Lucas Oil Stadium. Previously, the team had played for over two decades (1984–2007) at the RCA Dome. Since 1987, the Colts have been the host team for the NFL Scouting Combine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Chiefs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kansas-city-chiefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kansas-city-chiefs/</guid>
      <description>The Kansas City Chiefs are a professional American football team based in Kansas City, Missouri. Chiefs compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) West division. The team was founded in 1960 as the Dallas Texans by businessman Lamar Hunt and was a charter member of the American Football League (AFL). (They are not associated with the NFL Dallas Texans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Royals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kansas-city-royals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kansas-city-royals/</guid>
      <description> The Kansas City Royals are an American professional baseball team based in Kansas City, Missouri. The Royals compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member team of the American League (AL) Central division. The team was founded as an expansion franchise in 1969, and has participated in four World Series, winning in 1985 and 2015, and losing in 1980 and 2014.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Dodgers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-dodgers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-dodgers/</guid>
      <description>The Los Angeles Dodgers are an American professional baseball team based in Los Angeles, California. The Dodgers compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) West division. Established in 1883 in Brooklyn, New York, the team moved to Los Angeles before the 1958 season. They played for four seasons at the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum before moving to their current home of Dodger Stadium in 1962</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Rams</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-rams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-rams/</guid>
      <description>The Los Angeles Rams are a professional American football team based in Los Angeles, California. The Rams compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the National Football Conference (NFC) West division. The club won three NFL championships, and is the only one to win championships representing three different cities (Cleveland in 1945, Los Angeles in 1951, and St. Louis in 1999). The Rams play their home games at the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Dolphins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/miami-dolphins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/miami-dolphins/</guid>
      <description>The Miami Dolphins are a professional American football team based in the Miami metropolitan area. The Dolphins compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The Dolphins play their home games at Hard Rock Stadium in the northern suburb of Miami Gardens, Florida, and are headquartered in Davie, Florida. The Dolphins are Florida&amp;rsquo;s oldest professional sports team. Of the four AFC East teams, they are the only team in the division that was not a charter member of the American Football League (AFL).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milwaukee Brewers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/milwaukee-brewers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/milwaukee-brewers/</guid>
      <description> The Milwaukee Brewers are an American professional baseball team based in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. The Brewers compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. The team is named for the citys association with the brewing industry. Since 2001, the Brewers have played their home games at Miller Park, which has a seating capacity of 41,900.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota Twins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/minnesota-twins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/minnesota-twins/</guid>
      <description> The Minnesota Twins are an American professional baseball team based in Minneapolis, Minnesota. The team competes in the Central division of the American League (AL), and is named after the Twin Cities area comprising Minneapolis and St. Paul.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota Vikings</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/minnesota-vikings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/minnesota-vikings/</guid>
      <description> The Minnesota Vikings are a professional American football team based in Minneapolis, Minnesota. The Vikings joined the National Football League (NFL) as an expansion team in 1960, and first took the field for the 1961 season.[4] The team competes in the National Football Conference (NFC) North division.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLB</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mlb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mlb/</guid>
      <description>Major League Baseball (MLB) is a professional baseball organization, and the oldest of the four major professional sports leagues in the United States and Canada. A total of 30 teams play in the National League (NL) and American League (AL), with 15 teams in each league. The NL and AL were formed as separate legal entities in 1876 and 1901, respectively. After cooperating but remaining legally separate entities beginning in 1903, the leagues merged into a single organization led by the Commissioner of Baseball in 2000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mls/</guid>
      <description>Major League Soccer (MLS) is a men&amp;rsquo;s professional soccer league sanctioned by the United States Soccer Federation which represents the sport&amp;rsquo;s highest level in the United States. The league comprises 24 teams—21 in the U.S. and 3 in Canada and constitutes one of the major professional sports leagues in both countries. The regular season runs from March to October, with each team playing 34 games; the team with the best record is awarded the Supporters&amp;rsquo; Shield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MOL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mol/</guid>
      <description> MOL is a Japanese transport company headquartered in Toranomon, Minato, Tokyo, Japan. It is one of the largest shipping companies in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nba/</guid>
      <description> The National Basketball Association (NBA) is a men&amp;rsquo;s professional basketball league in North America, composed of 30 teams (29 in the United States and 1 in Canada). It is one of the four major professional sports leagues in the United States and Canada, and is widely considered to be the premier men&amp;rsquo;s professional basketball league in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Patriots</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots/</guid>
      <description>The New England Patriots are a professional American football team based in the Greater Boston area. The Patriots compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team plays its home games at Gillette Stadium in the town of Foxborough, Massachusetts, which is located 21 miles (34 km) southwest of downtown Boston, Massachusetts and 20 miles (32 km) northeast of downtown Providence, Rhode Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Saints</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-orleans-saints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-orleans-saints/</guid>
      <description> The New Orleans Saints are a professional American football team based in New Orleans, Louisiana. The Saints currently compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The team was founded by John W. Mecom Jr., David Dixon, and the city of New Orleans on November 1, 1966. The Saints began play in Tulane Stadium in 1967.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Giants</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-giants/</guid>
      <description>The New York Giants are a professional American football team based in the New York metropolitan area. The Giants compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) East division. The team plays its home games at MetLife Stadium in East Rutherford, New Jersey, which it shares with the New York Jets in a unique arrangement. The Giants hold their summer training camp at the Quest Diagnostics Training Center at the Meadowlands Sports Complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Jets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-jets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-jets/</guid>
      <description>The New York Jets are a professional American football team located in the New York metropolitan area. The Jets compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team is headquartered in Florham Park, New Jersey. In a unique arrangement for the league, the Jets share MetLife Stadium in East Rutherford, New Jersey with the New York Giants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Mets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-mets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-mets/</guid>
      <description> The New York Mets are an American professional baseball team based in the New York City borough of Queens. The Mets compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) East division. The Mets are one of two Major League clubs based in New York City; the other is the New York Yankees of the American League East.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Yankees</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees/</guid>
      <description>The New York Yankees are an American professional baseball team based in the New York City borough of the Bronx. The Yankees compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) East division. They are one of two major league clubs based in New York City; the other club is the National League (NL)&amp;rsquo;s New York Mets. In the 1901 season, the club began play in the AL as the Baltimore Orioles (no relation to the modern Baltimore Orioles).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nfl/</guid>
      <description>The National Football League (NFL) is a professional American football league consisting of 32 teams, divided equally between the National Football Conference (NFC) and the American Football Conference (AFC). The NFL is one of the four major professional sports leagues in North America, and the highest professional level of American football in the world. The NFL&amp;rsquo;s 17-week regular season runs from early September to late December, with each team playing 16 games and having one bye week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Athletics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oakland-athletics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oakland-athletics/</guid>
      <description>The Oakland Athletics, often referred to as the A&amp;rsquo;s, are an American professional baseball team based in Oakland, California. They compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West division. The team plays its home games at the RingCentral Coliseum. They have won nine World Series championships, tied for the third-most of all current MLB teams. The 2017 season was the club&amp;rsquo;s 50th while based in Oakland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Eagles</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-eagles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-eagles/</guid>
      <description>The Philadelphia Eagles are a professional American football team based in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. The Eagles compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) East division. In the 2017 season the team won Super Bowl LII, their first Super Bowl win in franchise history and their fourth NFL title overall, after winning the Championship Game in 1948, 1949, and 1960.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Phillies</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-phillies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-phillies/</guid>
      <description> The Philadelphia Phillies are a professional baseball team based in Philadelphia, USA. The Phillies compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the National League (NL) East division. Since 2004, the team&amp;rsquo;s home has been Citizens Bank Park, located in South Philadelphia.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Pirates</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-pirates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-pirates/</guid>
      <description>The Pittsburgh Pirates are an American professional baseball team based in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. The Pirates compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. The Pirates play their home games at PNC Park; the team previously played at Forbes Field and Three Rivers Stadium, the latter of which was named after its location near the confluence of the Allegheny, Monongahela, and Ohio Rivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Padres</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-padres/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-padres/</guid>
      <description>The San Diego Padres are an American professional baseball team based in San Diego, California. The Padres compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) West division. Founded in 1969, the Padres have won two NL pennants — in 1984 and 1998, losing in the World Series both years. As of 2018, they have had 14 winning seasons in franchise history. The Padres are one of two Major League Baseball teams (the other being the Los Angeles Angels) in California to originate from that state; the Athletics were originally from Philadelphia (and moved to the state from Kansas City), and the Dodgers and Giants are originally from two New York City boroughs – Brooklyn and Manhattan, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Mariners</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-mariners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-mariners/</guid>
      <description>The Seattle Mariners are an American professional baseball team based in Seattle, Washington. The Mariners compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West Division. The team joined the American League as an expansion team in 1977 playing their home games in the Kingdome. Since July 1999, the Mariners&amp;rsquo; home ballpark has been T-Mobile Park (formerly Safeco Field), located in the SoDo neighborhood of Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprite</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprite/</guid>
      <description> Sprite is a colorless, caffeine-free, lemon and lime-flavored soft drink created by The Coca-Cola Company. It was first developed in West Germany in 1959 as Fanta Klare Zitrone (“Clear Lemon Fanta”) and was introduced in the United States under the current brand name Sprite in 1961 as a competitor to 7 Up.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis Cardinals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-cardinals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-cardinals/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals are an American professional baseball team based in St. Louis, Missouri. The Cardinals compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. Busch Stadium has been their home ballpark since 2006. One of the most successful franchises in baseball history, the Cardinals have won 11 World Series championships, the second-most in Major League Baseball (behind the New York Yankees) and the most in the National League.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Bay Rays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-rays/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-rays/</guid>
      <description> The Tampa Bay Rays are an American professional baseball team based in St. Petersburg, Florida. The Rays compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the American League (AL) East division. Since its inception, the team&amp;rsquo;s home venue has been Tropicana Field.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Titans</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-titans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-titans/</guid>
      <description>The Tennessee Titans are a professional American football team based in Nashville, Tennessee. The Titans compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) South division. Previously known as the Houston Oilers, the team began play in 1960 in Houston, Texas, as a charter member of the American Football League (AFL). The Oilers won the first two AFL Championships, and joined the NFL as part of the AFL–NFL merger in 1970.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Rangers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/texas-rangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/texas-rangers/</guid>
      <description> The Texas Rangers are an American professional baseball team based in Arlington, Texas, located in the Dallas–Fort Worth metroplex. The Rangers franchise currently competes in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the American League (AL) West division. Since 1994, the Rangers have played in Globe Life Park in Arlington. The team&amp;rsquo;s name is borrowed from the famous law enforcement agency of the same name.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Blue Jays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-blue-jays/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-blue-jays/</guid>
      <description> The Toronto Blue Jays are a Canadian professional baseball team based in Toronto, Ontario. The Blue Jays compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) East division. The team plays its home games at the Rogers Centre.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Nationals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-nationals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/washington-nationals/</guid>
      <description> he Washington Nationals are a professional baseball team based in Washington, D.C. The Nationals compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) East division. From 2005 to 2007, the team played in RFK Stadium; since 2008 their home stadium has been Nationals Park on South Capitol Street in Southeast D.C., near the Anacostia River.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expedia Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/expedia-group/</guid>
      <description> Expedia Group is an American global travel technology company. Its websites, which are primarily travel fare aggregators and travel metasearch engines, include CarRentals.com, CheapTickets, Expedia.com, HomeAway, Hotels.com, Hotwire.com, Orbitz, Travelocity, trivago, and Venere.com.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</guid>
      <description> Home Depot is an American home improvement supplies retailing company that sells tools, construction products, and services. The company is headquartered at the Atlanta Store Support Center in unincorporated Cobb County, Georgia (with an Atlanta mailing address).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leroy-Merlin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</guid>
      <description> Leroy Merlin (French: [ləʁwa mɛʁlɛ̃]) is a French headquartered home improvement and gardening Retail serving several countries in Europe, Asia, South America, and Africa.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn is an American business and employment-oriented service that operates via websites and mobile apps. Founded on December 28, 2002, and launched on May 5, 2003, it is mainly used for professional networking, including employers posting jobs and job seekers posting their CVs. As of 2015, most of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue came from selling access to information about its members to recruiters and sales professionals. As of March 2019, LinkedIn had 610 million registered members in 200 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NJPAC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</guid>
      <description> The New Jersey Performing Arts Center (NJPAC), in downtown Newark, New Jersey, United States, is one of the largest performing arts centers in the United States. Home to the New Jersey Symphony Orchestra (NJSO), more than nine million visitors (including more than one million children) have visited the center since it opened in October 1997 on the site of the former Military Park Hotel.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</guid>
      <description> Popeyes is an American multinational chain of fried chicken fast food restaurants founded in 1972 in New Orleans, Louisiana and headquartered in Miami, Florida. Since 2008, its full brand name is Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen, Inc., and it was formerly named Popeyes Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits and Popeyes Famous Fried Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits. It is currently a subsidiary of Toronto-based Restaurant Brands International.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Royce</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce/</guid>
      <description>Rolls-Royce was a British luxury car and later an aero-engine manufacturing business established in 1904 by the partnership of Charles Rolls and Henry Royce. Building on Royce&amp;rsquo;s reputation established with his cranes they quickly developed a reputation for superior engineering by manufacturing the &amp;ldquo;best car in the world&amp;rdquo;. The First World War brought them into manufacturing aero-engines. Joint development of jet engines began in 1940 and they entered production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Royce Motors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</guid>
      <description>Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited is a British luxury automobile maker. A wholly owned subsidiary of German group BMW, it was established in 1998 after BMW was licensed the rights to the Rolls-Royce brand name and logo from Rolls-Royce plc and acquired the rights to the Spirit of Ecstasy and Rolls-Royce grill shape trademarks from Volkswagen AG. Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited operates from purpose-built administrative and production facilities opened in 2003 across from the historic Goodwood Circuit in Goodwood, West Sussex, England, United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toys R Us</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</guid>
      <description> Toys &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; Us is an international toy, clothing, video game, and baby product Retail owned by Tru Kids, Inc. (d.b.a. Tru Kids Brands) and various others. It was founded in April 1948, with its headquarters located in Wayne, New Jersey, in the New York metropolitan area.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7-eleven</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</guid>
      <description>7-Eleven Inc. is a Japanese-owned American international chain of convenience stores, headquartered in Dallas, Texas. The chain was founded in 1927 as Tote&amp;rsquo;m Stores until it was renamed in 1946. Its parent company since 2005, Seven-Eleven Japan Co., Ltd., operates, franchises, and licenses 68,236 stores in 17 countries as of June 2019. Seven-Eleven Japan is headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo and held by Seven &amp;amp; I Holdings Co., Ltd.. The most recent franchise agreement gives up to 59% of a franchise&amp;rsquo;s gross profit to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acrobat Pro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-pro/</guid>
      <description> Adobe Acrobat is a family of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Inc. to view, create, manipulate, print and manage files in Portable Document Format (PDF).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acrobat Reader</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-reader/</guid>
      <description> Adobe Acrobat is a family of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Inc. to view, create, manipulate, print and manage files in Portable Document Format (PDF).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acura</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</guid>
      <description>Acura (/ˈækjʊrə/) is the American luxury vehicle marque of Japanese automaker Honda. The brand was launched in the United States and Canada on 27 March 1986, marketing luxury, performance, and high-performance vehicles. It was introduced to Hong Kong in 1991, Mexico in 2004, China in 2006, Russia in 2014 (no longer available in Russia) and Kuwait in 2015, and is also sold in Ukraine. Honda&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce Acura to the Japanese domestic market (JDM) in 2008 was delayed, due to economic reasons,[4] and later withheld as a result of the 2008 financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Inc. is an American multinational computer software company headquartered in San Jose, California. It has historically focused upon the creation of multimedia and creativity software products, with a more recent foray towards digital marketing software. Adobe is best known for its Adobe Flash web software ecosystem, Photoshop image editing software, Acrobat Reader, the Portable Document Format (PDF), and Adobe Creative Suite, as well as its successor Adobe Creative Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aeroflot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</guid>
      <description> Aeroflot – Russian Airlines is the flag carrier and largest airline of the Russian Federation. The carrier is an open joint stock company that operates domestic and international passenger and services, mainly from its hub at Sheremetyevo International Airport.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china/</guid>
      <description> Air China Limited is the flag carrier and one of the major airlines of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, with its headquarters in Shunyi District, Beijing. Air China&amp;rsquo;s flight operations are based at Beijing Capital International Airport. In 2017, the airline carried 102 million domestic and international passengers with an average load factor of 81%.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/airbnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/airbnb/</guid>
      <description> A‌i‌r‌b‌n‌b‌,‌ ‌I‌n‌c‌.‌, is an American online marketplace and hospitality service brokerage company based in San Francisco, California, United States. Members can use the service to arrange or offer lodging, primarily homestays, or tourism experiences. The company does not own any of the real estate listings, nor does it host events; it acts as a broker, receiving commissions from each booking.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpina</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</guid>
      <description>Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners. For instance, the Alpina B7 is produced at the same assembly line in Dingolfing, Germany (BMW Plant Dingolfing), as BMW&amp;rsquo;s own 7 Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Americ Inn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/americ-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/americ-inn/</guid>
      <description> AmericInn provides genuine hospitality in 200 welcoming locations across the US. With free hot breakfast, updated guest rooms, on-site fitness centers and inviting indoor pools at select locations, AmericInn is proud to make all travelers feel like neighbors.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-airlines/</guid>
      <description>American Airlines, Inc. (AA) is a major American airline headquartered in Fort Worth, Texas, within the Dallas-Fort Worth metroplex. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline when measured by fleet size, revenue, scheduled passengers carried, scheduled passenger-kilometers flown, and number of destinations served. American, together with its regional partners, operates an extensive international and domestic network with almost 6,700 flights per day to nearly 350 destinations in more than 50 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aston-Martin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</guid>
      <description>Aston Martin Lagonda Global Holdings plc is a British independent manufacturer of luxury sports cars and grand tourers. It was founded in 1913 by Lionel Martin and Robert Bamford. Steered from 1947 by David Brown, it became associated with expensive grand touring cars in the 1950s and 1960s, and with the fictional character James Bond following his use of a DB5 model in the 1964 film Goldfinger. Their sports cars are regarded as a British cultural icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AXA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/axa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/axa/</guid>
      <description> AXA is a French multinational insurance firm headquartered in the 8th arrondissement of Paris that engages in global insurance, investment management, and other financial services.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bain Capital</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</guid>
      <description> Bain Capital is a private investment firm based in Boston, Massachusetts. It specializes in private equity, venture capital, credit, public equity, impact investing, life sciences and real estate. Bain Capital invests across a range of industry sectors and geographic regions. As of 2018, the firm managed more than $105 billion of investor capital.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bentley</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</guid>
      <description> Bentley Motors Limited is a British manufacturer and marketer of luxury cars and SUVs—and a subsidiary of the Volkswagen Group since 1998.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMW</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</guid>
      <description> BMW AG (German originally an initialism for Bayerische Motoren Werke in German, or Bavarian Motor Works in English) is a German multinational company which currently produces automobiles and motorcycles, and also produced aircraft engines until 1945.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buick</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buick/</guid>
      <description>Buick is a division of the American automobile manufacturer General Motors (GM). It was among the first American marques of automobiles, and was the company that established General Motors in 1908. Before the establishment of General Motors, GM founder William C. Durant had served as Buick&amp;rsquo;s general manager and major investor. Buick was the first production automobile maker in the world to equip its cars with overhead valve engines, which it did in 1904.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadillac</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac/</guid>
      <description> Cadillac /ˈkædɪlæk/ is a division of the American automobile manufacturer General Motors (GM) that designs and builds luxury vehicles. Its major markets are the United States, Canada, and China. Cadillac vehicles are distributed in 34 additional markets worldwide. Cadillac automobiles are at the top of the luxury field within the United States. In 2017, Cadillac&amp;rsquo;s U.S. sales were 156,440 vehicles and its global sales were 356,467 vehicles.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cathay Dragon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited is a Hong Kong-based international regional airline, with its corporate headquarters, Cathay Dragon House, and main hub at Hong Kong International Airport. As of 30 October 2013, the airline operates a scheduled passenger network to 47 destinations in 14 countries and territories across Asia. Additionally, the airline has three codeshares on routes served by partner airlines. It has an all Airbus fleet of 48 aircraft, consisting of A320s, A321s and A330s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colgate</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate/</guid>
      <description> Colgate is an umbrella brand principally used for oral hygiene products such as toothpastes, toothbrushes, mouthwashes and dental floss. Manufactured by the American consumer-goods conglomerate Colgate-Palmolive, Colgate oral hygiene products were first sold by the company in 1873, sixteen years after the death of the founder, William Colgate. The company originally sold soap.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daikin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</guid>
      <description> Daikin Industries, Ltd. (ダイキン工業株式会社 Daikin Kōgyō Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational air conditioning manufacturing company headquartered in Osaka. It has operations in the United States, Japan, China, Philippines, Australia, India, Southeast Asia, Europe, and South America.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Days Inn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/days-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/days-inn/</guid>
      <description> Days Inn is a hotel chain headquartered in the United States. It was founded in 1970 by Cecil B. Day, who opened the first location in Tybee Island, Georgia. The brand is now a part of the Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, headquartered in Parsippany, New Jersey, which used to be a part of Cendant. As of December 31, 2018, Days Inn includes 1,728 locations worldwide with 137,678 rooms.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</guid>
      <description> Dodge is an American brand of automobile manufactured by FCA US LLC (formerly known as Fiat Chrysler Group LLC), based in Auburn Hills, Michigan. Dodge vehicles currently include performance cars, though for much of its existence Dodge was Chrysler&amp;rsquo;s mid-priced brand above Plymouth.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doosan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</guid>
      <description> Doosan Group is a South Korean conglomerate company. In 2009, the company was placed 471st in the Fortune Global 500. It has been included in the Forbes Global 2000 companies from 2007.[citation needed] It is the parent company of ŠKODA power. Doosan was ranked 4th among the “World&amp;rsquo;s Best 40 Companies 2009” list, released in the latest issue of BusinessWeek, the U.S. economics magazine in October 2009.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emirates Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Emirates is an airline based in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. The airline is a subsidiary of The Emirates Group, which is wholly owned by the government of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Investment Corporation of Dubai. It is the largest airline in the Middle East, operating over 3,600 flights per week from its hub at Dubai International Airport, to more than 150 cities in 80 countries across six continents. Cargo activities are undertaken by Emirates SkyCargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ford</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ford/</guid>
      <description>Ford Motor Company is an American multinational automaker that has its main headquarter in Dearborn, Michigan, a suburb of Detroit. It was founded by Henry Ford and incorporated on June 16, 1903. The company sells automobiles and commercial vehicles under the Ford brand and most luxury cars under the Lincoln brand. Ford also owns Brazilian SUV manufacturer Troller, an 8% stake in Aston Martin of the United Kingdom and a 32% stake in Jiangling Motors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gap/</guid>
      <description>Gap was founded in 1969 by Donald Fisher and Doris F. Fisher and is headquartered in San Francisco, California. The company operates six primary divisions: Gap (the namesake banner), Banana Republic, Old Navy, Intermix, Hill City, and Athleta . Gap Inc. is the largest specialty Retail in the United States, and is 3rd in total international locations, behind Inditex Group and H&amp;amp;M. As of September 2008, the company has approximately 135,000 employees and operates 3,727 stores worldwide, of which 2,406 are located in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gm/</guid>
      <description>General Motors Company, is an American multinational corporation headquartered in Detroit that designs, manufactures, markets, and distributes vehicles and vehicle parts, and sells financial services, with global headquarters in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Renaissance Center. It was originally founded by William C. Durant on September 16, 1908 as a holding company. The company is the largest American automobile manufacturer, and one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest. As of 2018, General Motors is ranked #10 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/goldman-sachs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/goldman-sachs/</guid>
      <description> The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc., is an American multinational investment bank and financial services company headquartered in New York City. It offers services in investment management, securities, asset management, prime brokerage, and securities underwriting.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harley</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harley/</guid>
      <description>Harley-Davidson, Inc., H-D, or Harley, is an American motorcycle manufacturer founded in 1903 in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. It was one of two major American motorcycle manufacturers to survive the Great Depression, along with Indian. The company has survived numerous ownership arrangements, subsidiary arrangements, periods of poor economic health and product quality, and intense global competition to become one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest motorcycle manufacturers and an iconic brand widely known for its loyal following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hp/</guid>
      <description> HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</guid>
      <description>HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
  Source  Source In October 2014, the Hewlett-Packard Company announced its intention to split into two separate entities, signaling the largest corporate demerger in history. The two resulting companies would each remain Fortune 100 industry leaders—with HP, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Daniels</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jack-daniels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jack-daniels/</guid>
      <description> Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s is a brand of Tennessee whiskey and the top-selling American whiskey in the world. It is produced in Lynchburg, Tennessee, by the Jack Daniel Distillery, which has been owned by the Brown–Forman Corporation since 1956. Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s home county of Moore is a dry county, so the product is not available for purchase at stores or restaurants within the county.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Japan Airlines is an international airline, headquartered in Shinagawa Tokyo, Japan. Its main hubs are Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s Narita International Airport and Tokyo International Airport (Haneda Airport), as well as Osaka&amp;rsquo;s Kansai International Airport and Osaka International Airport. JAL group companies include Japan Airlines, J-Air, JAL Express, Japan Air Commuter, Japan Transocean Air, ZIPAIR Tokyo and Ryukyu Air Commuter for domestic feeder services, and JAL Cargo for cargo and mail services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeep</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jeep/</guid>
      <description> Jeep is a brand of American automobile and division of FCA US LLC (formerly Chrysler Group, LLC), a wholly owned subsidiary of the Italian-American corporation Fiat Chrysler Automobiles. Jeep has been a part of Chrysler since 1987, when Chrysler acquired the Jeep brand, along with remaining assets, from its previous owner American Motors Corporation (AMC).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JetBlue</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetblue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetblue/</guid>
      <description>JetBlue Airways Corporation, stylized as jetBlue, is an American low cost carrier scheduled passenger airline headquartered in New York City. A major air carrier and the sixth-largest airline in the United States, jetBlue is headquartered in the Long Island City neighborhood of the New York City borough of Queens, with its main base at John F. Kennedy International Airport. It also maintains corporate offices in Cottonwood Heights, Utah and Orlando, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kia/</guid>
      <description>Kia Motors Corporation, headquartered in Seoul, is South Korea&amp;rsquo;s second-largest automobile manufacturer, following the Hyundai Motor Company, with sales of over 3.3 million vehicles in 2015. As of December 2015, the Kia Motor Corporation is minority owned by Hyundai, which owns a 33.88% stake valued at just over US$6 billion. Kia in turn is a minority owner of more than twenty Hyundai subsidiaries ranging from 4.9% up to 45.37%, totaling more than US$8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lufthansa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa/</guid>
      <description>Deutsche Lufthansa AG Lufthansa (sometimes also as Lufthansa German Airlines), is the largest German airline and, when combined with its subsidiaries, also the largest airline in Europe in terms of passengers carried. The name of the company is derived from the German word Luft &amp;ldquo;air&amp;rdquo; and Hansa, the Hanseatic League. Lufthansa is one of the five founding members of Star Alliance, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline alliance, formed in 1997.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/malaysia-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/malaysia-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Malaysia Airlines Berhad (MAB) is an airline operating flights from Kuala Lumpur International Airport and from secondary hubs in Kota Kinabalu and Kuching to destinations throughout Asia, Oceania and Europe. Malaysia Airlines is the flag carrier of Malaysia and a member of the oneworld airline alliance. The company headquarters are located at Kuala Lumpur International Airport. In August 2014, the Malaysian government&amp;rsquo;s sovereign wealth fund Khazanah Nasional—which then owned 69.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</guid>
      <description> Nikon Corporation is a Japanese multinational corporation headquartered in Tokyo, Japan, specializing in optics and imaging products.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</guid>
      <description> Nintendo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese multinational consumer electronics and video game company headquartered in Kyoto. Nintendo is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest video game companies by market capitalization, creating some of the best-known and top-selling video game franchises, such as Mario, The Legend of Zelda, and Pokémon.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oracle/</guid>
      <description> Oracle Corporation is an American multinational computer technology corporation headquartered in Redwood Shores, California. The company sells database software and technology, cloud engineered systems, and enterprise software products—particularly its own brands of database management systems. In 2018, Oracle was the third-largest software company by revenue.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palmolive</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/palmolive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/palmolive/</guid>
      <description> Palmolive is the trademark of a line of products produced by the American company Colgate-Palmolive. The name originated in 1898, and the company sells associated products in various countries. Such products include soap, shampoo, hair conditioner, body wash and hand-wash liquid. In some countries, the line of products also includes a dishwashing liquid. In Japan, the products are distributed under license by Daiichi Sekken Co., Ltd. since 2018
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/principal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/principal/</guid>
      <description>The Principal Financial Group is a global financial investment management and insurance company headquartered in Des Moines, Iowa
  Source Enter Lippincott, who, through leadership workshops, gained clarity on the vision and business objectives. Principal then conducted a global study of 1,200 employees to mine for perceived strengths and desired shifts in the brand evolution. Whether by geography, business unit or tenure, employees were calling for a strong signal about and recognition of the company’s next era — one that was already global, bolder, more collaborative, and more humanly and intellectually inclusive than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qantas Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Qantas Airways Limited (/ˈkwɒntəs/) is the flag carrier of Australia and its largest airline by fleet size, international flights and international destinations. It is the third oldest airline in the world, after KLM and Avianca having been founded in November 1920; it began international passenger flights in May 1935. The Qantas name comes from &amp;ldquo;QANTAS&amp;rdquo;, an acronym for its original name, &amp;ldquo;Queensland and Northern Territory Aerial Services&amp;rdquo;, and it is nicknamed &amp;ldquo;The Flying Kangaroo&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/salesforce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/salesforce/</guid>
      <description> Salesforce.com, Inc. (usually abbreviated as SF or SFDC) is an American cloud-based software company headquartered in San Francisco, California. Though the bulk of its revenue comes from its customer-relationship management (CRM) service, Salesforce training also sells a complementary suite of enterprise applications focused on customer service, marketing automation, analytics and application development.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</guid>
      <description>SAP SE is a German multinational software corporation that makes enterprise software to manage business operations and customer relations. SAP is headquartered in Walldorf, Baden-Württemberg, Germany with regional offices in 180 countries. The company has over 425,000 customers in over 180 countries and is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
  Source  Subtle enhancements to the SAP logo make it feel more contemporary. Designed to live in the digital world, the new mark springs vividly from the screen, on any background, connecting with both large-scale business clients and individual consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/singapore-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/singapore-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Singapore Airlines Limited (SIA) is the flag carrier airline of Singapore with its hub at Singapore Changi Airport. The airline uses the Singapore Girl as its central figure in corporate branding. It is ranked as the world&amp;rsquo;s best airline, since 2018, while winning the top spot in three other categories in the same year including &amp;ldquo;Best First Class&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Best First Class Airline Seat&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Best Airline in Asia&amp;rdquo;. In 2018, the airline was placed 18th on the top 50 most admired companies worldwide, first in Asia and the only airline on the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skoda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/skoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/skoda/</guid>
      <description> ŠKODA AUTO is a Czech automobile manufacturer founded in 1895 as Laurin &amp;amp; Klement. Its headquarters are in Mladá Boleslav, Czech Republic.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/snapchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/snapchat/</guid>
      <description> Snapchat is a multimedia messaging app used globally, created by Evan Spiegel, Bobby Murphy, and Reggie Brown, former students at Stanford University, and developed by Snap Inc., originally Snapchat Inc.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</guid>
      <description> Spotify Technology S.A. (/ˈspɒtɪfaɪ/) is a Swedish media-services provider founded in 2006. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its audio streaming platform that provides DRM-protected music and podcasts from record labels and media companies. As a freemium service, basic features are free with advertisements or automatic music videos, while additional features, such as improved streaming quality, are offered via paid subscriptions.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subaru</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</guid>
      <description> Subaru is the automobile manufacturing division of Japanese transportation conglomerate Subaru Corporation (formerly known as Fuji Heavy Industries), the twenty-second largest automaker by production worldwide in 2012.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Swiss International Air Lines is the national airline of Switzerland, operating scheduled services in Europe and to North America, South America, Africa and Asia. Zurich Airport is its hub, Geneva Airport is a focus city. The airline was formed following the bankruptcy in 2002 of Swissair, Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s then flag carrier.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesla/</guid>
      <description>Tesla, Inc. (formerly Tesla Motors, Inc.) is an American automotive and energy company based in Palo Alto, California. The company specializes in electric car manufacturing and, through its SolarCity subsidiary, solar panel manufacturing. It operates multiple production and assembly plants, notably Gigafactory 1 near Reno, Nevada, and its main vehicle manufacturing facility at Tesla Factory in Fremont, California. As of March 2019, Tesla sells the Model S, Model X, and Model 3 automobiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkish-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkish-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Turkish Airlines (Turkish: Türk Hava Yolları) is the national flag carrier airline of Turkey. As of 2018, it operates scheduled services to 304 destinations in Europe, Asia, Africa, and the Americas, making it the largest carrier in the world by number of passenger destinations (excluding regional brands). It serves more destinations non-stop from a single airport than any other airline in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniqlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniqlo/</guid>
      <description> Uniqlo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese casual wear designer, manufacturer and Retail. The company is a wholly owned subsidiary of Fast Retailing Co., Ltd. The company operates in Japan and several other countries.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-airlines/</guid>
      <description>United Airlines, Inc. is a major American airline headquartered at Willis Tower in Chicago, Illinois. United operates a large domestic and international route network, with an extensive presence in the Asia-Pacific region. United is a founding member of the Star Alliance, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline alliance with a total of 28 member airlines. Regional service is operated by independent carriers under the brand name United Express. United was established by the amalgamation of several airlines in the late 1920s, the oldest of these being Varney Air Lines, which was founded in 1926.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volvo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</guid>
      <description> The Volvo Group (Swedish: Volvokoncernen; legally Aktiebolaget Volvo, shortened to AB Volvo) (stylized as VOLVO) is a Swedish multinational manufacturing company headquartered in Gothenburg. While its core activity is the production, distribution and sale of trucks, buses and construction equipment, Volvo also supplies marine and industrial drive systems and financial services. In 2016, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest manufacturer of heavy-duty trucks.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Browser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Browser (Яндекс браузер in Russian) is a freeware web browser developed by the Russian web search corporation Yandex that uses the Blink web browser engine and is based on the Chromium open source project. The browser checks webpage security with the Yandex security system and checks downloaded files with Kaspersky anti-virus. The browser also uses Opera Software&amp;rsquo;s Turbo technology to speed web browsing on slow connections.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walmart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</guid>
      <description>Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets, discount department stores, and grocery stores.
  Source The Walmart History  Walmart as Walmart know it today evolved from Sam Walton’s goals for great value and great customer service. “Mr. Sam,” as he was known, believed in leadership through service. This belief that true leadership depends on willing service was the principle on which Walmart was built, and drove the decisions the company has made for the past 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</guid>
      <description>Starbucks Corporation is an American coffee company and coffeehouse chain. Starbucks was founded in Seattle, Washington in 1971. As of early 2019, the company operates over 30,000 locations worldwide.
  Source The Starbucks History  Every day, Starbucks go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with Starbucks friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Electric</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/general-electric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/general-electric/</guid>
      <description> General Electric Company (GE) is an American multinational conglomerate incorporated in New York City and headquartered in Boston. As of 2018, the company operates through the following segments: aviation, healthcare, power, renewable energy, digital industry, additive manufacturing, venture capital and finance, lighting, and oil and gas.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Express</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</guid>
      <description>History of the American Express logo (from pentagram.com)
American Express is one of the world’s most trusted and recognized brands. Pentagram has refreshed the American Express visual identity, reasserting and amplifying the brand’s visual expression. The project sought to retool the iconic Blue Box logo, introduced in 1975, and to derive a typographic language that could also live outside the Blue Box, providing a bolder, more confident expression of the brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</guid>
      <description>History of the Bank of America logo (from Bank of America press release)
Bank of America today announced a new brand positioning focused on the question, “What would you like the power to do?” The positioning reflects the impact clients and communities can have when they have the power to achieve their goals, and the company’s role as a partner invested in their success. […]
The Flagscape logo is also getting its first update since being introduced in 1998, reflecting a more modern brand that delivers both cutting-edge technology and high-touch solutions for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</guid>
      <description>Target Corporation is the eighth-largest Retail in the United States, and is a component of the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index. Founded by George Dayton and headquartered in Minneapolis, the company was originally named Goodfellow Dry Goods in June 1902 before being renamed the Dayton&amp;rsquo;s Dry Goods Company in 1903 and later the Dayton Company in 1910. The first Target store opened in Roseville, Minnesota in 1962 while the parent company was renamed the Dayton Corporation in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>