<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>W on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/w/</link>
    <description>Recent content in W on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/w/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Walgreens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens/</guid>
      <description>Walgreen Company or simply Walgreens is an American company that operates as the second-largest pharmacy store chain in the United States behind CVS Health. It specializes in filling prescriptions, health and wellness products, health information, and photo services. As of August 31, 2018, the company operated 9,560 stores in all 50 states, the District of Columbia and the US territories of Puerto Rico and the U.S. Virgin Islands. It was founded in Chicago, Illinois, in 1901.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</guid>
      <description>Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc. (formerly Warner Bros. Pictures, Inc.), commonly referred to as Warner Bros. and abbreviated as WB, is an American entertainment company headquartered in Burbank, California and a subsidiary of AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. Founded in 1923, it has operations in film, television and video games and is one of the &amp;ldquo;Big Five&amp;rdquo; major American film studios, as well as a member of the Motion Picture Association of America</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walmart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</guid>
      <description>Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets, discount department stores, and grocery stores.
 Source The Walmart History  Walmart as we know it today evolved from Sam Walton’s goals for great value and great customer service. “Mr. Sam,” as he was known, believed in leadership through service. This belief that true leadership depends on willing service was the principle on which Walmart was built, and drove the decisions the company has made for the past 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Company</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Pictures</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Records</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-records/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fagro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fagro/</guid>
      <description>About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>