<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>L on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/l/</link><description>Recent content in L on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0009</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/l/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/louis-vuitton//file/louis-vuitton.svg</url><title>Louis Vuitton Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Louis Vuitton</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/louis-vuitton/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0009</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/louis-vuitton/</guid><description turbo="true">Louis Vuitton Malletier, commonly referred to as Louis Vuitton or shortened to LV, is a French fashion house and luxury retail company founded in 1854 by Louis Vuitton. The label&amp;rsquo;s LV monogram appears on most of its products, ranging from luxury trunks and leather goods to ready-to-wear, shoes, watches, jewelry, accessories, sunglasses and books. Louis Vuitton is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading international fashion houses; it sells its products through standalone boutiques, lease departments in high-end department stores, and through the e-commerce section of its website.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lg-twins//file/lg-twins.svg</url><title>LG Twins Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LG Twins</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lg-twins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lg-twins/</guid><description turbo="true">LG Twins (Korean: LG 트윈스) is a South Korean professional baseball team based in Seoul, South Korea. They are a member of the KBO League. The Twins play their home games at Jamsil Baseball Stadium, which they share with their rival, the Doosan Bears; the stadium is known as &amp;ldquo;Two families under one roof.&amp;rdquo;
The LG Twins are one of the most popular baseball teams in Korea.[citation needed] They gained many fans in the 1980s–2000s, most of whom live in Seoul.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte-giants//file/lotte-giants.svg</url><title>Lotte Giants Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lotte Giants</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte-giants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte-giants/</guid><description turbo="true">The Lotte Giants (Korean: 롯데 자이언츠) are a professional baseball team based in the southeastern city of Busan, South Korea, and one of the original franchises of the KBO League. The Lotte Giants are owned by Lotte Corporation, which also owns the Chiba Lotte Marines of Nippon Professional Baseball.
From 1982 through 1986, they played at Gudeok Baseball Stadium and since then have played at Sajik Baseball Stadium. They have won the Korean Series twice, in 1984 and 1992.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lightroom//file/lightroom.svg</url><title>Lightroom Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lightroom</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lightroom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lightroom/</guid><description turbo="true">Adobe Lightroom is a family of image organization and image manipulation software developed by Adobe Systems for Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, and tvOS (Apple TV). It allows importing/saving, viewing, organizing, tagging, editing, and sharing large numbers of digital images. Unlike Photoshop, Lightroom&amp;rsquo;s edits are always non-destructive by keeping the original image and the edits applied to it saved separately. Despite sharing its name with Adobe Photoshop, it cannot perform many Photoshop functions such as doctoring (adding, removing or altering the appearance of individual image items), rendering text or 3D objects on images, or modifying individual video frames.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste//file/lacoste.svg</url><title>Lacoste Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lacoste</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</guid><description turbo="true">Lacoste is a French company, founded in 1933 by tennis player René Lacoste and André Gillier. It sells clothing, footwear, sportswear, eyewear, leather goods, perfume, towels and watches. The company can be recognised by its green crocodile logo. René Lacoste, the company&amp;rsquo;s founder, was nicknamed &amp;ldquo;the Crocodile&amp;rdquo; by fans because of his tenacity on the tennis court. In November 2012 Lacoste was bought outright by Swiss family-held group Maus Frères.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lenovo//file/lenovo.svg</url><title>Lenovo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lenovo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lenovo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lenovo/</guid><description turbo="true">Lenovo Group Limited, often shortened to Lenovo (/lɛˈnoʊvoʊ/ leh-NOH-voh), is a Chinese multinational technology company that is headquartered in Beijing. The company designs, develops, manufactures, and sells personal computers, tablet computers, smartphones, workstations, servers, electronic storage devices, IT management software, and smart televisions. Lenovo is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest personal computer vendor by unit sales, as of March 2019. It markets the ThinkPad and ThinkBook business lines of notebook computers; IdeaPad, Yoga, and Legion consumer lines of notebook laptops; and the IdeaCentre and ThinkCentre lines of desktops.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media//file/liberty-media.svg</url><title>Liberty Media Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Liberty Media</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media/</guid><description turbo="true">Liberty Media Corporation (commonly referred to as Liberty Media or just Liberty) is an American mass media company controlled by chairman John C. Malone. The company has three divisions, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s ownership stakes in Formula One, SiriusXM, and the Atlanta Braves.
Source About Liberty Media Liberty Media Corporation owns interests in a broad range of media, communications and entertainment businesses. Those interests are attributed to three tracking stock groups: the Liberty SiriusXM Group, the Braves Group and the Formula One Group.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws//file/loblaws.svg</url><title>Loblaws Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Loblaws</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws/</guid><description turbo="true">Loblaws Inc. is a Canadian supermarket chain with stores located in the provinces of British Columbia, Saskatchewan, Alberta, Ontario and Quebec. Headquartered in Brampton, Ontario, Loblaws is a subsidiary of Loblaw Companies Limited, Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest food distributor.
Source About Loblaws Since the beginning, Loblaws love of food has driven us to find innovative ways to bring customers closer to their favourite products. In 1919, founders of the first Loblaw Groceterias were told their self-serve, cash-and-carry model would never work.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lockheed-martin//file/lockheed-martin.svg</url><title>Lockheed Martin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lockheed Martin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lockheed-martin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lockheed-martin/</guid><description turbo="true">Lockheed Martin Corporation is an American aerospace, defense, arms, security, and advanced technologies company with worldwide interests. It was formed by the merger of Lockheed Corporation with Martin Marietta in March 1995. It is headquartered in North Bethesda, Maryland, in the Washington, D.C., area. Lockheed Martin employs approximately 110,000 people worldwide as of January 2020.
Lockheed Martin is one of the largest companies in the aerospace, military support, security, and technologies industry.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/logo-tv//file/logo-tv.svg</url><title>Logo TV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Logo TV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/logo-tv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/logo-tv/</guid><description turbo="true"> Logo TV (often shortened to Logo, and stylized as Logo.) is an American pay television channel that is owned by ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks, a division of ViacomCBS. Launched in 2005, it was originally aimed primarily at LGBT viewers, but in 2012 it expanded towards general cultural and lifestyle programming. As of January 2016, approximately 50 million households receive Logo.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground//file/london-underground.svg</url><title>London Underground Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">London Underground</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground/</guid><description turbo="true">The London Underground (also known simply as the Underground, or by its nickname the Tube) is a public rapid transit system serving London region, England and some parts of the adjacent counties of Buckinghamshire, Essex and Hertfordshire in the United Kingdom.
The Underground has its origins in the Metropolitan Railway, the world&amp;rsquo;s first underground passenger railway. Opened in January 1863, it is now part of the Circle, Hammersmith &amp;amp; City and Metropolitan lines; the first line to operate underground electric traction trains, the City &amp;amp; South London Railway in 1890, is now part of the Northern line.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes//file/lowes.svg</url><title>Lowe’s Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lowe’s</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes/</guid><description turbo="true">Lowe&amp;rsquo;s Companies, Inc. (/loʊz/), doing business as Lowe&amp;rsquo;s, is an American retail company specializing in home improvement. Headquartered in Mooresville, North Carolina, the company operates a chain of retail stores in the United States and Canada. As of November 2018, Lowe&amp;rsquo;s and its related businesses operate 2,015 home improvement and hardware stores in North America.
Lowe&amp;rsquo;s is the second-largest hardware chain in the United States behind rival The Home Depot and ahead of Menards.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucasfilm//file/lucasfilm.svg</url><title>Lucasfilm Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lucasfilm</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lucasfilm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucasfilm/</guid><description turbo="true">Lucasfilm Ltd. LLC is an American film and television production company that is a subsidiary of The Walt Disney Studios, a division of The Walt Disney Company. The studio is best known for creating and producing the Star Wars and Indiana Jones franchises, as well as its leadership in developing special effects, sound and computer animation for films. Lucasfilm was founded by filmmaker George Lucas in 1971 in San Rafael, California; most of the company&amp;rsquo;s operations were moved to San Francisco in 2005.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucky//file/lucky.svg</url><title>Lucky Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lucky</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lucky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucky/</guid><description turbo="true">Lucky Stores is an American supermarket chain founded in San Leandro, California, in 1935. Lucky is currently operated by Save Mart Supermarkets in Northern California.
In 1998, Lucky&amp;rsquo;s parent company, American Stores, was taken over by Albertsons, and by 1999 the Lucky brand had disappeared. On January 23, 2006, SuperValu, CVS Pharmacy and an investment group led by Cerberus Capital Management announced they had agreed to acquire Albertsons for $17.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-wildcats//file/la-wildcats.svg</url><title>LA Wildcats Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LA Wildcats</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-wildcats/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-wildcats/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Los Angeles Wildcats (LA Wildcats) are a professional American football team based in the Los Angeles suburb of Carson, California. The team is a franchise of the new XFL founded by Vince McMahon’s Alpha Entertainment and plays its home games at the Dignity Health Sports Park, which is also home to the MLS’s LA Galaxy.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lawson//file/lawson.svg</url><title>Lawson Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lawson</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lawson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lawson/</guid><description turbo="true"> Lawson, Inc. (株式会社ローソン Kabushiki Kaisha Rōson, TYO: 2651) is a convenience store franchise chain in Japan. The store originated in Cuyahoga Falls, Ohio, but exists today as a Japanese company.
The Japanese company has its headquarters in East Tower of Gate City Ohsaki in Ōsaki, Shinagawa, Tokyo.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte//file/lotte.svg</url><title>Lotte Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lotte</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte/</guid><description turbo="true"> Lotte Corporation (Korean: 롯데 그룹 lotte geurup) is a South Korean multinational conglomerate. Lotte began its history on June 28, 1948, by Korean businessman Shin Kyuk-ho in Tokyo. Shin expanded Lotte to his ancestral country, South Korea, with the establishment of Lotte Confectionery in Seoul on April 3, 1967. Lotte eventually grew to become South Korea&amp;rsquo;s fifth largest business conglomerate.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus//file/lotus.svg</url><title>Lotus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lotus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus/</guid><description turbo="true">Lotus Cars Limited is a British automotive company that manufactures sports cars and racing cars with headquarters in Hethel, England. Lotus cars include the Esprit, Elan, Europa, Elise, Exige, Evora and Evija sports cars and it had motor racing success with Team Lotus in Formula One. Lotus Cars are based at the former site of RAF Hethel, a World War II airfield in Norfolk. The company designs and builds race and production automobiles of light weight and fine handling characteristics.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lending-club//file/lending-club.svg</url><title>Lending Club Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lending Club</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lending-club/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lending-club/</guid><description turbo="true"> LendingClub is an American peer-to-peer lending company, headquartered in San Francisco, California. It was the first peer-to-peer lender to register its offerings as securities with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and to offer loan trading on a secondary market. LendingClub is the worlds largest peer-to-peer lending platform. The company claims that $15.98 billion in loans had been originated through its platform up to December 31, 2015.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuniterx//file/reuniterx.svg</url><title>ReuniteRX Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ReuniteRX</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/reuniterx/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuniterx/</guid><description turbo="true"> LendingClub is an American peer-to-peer lending company, headquartered in San Francisco, California. It was the first peer-to-peer lender to register its offerings as securities with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and to offer loan trading on a secondary market. LendingClub is the worlds largest peer-to-peer lending platform. The company claims that $15.98 billion in loans had been originated through its platform up to December 31, 2015.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-quinta//file/la-quinta.svg</url><title>La Quinta Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">La Quinta</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-quinta/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-quinta/</guid><description turbo="true"> Thanks to the exclusive Bright Morning Bed,® free Bright Side Breakfast® and spacious in-room work areas, La Quinta Hotels are a bright spot in every traveler’s journey.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger//file/ledger.svg</url><title>Ledger Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ledger</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ledger is a fast paced, growing company developing security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies as well as blockchain applications for individuals and companies, by leveraging a distinctive, proprietary technology.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexicon//file/lexicon.svg</url><title>Lexicon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lexicon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lexicon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexicon/</guid><description turbo="true"> Lexicon is an American company that engineers, manufactures, and markets audio equipment as a brand of Harman International Industries, a subsidiary of South Korea-based firm Samsung Electronics. The company was founded in 1971 and headquartered in Waltham, Massachusetts with offices in Salt Lake City. It was acquired by Harman in 1993.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin//file/litecoin.svg</url><title>Litecoin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Litecoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Litecoin (LTC or Ł) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency and open-source software project released under the MIT/X11 license. Creation and transfer of coins is based on an open source cryptographic protocol and is not managed by any central authority.[citation needed] Litecoin was an early bitcoin spinoff or altcoin, starting in October 2011. In technical details, litecoin is nearly identical to Bitcoin.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lyft//file/lyft.svg</url><title>Lyft Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lyft</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lyft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lyft/</guid><description turbo="true"> Lyft, Inc. is a ridesharing company based in San Francisco, California and operating in 640 cities in the United States and 9 cities in Canada. It develops, markets, and operates the Lyft mobile app, offering car rides, scooters, and a bicycle-sharing system.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein//file/leonard-bernstein.svg</url><title>Leonard Bernstein Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Leonard Bernstein</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein/</guid><description turbo="true"> The 100th birthday of composer, conductor, and music educator Leonard Bernstein will be celebrated from August 2017 to August 2019. The symbol joins the Bernstein name with the concept of music for new generations of audiences who may not be as familiar with this luminary’s impact and legacy. Major events, concerts, and festivities are planned around the world—1,000 events taking place on six continents.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil//file/lukoil.svg</url><title>Lukoil Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lukoil</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</guid><description turbo="true">The PJSC Lukoil Oil Company is a Russian multinational energy corporation headquartered in Moscow, specializing in the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of petroleum, natural gas, and petroleum products. It was formed in 1991 when three state-run, western Siberian companies named after the respective town in Khanty–Mansi Autonomous Okrug that each was based in, Langepasneftegaz, Urayneftegaz, and Kogalymneftegaz, merged. Its name is the combination of the acronym LUK (initials of the oil-producing cities of Langepas, Uray, Kogalym) and the English word &amp;ldquo;oil&amp;rdquo;.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers//file/la-clippers.svg</url><title>LA Clippers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LA Clippers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Clippers (branded as the LA Clippers) are an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles. The Clippers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of Pacific Division of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference. The Clippers play their home games at the Staples Center, an arena they share with fellow NBA team the Los Angeles Lakers, as well as the Los Angeles Sparks of the Women&amp;rsquo;s National Basketball Association (WNBA) and the Los Angeles Kings of the National Hockey League (NHL).</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-galaxy//file/la-galaxy.svg</url><title>LA Galaxy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LA Galaxy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-galaxy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-galaxy/</guid><description turbo="true"> The LA Galaxy, also known as the Los Angeles Galaxy, is an American professional soccer franchise based in the Los Angeles suburb of Carson, California, that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), as a member of the Western Conference. The club began play in 1996 as one of the league&amp;rsquo;s eight charter members.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-fc//file/los-angeles-fc.svg</url><title>Los Angeles FC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles FC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-fc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-fc/</guid><description turbo="true">Los Angeles Football Club, commonly referred to as LAFC, is an American professional soccer franchise based in Los Angeles, California, that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the Western Conference. The team plays their home games at the Banc of California Stadium in Exposition Park. The team shares the Los Angeles area market with the LA Galaxy, and the two clubs compete in a rivalry dubbed El Tráfico.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings//file/los-angeles-kings.svg</url><title>Los Angeles Kings Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles Kings</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Kings are a professional ice hockey team based in Los Angeles. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was founded on June 5, 1967, after Jack Kent Cooke was awarded an NHL expansion franchise for Los Angeles on February 9, 1966, becoming one of the six teams that began play as part of the 1967 NHL expansion.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-lakers//file/los-angeles-lakers.svg</url><title>Los Angeles Lakers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles Lakers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-lakers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-lakers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Lakers are an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles. The Lakers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference in the Pacific Division. The Lakers play their home games at Staples Center, an arena shared with the NBA&amp;rsquo;s Los Angeles Clippers, the Los Angeles Sparks of the Women&amp;rsquo;s National Basketball Association, and the Los Angeles Kings of the National Hockey League.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-angels//file/la-angels.svg</url><title>LA Angels Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LA Angels</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-angels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-angels/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Angels are an American professional baseball franchise based in Anaheim, California. The Angels compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West division. The Angels have played home games at Angel Stadium since 1966. The current MLB franchise was established as an expansion team in 1961 by Gene Autry (1907–1998), the team&amp;rsquo;s first owner. Autry was a famous singing cowboy actor in a series of films in the 1930s to 1950s, and later was the subject of the Gene Autry Western Heritage Museum.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-chargers//file/los-angeles-chargers.svg</url><title>Los Angeles Chargers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles Chargers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-chargers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-chargers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Chargers are a professional American football team based in the Greater Los Angeles Area. The Chargers compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) West division. The team was founded on August 14, 1959, and began play on September 10, 1960, as a charter member of the American Football League (AFL), and spent its first season in Los Angeles, before moving to San Diego in 1961 to become the San Diego Chargers.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-dodgers//file/los-angeles-dodgers.svg</url><title>Los Angeles Dodgers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles Dodgers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-dodgers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-dodgers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Dodgers are an American professional baseball team based in Los Angeles, California. The Dodgers compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) West division. Established in 1883 in Brooklyn, New York, the team moved to Los Angeles before the 1958 season. They played for four seasons at the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum before moving to their current home of Dodger Stadium in 1962</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-rams//file/los-angeles-rams.svg</url><title>Los Angeles Rams Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles Rams</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-rams/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-rams/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Rams are a professional American football team based in Los Angeles, California. The Rams compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the National Football Conference (NFC) West division. The club won three NFL championships, and is the only one to win championships representing three different cities (Cleveland in 1945, Los Angeles in 1951, and St. Louis in 1999). The Rams play their home games at the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin//file/leroy-merlin.svg</url><title>Leroy-Merlin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Leroy-Merlin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Leroy Merlin (French: [ləʁwa mɛʁlɛ̃]) is a French headquartered home improvement and gardening Retail serving several countries in Europe, Asia, South America, and Africa.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin//file/linkedin.svg</url><title>LinkedIn Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LinkedIn</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</guid><description turbo="true">LinkedIn is an American business and employment-oriented service that operates via websites and mobile apps. Founded on December 28, 2002, and launched on May 5, 2003, it is mainly used for professional networking, including employers posting jobs and job seekers posting their CVs. As of 2015, most of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue came from selling access to information about its members to recruiters and sales professionals. As of March 2019, LinkedIn had 610 million registered members in 200 countries.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer//file/hummer.svg</url><title>Hummer Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hummer</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hummer was a brand of trucks and SUVs, first marketed in 1992 when AM General began selling a civilian version of the M998 Humvee. In 1998, General Motors (GM) purchased the brand name from AM General and marketed three vehicles: the original Hummer H1, based on the military Humvee, as well as the new H2 and H3 models that were based on smaller, civilian-market GM platforms.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini//file/lamborghini.svg</url><title>Lamborghini Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lamborghini</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini/</guid><description turbo="true"> Automobili Lamborghini is an Italian brand and manufacturer of luxury sports cars and SUVs based in Sant&amp;rsquo;Agata Bolognese and tractors Lamborghini Trattori in Pieve di Cento, Italy. The company is owned by the Volkswagen Group through its subsidiary Audi.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/liebherr//file/liebherr.svg</url><title>Liebherr Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Liebherr</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/liebherr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/liebherr/</guid><description turbo="true">The Liebherr Group is a large equipment manufacturer based in Switzerland with its main production facilities and origins in Germany. It consists of over 130 companies organized into eleven Divisions: Earthmoving, Mining, Mobile cranes, Tower cranes, Concrete technology, Maritime cranes, Aerospace and transportation systems, Machine tools and automation systems, Domestic appliances, and Components. It has a worldwide workforce of over 42,000, with 9 billion euros in revenue for 2017. By 2007, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest crane company.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lincoln//file/lincoln.svg</url><title>Lincoln Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lincoln</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lincoln/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lincoln/</guid><description turbo="true"> Lincoln, formally the Lincoln Motor Company, is a luxury vehicle brand of the American manufacturer Ford Motor Company. Marketed among the top luxury brands in the United States, Lincoln has competed closely against Cadillac for nearly its entire existence. Lincoln has the distinction of establishing the personal luxury car segment, with the entry of the Lincoln Continental into mass production in 1940.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/loreal//file/loreal.svg</url><title>LOreal Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LOreal</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/loreal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/loreal/</guid><description turbo="true"> L&amp;rsquo;Oréal S.A. is a French personal care company headquartered in Clichy, Hauts-de-Seine with a registered office in Paris. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest cosmetics company and has developed activities in the field concentrating on hair colour, skin care, sun protection, make-up, perfume, and hair care.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa//file/lufthansa.svg</url><title>Lufthansa Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lufthansa</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa/</guid><description turbo="true">Deutsche Lufthansa AG Lufthansa (sometimes also as Lufthansa German Airlines), is the largest German airline and, when combined with its subsidiaries, also the largest airline in Europe in terms of passengers carried. The name of the company is derived from the German word Luft &amp;ldquo;air&amp;rdquo; and Hansa, the Hanseatic League. Lufthansa is one of the five founding members of Star Alliance, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline alliance, formed in 1997.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus//file/lexus.svg</url><title>Lexus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lexus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:44 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus/</guid><description turbo="true"/>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lego//file/lego.svg</url><title>Lego Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lego</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lego/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:37 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lego/</guid><description turbo="true"/>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra//file/libra.svg</url><title>Libra Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Libra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</guid><description turbo="true">About Libra Libra is a new global cryptocurrency. Libra is built on a secure, scalable, and reliable blockchain and is designed to help bring people everywhere equal access to financial services. Libra is backed by a reserve of assets so that its value stays stable. Libra is reinventing money so it can be used in countries around the world. It can easily be sent to anyone and exchanged into local currencies.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item></channel></rss>