<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hospitality on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/hospitality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hospitality on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/hospitality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conrad Hotels</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels/</guid>
      <description>Conrad Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is an international brand of luxury hotels and resorts owned and operated by Hilton Worldwide. Conrad was considered the luxury flagship brand in the Hilton Family of Brands, named after company founder Conrad Hilton, until being supplanted by The Waldorf-Astoria Collection in 2006. As of December 31, 2018, it as 33 locations with 10,625 rooms, including two that are owned or leased with 778 rooms, 29 that are managed with 8,874 rooms, and two that are franchised with 973 rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DoubleTree</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doubletree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doubletree/</guid>
      <description> DoubleTree by Hilton is an American hotel chain and a part of Hilton Worldwide. Most DoubleTree hotels are independently owned and operated by franchisees, but some are managed by Hilton Worldwide.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilton</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hilton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hilton/</guid>
      <description> Hilton Worldwide Holdings Inc., formerly Hilton Hotels Corporation, is an American multinational hospitality company that manages and franchises a broad portfolio of hotels and resorts. Founded by Conrad Hilton in May 1919, the corporation is now led by Christopher J. Nassetta.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Inn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</guid>
      <description> Holiday Inn is a British-owned American brand of hotels, and a subsidiary of InterContinental Hotels Group. Founded as a U.S. motel chain, it has grown to be one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest hotel chains, with 1,173 active hotels and over 214,000 bedrooms as of September 30, 2018. The hotel chain&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Denham, Buckinghamshire.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyatt</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyatt/</guid>
      <description> Hyatt Hotels Corporation is an American multinational hospitality company that manages and franchises luxury hotels, resorts, and vacation properties. The Hyatt Corporation came into being upon purchase of the Hyatt House, at Los Angeles International Airport, on September 27, 1957. As of March 25, 2018, Hyatt has 777 properties in 54 countries. Fortune magazine ranked Hyatt #186 on its list of &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Best Employers&amp;rdquo; for 2018.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>