<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in art on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>British Council</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-council/</guid>
      <description> The British Council is a British organisation specialising in international cultural and educational opportunities. It works in over 100 countries: promoting a wider knowledge of the United Kingdom and the English language; encouraging cultural, scientific, technological and educational co-operation with the United Kingdom.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leonard Bernstein</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leonard-bernstein/</guid>
      <description> The 100th birthday of composer, conductor, and music educator Leonard Bernstein will be celebrated from August 2017 to August 2019. The symbol joins the Bernstein name with the concept of music for new generations of audiences who may not be as familiar with this luminary’s impact and legacy. Major events, concerts, and festivities are planned around the world—1,000 events taking place on six continents.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Met</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-met/</guid>
      <description> The Metropolitan Museum of Art of New York City, colloquially &amp;ldquo;the Met&amp;rdquo;, is the largest art museum in the United States. With 6,953,927 visitors to its three locations in 2018, it was the third most visited art museum in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ica/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NJPAC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</guid>
      <description> The New Jersey Performing Arts Center (NJPAC), in downtown Newark, New Jersey, United States, is one of the largest performing arts centers in the United States. Home to the New Jersey Symphony Orchestra (NJSO), more than nine million visitors (including more than one million children) have visited the center since it opened in October 1997 on the site of the former Military Park Hotel.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>