<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>media on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in media on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Def Jam</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/def-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/def-jam/</guid>
      <description>Def Jam Recordings is an American record label focused predominantly on hip hop, pop, and urban music, owned by Universal Music Group. In the UK, the label takes on the name Def Jam UK and is operated through Virgin EMI Records, while in Japan, it is known as Def Jam Japan, operating through Universal Music Japan. The label distributes releases of various record labels, including Kanye West&amp;rsquo;s GOOD Music, and Listen Up Forever Records, headed by producer, Ronny J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/espn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/espn/</guid>
      <description>ESPN (originally an initialism for Entertainment and Sports Programming Network) is an American basic cable sports channel owned by ESPN Inc., owned jointly by The Walt Disney Company (80%) and Hearst Communications (20%). The company was founded in 1979 by Bill Rasmussen along with his son Scott Rasmussen and Ed Egan.
 ESPN broadcasts primarily from studio facilities located in Bristol, Connecticut. The network also operates offices in Miami, New York City, Seattle, Charlotte, and Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flix/</guid>
      <description>Flix is an American premium cable and satellite television network that is owned by Showtime Networks, a subsidiary of ViacomCBS through its domestic networks division. Its programming consists solely of theatrically released feature films released from the 1970s to the present day, interspersed with some films from the 1950s and 1960s.
 It is the only premium television service in the United States that does not operate any multiplex channels that provide additional programming alongside the main service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hbo/</guid>
      <description>HBO (Home Box Office) is an American premium television network owned by Home Box Office, Inc., a subsidiary of WarnerMedia Entertainment. The programming featured on the network consists primarily of theatrically released motion pictures and original television shows, along with made-for-cable movies, documentaries and occasional comedy and concert specials.
 HBO is the oldest and longest continuously operating pay television service (basic or premium) in the United States, having been in operation since November 8, 1972.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iac/</guid>
      <description>IAC (InterActiveCorp) is an American holding company that owns brands across 100 countries, mostly in media and Internet. The company is headquartered in New York City and incorporated in Delaware. Joey Levin, who previously led the company&amp;rsquo;s search &amp;amp; applications segment, has served as Chief Executive Officer since June 2015.
 Source About IAC IAC builds companies. IAC are guided by curiosity, a questioning of the status quo, and a desire to invent or acquire new products and brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberty Media</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/liberty-media/</guid>
      <description>Liberty Media Corporation (commonly referred to as Liberty Media or just Liberty) is an American mass media company controlled by chairman John C. Malone. The company has three divisions, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s ownership stakes in Formula One, SiriusXM, and the Atlanta Braves.
 Source About Liberty Media Liberty Media Corporation owns interests in a broad range of media, communications and entertainment businesses. Those interests are attributed to three tracking stock groups: the Liberty SiriusXM Group, the Braves Group and the Formula One Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logo TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/logo-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/logo-tv/</guid>
      <description> Logo TV (often shortened to Logo, and stylized as Logo.) is an American pay television channel that is owned by ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks, a division of ViacomCBS. Launched in 2005, it was originally aimed primarily at LGBT viewers, but in 2012 it expanded towards general cultural and lifestyle programming. As of January 2016, approximately 50 million households receive Logo.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nat Geo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nat-geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nat-geo/</guid>
      <description>National Geographic (formerly the National Geographic Magazine and branded also as NAT GEO) is the official magazine of the National Geographic Society. It has been published continuously since its first issue in 1888, nine months after the Society itself was founded. It primarily contains articles about science, geography, history, and world culture. The magazine is known for its thick square-bound glossy format with a yellow rectangular border and its extensive use of dramatic photographs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paramount Network</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount-network/</guid>
      <description>Paramount Network is an American pay television channel owned by ViacomCBS. The network&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are located at the Paramount Pictures studio lot in Los Angeles.
 The channel was originally founded by a partnership between radio station WSM and Westinghouse Broadcasting as The Nashville Network (TNN) and began broadcasting March 7, 1983. It initially featured programming catering towards the culture of the Southern United States, including country music, variety shows, outdoors programming, and motor racing coverage (such as NASCAR).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SiriusXM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siriusxm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siriusxm/</guid>
      <description>SiriusXM is an American broadcasting company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City that provides satellite radio and online radio services operating in the United States. It was formed by the 2008 merger of Sirius Satellite Radio and XM Satellite Radio, merging them into SiriusXM Radio. The company also has a minor interest in Sirius XM Canada, an affiliate company that provides Sirius and XM service in Canada. At the end of 2013, Sirius XM reorganized their corporate structure, which made Sirius XM Radio Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sling TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sling-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sling-tv/</guid>
      <description>Sling Television, commonly known as Sling TV, is an American over-the-top internet television service owned by Dish Network and legally operated by Sling TV LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of Dish Network. Unveiled on January 5, 2015, at the Consumer Electronics Show, the virtual multichannel video programming distributor aims to complement subscription video on demand services for cord cutters, offering a selection of major cable channels and OTT-originated services that can be streamed through smart TVs, digital media players and apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syfy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/syfy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/syfy/</guid>
      <description> Syfy (formerly Sci-Fi Channel and Sci Fi; stylized as SYFY) is an American pay television channel that is owned by the NBCUniversal Television and Streaming division of NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast. The channel features science fiction, fantasy, horror, supernatural, paranormal, drama, and reality programming. Syfy is available to 92.4 million households in America.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bertelsmann Music Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bertelsmann-music-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bertelsmann-music-group/</guid>
      <description>Bertelsmann Music Group (BMG) was a division of German media company Bertelsmann before its completion of sale of the majority of its assets to Sony Corporation of America on 1 October 2008. Although it was established in 1987, the music company was formed as RCA/Ariola International in 1985 as a joint venture to combine the music label activities of RCA Corporation&amp;rsquo;s RCA Records division and Bertelsmann&amp;rsquo;s Ariola Records and its associated labels which include Arista Records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs/</guid>
      <description>CBS (an initialism of the network&amp;rsquo;s former name, the Columbia Broadcasting System) is an American English-language commercial broadcast television and radio network that is the flagship property of the CBS Entertainment Group division of ViacomCBS. The company is headquartered at the CBS Building in New York City with major production facilities and operations in New York City (at the CBS Broadcast Center) and Los Angeles (at CBS Television City and the CBS Studio Center).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deezer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</guid>
      <description>Deezer is a French online music streaming service. It allows users to listen to music content from record labels, including Universal Music Group, Sony Music and Warner Music Group (owned by Deezer&amp;rsquo;s parent company Access Industries) on various devices online or offline. Created in Paris, France, Deezer currently has 56 million licensed tracks in its library, with over 30,000 radio channels, 14 million monthly active users, and 7 million paid subscribers as of January 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beme</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beme/</guid>
      <description>Beme Inc. (/ˈbiːm/), stylized as beme, was a multimedia company founded by Matt Hackett and Casey Neistat, a vlogger and short film maker on YouTube. Beme Inc. was the creator of the mobile app, Beme. On November 28, 2016, CNN announced that it would acquire Beme. CNN intended to invest in the company and create a new brand focused on a young audience. The Beme app was officially shut down on January 31, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bloomberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bloomberg/</guid>
      <description> Bloomberg L.P. is a privately held financial, software, data, and media company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was founded by Michael Bloomberg in 1981, with the help of Thomas Secunda, Duncan MacMillan, Charles Zegar, and a 30% ownership investment by Merrill Lynch.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/forbes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/forbes/</guid>
      <description>Forbes is an American business magazine. Published bi-weekly, it features original articles on finance, industry, investing, and marketing topics. Forbes also reports on related subjects such as technology, communications, science, politics, and law. Its headquarters is located in Jersey City, New Jersey. Primary competitors in the national business magazine category include Fortune and Bloomberg Businessweek. The magazine is well known for its lists and rankings, including of the richest Americans (the Forbes 400), of the world&amp;rsquo;s top companies (the Forbes Global 2000), and The World&amp;rsquo;s Billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Corporation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Fox Corporation (abbreviated Fox Corp. and informally &amp;ldquo;New Fox&amp;rdquo;) is an American television broadcasting company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was formed from the 2019 acquisition of 21st Century Fox (itself formed from the 2013 split of News Corporation) by The Walt Disney Company. Fox Corp. was spun off from 21st Century Fox and its stock began trading on March 19, 2019. It is owned by the Murdoch family via a family trust with 39% interest; Rupert Murdoch is co-executive chairman, while his son Lachlan Murdoch is chairman and CEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports is the brand name for a number of sports channels, broadcast divisions, programming, and other media around the world that are either controlled or partially owned by the family of Rupert Murdoch. These assets are held mainly by Fox Corporation, with the exceptions of the operations in Australia, which are part of News Corp Australia and rest of the international Fox Sports channels and Fox Sports Networks which are owned by The Walt Disney Company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</guid>
      <description> Fox Television Stations, LLC (FTS; alternately Fox Television Stations Group, LLC), is a group of television stations located within the United States which are owned-and-operated by the Fox Broadcasting Company, a subsidiary of the Fox Corporation.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports 1 (FS1) is an American pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation.[1] FS1 replaced the motorsports network Speed on August 17, 2013, at the same time that its companion channel Fox Sports 2 replaced Fuel TV.[2] Both FS1 and FS2 absorbed most of the sports programming from its predecessors, as well as content from Fox Soccer, which was replaced by the entertainment-based channel FXX on September 2, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS2</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</guid>
      <description> Fox Sports 2 (FS2) is an American sports-oriented pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation. The channel is based at the Fox Sports division&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in the Westwood section of Los Angeles, California.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</guid>
      <description> Grupo Imagen is a Mexican media conglomerate, part of Grupo Empresarial Ángeles
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MyNetworkTV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv/</guid>
      <description>MyNetworkTV (unofficially abbreviated as MyTV, MyNet, MNT or MNTV), is an American television network/syndication service that is owned by Fox Corporation, operated by its Fox Television Stations division, and distributed through the syndication structure of 20th Television. MyNetworkTV began operations on September 5, 2006 with an initial affiliate lineup covering about 96% of the country, most of which consisted of stations that were former affiliates of The WB and UPN that did not join the successor of those two networks, The CW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBCUniversal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbcuniversal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbcuniversal/</guid>
      <description> NBCUniversal Media, LLC, d/b/a NBCUniversal, is an American worldwide mass media conglomerate owned by Comcast and headquartered at Rockefeller Plaza&amp;rsquo;s Comcast Building in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It is one of two successor companies to MCA Inc., the other being Vivendi through its subsidiary Universal Music Group.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pbs/</guid>
      <description>The Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) is an American public broadcaster and television program distributor. It is a nonprofit organization and the most prominent provider of educational television programming to public television stations in the United States, distributing series such as American Experience, America&amp;rsquo;s Test Kitchen, Antiques Roadshow, Arthur, Barney &amp;amp; Friends, Clifford the Big Red Dog, Downton Abbey, Finding Your Roots, Frontline, The Magic School Bus, Masterpiece, Mister Rogers&amp;rsquo; Neighborhood, Nature, Nova, the PBS NewsHour, Sesame Street, Teletubbies, and This Old House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Univision Networks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/univision-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/univision-networks/</guid>
      <description> The graphic identification for this large Spanish-language television network features a bold abstract letter “U”, which, with the upper left quadrant turned, also suggests an exuberantly colorful bird.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>USA Today is an internationally distributed American daily, middle-market newspaper that serves as the flagship publication of its owner, the Gannett Company. The newspaper has a generally centrist audience.[3] Founded by Al Neuharth on September 15, 1982, it operates from Gannett&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters on Jones Branch Drive, in McLean, Virginia.[4] It is printed at 37 sites across the United States and at five additional sites internationally. Its dynamic design influenced the style of local, regional, and national newspapers worldwide, through its use of concise reports, colorized images, informational graphics, and inclusion of popular culture stories, among other distinct features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</guid>
      <description>Virgin Media Limited is a British company which provides telephone, television and internet services in the United Kingdom. Its headquarters are in Hook, Hampshire. Since 2013, Virgin Media has been a subsidiary of Liberty Global plc, an international television and telecommunications company. The company was previously listed on the NASDAQ Stock Market and London Stock Exchange. Virgin Media is not a sister company of Virgin Mobile USA, which is owned by Sprint Corporation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</guid>
      <description> The Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) is Australia&amp;rsquo;s national broadcaster founded in 1929. It is principally funded by the direct grants from the Australian government, but is expressly independent of government and partisan politics. The ABC plays a leading role in journalistic independence and is fundamental in the history of broadcasting in Australia.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</guid>
      <description>Discovery Channel is an American pay television network and flagship channel owned by Discovery, Inc., a publicly traded company run by CEO David Zaslav. As of June 2012, Discovery Channel is the third most widely distributed subscription channel in the United States, behind TBS and The Weather Channel; it is available in 409 million households worldwide, through its U.S. flagship channel and its various owned or licensed television channels internationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</guid>
      <description> Spotify Technology S.A. (/ˈspɒtɪfaɪ/) is a Swedish media-services provider founded in 2006. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its audio streaming platform that provides DRM-protected music and podcasts from record labels and media companies. As a freemium service, basic features are free with advertisements or automatic music videos, while additional features, such as improved streaming quality, are offered via paid subscriptions.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Music» is a music streaming service developed by Yandex. Users select musical compositions, albums, collections of musical tracks to stream to their device on demand and receive personalized recommendations. The service is also available as a mobile app with versions compatible with iOS, Android. Service is available in Russia, Belarus, Kyrgyzstan, Kazakhstan, Armenia, Israel. Paid subscription service is available in all the other countries of the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime Video</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prime-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:58:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prime-video/</guid>
      <description>About Amazon Prime Prime Video, also referred to as Amazon Prime Video, is an Internet video on demand service that is developed, owned, and operated by Amazon. It offers television shows and films for rent or purchase and Prime Video, a selection of Amazon Studios original content and licensed acquisitions included in the Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Prime subscription. In the UK, US, Germany, Sweden, and Austria, access to Prime Video is also available through a video-only membership, which does not require a full Prime subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kusi News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kusi-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:23:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kusi-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE ABC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kvue-abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:46:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kvue-abc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Records</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-records/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV Plus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</guid>
      <description>About Apple TV+ (from apple.com)
Introducing Apple TV+, a new streaming service where the most creative minds in TV and film tell the kinds of stories only they can. Featuring original shows and movies across every genre, Apple TV+ is coming this fall. Exclusively on the Apple TV app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>