<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>media on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in media on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beme</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beme/</guid>
      <description>Beme Inc. (/ˈbiːm/), stylized as beme, was a multimedia company founded by Matt Hackett and Casey Neistat, a vlogger and short film maker on YouTube. Beme Inc. was the creator of the mobile app, Beme. On November 28, 2016, CNN announced that it would acquire Beme. CNN intended to invest in the company and create a new brand focused on a young audience. The Beme app was officially shut down on January 31, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bloomberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bloomberg/</guid>
      <description> Bloomberg L.P. is a privately held financial, software, data, and media company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was founded by Michael Bloomberg in 1981, with the help of Thomas Secunda, Duncan MacMillan, Charles Zegar, and a 30% ownership investment by Merrill Lynch.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports 1 (FS1) is an American pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation.[1] FS1 replaced the motorsports network Speed on August 17, 2013, at the same time that its companion channel Fox Sports 2 replaced Fuel TV.[2] Both FS1 and FS2 absorbed most of the sports programming from its predecessors, as well as content from Fox Soccer, which was replaced by the entertainment-based channel FXX on September 2, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS2</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</guid>
      <description> Fox Sports 2 (FS2) is an American sports-oriented pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation. The channel is based at the Fox Sports division&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in the Westwood section of Los Angeles, California.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Corporation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Fox Corporation (abbreviated Fox Corp. and informally &amp;ldquo;New Fox&amp;rdquo;) is an American television broadcasting company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was formed from the 2019 acquisition of 21st Century Fox (itself formed from the 2013 split of News Corporation) by The Walt Disney Company. Fox Corp. was spun off from 21st Century Fox and its stock began trading on March 19, 2019. It is owned by the Murdoch family via a family trust with 39% interest; Rupert Murdoch is co-executive chairman, while his son Lachlan Murdoch is chairman and CEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports is the brand name for a number of sports channels, broadcast divisions, programming, and other media around the world that are either controlled or partially owned by the family of Rupert Murdoch. These assets are held mainly by Fox Corporation, with the exceptions of the operations in Australia, which are part of News Corp Australia and rest of the international Fox Sports channels and Fox Sports Networks which are owned by The Walt Disney Company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</guid>
      <description> Fox Television Stations, LLC (FTS; alternately Fox Television Stations Group, LLC), is a group of television stations located within the United States which are owned-and-operated by the Fox Broadcasting Company, a subsidiary of the Fox Corporation.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</guid>
      <description> Grupo Imagen is a Mexican media conglomerate, part of Grupo Empresarial Ángeles
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aol/</guid>
      <description> AOL (stylized as Aol., formerly a company known as AOL Inc. and originally known as America Online) is an American web portal and online service provider based in New York City. It is a brand marketed by Verizon Media.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>USA Today is an internationally distributed American daily, middle-market newspaper that serves as the flagship publication of its owner, the Gannett Company. The newspaper has a generally centrist audience.[3] Founded by Al Neuharth on September 15, 1982, it operates from Gannett&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters on Jones Branch Drive, in McLean, Virginia.[4] It is printed at 37 sites across the United States and at five additional sites internationally. Its dynamic design influenced the style of local, regional, and national newspapers worldwide, through its use of concise reports, colorized images, informational graphics, and inclusion of popular culture stories, among other distinct features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</guid>
      <description>Virgin Media Limited is a British company which provides telephone, television and internet services in the United Kingdom. Its headquarters are in Hook, Hampshire. Since 2013, Virgin Media has been a subsidiary of Liberty Global plc, an international television and telecommunications company. The company was previously listed on the NASDAQ Stock Market and London Stock Exchange. Virgin Media is not a sister company of Virgin Mobile USA, which is owned by Sprint Corporation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rotten Tomatoes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rotten-tomatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rotten-tomatoes/</guid>
      <description> Rotten Tomatoes is an American review-aggregation website for film and television. The company was launched in August 1998 by three undergraduate students at the University of California, Berkeley: Senh Duong, Patrick Y. Lee, and Stephen Wang.The name &amp;ldquo;Rotten Tomatoes&amp;rdquo; derives from the practice of audiences throwing rotten tomatoes when disapproving of a poor stage performance.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</guid>
      <description> The Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) is Australia&amp;rsquo;s national broadcaster founded in 1929. It is principally funded by the direct grants from the Australian government, but is expressly independent of government and partisan politics. The ABC plays a leading role in journalistic independence and is fundamental in the history of broadcasting in Australia.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</guid>
      <description>Discovery Channel is an American pay television network and flagship channel owned by Discovery, Inc., a publicly traded company run by CEO David Zaslav. As of June 2012, Discovery Channel is the third most widely distributed subscription channel in the United States, behind TBS and The Weather Channel; it is available in 409 million households worldwide, through its U.S. flagship channel and its various owned or licensed television channels internationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</guid>
      <description> Spotify Technology S.A. (/ˈspɒtɪfaɪ/) is a Swedish media-services provider founded in 2006. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its audio streaming platform that provides DRM-protected music and podcasts from record labels and media companies. As a freemium service, basic features are free with advertisements or automatic music videos, while additional features, such as improved streaming quality, are offered via paid subscriptions.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Music» is a music streaming service developed by Yandex. Users select musical compositions, albums, collections of musical tracks to stream to their device on demand and receive personalized recommendations. The service is also available as a mobile app with versions compatible with iOS, Android. Service is available in Russia, Belarus, Kyrgyzstan, Kazakhstan, Armenia, Israel. Paid subscription service is available in all the other countries of the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime Video</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prime-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:58:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prime-video/</guid>
      <description>About Amazon Prime Prime Video, also referred to as Amazon Prime Video, is an Internet video on demand service that is developed, owned, and operated by Amazon. It offers television shows and films for rent or purchase and Prime Video, a selection of Amazon Studios original content and licensed acquisitions included in the Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Prime subscription. In the UK, US, Germany, Sweden, and Austria, access to Prime Video is also available through a video-only membership, which does not require a full Prime subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kusi News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kusi-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:23:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kusi-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE ABC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kvue-abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:46:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kvue-abc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Records</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-records/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV Plus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</guid>
      <description>About Apple TV+ (from apple.com)
Introducing Apple TV+, a new streaming service where the most creative minds in TV and film tell the kinds of stories only they can. Featuring original shows and movies across every genre, Apple TV+ is coming this fall. Exclusively on the Apple TV app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>