<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>telecom on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/telecom/</link><description>Recent content in telecom on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0017</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon//file/verizon.svg</url><title>Verizon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Verizon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0017</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</guid><description turbo="true"> Verizon Communications Inc. is an American multinational telecommunications conglomerate and a corporate component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average. The company is based at 1095 Avenue of the Americas in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, but is incorporated in Delaware.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/att//file/att.svg</url><title>AT&amp;T Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AT&amp;T</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/att/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0014</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/att/</guid><description turbo="true">About AT&amp;amp;T AT&amp;amp;T Inc. began its history as Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, which was a subsidiary of the Bell Telephone Company founded by Alexander Graham Bell in 1880. Bell Telephone Company evolved into American Telephone and Telegraph Company in 1885 which had since rebranded to AT&amp;amp;T Corporation. Now AT&amp;amp;T Inc. is an American multinational conglomerate holding company, headquartered at Whitacre Tower in downtown Dallas, Texas. AT&amp;amp;T is the world’s largest telecommunications company.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/beeline//file/beeline.svg</url><title>Beeline Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Beeline</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/beeline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beeline/</guid><description turbo="true">Beeline (Russian: Билайн), earlier Bee Line GSM (Russian: Би Лайн GSM) is a telecommunications brand by company PJSC VimpelCom, founded in Russia.
PJSC VimpelCom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s third-largest wireless and second-largest telecommunications operator. Its headquarters is located in Moscow. Since 2009, PJSC VimpelCom has been a subsidiary of VimpelCom Ltd., which has become Veon in 2017. It is based in Amsterdam. VimpelCom&amp;rsquo;s main competitors in Russia are Mobile TeleSystems, MegaFon and Tele2.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/megafon//file/megafon.svg</url><title>MegaFon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MegaFon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/megafon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/megafon/</guid><description turbo="true">MegaFon (Russian: МегаФон), previously known as North-West GSM, is the second largest mobile phone operator and the third largest telecom operator in Russia. It works in the GSM, UMTS and LTE standard. As of June 2012, the company serves 62.1 million subscribers in Russia and 1.6 million in Tajikistan. It is headquartered in Moscow.
In 2002 the company changed its name from North-West GSM to MegaFon when it acquired several regional companies, becoming the first GSM company in Russia to cover all its territory.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tele2//file/tele2.svg</url><title>Tele2 Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tele2</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tele2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tele2/</guid><description turbo="true">Tele2 AB is a European telecommunications operator headquartered in the Kista Science City, Stockholm, Sweden. It is a major telephone operator in the Nordic and Baltic countries and an alternative provider in many others, with about 17 million customers in 8 countries and under franchise in 1 additional countries.
Tele2 started as a telecommunications company in Sweden in 1993 by the company Investment AB Kinnevik.
Tele2 operates in Sweden, Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania, the Netherlands, Croatia, Russia and Germany.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkcell//file/turkcell.svg</url><title>Turkcell Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Turkcell</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/turkcell/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkcell/</guid><description turbo="true"> Turkcell is the leading mobile phone operator of Turkey, based in Istanbul. The company has 34.4 million subscribers as of September 30, 2011. In 2015, the company&amp;rsquo;s number of subscribers climbed to 68.9 million, in nine countries Largest shareholder is Telia Finland Oyj with 51% ownership. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest companies (Fortune 2000) list published by Fortune.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar//file/brightstar.svg</url><title>Brightstar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Brightstar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar/</guid><description turbo="true">Brightstar Corp., an American privately held corporation founded in 1997, distributes mobile phones and other devices, serving more than 200 carriers, 40,000+ retailers, and 15,000+ enterprise customers in more than 100 countries. It provides specialized global wireless distribution and services, serving mobile device manufacturers, wireless operators and retailers. Brightstar offers value-added device and accessories distribution, supply chain, handset protection and insurance, buyback and trade-in and omnichannel retail, and mobile digital products within the wireless telecommunications industry.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast//file/comcast.svg</url><title>Comcast Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Comcast</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast/</guid><description turbo="true">Comcast Corporation (formerly registered as Comcast Holdings)[note 1] is an American telecommunications conglomerate headquartered in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. It is the second-largest broadcasting and cable television company in the world by revenue and the largest pay-TV company, the largest cable TV company and largest home Internet service provider in the United States, and the nation&amp;rsquo;s third-largest home telephone service provider. Comcast services U.S. residential and commercial customers in 40 states and in the District of Columbia.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle//file/crown-castle.svg</url><title>Crown Castle Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Crown Castle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle/</guid><description turbo="true">Crown Castle is a real estate investment trust and the largest provider of shared communications infrastructure in the United States, with more than 40,000 cell towers and approximately 70,000 route miles of fiber supporting small cells and fiber solutions.
Source s</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/docomo//file/docomo.svg</url><title>Docomo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Docomo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/docomo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/docomo/</guid><description turbo="true">NTT Docomo Inc. is the predominant mobile phone operator in Japan. The name is officially an abbreviation of the phrase, &amp;ldquo;do communications over the mobile network&amp;rdquo;, and is also from a compound word dokomo, meaning &amp;ldquo;everywhere&amp;rdquo; in Japanese. Docomo provides phone, video phone (FOMA and Some PHS), i-mode (internet), and mail (i-mode mail, Short Mail, and SMS) services. The company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in the Sanno Park Tower, Nagatachō, Chiyoda, Tokyo.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprint//file/sprint.svg</url><title>Sprint Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sprint</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sprint/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprint/</guid><description turbo="true">Sprint Corporation is an American telecommunications company that provides wireless services and is an internet service provider, based in Overland Park, Kansas. It is the fourth-largest mobile network operator in the United States and serves 54.3 million customers as of June 30, 2019. The company also offers wireless voice, messaging, and broadband services through its various subsidiaries under the Boost Mobile and Open Mobile brands and wholesale access to its wireless networks to mobile virtual network operators.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymobile//file/ymobile.svg</url><title>Ymobile Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ymobile</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ymobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymobile/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ymobile Corporation , stylized Y!mobile, is a subsidiary of Japanese telecommunications company SoftBank Group Corporation that provides mobile telecommunications and ADSL services. The current CEO of the company is Ken Miyauchi. It was formed in 2014 through the merger of Willcom and eAccess, and uses the Y! moniker brand from Yahoo! Japan, which is partly-owned by SoftBank.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone//file/vodafone.svg</url><title>Vodafone Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Vodafone</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</guid><description turbo="true"> Vodafone plc /ˈvoʊdəfoʊn/ is a British multinational telecommunications conglomerate with headquarters in London and Newbury, Berkshire. It predominantly operates services in the regions of Asia, Africa, Europe, and Oceania. Among mobile operator groups globally, Vodafone ranked 4th (behind China Mobile, Bharti Airtel and Vodafone Idea) in the number of mobile customers (313 million) as of 2018
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom//file/rostelecom.svg</url><title>Rostelecom Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Rostelecom</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</guid><description turbo="true"> Rostelecom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s leading long-distance telephony provider. Domestic long distance service provides about 50% of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue; and international long distance calls provide about 25%.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent//file/tencent.svg</url><title>Tencent Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tencent</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item></channel></rss>