<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>telecom on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/telecom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in telecom on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</guid>
      <description> Vodafone plc /ˈvoʊdəfoʊn/ is a British multinational telecommunications conglomerate with headquarters in London and Newbury, Berkshire. It predominantly operates services in the regions of Asia, Africa, Europe, and Oceania. Among mobile operator groups globally, Vodafone ranked 4th (behind China Mobile, Bharti Airtel and Vodafone Idea) in the number of mobile customers (313 million) as of 2018
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verizon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</guid>
      <description> Verizon Communications Inc. is an American multinational telecommunications conglomerate and a corporate component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average. The company is based at 1095 Avenue of the Americas in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, but is incorporated in Delaware.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rostelecom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</guid>
      <description> Rostelecom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s leading long-distance telephony provider. Domestic long distance service provides about 50% of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue; and international long distance calls provide about 25%.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/att/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/att/</guid>
      <description>About AT&amp;amp;T AT&amp;amp;T Inc. began its history as Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, which was a subsidiary of the Bell Telephone Company founded by Alexander Graham Bell in 1880. Bell Telephone Company evolved into American Telephone and Telegraph Company in 1885 which had since rebranded to AT&amp;amp;T Corporation. Now AT&amp;amp;T Inc. is an American multinational conglomerate holding company, headquartered at Whitacre Tower in downtown Dallas, Texas. AT&amp;amp;T is the world’s largest telecommunications company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tencent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>