<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spain on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/spain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spain on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/spain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barcelona-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barcelona-fc/</guid>
      <description> Futbol Club Barcelona (Catalan pronunciation: fubˈbɔl ˈklub bəɾsəˈlonə), commonly referred to as Barcelona and colloquially known as Barça , is a Spanish professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1988 Barcelona</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1988-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1988-barcelona/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iberia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iberia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iberia/</guid>
      <description>Iberia is the flag carrier airline of Spain, founded in 1927. Based in Madrid, it operates an international network of services from its main base of Madrid-Barajas Airport. Iberia, with Iberia Regional (operated by an independent carrier Air Nostrum) and with Iberia Express, is a part of Iberia Group. In addition to transporting passengers and freight, Iberia Group carries out related activities, such as aircraft maintenance, handling in airports, IT systems and in-flight catering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santander</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/santander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/santander/</guid>
      <description>Banco Santander, S.A., doing business as Santander Group (/ˌsɑːntɑːnˈdɛər/), is a Spanish multinational commercial bank and financial services company founded and based in Santander, Spain. In addition to hubs in Madrid and Barcelona, Santander maintains a presence in all global financial centres as the largest Spanish banking institution in the world. Although known for its European banking operations, it has extended operations across North and South America, and more recently in continental Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zara</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</guid>
      <description>Zara SA is a Spanish fast fashion (clothing and accessories) Retail based in Arteixo (A Coruña) in Galicia. The company was founded in 1975 by Amancio Ortega and Rosalía Mera. It is the main brand of the Inditex group, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel Retail. The fashion group also owns brands such as Massimo Dutti, Pull&amp;amp;Bear, Bershka, Stradivarius, Oysho, Zara Home, and Uterqüe. Zara as of 2017 manages up to 20 clothing collections a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria, S.A. (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈbaŋko βilˈβao βiθˈkaʝa aɾxenˈtaɾja]), better known by its initialism BBVA, is a multinational Spanish banking group based in Madrid and Bilbao. It is one of the largest financial institutions in the world, and is present mainly in Spain, North America, South America and Turkey.
 The bank was founded as Banco de Bilbao, on May 28, 1857 in Bilbao, Biscay, where it has been headquartered since then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>