<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nonprofit on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/nonprofit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nonprofit on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/nonprofit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FIFA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fifa/</guid>
      <description>The Fédération Internationale de Football Association (FIFA /ˈfiːfə/ FEE-fə; French for &amp;lsquo;International Federation of Association Football&amp;rsquo;; Spanish: Federación Internacional de Fútbol Asociación; German: Internationaler Verband des Association Football) is a non-profit organization which describes itself as an international governing body of association football, fútsal, beach soccer, and efootball. It is the highest governing body of football.
 FIFA was founded in 1904 to oversee international competition among the national associations of Belgium, Denmark, France, Germany, the Netherlands, Spain, Sweden, and Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resolve</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/resolve/</guid>
      <description> RESOLVE is a non-profit, 501(c)(3) organization certified under the National Health Council Standards of Excellence and America’s Best Charities as well as earned the Guidestar Gold Seal of Transparency.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Appeal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</guid>
      <description> Human Appeal is a British international development and relief charity based in Manchester. It was established in 1991. It runs targeted poverty relief programmes in emergency response and sustainable development. In the past, the charity was known as Human Appeal International but was restyled in 2018. It is now known as Human Appeal.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelter</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shelter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shelter/</guid>
      <description>Shelter is a registered charity that campaigns to end homelessness and bad housing in England and Scotland. It gives advice, information and advocacy to people in need, and tackles the root causes of bad housing by lobbying government and local authorities for new laws and policies to improve the lives of homeless and badly housed people. It works in partnership with Shelter Cymru in Wales and the Housing Rights Service in Northern Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach First</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/teach-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/teach-first/</guid>
      <description> Teach First is a social enterprise registered as a charity which aims to address educational disadvantage in England and Wales. Teach First coordinates an employment-based teaching training programme whereby participants achieve Qualified Teacher Status through the participation in a two-year training programme that involves the completion of a PGDE along with wider leadership skills training and an optional master&amp;rsquo;s degree.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</guid>
      <description> The organization offers the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) designation, the Certificate in Investment Performance Measurement (CIPM) designation, and the Investment Foundations Certificate. It provides continuing education conferences, seminars, webcasts, and publications to allow members and other participants to stay current on developments in the investment industry. CFA Institute also oversees the CFA Institute Research Challenge for university students and the Research Foundation of CFA Institute.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</guid>
      <description> Conservation International (CI) is an American nonprofit environmental organization headquartered in Arlington, Virginia. Its goal is to protect nature as a source of food, fresh water, livelihoods and a stable climate.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epa/</guid>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is an independent agency[dubious – discuss] of the United States federal government for environmental protection. President Richard Nixon proposed the establishment of EPA on July 9, 1970 and it began operation on December 2, 1970, after Nixon signed an executive order. The order establishing the EPA was ratified by committee hearings in the House and Senate. The agency is led by its Administrator, who is appointed by the President and approved by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mercy For Animals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercy-for-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercy-for-animals/</guid>
      <description> Mercy For Animals (MFA) is an international nonprofit animal protection organization founded in 1999 by Milo Runkle. MFA’s mission is to “prevent cruelty to farmed animals and promote compassionate food choices and policies.”
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Visions</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-visions/</guid>
      <description>Launched in 1989, New Visions for Public Schools has become one of New York City’s largest educational nonprofits, supporting schools, training teachers, and operating a growing network of charter schools. The three bars of the new visual identity suggest growth, dynamism, the letter V, and climbing steps. It is simple enough to work everywhere, while standing out from the field of educational logos. To underscore the organization’s commitment to working within the public school system, Chermayeff &amp;amp; Geismar &amp;amp; Haviv gave all the words in the name equal emphasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oceano Azul Foundation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oceano-azul-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oceano-azul-foundation/</guid>
      <description>The Oceano Azul Foundation is an international organization founded by the Sociedade Francisco Manuel dos Santos and based in Portugal with the mission of contributing to the sustainability of a healthy and productive ocean. Combining scientific study, political and economic activism, together with a deep ethical commitment, the Foundation integrates many human perspectives to “look at the planet’s sustainability from the ocean’s point of view.” The Oceano Azul Foundation manages the Oceanário de Lisboa, for which Chermayeff &amp;amp; Geismar &amp;amp; Haviv designed the visual identity, as well as major tile murals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNDP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</guid>
      <description> The United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) is the United Nations&amp;rsquo; global development network. It advocates for change and connects countries to knowledge, experience and resources to help people build a better life for themselves. It provides expert advice, training and grants support to developing countries, with increasing emphasis on assistance to the least developed countries. It promotes technical and investment cooperation among nations.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Bicentennial</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-bicentennial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-bicentennial/</guid>
      <description> The United States Bicentennial was a series of celebrations and observances during the mid-1970s that paid tribute to historical events leading up to the creation of the United States of America as an independent republic. It was a central event in the memory of the American Revolution. The Bicentennial culminated on Sunday, July 4, 1976, with the 200th anniversary of the adoption of the Declaration of Independence.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eff/</guid>
      <description> The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is an international non-profit digital rights group based in San Francisco, California. The foundation was formed in July 1990 by John Gilmore, John Perry Barlow and Mitch Kapor to promote Internet civil liberties.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBB</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbb/</guid>
      <description> The Better Business Bureau, founded in 1912, is an organization focused on advancing marketplace trust, consisting of 106 independently incorporated local BBB organizations in the United States and Canada, coordinated under the Council of Better Business Bureaus in Arlington, Virginia.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>