<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>liquors on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/liquors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in liquors on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/liquors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Budweiser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/budweiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/budweiser/</guid>
      <description>Budweiser is an American-style pale lager produced by Anheuser-Busch, currently part of the transnational corporation Anheuser-Busch InBev and produced in various breweries around the world. There is an unrelated lager also called Budweiser, originating centuries ago in Budweis, Bohemia and made by Budweiser Budvar Brewery of České Budějovice, Czech Republic; this has given rise to a trademark dispute preventing Anheuser-Busch from using the &amp;ldquo;Budweiser&amp;rdquo; name in some regions, leading to the exclusive use of &amp;ldquo;Bud&amp;rdquo; in those markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Extra</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra/</guid>
      <description>Corona Extra is a pale lager produced by Cervecería Modelo in Mexico for domestic distribution and export to all other countries besides the United States, and by Constellation Brands in Mexico for export to the United States. The Corona brand is one of the top-selling beers worldwide. Outside Mexico, Corona is commonly served with a wedge of lime or lemon in the neck of the bottle to add tartness and flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heineken</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken/</guid>
      <description> Heineken Lager Beer is a pale lager beer with 5% alcohol by volume produced by the Dutch brewing company Heineken International. Heineken is well known for its signature green bottle and red star.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Daniels</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jack-daniels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jack-daniels/</guid>
      <description> Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s is a brand of Tennessee whiskey and the top-selling American whiskey in the world. It is produced in Lynchburg, Tennessee, by the Jack Daniel Distillery, which has been owned by the Brown–Forman Corporation since 1956. Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s home county of Moore is a dry county, so the product is not available for purchase at stores or restaurants within the county.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>