<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>liquors on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/liquors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in liquors on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/liquors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Molson Coors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors/</guid>
      <description>The Molson Coors Beverage Company is a multinational brewing company, formed in 2005 by the merger of Molson of Canada, and Coors of the United States. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s seventh largest brewer by volume.
 While the company is incorporated in the United States, it is traded on stock exchanges in both the United States and Canada, and control is equally shared between the Molson and Coors families. The company is headquartered at 1801 California Street, a 1,372,179-square-foot (127,479.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asahi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi/</guid>
      <description>Asahi Group Holdings, Ltd. is a global beer, spirits, soft drinks and food business group headquartered in Tokyo, Japan.
 In 2018, the group had a revenue JPY 2.1 trillion. Asahi&amp;rsquo;s revenue can be segmented as follows: alcoholic beverage business (41.3%), overseas business (32%), soft drinks business (16.6%), food business (5.2%) and &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; business (4.9%). Asahi, with a 37% market share, is the largest of the four major beer brewers in Japan followed by Kirin Beer with 34% and Suntory with 16%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kirin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kirin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kirin/</guid>
      <description> Kirin Company, Limited is an integrated beverages company. It is a subsidiary of Kirin Holdings Company, Limited. Its major operating units include Kirin Brewery Company, Limited, Mercian Corporation and Kirin Beverages Company, Limited. Kirin is a member of the Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group (MUFG) keiretsu.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schiotz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/schiotz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/schiotz/</guid>
      <description> A common interest in good beet was a vital element in the brewery’s history. And that was the special ingredient that made Albani into one of the most important breweries of the day with interesting recipes and skilled, dedicated brewery workers as the crucial factors.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diageo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diageo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diageo/</guid>
      <description> Diageo plc is a British multinational alcoholic beverages company, with its headquarters in London, England and offices on six continents. It was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest distiller until being overtaken by China&amp;rsquo;s Kweichow Moutai on 9 April 2017.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guinness</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/guinness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/guinness/</guid>
      <description>Guinness is a dark Irish dry stout that originated in the brewery of Arthur Guinness at St. James&amp;rsquo;s Gate, Dublin, Ireland, in 1759. It is one of the most successful beer brands worldwide, brewed in almost 50 countries, and available in over 120. Sales in 2011 amounted to 850 million litres (220,000,000 US gal). It is popular with the Irish, both in Ireland and abroad. In spite of declining consumption since 2001, it is still the best-selling alcoholic drink in Ireland where Guinness &amp;amp; Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimism Brewing</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/optimism-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/optimism-brewing/</guid>
      <description>Optimism is a brewery founded by husband and wife Troy Hakala and Gay Gilmore in 2013. It took more than a year to secure a location for the brewery and rehabilitation on the 100 year old warehouse took almost two years. Optimism is located in the Capitol Hill neighborhood of Seattle at the corner of Broadway and E Union Street (Map). The brewery opened and we served our first beers on December 5, 2015 (the anniversary of the Repeal of Prohibition).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smirnoff</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smirnoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smirnoff/</guid>
      <description>Smirnoff is a brand of vodka owned and produced by the British company Diageo. The Smirnoff brand began with a vodka distillery founded in Moscow by Pyotr Arsenievich Smirnov (1831–1898). It is now distributed in 130 countries[citation needed] and produced in several countries including Albania, Brazil, Honduras, India, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Mongolia, the Philippines, the United Kingdom and the United States[citation needed]. Smirnoff products include vodka, flavoured vodka, and malt beverages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hennessy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy/</guid>
      <description> Jas Hennessy &amp;amp; Co., commonly known simply as Hennessy, is a brandy distiller with its headquarters located in Cognac, France. Jas Hennessy &amp;amp; Co. sells about 50 million bottles a year worldwide, or more than 40 percent of the world&amp;rsquo;s cognac, making it the largest cognac producer.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnnie Walker</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker/</guid>
      <description> Johnnie Walker is a brand of Scotch whisky now owned by Diageo that originated in the Scottish town of Kilmarnock, East Ayrshire. The brand was first established by grocer John Walker. It is the most widely distributed brand of blended Scotch whisky in the world, sold in almost every country, with annual sales of the equivalent of over 223.7 million 700 ml bottles in 2016 (156.6 million litres)
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sapporo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sapporo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sapporo/</guid>
      <description> Sapporo Breweries Ltd. (サッポロビール株式会社 Sapporo Bīru Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese beer brewing company founded in 1876. Sapporo is the oldest brand of beer in Japan. It was first brewed in Sapporo, Japan, in 1876 by brewer Seibei Nakagawa. The world headquarters of Sapporo Breweries is in Ebisu, Shibuya, Tokyo. The company purchased the Canadian company Sleeman Breweries in 2006.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budweiser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/budweiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/budweiser/</guid>
      <description>Budweiser is an American-style pale lager produced by Anheuser-Busch, currently part of the transnational corporation Anheuser-Busch InBev and produced in various breweries around the world. There is an unrelated lager also called Budweiser, originating centuries ago in Budweis, Bohemia and made by Budweiser Budvar Brewery of České Budějovice, Czech Republic; this has given rise to a trademark dispute preventing Anheuser-Busch from using the &amp;ldquo;Budweiser&amp;rdquo; name in some regions, leading to the exclusive use of &amp;ldquo;Bud&amp;rdquo; in those markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Extra</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra/</guid>
      <description>Corona Extra is a pale lager produced by Cervecería Modelo in Mexico for domestic distribution and export to all other countries besides the United States, and by Constellation Brands in Mexico for export to the United States. The Corona brand is one of the top-selling beers worldwide. Outside Mexico, Corona is commonly served with a wedge of lime or lemon in the neck of the bottle to add tartness and flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heineken</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken/</guid>
      <description> Heineken Lager Beer is a pale lager beer with 5% alcohol by volume produced by the Dutch brewing company Heineken International. Heineken is well known for its signature green bottle and red star.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Daniels</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jack-daniels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jack-daniels/</guid>
      <description> Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s is a brand of Tennessee whiskey and the top-selling American whiskey in the world. It is produced in Lynchburg, Tennessee, by the Jack Daniel Distillery, which has been owned by the Brown–Forman Corporation since 1956. Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s home county of Moore is a dry county, so the product is not available for purchase at stores or restaurants within the county.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>