<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Italy on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/italy/</link><description>Recent content in Italy on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/italy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Off White</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/off-white/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/off-white/</guid><description>Off-White (stylized as OFF-WHITE c/o VIRGIL ABLOH) is an Italian luxury fashion label founded by American designer Virgil Abloh The company was incorporated in Milan in 2012.
The label has collaborated with Nike, Levi, Jimmy Choo, IKEA and Évian.
Source About Off White OFF-WHITE c/o VIRGIL ABLOH™ is a fashion label rooted in current culture at a taste-level particular to now. With a specific opinion and not necessarily same with vision seasonal men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s collections are offered.</description></item><item><title>Versace</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/versace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versace/</guid><description>Gianni Versace , usually referred to simply as Versace, is an Italian luxury fashion company and trade name founded by Gianni Versace in 1978. The main collection of the brand is Versace, which produces upmarket Italian-made ready-to-wear and leather accessories. The Versace logo is the head of Medusa, a Greek mythological figure. The logo came from the floor of ruins in the area of Reggio Calabria that the Versace siblings played in as children.</description></item><item><title>Ferrari</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ferrari/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ferrari/</guid><description>Ferrari is an Italian luxury sports car manufacturer based in Maranello. Founded by Enzo Ferrari in 1939 out of Alfa Romeo&amp;rsquo;s race division as Auto Avio Costruzioni, the company built its first car in 1940. However, the company&amp;rsquo;s inception as an auto manufacturer is usually recognized in 1947, when the first Ferrari-badged car was completed.
In 2014 Ferrari was rated the world&amp;rsquo;s most powerful brand by Brand Finance. In June 2018, the 1964 250 GTO became the most expensive car in history, setting an all-time record selling price of $70 million.</description></item><item><title>Maserati</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/maserati/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/maserati/</guid><description>Maserati is an Italian luxury vehicle manufacturer. Established on 1 December 1914, in Bologna, Italy, the company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are now in Modena, and its emblem is a trident. The company has been owned by FIAT Chrysler Automobiles (FCA) and FCA&amp;rsquo;s Italian predecessor FIAT S.p.A. since 1993. Maserati was initially associated with Ferrari. In May 2014, due to ambitious plans and product launches, Maserati sold a record of over 3,000 cars in one month.</description></item><item><title>Eni</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</guid><description>Eni S.p.A. is an Italian multinational oil and gas company headquartered in Rome. Considered one of the global supermajors, it has operations in 79 countries, and is currently world&amp;rsquo;s 11th largest industrial company with a market capitalization of 68 billion euros (US$ 90 billion), as of August 14, 2013 The Italian government owns a 30.303% golden share in the company, 3.934% held through the state Treasury and 26.369% held through the Cassa Depositi e Prestiti.</description></item><item><title>Enel</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</guid><description> Enel S.p.A., or the Enel Group, is an Italian multinational energy company that is active in the sectors of electricity generation and distribution, as well as in the distribution of natural gas.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>Prada</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prada/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prada/</guid><description> Prada S.p.A. is an Italian luxury fashion house, specializing in leather handbags, travel accessories, shoes, ready-to-wear, perfumes and other fashion accessories, founded in 1913 by Mario Prada.
Source</description></item><item><title>F1</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/f1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/f1/</guid><description>Formula One (also Formula 1 or F1) is the highest class of single-seater auto racing sanctioned by the Fédération Internationale de l&amp;rsquo;Automobile (FIA) and owned by the Formula One Group. The FIA Formula One World Championship has been one of the premier forms of racing around the world since its inaugural season in 1950. The word &amp;ldquo;formula&amp;rdquo; in the name refers to the set of rules to which all participants&amp;rsquo; cars must conform.</description></item><item><title>Fiat</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fiat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fiat/</guid><description> Fiat Automobiles is an Italian automobile manufacturer, a subsidiary of FCA Italy S.p.A., which is part of Fiat Chrysler Automobiles (previously Fiat S.p.A.). Fiat Automobiles was formed in January 2007 when Fiat reorganized its automobile business, and traces its history back to 1899 when the first Fiat automobile, the Fiat 4 HP, was produced.
Source</description></item><item><title>Gucci</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gucci/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gucci/</guid><description> Gucci is an Italian luxury brand of fashion and leather goods. Gucci was founded by Guccio Gucci in Florence, Tuscany, in 1921. Gucci generated about €4.2 billion in revenue worldwide in 2008 according to BusinessWeek and climbed to 41st position in the magazine&amp;rsquo;s annual 2009 &amp;ldquo;Top Global 100 Brands&amp;rdquo; chart created by Interbrand; it retained that rank in Interbrand&amp;rsquo;s 2014 index. Gucci is also the highest-selling Italian brand.
Source</description></item><item><title>Lamborghini</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lamborghini/</guid><description> Automobili Lamborghini is an Italian brand and manufacturer of luxury sports cars and SUVs based in Sant&amp;rsquo;Agata Bolognese and tractors Lamborghini Trattori in Pieve di Cento, Italy. The company is owned by the Volkswagen Group through its subsidiary Audi.
Source</description></item></channel></rss>