<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>education on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/education/</link><description>Recent content in education on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/udemy//file/udemy.svg</url><title>Udemy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Udemy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/udemy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/udemy/</guid><description turbo="true">Udemy, Inc. is an American massive open online course (MOOC) provider aimed at professional adults and students. It was founded in May 2010 by Eren Bali, Gagan Biyani, and Oktay Caglar.
As of Jan 2020, the platform has more than 35 million students and 57,000 instructors teaching courses in over 65 languages. There have been over 400 million course enrollments. Students and instructors come from 180+ countries and 2/3 of the students are located outside of the U.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/duolingo//file/duolingo.svg</url><title>Duolingo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Duolingo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/duolingo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/duolingo/</guid><description turbo="true">Duolingo is an American platform that includes a language-learning website and mobile app, as well as a digital language-proficiency assessment exam. The company uses the freemium model; the app and the website are accessible without charge, although Duolingo also offers a premium service for a fee.
As of November 2019 the language-learning website and app offer 94 different language courses in 23 languages. The app has over 300 million registered users across the world.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/oreilly-media//file/oreilly-media.svg</url><title>OReilly Media Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">OReilly Media</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/oreilly-media/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oreilly-media/</guid><description turbo="true">O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media (formerly O&amp;rsquo;Reilly &amp;amp; Associates) is an American learning company established by Tim O&amp;rsquo;Reilly that publishes books, produces tech conferences, and provides an online learning platform. Their distinctive brand features a woodcut of an animal on many of their book covers.
Source About O’Reilly O’Reilly’s mission is to change the world by sharing the knowledge of innovators. For over 40 years, we’ve inspired companies and individuals to do new things—and do things better—by providing them with the skills and understanding that’s necessary for success.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-peter-university//file/st-peter-university.svg</url><title>St Peter University Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">St Peter University</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/st-peter-university/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-peter-university/</guid><description turbo="true"> Saint Peter&amp;rsquo;s University is a private Jesuit university in Jersey City, New Jersey. It was founded as Saint Peter&amp;rsquo;s College in 1872 by the Society of Jesus. It offers over 60 undergraduate and graduate programs to more than 2,600 undergraduate and 800 graduate students. Its college mascot is the Peacock and its sports teams play in the Metro Atlantic Athletic Conference, of which it is a founding member.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh//file/hmh.svg</url><title>HMH Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HMH</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</guid><description turbo="true"> Houghton Mifflin Harcourt is a publisher of textbooks, instructional technology materials, assessments, reference works, and fiction and non-fiction for both young readers and adults.
Source Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford//file/nexford.svg</url><title>Nexford Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nexford</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</guid><description turbo="true"> Nexford University is a private for-profit online university headquartered in Washington, DC. It was founded in 2018 by Fadl Al Tarzi. The University offers programs through the process of online distance learning. Nexford is licensed to issue degrees by the Higher Education Licensure Commission (HELC) in Washington DC. Nexford is accredited by ASIC, an UK-based International accreditation agency operating in 60+ countries.
Source Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge//file/university-of-cambridge.svg</url><title>University of Cambridge Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">University of Cambridge</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</guid><description turbo="true">The University of Cambridge (legally The Chancellor, Masters, and Scholars of the University of Cambridge) is a collegiate public research university in Cambridge, United Kingdom. Founded in 1209 and granted a royal charter by King Henry III in 1231, Cambridge is the second-oldest university in the English-speaking world and the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-oldest surviving university. The university grew out of an association of scholars who left the University of Oxford after a dispute with the townspeople.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown//file/brown.svg</url><title>Brown Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Brown</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</guid><description turbo="true"> Brown University is a private Ivy League research university in Providence, Rhode Island. Founded in 1764 as the College in the English Colony of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, it is the seventh-oldest institution of higher education in the United States and one of the nine colonial colleges chartered before the American Revolution.
Source Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bu//file/bu.svg</url><title>BU Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">BU</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bu/</guid><description turbo="true"> Boston University (commonly referred to as BU) is a private research university in Boston, Massachusetts. The university is nonsectarian, but has been historically affiliated with the United Methodist Church.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell//file/cornell.svg</url><title>Cornell Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cornell</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</guid><description turbo="true">Cornell University (/kɔːrˈnɛl/ kor-NEL) is a private and statutory Ivy League research university in Ithaca, New York. Founded in 1865 by Ezra Cornell and Andrew Dickson White, the university was intended to teach and make contributions in all fields of knowledge—from the classics to the sciences, and from the theoretical to the applied. These ideals, unconventional for the time, are captured in Cornell&amp;rsquo;s founding principle, a popular 1868 Ezra Cornell quotation: &amp;ldquo;I would found an institution where any person can find instruction in any study.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero//file/course-hero.svg</url><title>Course Hero Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Course Hero</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</guid><description turbo="true">Course Hero is an education technology website company based in Redwood City, California, which operates an online learning platform for students to access course-specific study resources contributed by a community of students and educators. The crowdsourced learning platform contains practice problems, study guides, infographics, class notes, step-by-step explanations, essays, lab reports, videos, user-submitted questions paired with answers from tutors, and original materials created and uploaded by educators. Users either buy a subscription or upload original documents to receive unlocks that are used to view and download full Course Hero documents.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/csu//file/csu.svg</url><title>CSU Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CSU</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/csu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/csu/</guid><description turbo="true"> Colorado State University (also referred to as Colorado State, State, and CSU) is a public research university in Fort Collins, Colorado. The university is the state&amp;rsquo;s land grant university and the flagship university of the Colorado State University System.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mit//file/mit.svg</url><title>MIT Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MIT</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mit/</guid><description turbo="true">The Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) is a private research university in Cambridge, Massachusetts. The Institute is a land-grant, sea-grant, and space-grant university, with an urban campus that extends more than a mile (1.6 km) alongside the Charles River. The Institute also encompasses a number of major off-campus facilities such as the MIT Lincoln Laboratory, the Bates Center, and the Haystack Observatory, as well as affiliated laboratories such as the Broad and Whitehead Institutes.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu//file/nyu.svg</url><title>NYU Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NYU</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu/</guid><description turbo="true"> New York University (NYU) is a private research university based in New York City. Founded in 1831, NYU&amp;rsquo;s historical campus is in Greenwich Village, Lower Manhattan. NYU also has degree-granting campuses in Abu Dhabi and Shanghai, and academic centers in Accra, Berlin, Buenos Aires, Florence, London, Los Angeles, Madrid, Paris, Prague, Sydney, Tel Aviv, and Washington, D.C.
Source Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/open-english//file/open-english.svg</url><title>Open English Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Open English</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/open-english/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/open-english/</guid><description turbo="true"> Open English is an online English school with headquarters in Coconut Grove, Florida. In 2014, the school had 100,000 students in the Spanish speaking world.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts//file/tufts.svg</url><title>Tufts Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tufts</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts/</guid><description turbo="true">Tufts University is a private research university in Medford and Somerville, Massachusetts. A charter member of the New England Small College Athletic Conference (NESCAC), Tufts College was founded in 1852 by Christian universalists who worked for years to open a nonsectarian institution of higher learning. It was a small New England liberal arts college until its transformation into a larger research university in the 1970s. The university emphasizes active citizenship and public service in all its disciplines, and is known for its internationalism and study abroad programs</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh//file/unh.svg</url><title>UNH Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">UNH</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</guid><description turbo="true"> The University of New Hampshire (UNH) is a public research university with its main campus in Durham, New Hampshire. It was founded and incorporated in 1866 as a land grant college in Hanover in connection with Dartmouth College. In 1893, UNH moved to Durham.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio//file/universidad-tecmilenio.svg</url><title>Universidad Tecmilenio Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Universidad Tecmilenio</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</guid><description turbo="true">The Universidad TecMilenio (UTM) (TecMilenio University) is a private institution of higher education. The institution is part of Monterrey Institute of Technology and Higher Education TecMilenio University ITESM System, an educational system with national and international levels, through 30 campus and an online campus with a unique and innovative educational model that forms professionals with the skills needed by modern businesses and organizations. For-profit schools that have entered the country in recent years, the university serves some 21,000 students on its own at high school, undergraduate and postgraduate level, frequently through distance learning.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy//file/codecademy.svg</url><title>Codecademy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Codecademy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy/</guid><description turbo="true"> Codecademy is an online interactive platform that offers free coding classes in 12 different programming languages including Python, Java, JavaScript (jQuery, AngularJS, React.js), Ruby, SQL, C++, and Sass, as well as markup languages HTML and CSS. The site also offers a paid &amp;ldquo;pro&amp;rdquo; option that gives users access to a personalized learning plan, quizzes, realistic projects, and live help from advisors.[
Source Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca//file/ymca.svg</url><title>YMCA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">YMCA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</guid><description turbo="true"> YMCA, sometimes regionally called the Y, is a worldwide organisation based in Geneva, Switzerland, with more than 64 million beneficiaries from 120 national associations. It was founded on 6 June 1844 by Sir George Williams in London, originally as the Young Men&amp;rsquo;s Christian Association and aims to put Christian principles into practice by developing a healthy &amp;ldquo;body, mind, and spirit&amp;rdquo;.
Source Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university//file/northwestern-university.svg</url><title>Northwestern University Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Northwestern University</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university/</guid><description turbo="true"/>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school//file/harvard-medical-school.svg</url><title>Harvard Medical School Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harvard Medical School</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school/</guid><description turbo="true">About Harvard Medical School (from harvard.edu)
Established in 1782, Harvard Medical School began with a handful of students and a faculty of three. The first classes were held in Harvard Hall in Cambridge, long before the School’s iconic quadrangle was built in Boston. With each passing decade, the School’s faculty and trainees amassed knowledge and influence, shaping medicine in the United States and beyond. Some community members—and their accomplishments—have assumed the status of legend.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university//file/harvard-university.svg</url><title>Harvard University Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harvard University</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university/</guid><description turbo="true">About Harvard Univarsity (from wikipedia.org)
Harvard University Coat of Arms Harvard University is a private Ivy League research university in Cambridge, Massachusetts, with about 6,700 undergraduate students and about 15,250 postgraduate students. Established in 1636 and named for its first benefactor, clergyman John Harvard, Harvard is the United States&amp;rsquo; oldest institution of higher learning. Its history, influence, and wealth have made it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prestigious universities.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item></channel></rss>