<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Korea on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/korea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Korea on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/korea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinsegae</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</guid>
      <description> Shinsegae (Korean: 신세계, KRX: 004170) is a South Korean department store franchise, along with several other businesses, headquartered in Seoul, South Korea. The name Shinsegae literally means &amp;ldquo;New World&amp;rdquo; in Korean. Its flagship store in Centum City, Busan, was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest department store at 3,163,000 square feet (293,900 m2), surpassing Macy&amp;rsquo;s flagship Herald Square in New York City in 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1984 Seoul</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1984-seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1984-seoul/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doosan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</guid>
      <description> Doosan Group is a South Korean conglomerate company. In 2009, the company was placed 471st in the Fortune Global 500. It has been included in the Forbes Global 2000 companies from 2007.[citation needed] It is the parent company of ŠKODA power. Doosan was ranked 4th among the “World&amp;rsquo;s Best 40 Companies 2009” list, released in the latest issue of BusinessWeek, the U.S. economics magazine in October 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</guid>
      <description> The Hyundai Motor Company, is a South Korean multinational automotive manufacturer headquartered in Seoul. The company was founded in 1967 and, along with its 32.8% owned subsidiary, Kia Motors, and its 100% owned luxury subsidiary Genesis Motor, altogether comprise the Hyundai Motor Group. It is the third largest vehicle manufacturer in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kia/</guid>
      <description>Kia Motors Corporation, headquartered in Seoul, is South Korea&amp;rsquo;s second-largest automobile manufacturer, following the Hyundai Motor Company, with sales of over 3.3 million vehicles in 2015. As of December 2015, the Kia Motor Corporation is minority owned by Hyundai, which owns a 33.88% stake valued at just over US$6 billion. Kia in turn is a minority owner of more than twenty Hyundai subsidiaries ranging from 4.9% up to 45.37%, totaling more than US$8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/samsung/</guid>
      <description> Samsung is a South Korean multinational conglomerate headquartered in Samsung Town, Seoul. It comprises numerous affiliated businesses, most of them united under the Samsung brand, and is the largest South Korean chaebol (business conglomerate).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>