<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>2014 on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/year/2014/</link><description>Recent content in 2014 on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate//file/minergate.svg</url><title>MinerGate Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MinerGate</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate/</guid><description turbo="true"> MinerGate is one of the largest multicurrency mining pools, where users join resources to get a share of profits. The project was started in 2014 by a group of blockchain enthusiasts, led by Claude Lecomte. MinerGate operates with 10 coins and supports 4 major mining algorithms.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum//file/ethereum.svg</url><title>Ethereum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ethereum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ethereum is an open source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform and operating system featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It supports a modified version of Nakamoto consensus via transaction-based state transitions. Ether is a cryptocurrency generated by the Ethereum platform and used to compensate mining nodes for computations performed. Each Ethereum account has an ether balance and ether may be transferred from one account to another.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk//file/gsk.svg</url><title>GSK Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">GSK</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</guid><description turbo="true"> GlaxoSmithKline plc (GSK) is a British multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Brentford, London. Established in 2000 by a merger of Glaxo Wellcome and SmithKline Beecham, GSK was the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth largest pharmaceutical company as of 2015, after Pfizer, Novartis, Merck, Hoffmann-La Roche and Sanofi.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets//file/charlotte-hornets.svg</url><title>Charlotte Hornets Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Charlotte Hornets</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Charlotte Hornets are an American professional basketball team based in Charlotte, North Carolina. The Hornets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Southeast Division. The team is largely owned by retired NBA player Michael Jordan, who acquired controlling interest in the team in 2010. The Hornets play their home games at the Spectrum Center in Uptown Charlotte.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/orlando-city-sc//file/orlando-city-sc.svg</url><title>Orlando City SC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Orlando City SC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/orlando-city-sc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/orlando-city-sc/</guid><description turbo="true"> Orlando City Soccer Club is an American professional soccer club in Orlando, Florida, that competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS). Orlando City SC began play in 2015 as an expansion team and is the first MLS franchise in the state since Miami Fusion and Tampa Bay Mutiny folded following the 2001 season. The team plays at Exploria Stadium in Downtown Orlando.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes//file/sj-earthquakes.svg</url><title>SJ Earthquakes Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">SJ Earthquakes</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes/</guid><description turbo="true">The San Jose Earthquakes are an American professional soccer team based in San Jose, California, United States, that competes as a member of the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The franchise began play in 1996 (originally as the San Jose Clash) as one of the charter clubs of the league. The Earthquakes took part in the first game in MLS history, defeating D.C. United 1–0. The Earthquakes have won two MLS Cup titles, in 2001 and 2003, and two Supporters&amp;rsquo; Shields in 2005 and 2012.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians//file/cleveland-indians.svg</url><title>Cleveland Indians Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cleveland Indians</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians/</guid><description turbo="true">The Cleveland Indians are an American professional baseball team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Indians compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) Central division. Since 1994, they have played at Progressive Field. The team&amp;rsquo;s spring training facility is at Goodyear Ballpark in Goodyear, Arizona. Since their establishment as a major league franchise in 1901, the Indians have won two World Series championships: in 1920 and 1948, along with 10 Central Division titles and six American League pennants.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-pirates//file/pittsburgh-pirates.svg</url><title>Pittsburgh Pirates Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Pittsburgh Pirates</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-pirates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-pirates/</guid><description turbo="true">The Pittsburgh Pirates are an American professional baseball team based in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. The Pirates compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. The Pirates play their home games at PNC Park; the team previously played at Forbes Field and Three Rivers Stadium, the latter of which was named after its location near the confluence of the Allegheny, Monongahela, and Ohio Rivers.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/jll//file/jll.svg</url><title>JLL Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">JLL</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/jll/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jll/</guid><description turbo="true"> Jones Lang LaSalle Incorporated or JLL is a commercial real estate services firm. It is the second-largest company of its kind in the world, smaller only than CBRE Group.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi//file/olympics-2014-sochi.svg</url><title>Olympics 2014 Sochi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Olympics 2014 Sochi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi/</guid><description turbo="true">The 2014 Winter Olympics, officially called the XXII Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XXIIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver) (Russian: XXII Олимпийские зимние игры, tr. XXII Olimpiyskiye zimniye igry) and commonly known as Sochi 2014, was an international winter multi-sport event that was held from 7 to 23 February 2014 in Sochi, Krasnodar Krai, Russia, with opening rounds in certain events held on the eve of the opening ceremony, 6 February 2014.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe//file/hpe.svg</url><title>HPE Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HPE</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</guid><description turbo="true">HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
Source Source In October 2014, the Hewlett-Packard Company announced its intention to split into two separate entities, signaling the largest corporate demerger in history. The two resulting companies would each remain Fortune 100 industry leaders—with HP, Inc.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines//file/southwest-airlines.svg</url><title>Southwest Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Southwest Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo//file/volvo.svg</url><title>Volvo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Volvo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Volvo Group (Swedish: Volvokoncernen; legally Aktiebolaget Volvo, shortened to AB Volvo) (stylized as VOLVO) is a Swedish multinational manufacturing company headquartered in Gothenburg. While its core activity is the production, distribution and sale of trucks, buses and construction equipment, Volvo also supplies marine and industrial drive systems and financial services. In 2016, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest manufacturer of heavy-duty trucks.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content/></rss>