<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>airlines on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/airlines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in airlines on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/airlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aer Lungus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</guid>
      <description>Aer Lingus is the flag carrier airline of Ireland and the second-largest airline in the country after Ryanair. Founded by the Irish government, it was privatised between 2006 and 2015 and it is now a wholly owned subsidiary of International Airlines Group (IAG), the parent company of British Airways and Iberia. The airline&amp;rsquo;s head office is on the grounds of Dublin Airport in Cloghran, County Dublin, Ireland.
 Source Aer Lingus tasked Lippincott with creating a brand that would reflect the radically different airline it had become, yet preserve the emotional bond with Ireland that it has always had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aeroflot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</guid>
      <description> Aeroflot – Russian Airlines is the flag carrier and largest airline of the Russian Federation. The carrier is an open joint stock company that operates domestic and international passenger and services, mainly from its hub at Sheremetyevo International Airport.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cathay Dragon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited is a Hong Kong-based international regional airline, with its corporate headquarters, Cathay Dragon House, and main hub at Hong Kong International Airport. As of 30 October 2013, the airline operates a scheduled passenger network to 47 destinations in 14 countries and territories across Asia. Additionally, the airline has three codeshares on routes served by partner airlines. It has an all Airbus fleet of 48 aircraft, consisting of A320s, A321s and A330s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hainan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hainan Airlines is an airline headquartered in Haikou, Hainan, People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It is the largest civilian-run air transport company, the fourth-largest airline in terms of fleet size in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, and fourth-largest airline in Asia in terms of passengers carried. It operates scheduled domestic and international services on 500 routes from Hainan and nine locations on the mainland, as well as charter services. Its main base is Haikou Meilan International Airport, with hubs at Beijing Capital International Airport and Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport and several focus cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lufthansa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lufthansa/</guid>
      <description>Deutsche Lufthansa AG Lufthansa (sometimes also as Lufthansa German Airlines), is the largest German airline and, when combined with its subsidiaries, also the largest airline in Europe in terms of passengers carried. The name of the company is derived from the German word Luft &amp;ldquo;air&amp;rdquo; and Hansa, the Hanseatic League. Lufthansa is one of the five founding members of Star Alliance, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline alliance, formed in 1997.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qantas Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Qantas Airways Limited (/ˈkwɒntəs/) is the flag carrier of Australia and its largest airline by fleet size, international flights and international destinations. It is the third oldest airline in the world, after KLM and Avianca having been founded in November 1920; it began international passenger flights in May 1935. The Qantas name comes from &amp;ldquo;QANTAS&amp;rdquo;, an acronym for its original name, &amp;ldquo;Queensland and Northern Territory Aerial Services&amp;rdquo;, and it is nicknamed &amp;ldquo;The Flying Kangaroo&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkish-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkish-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Turkish Airlines (Turkish: Türk Hava Yolları) is the national flag carrier airline of Turkey. As of 2018, it operates scheduled services to 304 destinations in Europe, Asia, Africa, and the Americas, making it the largest carrier in the world by number of passenger destinations (excluding regional brands). It serves more destinations non-stop from a single airport than any other airline in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Vietnam Airlines (Vietnamese: Hãng Hàng không Quốc gia Việt Nam) is the flag carrier of Vietnam. The airline was founded in 1956 and later established as a state-owned enterprise in April 1989. Vietnam Airlines is headquartered in Long Biên District, Hanoi, with hubs at Noi Bai International Airport and Tan Son Nhat International Airport. The airline flies to 64 destinations in 17 countries, excluding codeshared services.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>