<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>airlines on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/airlines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in airlines on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/airlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aer Lungus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</guid>
      <description>Aer Lingus is the flag carrier airline of Ireland and the second-largest airline in the country after Ryanair. Founded by the Irish government, it was privatised between 2006 and 2015 and it is now a wholly owned subsidiary of International Airlines Group (IAG), the parent company of British Airways and Iberia. The airline&amp;rsquo;s head office is on the grounds of Dublin Airport in Cloghran, County Dublin, Ireland.
 Source Aer Lingus tasked Lippincott with creating a brand that would reflect the radically different airline it had become, yet preserve the emotional bond with Ireland that it has always had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>