<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>electrical equipment on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/electrical-equipment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in electrical equipment on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/electrical-equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fitbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fitbit/</guid>
      <description>Fitbit, Inc. is an American company headquartered in San Francisco, California. Its products are activity trackers, smartwatches, wireless-enabled wearable technology devices that measure data such as the number of steps walked, heart rate, quality of sleep, steps climbed, and other personal metrics involved in fitness. Before October 2007, the company was previously named Healthy Metrics Research, Inc. While these devices appear to increase physical activities, there is little evidence that they improve health outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fujifilm</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujifilm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujifilm/</guid>
      <description>Fujifilm Holdings Corporation (富士フイルム株式会社, Fujifuirumu Kabushiki-kaisha), trading as Fujifilm (stylized as FUJiFILM), or simply Fuji, is a Japanese multinational photography and imaging company headquartered in Tokyo.
 Fujifilm&amp;rsquo;s principal activities are the development, production, sale and servicing of business document solutions, medical imaging and diagnostics equipment, cosmetics, regenerative medicine, stem cells, biologics manufacturing, optical films for flat panel displays, optical devices, photocopiers and printers, digital cameras, color film, color paper, photofinishing equipment, photofinishing chemicals, graphic arts equipment and materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/broadcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/broadcom/</guid>
      <description> Broadcom Inc. is an American designer, developer, manufacturer and global supplier of a wide range of semiconductor and infrastructure software products, Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio serves the data center, networking, software, broadband, wireless, and storage and industrial markets.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daikin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</guid>
      <description> Daikin Industries, Ltd. (ダイキン工業株式会社 Daikin Kōgyō Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational air conditioning manufacturing company headquartered in Osaka. It has operations in the United States, Japan, China, Philippines, Australia, India, Southeast Asia, Europe, and South America.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>