<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Z on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/z/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Z on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/z/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zcash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</guid>
      <description> Zcash is a cryptocurrency aimed at using cryptography to provide enhanced privacy for its users compared to other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zocdoc</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zocdoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zocdoc/</guid>
      <description> Zocdoc is an online medical care appointment booking service, providing free of charge medical care search facility for end users by integrating information about medical practices and doctors individual schedules in a central location. The company is based in New York City, with offices in Scottsdale, Arizona and Pune, India.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zara</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</guid>
      <description>Zara SA is a Spanish fast fashion (clothing and accessories) Retail based in Arteixo (A Coruña) in Galicia. The company was founded in 1975 by Amancio Ortega and Rosalía Mera. It is the main brand of the Inditex group, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel Retail. The fashion group also owns brands such as Massimo Dutti, Pull&amp;amp;Bear, Bershka, Stradivarius, Oysho, Zara Home, and Uterqüe. Zara as of 2017 manages up to 20 clothing collections a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zillow</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zillow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zillow/</guid>
      <description>Zillow Group, Inc., or simply Zillow, is an online real estate database company that was founded in 2006, and was created by Rich Barton and Lloyd Frink, former Microsoft executives and founders of Microsoft spin-off Expedia. In 2018, Zillow signed a partnership with Century 21 Canada to begin listing Canadian properties on the site, marking the first international country that Zillow.com supports. Barton is the current CEO of Zillow, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zuca</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zuca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 22:43:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zuca/</guid>
      <description>About Zuca  ZÜCA has been on a roll since 2004, making lives better—and making people smile—with our patented, super-durable and versatile, fashionable carry–all bags. We have revolutionized how people transport their belongings by helping them get around in a healthy way. Kids can transport all of their books without straining their backs, and they can grab a seat anywhere. Professionals can organize and protect their tools and samples on the go—and look totally put together for every client meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>