<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Y on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/y/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Y on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/y/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yammer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yammer/</guid>
      <description>Yammer is a freemium enterprise social networking service used for private communication within organizations. Access to a Yammer network is determined by a user&amp;rsquo;s Internet domain so that only individuals with approved email addresses may join their respective networks.
 The service began as an internal communication system for the genealogy website Geni.com, and was launched as an independent product in 2008. Microsoft later acquired Yammer in 2012 for US$1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo Japan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo-japan/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Japan Corporation is a Japanese internet company originally formed as a joint venture between the American internet company Yahoo! (later divested by Verizon into Altaba) and the Japanese company SoftBank. It is headquartered at Kioi Tower in the Tokyo Garden Terrace Kioicho complex in Kioicho, Chiyoda, Tokyo. Yahoo! Japan&amp;rsquo;s web portal is the most visited website in Japan, and its internet services are mostly dominant in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yelp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yelp/</guid>
      <description> Yelp is a business directory service and crowd-sourced review forum, and a public company of the same name that is headquartered in San Francisco, California. The company develops, hosts, and markets the Yelp.com website and the Yelp mobile app, which publish crowd-sourced reviews about businesses. It also operates an online reservation service called Yelp Reservations.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ymobile</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymobile/</guid>
      <description> Ymobile Corporation , stylized Y!mobile, is a subsidiary of Japanese telecommunications company SoftBank Group Corporation that provides mobile telecommunications and ADSL services. The current CEO of the company is Ken Miyauchi. It was formed in 2014 through the merger of Willcom and eAccess, and uses the Y! moniker brand from Yahoo! Japan, which is partly-owned by SoftBank.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yodobashi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yodobashi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yodobashi/</guid>
      <description>Yodobashi Camera Co., Ltd. (株式会社ヨドバシカメラ, Kabushiki gaisha Yodobashi Kamera) is a major Japanese retail chain specializing in electronics, PCs, cameras and photographic equipment.
 Yodobashi Camera&amp;rsquo;s sales rank fourth among consumer electronics mass retailers in Japan, after Yamada Denki, Bic Camera and the EDION Group. There are 23 stores operating as of October 2015. In recent years the online shopping platform has been developed to become the second largest in Japan only behind Amazon (though sales of Amazon are over 10 times higher).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! is an American web services provider headquartered in Sunnyvale, California, and owned by Verizon Media. The original Yahoo! company was founded by Jerry Yang and David Filo in January 1994 and was incorporated on March 2, 1995. Yahoo was one of the pioneers of the early Internet era in the 1990s.
 About new Yahoo! logo  With its new products, Yahoo will empower users to better sift out irrelevant parts of the digital world, giving them more control of what they see and when they see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yamaha</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yamaha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yamaha/</guid>
      <description> Yamaha Corporation is a Japanese multinational corporation and conglomerate with a very wide range of products and services. It is one of the constituents of Nikkei 225 and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest piano manufacturing company. The former motorcycle division was established in 1955 as Yamaha Motor Co., Ltd., which started as an affiliated company but later became independent, although Yamaha Corporation is still a major shareholder.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y Combinator</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/y-combinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/y-combinator/</guid>
      <description> Y Combinator is an American seed accelerator which was launched in March 2005. Y Combinator is consistently ranked at the top of U.S. accelerators.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoshinoya</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</guid>
      <description> Yoshinoya is a Japanese multinational fast food chain, and the second-largest chain of gyūdon (beef bowl) restaurants. The chain was established in Japan in 1899. Its motto is &amp;ldquo;Tasty, low-priced, and quick&amp;rdquo;.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yum! Brands</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yum-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yum-brands/</guid>
      <description> Yum! Brands, Inc., or Yum! and formerly Tricon Global Restaurants, Inc., is an American fast food company. A Fortune 500 corporation, Yum! operates the brands Taco Bell, KFC, Pizza Hut, and WingStreet worldwide, except in China, where the brands are operated by a separate company, Yum China. Prior to 2011, Yum! owned Long John Silver&amp;rsquo;s and A&amp;amp;W Restaurants.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 22:48:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/youtube/</guid>
      <description>The YouTube logo is made of a red round-rectangular box with a white &amp;ldquo;play&amp;rdquo; button inside and the word &amp;ldquo;YouTube&amp;rdquo; written in black.
 2017 YouTube Logo Update The bright red cherry on top of this update sundae is a refreshed YouTube Logo and YouTube Icon. Designed for YouTube multi-screen world, the updated Logo combines a cleaned up version of the YouTube wordmark and Icon, creating a more flexible design that works better across a variety of devices, even on the tiniest screens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</guid>
      <description>Yandex N.V. is a Russian multinational corporation specializing in Internet-related products and services, including search and information services, eCommerce, transportation, navigation, mobile applications, and online advertising. Yandex provides over 70 services in total. Incorporated in the Netherlands, Yandex primarily serves audiences in Russia and the Commonwealth of Independent States. The company founders and most of the team members are located in Russia. The company has 18 commercial offices worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Alisa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-alisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-alisa/</guid>
      <description> Alice (Russian: Алиса (Alisa)) is a Russian intelligent personal assistant for Android, iOS and Windows operating systems developed by Yandex. Alice was officially introduced on 10 October 2017. Aside from common tasks, such as internet search or weather forecasts, it can also run applications and chit-chat. Alice is also the virtual assistant used for the Yandex Station smart speaker.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Browser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Browser (Яндекс браузер in Russian) is a freeware web browser developed by the Russian web search corporation Yandex that uses the Blink web browser engine and is based on the Chromium open source project. The browser checks webpage security with the Yandex security system and checks downloaded files with Kaspersky anti-virus. The browser also uses Opera Software&amp;rsquo;s Turbo technology to speed web browsing on slow connections.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Money</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</guid>
      <description> Yandex.Money is Russia’s largest electronic payment service according to a 2016 survey by TNS. It is an online payment service that works with two types of clients — individual users and merchants.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Music» is a music streaming service developed by Yandex. Users select musical compositions, albums, collections of musical tracks to stream to their device on demand and receive personalized recommendations. The service is also available as a mobile app with versions compatible with iOS, Android. Service is available in Russia, Belarus, Kyrgyzstan, Kazakhstan, Armenia, Israel. Paid subscription service is available in all the other countries of the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMCA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</guid>
      <description> YMCA, sometimes regionally called the Y, is a worldwide organisation based in Geneva, Switzerland, with more than 64 million beneficiaries from 120 national associations. It was founded on 6 June 1844 by Sir George Williams in London, originally as the Young Men&amp;rsquo;s Christian Association and aims to put Christian principles into practice by developing a healthy &amp;ldquo;body, mind, and spirit&amp;rdquo;.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>