<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1998 on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/year/1998/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1998 on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/1998/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1998 Nagano</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1998-nagano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1998-nagano/</guid>
      <description>The 1998 Winter Olympics, officially the XVIII Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XVIIIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver)[1] (Japanese: 第十八回オリンピック冬季競技大会 Dai Jūhachi-kai Orinpikku Tōkikyōgi Taikai), and commonly known as Nagano 1998, was a winter multi-sport event celebrated from 7 to 22 February 1998 that were centered in Nagano, Japan. The Games also took place in the nearby mountain communities of Hakuba, Karuizawa, Nozawa Onsen, and Yamanouuchi. The city of Nagano had previously been a candidate to host the 1940 Winter Olympics (which were later cancelled), as well as the 1972 Winter Olympics, but each time Nagano was eliminated at the national level by Sapporo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Group logo (from pentagram.com and medium.com)
Citi Group  In Spring of 1998, Citi announced a merger with Travelers Insurance. At the time, it was the largest merger in the world and the brands needed to be unified to reflect that.
After a brief negotiation the budget for the brand overhaul was pegged at almost $10m, with the design of the logo itself making up $1.5m of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citibank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
In 1998 financial giants Citicorp and Travelers Group merged to create Citigroup, the largest financial company in the world. After having designed the now ubiquitous identity for the newly formed entity, a three dimensional extension of the brand in the form of Citibank branch interiors and fascias was developed and implemented worldwide.
A visual language and colors and materials palette were developed to represent the new brand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>