<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>heavy equipment on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/heavy-equipment/</link><description>Recent content in heavy equipment on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/heavy-equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb//file/jcb.svg</url><title>JCB Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">JCB</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb/</guid><description turbo="true">JCB is a manufacturer of equipment for construction, agriculture, waste handling, and demolition, based in Rocester, Staffordshire, England. It produces over 300 types of machines, including diggers (backhoes), excavators, tractors, and diesel engines, across 22 factories spanning Asia, Europe, North America, and South America; its products are sold in over 150 countries.
Joseph Cyril Bamford Excavators Ltd. was founded in 1945 by Joseph Cyril Bamford and continues to be owned by the Bamford family.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/caterpillar//file/caterpillar.svg</url><title>Caterpillar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Caterpillar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/caterpillar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/caterpillar/</guid><description turbo="true"> Caterpillar Inc. is an American Fortune 100 corporation which designs, develops, engineers, manufactures, markets and sells machinery, engines, financial products and insurance to customers via a worldwide dealer network. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest construction equipment manufacturer. In 2018, Caterpillar was ranked #65 on the Fortune 500 list and #238 on the Global Fortune 500 list. Caterpillar stock is a component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan//file/doosan.svg</url><title>Doosan Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Doosan</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</guid><description turbo="true"> Doosan Group is a South Korean conglomerate company. In 2009, the company was placed 471st in the Fortune Global 500. It has been included in the Forbes Global 2000 companies from 2007.[citation needed] It is the parent company of ŠKODA power. Doosan was ranked 4th among the “World&amp;rsquo;s Best 40 Companies 2009” list, released in the latest issue of BusinessWeek, the U.S. economics magazine in October 2009.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/john-deere//file/john-deere.svg</url><title>John Deere Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">John Deere</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/john-deere/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/john-deere/</guid><description turbo="true"> John Deere is the brand name of Deere &amp;amp; Company, an American corporation that manufactures agricultural, construction, and forestry machinery, diesel engines, drivetrains (axles, transmissions, gearboxes) used in heavy equipment, and lawn care equipment. In 2018, it was listed as 102nd in the Fortune 500 America&amp;rsquo;s ranking and was ranked 394th in the global ranking. The company also provides financial services and other related activities.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/komatsu//file/komatsu.svg</url><title>Komatsu Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Komatsu</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/komatsu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/komatsu/</guid><description turbo="true">Komatsu Ltd. is a Japanese multinational corporation that manufactures construction, mining, forestry, and military equipment, as well as industrial equipment like press machines, lasers and thermoelectric generators. Its headquarters are in Minato, Tokyo, Japan. The corporation was named after the city of Komatsu, Ishikawa Prefecture, where the company was founded in 1921. Worldwide, the Komatsu Group consists of Komatsu Ltd. and 258 other companies (215 consolidated subsidiaries and 42 companies accounted for by the equity method).</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/liebherr//file/liebherr.svg</url><title>Liebherr Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Liebherr</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/liebherr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/liebherr/</guid><description turbo="true">The Liebherr Group is a large equipment manufacturer based in Switzerland with its main production facilities and origins in Germany. It consists of over 130 companies organized into eleven Divisions: Earthmoving, Mining, Mobile cranes, Tower cranes, Concrete technology, Maritime cranes, Aerospace and transportation systems, Machine tools and automation systems, Domestic appliances, and Components. It has a worldwide workforce of over 42,000, with 9 billion euros in revenue for 2017. By 2007, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest crane company.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany//file/sany.svg</url><title>Sany Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sany</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</guid><description turbo="true"> Sany Heavy Industry Co., Ltd. is a Chinese multinational heavy equipment manufacturing company headquartered in Changsha, Hunan Province. It is the sixth-largest heavy equipment manufacturer in the world, and the first in its industry in China to enter the FT Global 500 and the Forbes Global 2000 rankings. Its founder and main shareholder is Liang Wengen.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content/></rss>