<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>healthcare on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/healthcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in healthcare on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stryker</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/stryker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/stryker/</guid>
      <description>Stryker Corporation is an American multinational medical technologies corporation based in Kalamazoo, Michigan. Stryker&amp;rsquo;s products include implants used in joint replacement and trauma surgeries; surgical equipment and surgical navigation systems; endoscopic and communications systems; patient handling and emergency medical equipment; neurosurgical, neurovascular and spinal devices; as well as other medical device products used in a variety of medical specialties.
 In the United States, most of Stryker&amp;rsquo;s products are marketed directly to doctors, hospitals and other healthcare facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealth</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unitedhealth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unitedhealth/</guid>
      <description>UnitedHealth Group Incorporated is an American for-profit managed health care company based in Minnetonka, Minnesota. It offers health care products and insurance services. It is the largest healthcare company in the world by revenue, with 2019 revenue of $242.2 billion. UnitedHealthcare revenues comprise 80% of the Group&amp;rsquo;s overall revenue.
 The company is ranked 7th on the 2020 Fortune 500.
Source About UnitedHealth UnitedHealth Group is committed to leading the development of a more modern, progressive and effective health system that provides extraordinary value for society — building healthier communities and improving the quality of life for those we serve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Health Organization</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/world-health-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/world-health-organization/</guid>
      <description>The World Health Organization (WHO) is a specialized agency of the United Nations responsible for international public health. The WHO Constitution, which establishes the agency&amp;rsquo;s governing structure and principles, states its main objective as &amp;ldquo;the attainment by all peoples of the highest possible level of health.&amp;rdquo; It is headquartered in Geneva, Switzerland, with six semi-autonomous regional offices and 150 field offices worldwide.
 The WHO was established by constitution on 7 April 1948, which is commemorated as World Health Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CDC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 22:22:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc/</guid>
      <description>CDC is responding to the novel coronavirus outbreak. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is the leading national public health institute of the United States. The CDC is a United States federal agency under the Department of Health and Human Services and is headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmg/</guid>
      <description> BMG are an established medical practice with strong ties to St. Francis Hospital, California Pacific Medical Center, and UCSF Medical Center. BMG providers have completed their medical training at various prestigious universities. Bayspring has a long established reputation for being an excellent community medical practice that offers warm and personalized attention from a diverse group of medical providers.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conceive Abilities</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</guid>
      <description> At ConceiveAbilities® Conceive Abilities believe that everyone who wants to become a parent, can. Conceive Abilities have helped build thousands of families for nearly 25 years. Whether you are an intended parent ready to fulfill your family destiny, a surrogate answering your calling or an egg donor wanting to expand what’s possible in your life—Conceive Abilities are your people.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donor Concierge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/donor-concierge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/donor-concierge/</guid>
      <description>The Donor Concierge team is comprised of compassionate, educated, and knowledgeable case managers, with a track record of outstanding results to help families find the right donor/surrogate choice through the best industry connections. Donor Concierge have chosen each team member for her unique ability to relate to Donor Concierge clients. Donor Concierge have a multinational office with Canadian, Chinese, Filipino, and American case managers who speak a variety of languages including Mandarin, French, Tagalog, Spanish, and English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DWH</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dwh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dwh/</guid>
      <description> DWH believe in a comprehensive approach to your healthcare - one that focuses on your emotional and practice needs as well as your medical status.
 Women today know that they play an important role in making treatment choices about their health care. DWH invite you to join us as partners in your healthcare decisions.
Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eda/</guid>
      <description> Egg Donor America, a leading center for egg donation. EDA primary goal is to make the process of selecting an egg donor as easy and as comfortable as possible. Egg Donor America was founded by fertility expert Dr. Pierre Asmar. Dr. Asmar oversees every aspect of the egg donor program.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fertility Solutions</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertility-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertility-solutions/</guid>
      <description> Fertility Solutions is a patient-centered practice that provides a full spectrum of infertility diagnosis and treatment. From lifestyle modifications to the latest in assisted reproductive technology, Fertility Solutions offer a decidedly different, more personal approach to fertility care.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDFC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sdfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sdfc/</guid>
      <description>At San Diego Fertility Center® SDFC have been creating miracles every day for over 20 years. Regardless of your situation, SDFC nationally recognized infertility specialists can work closely with you to develop a personalized fertility treatment plan, including IVF, PGD, egg donation &amp;amp; surrogacy and other fertility options. As a leading destination for fertility tourism and travel, SDFC fertility center offers hope to patients around the world. San Diego Fertility Center takes your dreams seriously and is dedicated to providing compassionate care, so why not get to know us bette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spine RX</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/spine-rx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spine-rx/</guid>
      <description>When you visit SPINE/RX, you’ll see the difference right away. At your first consultation, Spine RX surgical team will explain how modern spine surgery solutions are different from traditional spine surgery. They will take the time to understand your pain, evaluate your condition, and explain your options for more definitive pain relief. Many of Spine RX procedures are same day, minimally-invasive, and have shorter recovery times - getting you back on track fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sshc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sshc/</guid>
      <description>At The Spine &amp;amp; Sports Health Center, SSHC top interventional pain management physicians will take the time to understand your pain, listen and focus on what matters most to you. SSHC use the latest diagnostic technology (and good old-fashioned listening and observation) to develop an accurate diagnosis. And, SSHC&amp;rsquo;ll develop a personalized treatment plan combining the most effective and least invasive options to fit your needs &amp;ndash;without the risks or complications of surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearing Australia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</guid>
      <description> Hearing Australia is a statutory authority constituted under the Australian Hearing Services Act 1991, reporting to the Minister for Human Services, and is within the Department of Human Services portfolio. Hearing Australia is the largest Australian government-funded hearing aid dispensing company providing hearing care and technologies. One of their areas of interest is hearing testing and rehabilitation of children under the age of 26.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount Sinai</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mount-sinai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mount-sinai/</guid>
      <description>Mount Sinai Hospital, founded in 1852, is one of the oldest and largest teaching hospitals in the United States. It is located on the Upper East Side in the New York City borough of Manhattan, on the eastern border of Central Park stretching along Fifth Avenue, between East 98th Street and East 103rd Street. The entire Mount Sinai health system has over 7,400 physicians, as well as 3,815 beds, and delivers over 16,000 babies a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superwalk</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/superwalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/superwalk/</guid>
      <description>For more than 30 years participants from across the country have come together to show one another that they are not alone. Now, guided by the relentless perseverance of people living with Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s standing up to their diagnosis more than 10,000 participants in 80 communities stand together on SuperWalk weekend.
 Parkinson Canada SuperWalk takes place each September. Since 1990 walkers like you have raised more than $38 Million to support a better life today for Canadians living with Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s, a world without Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardinal Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health/</guid>
      <description>Cardinal Health, Inc. is an American multinational health care services company, and the 14th highest revenue generating company in the United States. Its headquarters are based in Dublin, Ohio and Dublin, Ireland (EMEA). The company specializes in distribution of pharmaceuticals and medical products, serving more than 100,000 locations. The company also manufactures medical and surgical products, including gloves, surgical apparel and fluid management products. In addition, it operates the largest network of radiopharmacies in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flatiron Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</guid>
      <description> Flatiron is a healthcare technology company providing software and data analytics services to the FDA, cancer researchers, and care providers. Flatiron’s Learning Oncology Platform supports over 260 community oncology practices across the U.S, 10 of the top 12 life science companies and three major academic research centers. Early investors include Google Ventures, First Round Capital, Roche and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthPartners</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</guid>
      <description> HealthPartners is an integrated, nonprofit health care provider and health insurance company located in Bloomington, Minnesota offering care, coverage, research and education to its members, patients and the community.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RMA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma/</guid>
      <description> Reproductive Medicine Associates of New York is dedicated to providing patients the highest quality care in a compassionate and supportive manner. Helping couples successfully achieve their family-building goals has been RMA of New York’s focus since 2001.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BHF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</guid>
      <description> The British Heart Foundation (BHF) is a charity organisation in the United Kingdom. It funds research to beat heartbreak from heart and circulatory diseases and their risk factors.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zocdoc</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zocdoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zocdoc/</guid>
      <description> Zocdoc is an online medical care appointment booking service, providing free of charge medical care search facility for end users by integrating information about medical practices and doctors individual schedules in a central location. The company is based in New York City, with offices in Scottsdale, Arizona and Pune, India.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aetna</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna/</guid>
      <description> Aetna Inc. is an American managed health care company that sells traditional and consumer directed health care insurance and related services, such as medical, pharmaceutical, dental, behavioral health, long-term care, and disability plans, primarily through employer-paid (fully or partly) insurance and benefit programs, and through Medicare. Since November 28, 2018, the company has been a subsidiary of CVS Health.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Versant Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joint Commission</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</guid>
      <description>About The Joint Commission (from wikipedia.org)
The Joint Commission is a United States-based nonprofit tax-exempt 501(c) organization that accredits more than 21,000 US health care organizations and programs.The international branch accredits medical services from around the world. A majority of US state governments recognize Joint Commission accreditation as a condition of licensure for the receipt of Medicaid and Medicare reimbursements.
The Joint Commission was formerly the Joint Commission on Accreditation of healthcare Organizations (JCAHO) and previous to that the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals (JCAH)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Sharp healthcare (from sharp.org)
Sharp healthcare is San Diego&amp;rsquo;s health care leader with hospitals in San Diego, affiliated medical groups, urgent care centers and a health plan. Sharp provides medical services in virtually all fields of medicine, including primary care, heart care, cancer treatment, orthopedics and women&amp;rsquo;s health.
 Sharp is not for profit, but for people, which means all of Sharp Healthcare resources are dedicated to delivering the highest quality patient-centered care, the latest medical technology and superior service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper healthcare (from prosperhealthcare.com)
Prosper healthcare Lending is a patient financing marketplace company headquartered in Salt Lake City, Utah at the heart of the “Silicon Slopes”. Prosper healthcare sit at the intersection of the healthcare, technology, and financial services markets and Prosper healthcare are using technology to bring innovative financial services solutions to a massive healthcare problem. Prosper healthcare patient financing platform allows healthcare providers nationwide to help Make healthcare Affordable™ for patients every day by referring patients with good credit to affordable installment loans offered through Prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SART</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Path2Parenthood</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</guid>
      <description>About Path2Parenthoods Path2Parenthood (P2P) is an inclusive organization committed to helping people create their families by providing leading-edge outreach programs and timely educational information. The scope of Path2Parenthood work encompasses reproductive health, infertility prevention and treatment, and family-building options including adoption and third party solutions. P2P is a national, not-for-profit 501(c)(3) charitable organization headquartered in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSHA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/osha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:23:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/osha/</guid>
      <description>About OSHA The Occupational Safety and Health Administration is an agency of the United States Department of Labor. Congress established the agency under the Occupational Safety and Health Act, which President Richard M. Nixon signed into law on December 29, 1970. OSHA&amp;rsquo;s mission is to &amp;ldquo;assure safe and healthy working conditions for working men and women by setting and enforcing standards and by providing training, outreach, education and assistance&amp;rdquo;. The agency is also charged with enforcing a variety of whistleblower statutes and regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FertileHope</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertilehope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertilehope/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fda/</guid>
      <description>About FDA (from wikipedia.org)
The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or USFDA) is a federal agency of the United States Department of Health and Human Services, one of the United States federal executive departments. The FDA is responsible for protecting and promoting public health through the control and supervision of food safety, tobacco products, dietary supplements, prescription and over-the-counter pharmaceutical drugs (medications), vaccines, biopharmaceuticals, blood transfusions, medical devices, electromagnetic radiation emitting devices (ERED), cosmetics, animal foods &amp;amp; feed and veterinary products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College of American Pathologists</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:21:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</guid>
      <description> The College of American Pathologists is a member-based physician organization founded in 1946 comprising approximately 18,000 board-certified pathologists. It serves patients, pathologists, and the public by fostering and advocating best practices in pathology and laboratory medicine.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASRM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm/</guid>
      <description> The American Society for Reproductive Medicine is a multidisciplinary organization dedicated to the advancement of the science and practice of reproductive medicine. It provides a forum for lay public, researchers, physicians and affiliated health workers through education, publications, and meetings. The Society has its headquarters in Birmingham, AL and a public affairs office in Washington, DC.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Surrogacy Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/illinois-surrogacy-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:49:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/illinois-surrogacy-center/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago IVF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:32:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf/</guid>
      <description>About Chicago IFV (from chicagoivf.com)
Chicago IVF’s offices and state-of-the-art facilities are conveniently located throughout Chicagoland and eastward into the state of Indiana, in close proximity to domestic and international airports. The fertility and surrogacy-friendly legal environment of Illinois makes the location of Chicago IVF practice an ideal destination for treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RMA of Texas</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma-of-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:46:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma-of-texas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Fertility Specialists</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspire Fertility</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Fertility Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</guid>
      <description>About Pacific Fertility Center Pacific Fertility Center®, located in Northern California&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco Bay Area, is an international destination for male and female fertility treatment and care. Pacific Fertility Center also regularly see patients from surrounding areas in California, like Berkeley, Oakland, Palo Alto, and Marin County. For updated information about Pacific Fertility Center fertility clinic, infertility treatment options, IVF success rates and more, read Pacific Fertility Center infertility doctor blog or subscribe to Pacific Fertility Center&amp;rsquo;s Fertility Flash newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproductive Biology Associates</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/reproductive-biology-associates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reproductive-biology-associates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Reproductive Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kentucky-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kentucky-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prelude Fertility</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 21:15:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</guid>
      <description>About Prelude (from Prelude brandbook)
Prelude Pagoda  Prelude is a network of top-tier fertility centers across the US offering comprehensive fertility care. Whether you’re hoping to build your family now or looking to preserve your options for the future, Prelude meets you where you are.
The story behind the logo The Pagoda plays a key role in the Prelude Network identity. It is a simple, functional device that communicates Prelude Fertility mission yet allows for interpretation at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>