<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>healthcare on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/healthcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in healthcare on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardinal Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health/</guid>
      <description>Cardinal Health, Inc. is an American multinational health care services company, and the 14th highest revenue generating company in the United States. Its headquarters are based in Dublin, Ohio and Dublin, Ireland (EMEA). The company specializes in distribution of pharmaceuticals and medical products, serving more than 100,000 locations. The company also manufactures medical and surgical products, including gloves, surgical apparel and fluid management products. In addition, it operates the largest network of radiopharmacies in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flatiron Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</guid>
      <description> Flatiron is a healthcare technology company providing software and data analytics services to the FDA, cancer researchers, and care providers. Flatiron’s Learning Oncology Platform supports over 260 community oncology practices across the U.S, 10 of the top 12 life science companies and three major academic research centers. Early investors include Google Ventures, First Round Capital, Roche and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthPartners</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</guid>
      <description> HealthPartners is an integrated, nonprofit health care provider and health insurance company located in Bloomington, Minnesota offering care, coverage, research and education to its members, patients and the community.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BHF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</guid>
      <description> The British Heart Foundation (BHF) is a charity organisation in the United Kingdom. It funds research to beat heartbreak from heart and circulatory diseases and their risk factors.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zocdoc</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zocdoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zocdoc/</guid>
      <description> Zocdoc is an online medical care appointment booking service, providing free of charge medical care search facility for end users by integrating information about medical practices and doctors&amp;rsquo; individual schedules in a central location. The company is based in New York City, with offices in Scottsdale, Arizona and Pune, India.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Versant Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joint Commission</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</guid>
      <description>About The Joint Commission (from wikipedia.org)
The Joint Commission is a United States-based nonprofit tax-exempt 501&amp;copy; organization that accredits more than 21,000 US health care organizations and programs.The international branch accredits medical services from around the world. A majority of US state governments recognize Joint Commission accreditation as a condition of licensure for the receipt of Medicaid and Medicare reimbursements.
The Joint Commission was formerly the Joint Commission on Accreditation of healthcare Organizations (JCAHO) and previous to that the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals (JCAH)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Sharp healthcare (from sharp.org)
Sharp healthcare is San Diego&amp;rsquo;s health care leader with hospitals in San Diego, affiliated medical groups, urgent care centers and a health plan. Sharp provides medical services in virtually all fields of medicine, including primary care, heart care, cancer treatment, orthopedics and women&amp;rsquo;s health.
 Sharp is not for profit, but for people, which means all of our resources are dedicated to delivering the highest quality patient-centered care, the latest medical technology and superior service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper healthcare (from prosperhealthcare.com)
Prosper healthcare Lending is a patient financing marketplace company headquartered in Salt Lake City, Utah at the heart of the “Silicon Slopes”. We sit at the intersection of the healthcare, technology, and financial services markets and we are using technology to bring innovative financial services solutions to a massive healthcare problem. Our patient financing platform allows healthcare providers nationwide to help Make healthcare Affordable™ for patients every day by referring patients with good credit to affordable installment loans offered through Prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SART</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Path2Parenthood</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</guid>
      <description>About Path2Parenthoods Path2Parenthood (P2P) is an inclusive organization committed to helping people create their families by providing leading-edge outreach programs and timely educational information. The scope of our work encompasses reproductive health, infertility prevention and treatment, and family-building options including adoption and third party solutions. P2P is a national, not-for-profit 501&amp;copy;(3) charitable organization headquartered in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSHA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/osha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:23:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/osha/</guid>
      <description>About OSHA The Occupational Safety and Health Administration is an agency of the United States Department of Labor. Congress established the agency under the Occupational Safety and Health Act, which President Richard M. Nixon signed into law on December 29, 1970. OSHA&amp;rsquo;s mission is to &amp;ldquo;assure safe and healthy working conditions for working men and women by setting and enforcing standards and by providing training, outreach, education and assistance&amp;rdquo;. The agency is also charged with enforcing a variety of whistleblower statutes and regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FertileHope</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertilehope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertilehope/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fda/</guid>
      <description>About FDA (from wikipedia.org)
The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or USFDA) is a federal agency of the United States Department of Health and Human Services, one of the United States federal executive departments. The FDA is responsible for protecting and promoting public health through the control and supervision of food safety, tobacco products, dietary supplements, prescription and over-the-counter pharmaceutical drugs (medications), vaccines, biopharmaceuticals, blood transfusions, medical devices, electromagnetic radiation emitting devices (ERED), cosmetics, animal foods &amp;amp; feed and veterinary products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CDC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc/</guid>
      <description> The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is the leading national public health institute of the United States. The CDC is a United States federal agency under the Department of Health and Human Services and is headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College of American Pathologists</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:21:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</guid>
      <description> The College of American Pathologists is a member-based physician organization founded in 1946 comprising approximately 18,000 board-certified pathologists. It serves patients, pathologists, and the public by fostering and advocating best practices in pathology and laboratory medicine.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASRM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm/</guid>
      <description> The American Society for Reproductive Medicine is a multidisciplinary organization dedicated to the advancement of the science and practice of reproductive medicine. It provides a forum for lay public, researchers, physicians and affiliated health workers through education, publications, and meetings. The Society has its headquarters in Birmingham, AL and a public affairs office in Washington, DC.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Surrogacy Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/illinois-surrogacy-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:49:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/illinois-surrogacy-center/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago IVF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:32:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf/</guid>
      <description>About Chicago IFV (from chicagoivf.com)
Chicago IVF’s offices and state-of-the-art facilities are conveniently located throughout Chicagoland and eastward into the state of Indiana, in close proximity to domestic and international airports. The fertility and surrogacy-friendly legal environment of Illinois makes the location of our practice an ideal destination for treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RMA of Texas</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma-of-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:46:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma-of-texas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Fertility Specialists</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspire Fertility</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Fertility Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</guid>
      <description>About Pacific Fertility Center Pacific Fertility Center®, located in Northern California&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco Bay Area, is an international destination for male and female fertility treatment and care. We also regularly see patients from surrounding areas in California, like Berkeley, Oakland, Palo Alto, and Marin County. For updated information about our fertility clinic, infertility treatment options, IVF success rates and more, read our infertility doctor blog or subscribe to Pacific Fertility Center&amp;rsquo;s Fertility Flash newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproductive Biology Associates</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/reproductive-biology-associates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reproductive-biology-associates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Reproductive Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kentucky-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kentucky-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prelude Fertility</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 21:15:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</guid>
      <description>About Prelude (from Prelude brandbook)
Prelude Pagoda  Prelude is a network of top-tier fertility centers across the US offering comprehensive fertility care. Whether you’re hoping to build your family now or looking to preserve your options for the future, Prelude meets you where you are.
The story behind the logo The Pagoda plays a key role in the Prelude Network identity. It is a simple, functional device that communicates our mission yet allows for interpretation at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>