<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>France on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/france/</link>
    <description>Recent content in France on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Groupe PSA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/groupe-psa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/groupe-psa/</guid>
      <description>Groupe PSA (French pronunciation: ​[ɡʁup pe ɛs a]; also known as the PSA Group in English; formerly known as PSA Peugeot Citroën from 1991 to 2016) is a French multinational manufacturer of automobiles and motorcycles sold under the Peugeot, Citroën, DS, Opel and Vauxhall brands. Peugeot is the largest PSA brand. PSA is listed on the Euronext Paris stock exchange and is a constituent of the CAC 40 index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lacoste</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</guid>
      <description>Lacoste is a French company, founded in 1933 by tennis player René Lacoste and André Gillier. It sells clothing, footwear, sportswear, eyewear, leather goods, perfume, towels and watches. The company can be recognised by its green crocodile logo. René Lacoste, the company&amp;rsquo;s founder, was nicknamed &amp;ldquo;the Crocodile&amp;rdquo; by fans because of his tenacity on the tennis court. In November 2012 Lacoste was bought outright by Swiss family-held group Maus Frères.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/michelin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/michelin/</guid>
      <description>Michelin (/ˈmɪʃəlɪn, -læ̃/; full name: Compagnie Générale des Établissements Michelin SCA) is a French multinational tyre manufacturer based in Clermont-Ferrand in the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes région of France. It is the second largest tyre manufacturer in the world after Bridgestone and larger than both Goodyear and Continental. In addition to the Michelin brand, it also owns the Kléber tyres company, Uniroyal-Goodrich Tire Company, SASCAR, Bookatable and Camso brands. Michelin is also notable for its Red and Green travel guides, its roadmaps, the Michelin stars that the Red Guide awards to restaurants for their cooking, and for its company mascot Bibendum, colloquially known as the Michelin Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bugatti</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</guid>
      <description> Automobiles Ettore Bugatti was a French car manufacturer of high-performance automobiles, founded in 1909 in the then-German city of Molsheim, Alsace by the Italian-born industrial designer Ettore Bugatti. The cars were known for their design beauty and for their many race victories. Famous Bugattis include the Type 35 Grand Prix cars, the Type 41 &amp;ldquo;Royale&amp;rdquo;, the Type 57 &amp;ldquo;Atlantic&amp;rdquo; and the Type 55 sports car.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deezer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</guid>
      <description>Deezer is a French online music streaming service. It allows users to listen to music content from record labels, including Universal Music Group, Sony Music and Warner Music Group (owned by Deezer&amp;rsquo;s parent company Access Industries) on various devices online or offline. Created in Paris, France, Deezer currently has 56 million licensed tracks in its library, with over 30,000 radio channels, 14 million monthly active users, and 7 million paid subscribers as of January 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ledger</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</guid>
      <description> Ledger is a fast paced, growing company developing security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies as well as blockchain applications for individuals and companies, by leveraging a distinctive, proprietary technology.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France 24</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</guid>
      <description> France 24 (pronounced &amp;ldquo;France vingt-quatre&amp;rdquo;) is a state-owned international news and current affairs television network based in Paris. Its channels broadcast in French, English, Arabic, and Spanish and are aimed at the overseas market, similar to DD News, BBC World News, DW and RT.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Gobain</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/saint-gobain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/saint-gobain/</guid>
      <description> Compagnie de Saint-Gobain S.A. is a French multinational corporation, founded in 1665 in Paris and headquartered on the outskirts of Paris, at La Défense and in Courbevoie. Originally a mirror manufacturer, it now also produces a variety of construction and high-performance materials. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanofi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanofi/</guid>
      <description> Sanofi S.A. is a French multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Paris, France, as of 2013 the world&amp;rsquo;s fifth-largest by prescription sales. The company was formed as Sanofi-Aventis in 2004 by the merger of Aventis and Sanofi-Synthélabo, which were each the product of several previous mergers. It changed its name to Sanofi in May 2011. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total SA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa/</guid>
      <description> Total S.A. is a French multinational integrated oil and gas company founded in 1924 and one of the seven &amp;ldquo;Supermajor&amp;rdquo; oil companies in the world. Its businesses cover the entire oil and gas chain, from crude oil and natural gas exploration and production to power generation, transportation, refining, petroleum product marketing, and international crude oil and product trading. Total is also a large scale chemicals manufacturer.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hennessy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy/</guid>
      <description> Jas Hennessy &amp;amp; Co., commonly known simply as Hennessy, is a brandy distiller with its headquarters located in Cognac, France. Jas Hennessy &amp;amp; Co. sells about 50 million bottles a year worldwide, or more than 40 percent of the world&amp;rsquo;s cognac, making it the largest cognac producer.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leroy-Merlin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</guid>
      <description> Leroy Merlin (French: [ləʁwa mɛʁlɛ̃]) is a French headquartered home improvement and gardening Retail serving several countries in Europe, Asia, South America, and Africa.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1992 Albertville</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1992-albertville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:28:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1992-albertville/</guid>
      <description>The 1992 Winter Olympics, officially known as the XVI Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XVIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver), were a winter multi-sport event celebrated from 8 to 23 February 1992 in Albertville, France. They were the last Winter Olympics to be held the same year as the Summer Olympics,[1][2] and the first where the Winter Paralympics were held at the same site. Albertville was selected as host in 1986, beating Sofia, Falun, Lillehammer, Cortina d&amp;rsquo;Ampezzo, Anchorage and Berchtesgaden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1968 Grenoble</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1968-grenoble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:27:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1968-grenoble/</guid>
      <description>The official poster of the 1968 Winter Olympics   The 1968 Winter Olympics, officially known as the X Olympic Winter Games (French: Les Xes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver), were a winter multi-sport event which was celebrated in 1968 in Grenoble, France, and opened on 6 February. Thirty-seven countries participated. The year 1968 marked the first time the IOC first permitted East and West Germany to enter separately, and the first time the IOC ever ordered drug and gender testing of competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2024 Paris</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2024-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:33:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2024-paris/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air France</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france/</guid>
      <description>Air France is the French flag carrier headquartered in Tremblay-en-France. It is a subsidiary of the Air France–KLM Group and a founding member of the SkyTeam global airline alliance. As of 2013 Air France serves 36 destinations in France and operates worldwide scheduled passenger and cargo services to 168 destinations in 78 countries (93 including overseas departments and territories of France) and also carried 46,803,000 passengers in 2015. The airline&amp;rsquo;s global hub is at Charles de Gaulle Airport with Orly Airport as the primary domestic hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AXA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/axa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/axa/</guid>
      <description> AXA is a French multinational insurance firm headquartered in the 8th arrondissement of Paris that engages in global insurance, investment management, and other financial services.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartier</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartier/</guid>
      <description>CARTIER International SNC, or simply Cartier is a French luxury goods conglomerate which designs, manufactures, distributes, and sells jewellery and watches. Founded by Louis-François Cartier in Paris in 1847, the company remained under family control until 1964. The company maintains its headquarters in Paris, although it has been a wholly owned subsidiary of the Swiss Richemont Group. Cartier operates more than 200 stores in 125 countries, with three Temples (Historical Maison) in London, New York, and Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chanel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel/</guid>
      <description>Chanel S.A. is a French privately held company owned by Alain Wertheimer and Gérard Wertheimer, grandsons of Pierre Wertheimer, who was an early business partner of the couturière Coco Chanel. Chanel S.A. is a high fashion house that specializes in haute couture and ready-to-wear clothes, luxury goods, and fashion accessories. In her youth, Gabrielle Chanel gained the nickname Coco from her time as a chanteuse. As a fashion designer, Coco Chanel catered to women&amp;rsquo;s taste for elegance in dress, with blouses and suits, trousers and dresses, and jewellery (gemstone and bijouterie) of simple design, that replaced the opulent, over-designed, and constrictive clothes and accessories of 19th-century fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citroen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</guid>
      <description> Citroën is a French automobile manufacturer, part of the PSA Peugeot Citroën group since 1976, founded in 1919 by French industrialist André-Gustave Citroën (1878–1935). In 1934, the firm established its reputation for innovative technology with the Traction Avant. This car was the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass-produced front wheel drive car, and also one of the first to feature a unitary type body, with no chassis supporting the mechanical components.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</guid>
      <description> Danone S.A. is a French multinational food-products corporation based in Paris and founded in Barcelona, Spain. The company is listed on Euronext Paris where it is a component of the CAC 40 stock market index. Some of the company’s products are branded Dannon in the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dior</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</guid>
      <description> Christian Dior SE , commonly known as Dior, is a French luxury goods company controlled and chaired by French businessman Bernard Arnault, who also heads LVMH, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest luxury group. Dior itself holds 42.36% shares of and 59.01% voting rights within LVMH. Since 1997, the CEO is Sidney Toledano.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</guid>
      <description> Hermès International S.A., or simply Hermès is a French high fashion luxury goods manufacturer established in 1837. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. Its logo, since the 1950s, is of a Duc carriage with horse. Nadège Vanhee-Cybulski is the current creative director.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenzo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo/</guid>
      <description>Kenzo (stylized as KENZO) is a French luxury fashion house founded in 1970 by Japanese designer Kenzo Takada. Kenzo Takada was born in Japan and moved to Paris in 1964 to start his fashion career. He then became known for using Asian and Japanese influenced style with the construction of European fashion. He started out with a &amp;lsquo;Jungle Jap&amp;rsquo; boutique located in Paris and decorated in jungle inspired decor. He began with handmade women&amp;rsquo;s clothing, then in 1983 Kenzo started designing men and then kids and home collections in 1987.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOreal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/loreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/loreal/</guid>
      <description> L&amp;rsquo;Oréal S.A. is a French personal care company headquartered in Clichy, Hauts-de-Seine with a registered office in Paris. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest cosmetics company and has developed activities in the field concentrating on hair colour, skin care, sun protection, make-up, perfume, and hair care.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louis Vuitton</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/louis-vuitton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/louis-vuitton/</guid>
      <description>Louis Vuitton Malletier, commonly referred to as Louis Vuitton or shortened to LV, is a French fashion house and luxury retail company founded in 1854 by Louis Vuitton. The label&amp;rsquo;s LV monogram appears on most of its products, ranging from luxury trunks and leather goods to ready-to-wear, shoes, watches, jewelry, accessories, sunglasses and books. Louis Vuitton is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading international fashion houses; it sells its products through standalone boutiques, lease departments in high-end department stores, and through the e-commerce section of its website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>