<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>France on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/france/</link>
    <description>Recent content in France on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:28:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1992 Albertville</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1992-albertville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:28:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1992-albertville/</guid>
      <description>The 1992 Winter Olympics, officially known as the XVI Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XVIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver), were a winter multi-sport event celebrated from 8 to 23 February 1992 in Albertville, France. They were the last Winter Olympics to be held the same year as the Summer Olympics,[1][2] and the first where the Winter Paralympics were held at the same site. Albertville was selected as host in 1986, beating Sofia, Falun, Lillehammer, Cortina d&amp;rsquo;Ampezzo, Anchorage and Berchtesgaden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1968 Grenoble</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1968-grenoble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:27:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1968-grenoble/</guid>
      <description>The official poster of the 1968 Winter Olympics   The 1968 Winter Olympics, officially known as the X Olympic Winter Games (French: Les Xes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver), were a winter multi-sport event which was celebrated in 1968 in Grenoble, France, and opened on 6 February. Thirty-seven countries participated. The year 1968 marked the first time the IOC first permitted East and West Germany to enter separately, and the first time the IOC ever ordered drug and gender testing of competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2024 Paris</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2024-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:33:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2024-paris/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air France</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france/</guid>
      <description>Air France is the French flag carrier headquartered in Tremblay-en-France. It is a subsidiary of the Air France–KLM Group and a founding member of the SkyTeam global airline alliance. As of 2013 Air France serves 36 destinations in France and operates worldwide scheduled passenger and cargo services to 168 destinations in 78 countries (93 including overseas departments and territories of France) and also carried 46,803,000 passengers in 2015. The airline&amp;rsquo;s global hub is at Charles de Gaulle Airport with Orly Airport as the primary domestic hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citroen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</guid>
      <description> Citroën is a French automobile manufacturer, part of the PSA Peugeot Citroën group since 1976, founded in 1919 by French industrialist André-Gustave Citroën (1878–1935). In 1934, the firm established its reputation for innovative technology with the Traction Avant. This car was the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass-produced front wheel drive car, and also one of the first to feature a unitary type body, with no chassis supporting the mechanical components.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenzo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo/</guid>
      <description>Kenzo (stylized as KENZO) is a French luxury fashion house founded in 1970 by Japanese designer Kenzo Takada. Kenzo Takada was born in Japan and moved to Paris in 1964 to start his fashion career. He then became known for using Asian and Japanese influenced style with the construction of European fashion. He started out with a &amp;lsquo;Jungle Jap&amp;rsquo; boutique located in Paris and decorated in jungle inspired decor. He began with handmade women&amp;rsquo;s clothing, then in 1983 Kenzo started designing men and then kids and home collections in 1987.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>