<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pentagram on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/pentagram/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pentagram on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:52:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/pentagram/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amalgamated Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:52:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Amalgamated Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
Amalgamated Bank is the leading financial institution dedicated to providing affordable banking services to working people, unions, and progressive organizations and businesses. Established in 1923 as New York City’s first labor bank, Amalgamated is now the largest union-owned bank in the United States, with locations across the city, as well as in Washington DC, New Jersey, Nevada and California. Pentagram has designed a new brand identity for the bank that updates its look while also honoring its legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Maestro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Cirrus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</guid>
      <description>History of the MasterCard logo (from pentagram.com)
The iconic red and yellow intersecting circles of Mastercard are one of the world’s most recognized brands. Today the company launches an evolution of its brand identity featuring a new mark that highlights the connectivity and seamlessness of Mastercard and its payment systems. Designed by Pentagram, the identity brings simplicity and clarity with an increased emphasis on the interlocking circles, and is optimized for use in digital contexts, an increasingly important part of Mastercard’s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Group logo (from pentagram.com)
In 1998 financial giants Citicorp and Travelers Group merged to create Citigroup, the largest financial company in the world. After having designed the now ubiquitous identity for the newly formed entity, a three dimensional extension of the brand in the form of Citibank branch interiors and fascias was developed and implemented worldwide.
A visual language and colors and materials palette were developed to represent the new brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citibank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
In 1998 financial giants Citicorp and Travelers Group merged to create Citigroup, the largest financial company in the world. After having designed the now ubiquitous identity for the newly formed entity, a three dimensional extension of the brand in the form of Citibank branch interiors and fascias was developed and implemented worldwide.
A visual language and colors and materials palette were developed to represent the new brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Express</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</guid>
      <description>History of the American Express logo (from pentagram.com)
American Express is one of the world’s most trusted and recognized brands. Pentagram has refreshed the American Express visual identity, reasserting and amplifying the brand’s visual expression. The project sought to retool the iconic Blue Box logo, introduced in 1975, and to derive a typographic language that could also live outside the Blue Box, providing a bolder, more confident expression of the brand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>