<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>H on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/h/</link><description>Recent content in H on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/h/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanshin-tigers//file/hanshin-tigers.svg</url><title>Hanshin Tigers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hanshin Tigers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hanshin-tigers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanshin-tigers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Hanshin Tigers (Japanese: 阪神タイガース Hanshin Taigāsu) are a Nippon Professional Baseball team playing in the Central League. The team is based in Nishinomiya, Hyōgo Prefecture, Japan, and are owned by Hanshin Electric Railway Co., Ltd., a subsidiary of Hankyu Hanshin Holdings Inc.
The Hanshin Tigers are one of the oldest professional clubs in Japan. They played their first season in 1936 as the Osaka Tigers and assumed their current team name in 1961.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles//file/hanwha-eagles.svg</url><title>Hanwha Eagles Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hanwha Eagles</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles/</guid><description turbo="true">The Hanwha Eagles (Korean: 한화 이글스) is a South Korean professional baseball club based in the city of Daejeon. They are a member of the KBO League. The Eagles&amp;rsquo; home ballpark is Daejeon Hanbat Baseball Stadium. The Eagles have won the Korean Series once, in 1999, and the league pennant twice. As of 2020, the Eagles have played in the postseason 13 times, being the runner-up in the Korean Series five times.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/haggen//file/haggen.svg</url><title>Haggen Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Haggen</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/haggen/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/haggen/</guid><description turbo="true">Haggen Food &amp;amp; Pharmacy is a grocery retailer in Washington state.
Haggen is headquartered in Bellingham, Washington, where it started in 1933 when Ben Haggen, Dorothy Haggen, and Doug Clark opened the first store on Bay Street in Bellingham. For many years, Haggen was the largest independent grocery retailer in the Pacific Northwest, with locations in Washington and Oregon. From 1982 through 2014, Haggen also operated Top Food &amp;amp; Drug.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hbo//file/hbo.svg</url><title>HBO Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HBO</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hbo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hbo/</guid><description turbo="true">HBO (Home Box Office) is an American premium television network owned by Home Box Office, Inc., a subsidiary of WarnerMedia Entertainment. The programming featured on the network consists primarily of theatrically released motion pictures and original television shows, along with made-for-cable movies, documentaries and occasional comedy and concert specials.
HBO is the oldest and longest continuously operating pay television service (basic or premium) in the United States, having been in operation since November 8, 1972.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz//file/heinz.svg</url><title>Heinz Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Heinz</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz/</guid><description turbo="true">The H. J. Heinz Company, better known as Heinz, is an American food processing company headquartered at One PPG Place in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, part of the Kraft Heinz Company. The company was founded by Henry John Heinz in 1869. Heinz manufactures thousands of food products in plants on six continents, and markets these products in more than 200 countries and territories. The company claims to have 150 number-one or number-two brands worldwide.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/htc//file/htc.svg</url><title>HTC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HTC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/htc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/htc/</guid><description turbo="true">HTC Corporation (High Tech Computer Corporation, literally Hongda International Electronics Co., Ltd.) is a Taiwanese consumer electronics company headquartered in Xindian District, New Taipei City, Taiwan. Founded in 1997, HTC began as an original design manufacturer and original equipment manufacturer, designing and manufacturing laptop computers.
After initially making smartphones based mostly on Windows Mobile, HTC became a co-founding member of the Open Handset Alliance, a group of handset manufacturers and mobile network operators dedicated to the development of the Android mobile operating system.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harman//file/harman.svg</url><title>Harman Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harman</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harman/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harman/</guid><description turbo="true">Harman International Industries, Inc., commonly known as Harman, is a subsidiary of South Korea-based Samsung Electronics that produces, designs and engineers connected products for automakers, consumers and enterprises worldwide, including connected car systems; audio and visual products, enterprise automation; and connected services. Headquartered in Stamford, Connecticut, Harman maintains major operations in the Americas, Europe, as well as Asia and markets its products under several brands; such as AKG, AMX, Becker, Crown, Harman Kardon, Infinity, JBL, Lexicon, dbx, DigiTech, Mark Levinson, Martin, Revel, Soundcraft, Studer, Arcam, and BSS Audio.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harman-kardon//file/harman-kardon.svg</url><title>Harman Kardon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harman Kardon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harman-kardon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harman-kardon/</guid><description turbo="true"> Harman Kardon (styled as harman / kardon) is a division of Stamford-based Harman International Industries, a subsidiary of South Korean firm Samsung Electronics, and manufactures home and car audio equipment. It was its original division, founded in 1953 by Sidney Harman and Bernard Kardon.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawthorn//file/hawthorn.svg</url><title>Hawthorn Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hawthorn</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hawthorn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawthorn/</guid><description turbo="true"> Stay Hawthorn. Stay as you are. With free WiFi, on-site laundry services, healthy breakfast options and fitness centers, Hawthorn Suites provides everything guests need to stay on track during extended stays. Each spacious suite includes a full kitchen with dishware, glassware and utensils provided.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia//file/hearing-australia.svg</url><title>Hearing Australia Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hearing Australia</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hearing Australia is a statutory authority constituted under the Australian Hearing Services Act 1991, reporting to the Minister for Human Services, and is within the Department of Human Services portfolio. Hearing Australia is the largest Australian government-funded hearing aid dispensing company providing hearing care and technologies. One of their areas of interest is hearing testing and rehabilitation of children under the age of 26.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh//file/hmh.svg</url><title>HMH Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HMH</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</guid><description turbo="true"> Houghton Mifflin Harcourt is a publisher of textbooks, instructional technology materials, assessments, reference works, and fiction and non-fiction for both young readers and adults.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/howard-johnson//file/howard-johnson.svg</url><title>Howard Johnson Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Howard Johnson</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/howard-johnson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/howard-johnson/</guid><description turbo="true">Howard Johnson&amp;rsquo;s, or Howard Johnson by Wyndham, is an American chain of hotels and motels located primarily throughout the United States and Canada. It had also once been a chain of restaurants for over 90 years and its name was widely known for that alone. Founded by Howard Deering Johnson, it was the largest restaurant chain in the U.S. throughout the 1960s and 1970s, with more than 1,000 combined company-owned and franchised outlets.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot//file/hubspot.svg</url><title>HubSpot Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HubSpot</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot/</guid><description turbo="true"> HubSpot is a developer and marketer of software products for inbound marketing and sales. It was founded by Brian Halligan and Dharmesh Shah in 2006. Its products and services aim to provide tools for social media marketing, content management, web analytics and search engine optimization.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal//file/human-appeal.svg</url><title>Human Appeal Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Human Appeal</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</guid><description turbo="true"> Human Appeal is a British international development and relief charity based in Manchester. It was established in 1991. It runs targeted poverty relief programmes in emergency response and sustainable development. In the past, the charity was known as Human Appeal International but was restyled in 2018. It is now known as Human Appeal.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi//file/huobi.svg</url><title>Huobi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Huobi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi/</guid><description turbo="true"> Huobi (Chinese: 火币网; pinyin: Huǒbìwǎng) is a Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange. Founded in China, the company now has offices in Hong Kong, Korea, Japan and the United States. In August 2018 it became a publicly listed Hong Kong company.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins//file/harpercollins.svg</url><title>HarperCollins Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HarperCollins</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harpercollins/</guid><description turbo="true">HarperCollins Publishers L.L.C. is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest publishing companies and is one of the Big Five English-language publishing companies, alongside Penguin Random House, Simon &amp;amp; Schuster, Hachette and Macmillan. The company is headquartered in New York City and is a subsidiary of News Corp. The name is a combination of several publishing firm names: Harper &amp;amp; Row, an American publishing company acquired in 1987 (whose own name was the result of an earlier merger of Harper &amp;amp; Brothers (founded 1817) and Row, Peterson &amp;amp; Company), together with UK publishing company William Collins, Sons (founded 1819), acquired in 1990.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press//file/harvard-university-press.svg</url><title>Harvard University Press Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harvard University Press</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university-press/</guid><description turbo="true"> Harvard University Press (HUP) is a publishing house established on January 13, 1913, as a division of Harvard University, and focused on academic publishing. It is a member of the Association of American University Presses. After the retirement of William P. Sisler in 2017, the university appointed as Director George Andreou.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners//file/healthpartners.svg</url><title>HealthPartners Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HealthPartners</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/healthpartners/</guid><description turbo="true"> HealthPartners is an integrated, nonprofit health care provider and health insurance company located in Bloomington, Minnesota offering care, coverage, research and education to its members, patients and the community.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hellenic-petroleum//file/hellenic-petroleum.svg</url><title>Hellenic Petroleum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hellenic Petroleum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hellenic-petroleum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hellenic-petroleum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hellenic Petroleum S.A. is one of the largest oil companies in the Balkans and with its roots dating to 1958 with the establishment of the first oil refinery in Greece (Aspropyrgos).
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hilton//file/hilton.svg</url><title>Hilton Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hilton</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hilton/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hilton/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hilton Worldwide Holdings Inc., formerly Hilton Hotels Corporation, is an American multinational hospitality company that manages and franchises a broad portfolio of hotels and resorts. Founded by Conrad Hilton in May 1919, the corporation is now led by Christopher J. Nassetta.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn//file/hkbn.svg</url><title>HKBN Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HKBN</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn/</guid><description turbo="true"> HKBN Limited (Chinese: 香港寬頻有限公司), commonly known for its subsidiary Hong Kong Broadband Network Limited (Chinese: 香港寬頻網絡), is a Hong Kong-based telecommunication company. Hong Kong Broadband Network Limited was established on 23 August 1999, is one of the largest residential broadband and telecommunications service providers in Hong Kong. HKBN operates in both Hong Kong and Guangzhou, and employs about 2,900 personnel
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn//file/holiday-inn.svg</url><title>Holiday Inn Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Holiday Inn</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</guid><description turbo="true"> Holiday Inn is a British-owned American brand of hotels, and a subsidiary of InterContinental Hotels Group. Founded as a U.S. motel chain, it has grown to be one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest hotel chains, with 1,173 active hotels and over 214,000 bedrooms as of September 30, 2018. The hotel chain&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Denham, Buckinghamshire.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyatt//file/hyatt.svg</url><title>Hyatt Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hyatt</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hyatt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyatt/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hyatt Hotels Corporation is an American multinational hospitality company that manages and franchises luxury hotels, resorts, and vacation properties. The Hyatt Corporation came into being upon purchase of the Hyatt House, at Los Angeles International Airport, on September 27, 1957. As of March 25, 2018, Hyatt has 777 properties in 54 countries. Fortune magazine ranked Hyatt #186 on its list of &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Best Employers&amp;rdquo; for 2018.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo//file/houston-dynamo.svg</url><title>Houston Dynamo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houston Dynamo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo/</guid><description turbo="true">Houston Dynamo are an American professional soccer club based in Houston, Texas. The franchise competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), as a member of the Western Conference. The Dynamo had first played their home games at Robertson Stadium on the University of Houston campus until 2011. Since 2012, the Dynamo has played home matches at BBVA Stadium, a soccer-specific stadium located in Houston. The team&amp;rsquo;s head coach is Wilmer Cabrera.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-rockets//file/houston-rockets.svg</url><title>Houston Rockets Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houston Rockets</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-rockets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-rockets/</guid><description turbo="true">The Houston Rockets are an American professional basketball team based in Houston, Texas. The Rockets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The team plays its home games at the Toyota Center, located in downtown Houston. The Rockets have won two NBA championships and four Western Conference titles. The team was established in 1967 as the San Diego Rockets, an expansion team originally based in San Diego.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy//file/hennessy.svg</url><title>Hennessy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hennessy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hennessy/</guid><description turbo="true"> Jas Hennessy &amp;amp; Co., commonly known simply as Hennessy, is a brandy distiller with its headquarters located in Cognac, France. Jas Hennessy &amp;amp; Co. sells about 50 million bottles a year worldwide, or more than 40 percent of the world&amp;rsquo;s cognac, making it the largest cognac producer.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros//file/houston-astros.svg</url><title>Houston Astros Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houston Astros</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Houston Astros are an American professional baseball team based in Houston, Texas. The Astros compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West division, having moved to the division in 2013 after spending their first 51 seasons in the National League (NL). The Astros have played their home games at Minute Maid Park since 2000.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-texans//file/houston-texans.svg</url><title>Houston Texans Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houston Texans</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-texans/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-texans/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Houston Texans are a professional American football team based in Houston, Texas. The Texans compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) South division. The team plays its home games at NRG Stadium.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi//file/hitachi.svg</url><title>Hitachi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hitachi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi/</guid><description turbo="true">Hitachi, Ltd. is a Japanese multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan. It is the parent company of the Hitachi Group (Hitachi Gurūpu) and forms part of the DKB Group of companies. Hitachi is a highly diversified company that operates eleven business segments: Information &amp;amp; Telecommunication Systems, Social Infrastructure, High Functional Materials &amp;amp; Components, Financial Services, Power Systems, Electronic Systems &amp;amp; Equipment, Automotive Systems, Railway &amp;amp; Urban Systems, Digital Media &amp;amp; Consumer Products, Construction Machinery and Other Components &amp;amp; Systems.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot//file/home-depot.svg</url><title>Home Depot Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Home Depot</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</guid><description turbo="true"> Home Depot is an American home improvement supplies retailing company that sells tools, construction products, and services. The company is headquartered at the Atlanta Store Support Center in unincorporated Cobb County, Georgia (with an Atlanta mailing address).
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houzz//file/houzz.svg</url><title>Houzz Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houzz</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houzz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houzz/</guid><description turbo="true"> Houzz is a website and online community about architecture, interior design and decorating, landscape design and home improvement. It was founded in 2009 and is based in Palo Alto, California, United States.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm//file/hm.svg</url><title>H&amp;M Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">H&amp;M</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</guid><description turbo="true">Hennes &amp;amp; Mauritz AB is a Swedish multinational clothing-retail company known for its fast-fashion clothing for men, women, teenagers and children. H&amp;amp;M and its associated companies operate in 62 countries with over 4,500 stores and as of 2015 employed around 132,000 people. It is the second-largest global clothing Retail, just behind Spain-based Inditex (parent company of Zara). The company has a significant online presence, with online shopping available in 33 countries:</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines//file/hainan-airlines.svg</url><title>Hainan Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hainan Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">Hainan Airlines is an airline headquartered in Haikou, Hainan, People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It is the largest civilian-run air transport company, the fourth-largest airline in terms of fleet size in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, and fourth-largest airline in Asia in terms of passengers carried. It operates scheduled domestic and international services on 500 routes from Hainan and nine locations on the mainland, as well as charter services. Its main base is Haikou Meilan International Airport, with hubs at Beijing Capital International Airport and Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport and several focus cities.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harley//file/harley.svg</url><title>Harley Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harley</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harley/</guid><description turbo="true">Harley-Davidson, Inc., H-D, or Harley, is an American motorcycle manufacturer founded in 1903 in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. It was one of two major American motorcycle manufacturers to survive the Great Depression, along with Indian. The company has survived numerous ownership arrangements, subsidiary arrangements, periods of poor economic health and product quality, and intense global competition to become one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest motorcycle manufacturers and an iconic brand widely known for its loyal following.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines//file/hawaiian-airlines.svg</url><title>Hawaiian Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hawaiian Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken//file/heineken.svg</url><title>Heineken Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Heineken</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/heineken/</guid><description turbo="true"> Heineken Lager Beer is a pale lager beer with 5% alcohol by volume produced by the Dutch brewing company Heineken International. Heineken is well known for its signature green bottle and red star.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes//file/hermes.svg</url><title>Hermes Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hermes</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hermès International S.A., or simply Hermès is a French high fashion luxury goods manufacturer established in 1837. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. Its logo, since the 1950s, is of a Duc carriage with horse. Nadège Vanhee-Cybulski is the current creative director.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda//file/honda.svg</url><title>Honda Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Honda</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</guid><description turbo="true"> Honda Motor Company, Ltd. is a Japanese public multinational conglomerate corporation primarily known as a manufacturer of automobiles, motorcycles, and power equipment.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hp//file/hp.svg</url><title>HP Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HP</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hp/</guid><description turbo="true"> HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe//file/hpe.svg</url><title>HPE Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HPE</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</guid><description turbo="true">HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
Source Source In October 2014, the Hewlett-Packard Company announced its intention to split into two separate entities, signaling the largest corporate demerger in history. The two resulting companies would each remain Fortune 100 industry leaders—with HP, Inc.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei//file/huawei.svg</url><title>Huawei Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Huawei</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</guid><description turbo="true"> Huawei Technologies Co. Ltd. is a Chinese multinational technology company that provides telecommunications equipment and sells consumer electronics, including smartphones, headquartered in Shenzhen, Guangdong.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai//file/hyundai.svg</url><title>Hyundai Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hyundai</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Hyundai Motor Company, is a South Korean multinational automotive manufacturer headquartered in Seoul. The company was founded in 1967 and, along with its 32.8% owned subsidiary, Kia Motors, and its 100% owned luxury subsidiary Genesis Motor, altogether comprise the Hyundai Motor Group. It is the third largest vehicle manufacturer in the world.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school//file/harvard-medical-school.svg</url><title>Harvard Medical School Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harvard Medical School</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school/</guid><description turbo="true">About Harvard Medical School (from harvard.edu)
Established in 1782, Harvard Medical School began with a handful of students and a faculty of three. The first classes were held in Harvard Hall in Cambridge, long before the School’s iconic quadrangle was built in Boston. With each passing decade, the School’s faculty and trainees amassed knowledge and influence, shaping medicine in the United States and beyond. Some community members—and their accomplishments—have assumed the status of legend.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university//file/harvard-university.svg</url><title>Harvard University Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Harvard University</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university/</guid><description turbo="true">About Harvard Univarsity (from wikipedia.org)
Harvard University Coat of Arms Harvard University is a private Ivy League research university in Cambridge, Massachusetts, with about 6,700 undergraduate students and about 15,250 postgraduate students. Established in 1636 and named for its first benefactor, clergyman John Harvard, Harvard is the United States&amp;rsquo; oldest institution of higher learning. Its history, influence, and wealth have made it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prestigious universities.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists//file/houston-fertility-specialists.svg</url><title>Houston Fertility Specialists Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houston Fertility Specialists</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</guid><description turbo="true"/></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank//file/hsbc-bank.svg</url><title>Hsbc Bank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hsbc Bank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</guid><description turbo="true">About HSBC Bank The HSBC brand is recognised worldwide. Hsbc Bank latest advertising illustrates Hsbc Bank role in helping people, businesses and communities to thrive.
HSBC is one of the largest banking and financial services organisations in the world, with operations in 66 countries and territories. Hsbc Bank aim to be where the growth is, enabling businesses to thrive and economies to prosper, and, ultimately, helping people to fulfil their hopes and realise their ambitions.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content/></rss>