<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>H on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/h/</link>
    <description>Recent content in H on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/h/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi/</guid>
      <description>Hitachi, Ltd. is a Japanese multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan. It is the parent company of the Hitachi Group (Hitachi Gurūpu) and forms part of the DKB Group of companies. Hitachi is a highly diversified company that operates eleven business segments: Information &amp;amp; Telecommunication Systems, Social Infrastructure, High Functional Materials &amp;amp; Components, Financial Services, Power Systems, Electronic Systems &amp;amp; Equipment, Automotive Systems, Railway &amp;amp; Urban Systems, Digital Media &amp;amp; Consumer Products, Construction Machinery and Other Components &amp;amp; Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</guid>
      <description> Home Depot is an American home improvement supplies retailing company that sells tools, construction products, and services. The company is headquartered at the Atlanta Store Support Center in unincorporated Cobb County, Georgia (with an Atlanta mailing address).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houzz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houzz/</guid>
      <description> Houzz is a website and online community about architecture, interior design and decorating, landscape design and home improvement. It was founded in 2009 and is based in Palo Alto, California, United States.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hainan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hainan Airlines is an airline headquartered in Haikou, Hainan, People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It is the largest civilian-run air transport company, the fourth-largest airline in terms of fleet size in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, and fourth-largest airline in Asia in terms of passengers carried. It operates scheduled domestic and international services on 500 routes from Hainan and nine locations on the mainland, as well as charter services. Its main base is Haikou Meilan International Airport, with hubs at Beijing Capital International Airport and Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport and several focus cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</guid>
      <description> Honda Motor Company, Ltd. is a Japanese public multinational conglomerate corporation primarily known as a manufacturer of automobiles, motorcycles, and power equipment.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hyundai/</guid>
      <description> The Hyundai Motor Company, is a South Korean multinational automotive manufacturer headquartered in Seoul. The company was founded in 1967 and, along with its 32.8% owned subsidiary, Kia Motors, and its 100% owned luxury subsidiary Genesis Motor, altogether comprise the Hyundai Motor Group. It is the third largest vehicle manufacturer in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard Medical School</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-medical-school/</guid>
      <description>About Harvard Medical School (from harvard.edu)
Established in 1782, Harvard Medical School began with a handful of students and a faculty of three. The first classes were held in Harvard Hall in Cambridge, long before the School’s iconic quadrangle was built in Boston. With each passing decade, the School’s faculty and trainees amassed knowledge and influence, shaping medicine in the United States and beyond. Some community members—and their accomplishments—have assumed the status of legend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard University</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harvard-university/</guid>
      <description>About Harvard Univarsity (from wikipedia.org)
Harvard University Coat of Arms  Harvard University is a private Ivy League research university in Cambridge, Massachusetts, with about 6,700 undergraduate students and about 15,250 postgraduate students. Established in 1636 and named for its first benefactor, clergyman John Harvard, Harvard is the United States&amp;rsquo; oldest institution of higher learning. Its history, influence, and wealth have made it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prestigious universities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Fertility Specialists</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hsbc Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</guid>
      <description>About HSBC Bank  The HSBC brand is recognised worldwide. Our latest advertising illustrates our role in helping people, businesses and communities to thrive.
 HSBC is one of the largest banking and financial services organisations in the world, with operations in 66 countries and territories. We aim to be where the growth is, enabling businesses to thrive and economies to prosper, and, ultimately, helping people to fulfil their hopes and realise their ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>