<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>A on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/a/</link><description>Recent content in A on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amy-klobuchar//file/amy-klobuchar.svg</url><title>Amy Klobuchar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Amy Klobuchar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amy-klobuchar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amy-klobuchar/</guid><description turbo="true"> The 2020 Presidential Campaign of Amy Klobuchar, the senior United States senator from Minnesota and former Hennepin County attorney, was formally announced on February 10, 2019 in Minneapolis. Prior to her announcement, Klobuchar had been discussed as a potential candidate for the office by multiple news publications.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/att//file/att.svg</url><title>AT&amp;T Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AT&amp;T</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/att/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0014</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/att/</guid><description turbo="true">About AT&amp;amp;T AT&amp;amp;T Inc. began its history as Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, which was a subsidiary of the Bell Telephone Company founded by Alexander Graham Bell in 1880. Bell Telephone Company evolved into American Telephone and Telegraph Company in 1885 which had since rebranded to AT&amp;amp;T Corporation. Now AT&amp;amp;T Inc. is an American multinational conglomerate holding company, headquartered at Whitacre Tower in downtown Dallas, Texas. AT&amp;amp;T is the world’s largest telecommunications company.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon//file/amazon.svg</url><title>Amazon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Amazon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0004</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon/</guid><description turbo="true">History of the Amazon Logo (from logomyway.com and 1000logos.net) The Amazon logo has had three different iterations over the years, but neither of the first two stuck around for very long. The company’s first logo was simply the word Amazon.com spelled out in black font with a larger, yellow font used for the “o”. This design was later replaced with a logo that featured the company name with a near-straight yellow line beneath it.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple//file/apple.svg</url><title>Apple Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0001</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</guid><description turbo="true">History of Apple logo At the time of his initial meeting with Steve Jobs in early 1977, Apple Computer was still very much in its infancy, having been incorporated for less than a year. Apple’s offices were in a local strip mall, and consisted of just the three partners – Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Mike Markkula.
The initial identity development was to coincide with the introduction of the brand’s first personal computer, the Apple II.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe-audition//file/adobe-audition.svg</url><title>Adobe Audition Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Adobe Audition</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe-audition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe-audition/</guid><description turbo="true">Adobe Audition, formerly Cool Edit Pro, is a digital audio workstation from Adobe Systems featuring both a multitrack, non-destructive mix/edit environment and a destructive-approach waveform editing view.
Source About Adobe Audition Edit, mix, record, and restore audio. Audition is a comprehensive toolset that includes multitrack, waveform, and spectral display for creating, mixing, editing, and restoring audio content. This powerful audio workstation is designed to accelerate video production workflows and audio finishing — and deliver a polished mix with pristine sound.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/autocad//file/autocad.svg</url><title>AutoCAD Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AutoCAD</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/autocad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/autocad/</guid><description turbo="true">AutoCAD is a commercial computer-aided design (CAD) and drafting software application. Developed and marketed by Autodesk, AutoCAD was first released in December 1982 as a desktop app running on microcomputers with internal graphics controllers.[2] Before AutoCAD was introduced, most commercial CAD programs ran on mainframe computers or minicomputers, with each CAD operator (user) working at a separate graphics terminal. Since 2010, AutoCAD was released as a mobile- and web app as well, marketed as AutoCAD 360.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk//file/autodesk.svg</url><title>Autodesk Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Autodesk</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk/</guid><description turbo="true">Autodesk, Inc. is an American multinational software corporation that makes software products and services for the architecture, engineering, construction, manufacturing, media, education, and entertainment industries. Autodesk is headquartered in San Rafael, California, and features a gallery of its customers&amp;rsquo; work in its San Francisco building. The company has offices worldwide. Its U.S. locations are California, Oregon, Colorado, Texas, Michigan, New Hampshire and Massachusetts. Its Canada offices are located in Ontario, Quebec, and Alberta.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk-123d//file/autodesk-123d.svg</url><title>Autodesk 123D Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Autodesk 123D</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk-123d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/autodesk-123d/</guid><description turbo="true">Autodesk 123D was a suite of hobbyist CAD and 3D modelling tools created by Autodesk. It is similar in scope to Trimble SketchUp and is based on Autodesk Inventor. As well as the more basic drawing and modelling capabilities it also has assembly and constraint support and STL export. Available for the software is also a library of ready-made blocks and objects.
Autodesk is also working in collaboration with three companies (Ponoko, Techshop and 3D Systems) to enable users of 123D to create physical objects from their designs using 3D printing technology.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/avast//file/avast.svg</url><title>Avast Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Avast</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/avast/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/avast/</guid><description turbo="true">Avast Software s.r.o. is a Czech multinational cybersecurity software company headquartered in Prague, Czech Republic that researches and develops computer security software, machine learning and artificial intelligence. Avast has more than 435 million monthly active users and the second largest market share among anti-malware application vendors worldwide as of April 2020. The company has approximately 1,700 employees across its 25 offices worldwide.
Avast was founded by Pavel Baudiš and Eduard Kučera in 1988 as a cooperative.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/azure//file/azure.svg</url><title>Azure Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Azure</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/azure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/azure/</guid><description turbo="true">Microsoft Azure, commonly referred to as Azure (/ˈæʒər/), is a cloud computing service created by Microsoft for building, testing, deploying, and managing applications and services through Microsoft-managed data centers. It provides software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (PaaS) and infrastructure as a service (IaaS) and supports many different programming languages, tools, and frameworks, including both Microsoft-specific and third-party software and systems.
Azure was announced in October 2008, started with codename &amp;ldquo;Project Red Dog&amp;rdquo;, and released on February 1, 2010, as Windows Azure before being renamed to Microsoft Azure on March 25, 2014.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/acer//file/acer.svg</url><title>Acer Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Acer</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/acer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acer/</guid><description turbo="true"> Acer Inc. (/ˈeɪsər/ AY-sər; Chinese: 宏碁股份有限公司; pinyin: Hóngqí Gǔfèn Yǒuxiàn Gōngsī, lit. Hongqi Corporation Ltd.; commonly known as Acer and stylized as acer) is a Taiwanese multinational hardware and electronics corporation, specializing in advanced electronics technology, headquartered in Xizhi, New Taipei City, Taiwan. Acer&amp;rsquo;s products include desktop PCs, laptop PCs (clamshells, 2-in-1s, convertibles and Chromebooks), tablets, servers, storage devices, virtual reality devices, displays, smartphones and peripherals.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/acme//file/acme.svg</url><title>ACME Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ACME</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/acme/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acme/</guid><description turbo="true"> Acme Markets Inc. is a supermarket chain operating 164 stores throughout Connecticut, Delaware, Maryland, New Jersey, New York, and Pennsylvania and, as of 1999, is a subsidiary of Albertsons, and part of its presence in the Northeast. It is headquartered in East Whiteland Township, Pennsylvania, near Malvern, a Philadelphia suburb.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/activision//file/activision.svg</url><title>Activision Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Activision</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/activision/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/activision/</guid><description turbo="true"> Activision Publishing, Inc. is an American video game publisher based in Santa Monica, California. It currently serves as the publishing business for its parent company, Activision Blizzard, and consists of several subsidiary studios. Activision is one of the largest third-party video game publishers in the world and was the top United States publisher in 2016.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts//file/advance-auto-parts.svg</url><title>Advance Auto Parts Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Advance Auto Parts</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts/</guid><description turbo="true">Advance Auto Parts, Inc. (Advance) is an American automotive aftermarket parts provider. Headquartered in Raleigh, North Carolina, it serves both professional installer and do-it-yourself (DIY) customers. As of July 13, 2019, Advance operated 4,912 stores and 150 Worldpac branches in the United States and Canada. The Company also serves 1,250 independently owned Carquest branded stores across these locations in addition to Mexico, the Bahamas, Turks and Caicos and British Virgin Islands.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-jordan//file/air-jordan.svg</url><title>Air Jordan Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Air Jordan</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/air-jordan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-jordan/</guid><description turbo="true"> Air Jordan is a brand of basketball shoes, athletic, casual, and style clothing produced by Nike. It was created for former NBA player and 6 time NBA Finals MVP Michael Jordan. The original Air Jordan sneakers were produced exclusively for Michael Jordan in early 1984, and released to the public in late 1984. The shoes were designed for Nike by Peter Moore, Tinker Hatfield, and Bruce Kilgore.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/airasia//file/airasia.svg</url><title>AirAsia Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AirAsia</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/airasia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/airasia/</guid><description turbo="true">AirAsia Berhad is a Malaysian low-cost airline headquartered near Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. It is the largest airline in Malaysia by fleet size and destinations. AirAsia Group operates scheduled domestic and international flights to more than 165 destinations spanning 25 countries. Its main hub is klia2, the low-cost carrier terminal at Kuala Lumpur International Airport (KLIA) in Sepang, Selangor, Malaysia. Its affiliate airlines Thai AirAsia, Indonesia AirAsia, Philippines AirAsia, AirAsia India and AirAsia Japan have hubs in Bangkok-Don Mueang, Jakarta-Soekarno–Hatta , Manila-Ninoy Aquino, Bengaluru (Bangalore)-Kempegowda and Nayoga-Chübu Centair airports respectively, while its sister airline, AirAsia X, focuses on long-haul routes.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/akamai//file/akamai.svg</url><title>Akamai Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Akamai</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/akamai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/akamai/</guid><description turbo="true">Akamai Technologies, Inc. is an American content delivery network (CDN), cybersecurity, and cloud service provider headquartered in Cambridge, Massachusetts, in the United States. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s content delivery network is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest distributed computing platforms, responsible for serving between 15% and 30% of all web traffic. The company operates a network of servers around the world and rents out capacity on these servers to customers who want their websites to work faster by distributing content from locations close to the user.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/alaska-airlines//file/alaska-airlines.svg</url><title>Alaska Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Alaska Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/alaska-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alaska-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">Alaska Airlines is a major American airline headquartered in SeaTac, Washington, within the Seattle metropolitan area. It is the fifth largest airline in the United States when measured by fleet size, scheduled passengers carried, and number of destinations served. Alaska, together with its regional partners Horizon Air and SkyWest Airlines, operate a large domestic route network, primarily focused on connecting from the Pacific Northwest and Alaska to over one hundred destinations in the contiguous United States, Hawaii, Canada, Costa Rica, and Mexico.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/albertsons//file/albertsons.svg</url><title>Albertsons Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Albertsons</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/albertsons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/albertsons/</guid><description turbo="true">Albertsons Companies, Inc. is an American grocery company founded and headquartered in Boise, Idaho. It is privately owned and operated by investors, including Cerberus Capital Management.
With 2,260 stores as of the third quarter of fiscal 2019 and 267,000 employees as of fiscal 2018, the company is the second-largest supermarket chain in North America after Kroger, which has 2,758 stores. Albertsons ranked 53rd in the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/alibaba//file/alibaba.svg</url><title>Alibaba Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Alibaba</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/alibaba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alibaba/</guid><description turbo="true">Alibaba Group Holding Limited (also known as Alibaba Group and as Alibaba) is a Chinese multinational technology company specializing in e-commerce, retail, Internet, and technology. Founded on 4 April 1999 in Hangzhou, Zhejiang, the company provides consumer-to-consumer (C2C), business-to-consumer (B2C), and business-to-business (B2B) sales services via web portals, as well as electronic payment services, shopping search engines and cloud computing services. It owns and operates a diverse array of businesses around the world in numerous sectors, and is named as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most admired companies by Fortune.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/allergan//file/allergan.svg</url><title>Allergan Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Allergan</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/allergan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/allergan/</guid><description turbo="true">Allergan plc is an Irish-domiciled pharmaceutical company that acquires, develops, and markets brand name drugs, and in 2017 generated 80% net sales from the U.S. healthcare system. Allergan plc was formed in February 2015 when Irish–registered Actavis plc acquired U.S.–registered Allergan, Inc., and assumed the Allergan name. Actavis was a 2013 U.S. tax inversion that moved its legal domicile to Ireland to avoid U.S. taxes. Actavis used the Irish low-tax corporate system to acquire large U.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amd//file/amd.svg</url><title>AMD Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AMD</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amd/</guid><description turbo="true">Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (AMD) is a multinational semiconductor company based in Santa Clara County, California that develops computer processors and related technologies for business and consumer markets. While initially it manufactured its own processors, the company later outsourced its manufacturing, a practice known as going fabless, after GlobalFoundries was spun off in 2009. AMD&amp;rsquo;s main products include microprocessors, motherboard chipsets, embedded processors and graphics processors for servers, workstations, personal computers and embedded system applications.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amerisourcebergen//file/amerisourcebergen.svg</url><title>AmerisourceBergen Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AmerisourceBergen</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amerisourcebergen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amerisourcebergen/</guid><description turbo="true">AmerisourceBergen Corporation is an American drug wholesale company that was formed by the merger of Bergen Brunswig and AmeriSource in 2001. They provide drug distribution and related services designed to reduce costs and improve patient outcomes, distribute a line of brand name and generic pharmaceuticals, over-the-counter (OTC) health care products and home health care supplies and equipment to a wide variety of health care providers located throughout the United States, including acute care hospitals and health systems, independent and chain retail pharmacies, mail-order facilities, physicians, clinics and other alternate site facilities, as well as skilled nursing and assisted living centers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apache//file/apache.svg</url><title>Apache Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apache</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apache/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apache/</guid><description turbo="true"> Apache Corporation is a company engaged in hydrocarbon exploration. It is organized in Delaware and headquartered in Houston. The company is ranked 411th on the Fortune 500.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arm//file/arm.svg</url><title>ARM Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ARM</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arm/</guid><description turbo="true">Arm Holdings (stylized as arm) is a global semiconductor and software design company, owned by the Japanese SoftBank Group and its Vision Fund. With its global headquarters in Cambridgeshire, in the United Kingdom, and its US headquarters in San Jose, California, its primary business is in the design of ARM processors (CPUs), although it also designs software development tools under the DS-5, RealView and Keil brands, as well as systems and platforms, system-on-a-chip (SoC) infrastructure and software.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi//file/asahi.svg</url><title>Asahi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Asahi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asahi/</guid><description turbo="true">Asahi Group Holdings, Ltd. is a global beer, spirits, soft drinks and food business group headquartered in Tokyo, Japan.
In 2018, the group had a revenue JPY 2.1 trillion. Asahi&amp;rsquo;s revenue can be segmented as follows: alcoholic beverage business (41.3%), overseas business (32%), soft drinks business (16.6%), food business (5.2%) and &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; business (4.9%). Asahi, with a 37% market share, is the largest of the four major beer brewers in Japan followed by Kirin Beer with 34% and Suntory with 16%.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amx//file/amx.svg</url><title>AMX Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AMX</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amx/</guid><description turbo="true"> AMX (formerly AMX, LLC) is an American manufacturer of video switching and control devices. It is currently owned by Samsung Electronics through Harman International Industries, and is part of the Harman Professional Division.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/android//file/android.svg</url><title>Android Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Android</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/android/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/android/</guid><description turbo="true"> Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android is developed by a consortium of developers known as the Open Handset Alliance, with the main contributor and commercial marketer being Google.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlassian//file/atlassian.svg</url><title>Atlassian Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Atlassian</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/atlassian/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlassian/</guid><description turbo="true"> Atlassian Corporation Plc is an Australian enterprise software company that develops products for software developers, project managers, and content management. It is best known for its issue tracking application, Jira, and its team collaboration and wiki product, Confluence. Atlassian serves over 135,000 customers.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/audio-technica//file/audio-technica.svg</url><title>Audio-Technica Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Audio-Technica</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/audio-technica/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/audio-technica/</guid><description turbo="true"> Audio-Technica Corporation (株式会社オーディオテクニカ Kabushiki Kaisha Ōdio Tekunika) is a Japanese company that designs and manufactures professional microphones, headphones, phonographic magnetic cartridges, and other audio equipment.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-new-zealand//file/air-new-zealand.svg</url><title>Air New Zealand Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Air New Zealand</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/air-new-zealand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-new-zealand/</guid><description turbo="true"> Air New Zealand Limited is the flag carrier airline of New Zealand. Based in Auckland, the airline operates scheduled passenger flights to 20 domestic and 31 international destinations in 19 countries around the Pacific Rim and the United Kingdom. The airline has been a member of the Star Alliance since 1999.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/al-jazeera//file/al-jazeera.svg</url><title>Al Jazeera Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Al Jazeera</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/al-jazeera/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/al-jazeera/</guid><description turbo="true"> Al Jazeera is a state-funded broadcaster in Doha, Qatar, owned by the Al Jazeera Media Network. Initially launched as an Arabic news and current-affairs satellite TV channel, Al Jazeera has since expanded into a network with several outlets, including the Internet and specialty television channels in multiple languages.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet//file/animal-planet.svg</url><title>Animal Planet Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Animal Planet</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</guid><description turbo="true"> Animal Planet is an American pay television channel owned by Discovery, Inc. First established on October 1, 1996, the network is primarily devoted to series and documentaries about wild animals and domestic pets.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium//file/arthur-ashe-stadium.svg</url><title>Arthur Ashe Stadium Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Arthur Ashe Stadium</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</guid><description turbo="true"> Arthur Ashe Stadium is a tennis stadium at Flushing Meadows-Corona Park in Queens, New York City. Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center, it is the main stadium of the US Open tennis tournament, and the largest tennis stadium in the world, with a capacity of 23,771.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/avery//file/avery.svg</url><title>Avery Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Avery</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/avery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/avery/</guid><description turbo="true"> Avery Products Corporation is one of the world’s leading manufacturers of self-adhesive labels, labeling software, binders, dividers and other products, and markets under the well-known Avery® brand. Throughout Avery history, Avery has built a solid reputation as the trusted brand and leading resource for organization and identification solutions.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/anaheim-ducks//file/anaheim-ducks.svg</url><title>Anaheim Ducks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Anaheim Ducks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/anaheim-ducks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/anaheim-ducks/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Anaheim Ducks are a professional ice hockey team based in Anaheim, California. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). Since their inception, the Ducks have played their home games at the Honda Center.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-coyotes//file/arizona-coyotes.svg</url><title>Arizona Coyotes Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Arizona Coyotes</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-coyotes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-coyotes/</guid><description turbo="true">The Arizona Coyotes are a professional ice hockey team based in the Phoenix suburb of Glendale, Arizona. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Coyotes first played at America West Arena in downtown Phoenix, before moving to Glendale&amp;rsquo;s Gila River Arena in 2003. In 2021, the Coyotes are scheduled to return to the Central Division when an expansion team in Seattle joins the league.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-hawks//file/atlanta-hawks.svg</url><title>Atlanta Hawks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Atlanta Hawks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-hawks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-hawks/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Atlanta Hawks are an American professional basketball team based in Atlanta, Georgia. The Hawks compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Southeast Division. The team plays its home games at State Farm Arena.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-united-fc//file/atlanta-united-fc.svg</url><title>Atlanta United FC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Atlanta United FC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-united-fc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-united-fc/</guid><description turbo="true"> Atlanta United FC, commonly known as Atlanta United, is an American professional soccer club based in Atlanta, Georgia that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference. It is the most recent winner of the MLS Cup.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/austin-fc//file/austin-fc.svg</url><title>Austin FC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Austin FC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/austin-fc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/austin-fc/</guid><description turbo="true"> Austin FC is a professional soccer franchise based in Austin, Texas. Austin FC will compete in Major League Soccer in 2021, and will open a new stadium on McKalla Place in north central Austin the same year.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants//file/aw-restaurants.svg</url><title>AW Restaurants Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AW Restaurants</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants/</guid><description turbo="true">A&amp;amp;W Restaurants, Inc. is a chain of fast-food restaurants distinguished by its draft root beer, root beer floats and burgers. Its origins date back to 1919 when Roy W. Allen opened a walk-up root beer stand in Lodi, California. Allen&amp;rsquo;s employee Frank Wright partnered with him and they founded their first restaurant in Sacramento, California, in 1923. The company name was taken respectively from the initials of their last names—Allen and Wright.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer//file/aw-root-beer.svg</url><title>AW Root Beer Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AW Root Beer</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</guid><description turbo="true"> A&amp;amp;W Root Beer is a root beer brand primarily available in the United States and Canada, started in 1919 by Roy W. Allen. In 1922, Allen partnered with Frank Wright. They combined their initials to create the brand &amp;ldquo;A&amp;amp;W&amp;rdquo; and inspired a restaurant chain, founded in 1922. Originally, A&amp;amp;W root beer drinks sold for five cents.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aol//file/aol.svg</url><title>AOL Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AOL</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aol/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aol/</guid><description turbo="true"> AOL (stylized as Aol., formerly a company known as AOL Inc. and originally known as America Online) is an American web portal and online service provider based in New York City. It is a brand marketed by Verizon Media.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-cardinals//file/arizona-cardinals.svg</url><title>Arizona Cardinals Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Arizona Cardinals</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-cardinals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-cardinals/</guid><description turbo="true">The Arizona Cardinals are a professional American football franchise based in the Phoenix metropolitan area. The Cardinals compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) West division. The Cardinals were founded as the Morgan Athletic Club in 1898, and are the oldest continuously run professional football team in the United States.[4] The Cardinals play their home games at State Farm Stadium, which opened in 2006 and is located in the northwestern suburb of Glendale.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-diamondbacks//file/arizona-diamondbacks.svg</url><title>Arizona Diamondbacks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Arizona Diamondbacks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-diamondbacks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-diamondbacks/</guid><description turbo="true">The Arizona Diamondbacks, often shortened as the D-backs, are an American professional baseball team based in Phoenix, Arizona. The club competes in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the National League (NL) West division. The team has played every home game in franchise history at Chase Field, formerly known as Bank One Ballpark. The Diamondbacks have won one World Series championship (defeating the New York Yankees in 2001) – becoming the fastest expansion team in the Major Leagues to win a championship, which it did in only the fourth season since the franchise&amp;rsquo;s inception.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-braves//file/atlanta-braves.svg</url><title>Atlanta Braves Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Atlanta Braves</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-braves/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-braves/</guid><description turbo="true">The Atlanta Braves are an American professional baseball franchise based in the Atlanta metropolitan area. The franchise competes in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the National League (NL) East division. The Braves played home games at Atlanta–Fulton County Stadium from 1966 to 1996, and Turner Field from 1997 to 2016. Since 2017, their home stadium has been SunTrust Park, located 10 miles (16 km) northwest of downtown Atlanta in Cumberland, Georgia.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-falcons//file/atlanta-falcons.svg</url><title>Atlanta Falcons Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Atlanta Falcons</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-falcons/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-falcons/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Atlanta Falcons are a professional American football team based in Atlanta, Georgia. The Falcons compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The Falcons joined the NFL in 1965[5] as an expansion team, after the NFL offered then-owner Rankin Smith a franchise to keep him from joining the rival American Football League (AFL).
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/adidas//file/adidas.svg</url><title>Adidas Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Adidas</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/adidas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/adidas/</guid><description turbo="true">Adidas AG is a multinational corporation, founded and headquartered in Herzogenaurach, Germany, that designs and manufactures shoes, clothing and accessories. It is the largest sportswear manufacturer in Europe, and the second largest in the world, after Nike. It is the holding company for the Adidas Group, which consists of the Reebok sportswear company, TaylorMade golf company (including Ashworth), Runtastic, an Austrian fitness technology company and 8.33% of German football club Bayern Munich.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/asics//file/asics.svg</url><title>Asics Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Asics</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/asics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asics/</guid><description turbo="true">ASICS (アシックス Ashikkusu) (stylized in all lowercase and italicized) is a Japanese multinational corporation which produces footwear and sports equipment designed for a wide range of sports, generally in the upper price range. The name is an acronym for the Latin phrase anima sana in corpore sano, which translates as &amp;ldquo;Healthy soul in a healthy body&amp;rdquo;. In recent years their running shoes have often been ranked among the top performance footwear in the market.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc//file/abc.svg</url><title>ABC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ABC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) is Australia&amp;rsquo;s national broadcaster founded in 1929. It is principally funded by the direct grants from the Australian government, but is expressly independent of government and partisan politics. The ABC plays a leading role in journalistic independence and is fundamental in the history of broadcasting in Australia.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/accenture//file/accenture.svg</url><title>Accenture Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Accenture</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/accenture/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/accenture/</guid><description turbo="true">Accenture plc is a multinational professional services company that provides services in strategy, consulting, digital, technology and operations. A Fortune Global 500 company, it has been incorporated in Dublin, Ireland, since 1 September 2009. In 2018, the company reported net revenues of $39.6 billion, with more than 459,000 employees serving clients in more than 200 cities in 120 countries. In 2015, the company had about 150,000 employees in India, about 48,000 in the US, and about 50,000 in the Philippines.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-pro//file/acrobat-pro.svg</url><title>Acrobat Pro Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Acrobat Pro</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-pro/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-pro/</guid><description turbo="true"> Adobe Acrobat is a family of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Inc. to view, create, manipulate, print and manage files in Portable Document Format (PDF).
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-reader//file/acrobat-reader.svg</url><title>Acrobat Reader Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Acrobat Reader</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-reader/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acrobat-reader/</guid><description turbo="true"> Adobe Acrobat is a family of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Inc. to view, create, manipulate, print and manage files in Portable Document Format (PDF).
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura//file/acura.svg</url><title>Acura Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Acura</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</guid><description turbo="true">Acura (/ˈækjʊrə/) is the American luxury vehicle marque of Japanese automaker Honda. The brand was launched in the United States and Canada on 27 March 1986, marketing luxury, performance, and high-performance vehicles. It was introduced to Hong Kong in 1991, Mexico in 2004, China in 2006, Russia in 2014 (no longer available in Russia) and Kuwait in 2015, and is also sold in Ukraine. Honda&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce Acura to the Japanese domestic market (JDM) in 2008 was delayed, due to economic reasons,[4] and later withheld as a result of the 2008 financial crisis.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe//file/adobe.svg</url><title>Adobe Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Adobe</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/adobe/</guid><description turbo="true">Adobe Inc. is an American multinational computer software company headquartered in San Jose, California. It has historically focused upon the creation of multimedia and creativity software products, with a more recent foray towards digital marketing software. Adobe is best known for its Adobe Flash web software ecosystem, Photoshop image editing software, Acrobat Reader, the Portable Document Format (PDF), and Adobe Creative Suite, as well as its successor Adobe Creative Cloud.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus//file/aer-lungus.svg</url><title>Aer Lungus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aer Lungus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</guid><description turbo="true">Aer Lingus is the flag carrier airline of Ireland and the second-largest airline in the country after Ryanair. Founded by the Irish government, it was privatised between 2006 and 2015 and it is now a wholly owned subsidiary of International Airlines Group (IAG), the parent company of British Airways and Iberia. The airline&amp;rsquo;s head office is on the grounds of Dublin Airport in Cloghran, County Dublin, Ireland.
Source Aer Lingus tasked Lippincott with creating a brand that would reflect the radically different airline it had become, yet preserve the emotional bond with Ireland that it has always had.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot//file/aeroflot.svg</url><title>Aeroflot Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aeroflot</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</guid><description turbo="true"> Aeroflot – Russian Airlines is the flag carrier and largest airline of the Russian Federation. The carrier is an open joint stock company that operates domestic and international passenger and services, mainly from its hub at Sheremetyevo International Airport.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna//file/aetna.svg</url><title>Aetna Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aetna</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna/</guid><description turbo="true"> Aetna Inc. is an American managed health care company that sells traditional and consumer directed health care insurance and related services, such as medical, pharmaceutical, dental, behavioral health, long-term care, and disability plans, primarily through employer-paid (fully or partly) insurance and benefit programs, and through Medicare. Since November 28, 2018, the company has been a subsidiary of CVS Health.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-designer//file/affinity-designer.svg</url><title>Affinity Designer Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Affinity Designer</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-designer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-designer/</guid><description turbo="true"> Affinity Designer is a vector graphics editor developed by Serif for macOS, iOS, and Microsoft Windows. It is part of the &amp;ldquo;Affinity trinity&amp;rdquo; alongside Affinity Photo and Affinity Publisher. Affinity Designer is available for purchase directly from the company website and in the Mac App Store, iOS App Store, and the Microsoft Store.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-photo//file/affinity-photo.svg</url><title>Affinity Photo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Affinity Photo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-photo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-photo/</guid><description turbo="true"> Affinity Photo is a raster graphics editor developed by Serif for macOS, iOS and Windows. It is part of the &amp;ldquo;Affinity trinity&amp;rdquo; alongside Affinity Designer and Affinity Publisher. Affinity Photo is available for purchase in the Mac App Store, iOS App Store, and the Microsoft Store.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-publisher//file/affinity-publisher.svg</url><title>Affinity Publisher Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Affinity Publisher</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-publisher/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-publisher/</guid><description turbo="true"> Affinity Publisher is a desktop publishing application developed by Serif for macOS and Microsoft Windows. It is a part of the Affinity product line along with Affinity Photo and Affinity Designer.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/after-effects//file/after-effects.svg</url><title>After Effects Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">After Effects</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/after-effects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/after-effects/</guid><description turbo="true">Adobe After Effects is a digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Systems and used in the post-production process of film making and television production. Among other things, After Effects can be used for keying, tracking, compositing, and animation. It also functions as a very basic non-linear editor, audio editor, and media transcoder. In 2019, the program won an Academy Award for scientific and technical achievement.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-canada//file/air-canada.svg</url><title>Air Canada Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Air Canada</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/air-canada/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-canada/</guid><description turbo="true">Air Canada is the flag carrier and the largest airline of Canada by fleet size and passengers carried. The airline, founded in 1937, provides scheduled and charter air transport for passengers and cargo to 207 destinations worldwide. It is a founding member of the Star Alliance. Air Canada&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters are in Montreal, Quebec, while its largest hub is at Toronto Pearson International Airport. The airline&amp;rsquo;s regional service is Air Canada Express.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china//file/air-china.svg</url><title>Air China Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Air China</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china/</guid><description turbo="true"> Air China Limited is the flag carrier and one of the major airlines of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, with its headquarters in Shunyi District, Beijing. Air China&amp;rsquo;s flight operations are based at Beijing Capital International Airport. In 2017, the airline carried 102 million domestic and international passengers with an average load factor of 81%.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france//file/air-france.svg</url><title>Air France Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Air France</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-france/</guid><description turbo="true">Air France is the French flag carrier headquartered in Tremblay-en-France. It is a subsidiary of the Air France–KLM Group and a founding member of the SkyTeam global airline alliance. As of 2013 Air France serves 36 destinations in France and operates worldwide scheduled passenger and cargo services to 168 destinations in 78 countries (93 including overseas departments and territories of France) and also carried 46,803,000 passengers in 2015. The airline&amp;rsquo;s global hub is at Charles de Gaulle Airport with Orly Airport as the primary domestic hub.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/airbnb//file/airbnb.svg</url><title>Airbnb Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Airbnb</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/airbnb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/airbnb/</guid><description turbo="true"> A‌i‌r‌b‌n‌b‌,‌ ‌I‌n‌c‌.‌, is an American online marketplace and hospitality service brokerage company based in San Francisco, California, United States. Members can use the service to arrange or offer lodging, primarily homestays, or tourism experiences. The company does not own any of the real estate listings, nor does it host events; it acts as a broker, receiving commissions from each booking.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/akg//file/akg.svg</url><title>AKG Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AKG</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/akg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/akg/</guid><description turbo="true"> AKG Acoustics (originally Akustische und Kino-Geräte Gesellschaft m.b.H., English: Acoustic and Cinema Equipment) is an acoustics engineering and manufacturing company. It was founded in 1947 by Dr. Rudolf Görike and Ernest Plass in Vienna, Austria. It is a subsidiary of Harman International Industries, a division of Samsung Electronics.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank//file/alfa-bank.svg</url><title>Alfa Bank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Alfa Bank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</guid><description turbo="true">Alfa Bank JSC, the corporate treasury of the Alfa Group, is one of the largest private commercial banks in Russia. It was founded by Russian businessman Mikhail Fridman, who is still the controlling owner today. It is headquartered in Moscow. It operates in seven countries, providing financial services to over 381,600 active corporate customers and 14.2 million retail clients. Alfa-Bank is particularly active in Russia and Ukraine, ranking among top 10 largest banks in terms of capital in both countries.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/allianz//file/allianz.svg</url><title>Allianz Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Allianz</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/allianz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/allianz/</guid><description turbo="true">Allianz SE is a German multinational financial services company headquartered in Munich, Germany. Its core businesses are insurance and asset management. As of 2014, it is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest insurance company, the largest financial services group and the largest company according to a composite measure by Forbes magazine, as well as the largest financial services company when measured by 2013 revenue. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina//file/alpina.svg</url><title>Alpina Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Alpina</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</guid><description turbo="true">Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners. For instance, the Alpina B7 is produced at the same assembly line in Dingolfing, Germany (BMW Plant Dingolfing), as BMW&amp;rsquo;s own 7 Series.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/americ-inn//file/americ-inn.svg</url><title>Americ Inn Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Americ Inn</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/americ-inn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/americ-inn/</guid><description turbo="true"> AmericInn provides genuine hospitality in 200 welcoming locations across the US. With free hot breakfast, updated guest rooms, on-site fitness centers and inviting indoor pools at select locations, AmericInn is proud to make all travelers feel like neighbors.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-airlines//file/american-airlines.svg</url><title>American Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">American Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/american-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">American Airlines, Inc. (AA) is a major American airline headquartered in Fort Worth, Texas, within the Dallas-Fort Worth metroplex. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline when measured by fleet size, revenue, scheduled passengers carried, scheduled passenger-kilometers flown, and number of destinations served. American, together with its regional partners, operates an extensive international and domestic network with almost 6,700 flights per day to nearly 350 destinations in more than 50 countries.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amg//file/amg.svg</url><title>AMG Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AMG</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amg/</guid><description turbo="true"> Mercedes-AMG GmbH, commonly known as AMG, is the high-performance brand used by Mercedes-Benz. AMG independently hires engineers and contracts with manufacturers to customize Mercedes-Benz AMG vehicles. Mercedes-AMG is headquartered in Affalterbach, Baden-Württemberg, Germany.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin//file/aston-martin.svg</url><title>Aston-Martin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aston-Martin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</guid><description turbo="true">Aston Martin Lagonda Global Holdings plc is a British independent manufacturer of luxury sports cars and grand tourers. It was founded in 1913 by Lionel Martin and Robert Bamford. Steered from 1947 by David Brown, it became associated with expensive grand touring cars in the 1950s and 1960s, and with the fictional character James Bond following his use of a DB5 model in the 1964 film Goldfinger. Their sports cars are regarded as a British cultural icon.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/audi//file/audi.svg</url><title>Audi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Audi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/audi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/audi/</guid><description turbo="true">Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners. For instance, the Alpina B7 is produced at the same assembly line in Dingolfing, Germany (BMW Plant Dingolfing), as BMW&amp;rsquo;s own 7 Series.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/axa//file/axa.svg</url><title>AXA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AXA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/axa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/axa/</guid><description turbo="true"> AXA is a French multinational insurance firm headquartered in the 8th arrondissement of Paris that engages in global insurance, investment management, and other financial services.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm//file/asrm.svg</url><title>ASRM Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ASRM</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asrm/</guid><description turbo="true"> The American Society for Reproductive Medicine is a multidisciplinary organization dedicated to the advancement of the science and practice of reproductive medicine. It provides a forum for lay public, researchers, physicians and affiliated health workers through education, publications, and meetings. The Society has its headquarters in Birmingham, AL and a public affairs office in Washington, DC.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank//file/amalgamated-bank.svg</url><title>Amalgamated Bank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Amalgamated Bank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:52:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</guid><description turbo="true">History of the Amalgamated Bank logo Amalgamated Bank is the leading financial institution dedicated to providing affordable banking services to working people, unions, and progressive organizations and businesses. Established in 1923 as New York City’s first labor bank, Amalgamated is now the largest union-owned bank in the United States, with locations across the city, as well as in Washington DC, New Jersey, Nevada and California. Pentagram has designed a new brand identity for the bank that updates its look while also honoring its legacy.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility//file/aspire-fertility.svg</url><title>Aspire Fertility Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aspire Fertility</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aspire-fertility/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute//file/arizona-reproductive-institute.svg</url><title>Arizona Reproductive Institute Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Arizona Reproductive Institute</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arizona-reproductive-institute/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aab//file/aab.svg</url><title>AAB Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">AAB</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:27:27 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aab/</guid><description turbo="true"> AAB is dedicated to serving the community clinical laboratory and the professionals involved in clinical laboratory operations. Founded in 1956, AAB members are clinical laboratory directors, managers, supervisors, technologists, technicians, and phlebotomists. Laboratories can also become members through AAB&amp;rsquo;s National Independent Laboratory Association (NILA).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-web-services//file/amazon-web-services.svg</url><title>Amazon Web Services Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Amazon Web Services</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-web-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:21:27 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-web-services/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-echo//file/amazon-echo.svg</url><title>Amazon Echo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Amazon Echo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-echo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:13:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-echo/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express//file/american-express.svg</url><title>American Express Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">American Express</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</guid><description turbo="true">History of the American Express logo (from pentagram.com)
American Express is one of the world’s most trusted and recognized brands. Pentagram has refreshed the American Express visual identity, reasserting and amplifying the brand’s visual expression. The project sought to retool the iconic Blue Box logo, introduced in 1975, and to derive a typographic language that could also live outside the Blue Box, providing a bolder, more confident expression of the brand.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music//file/apple-music.svg</url><title>Apple Music Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple Music</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-music/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-pay//file/apple-pay.svg</url><title>Apple Pay Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple Pay</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-pay/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv//file/apple-tv.svg</url><title>Apple TV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple TV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv/</guid><description turbo="true">History of Apple logo (from RobJanoff.com)
At the time of his initial meeting with Steve Jobs in early 1977, Apple Computer was still very much in its infancy, having been incorporated for less than a year. Apple’s offices were in a local strip mall, and consisted of just the three partners – Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Mike Markkula.
The initial identity development was to coincide with the introduction of the brand’s first personal computer, the Apple II.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-watch//file/apple-watch.svg</url><title>Apple Watch Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple Watch</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-watch/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus//file/apple-tv-plus.svg</url><title>Apple TV Plus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple TV Plus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</guid><description turbo="true">About Apple TV+ (from apple.com)
Introducing Apple TV+, a new streaming service where the most creative minds in TV and film tell the kinds of stories only they can. Featuring original shows and movies across every genre, Apple TV+ is coming this fall. Exclusively on the Apple TV app.</description></item></channel></rss>