<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>manufacturing on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/manufacturing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in manufacturing on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/manufacturing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avery</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/avery/</guid>
      <description> Avery Products Corporation is one of the world’s leading manufacturers of self-adhesive labels, labeling software, binders, dividers and other products, and markets under the well-known Avery® brand. Throughout our history, Avery has built a solid reputation as the trusted brand and leading resource for organization and identification solutions.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bemis Company</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</guid>
      <description> Bemis Company, Inc. is a global manufacturer of flexible packaging products (ranging from self-venting cook-in-bag packaging and retort packaging for shelf-stable products, to vacuum packaging for meat products and puncture-resistant, sterile medical packaging) and pressure-sensitive materials. Bemis is headquartered in Neenah, Wisconsin in the United States. Its divisions are located in 12 countries and its films for packaging products and adhesive materials are distributed worldwide.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThyssenKrupp</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/thyssenkrupp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/thyssenkrupp/</guid>
      <description>thyssenkrupp AG /ˈtɪsɛn.krʊp/ is a German multinational conglomerate with focus on industrial engineering and steel production. The company is based in Duisburg and Essen and divided into 670 subsidiaries worldwide. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest steel producers; it was ranked tenth-largest worldwide by revenue in 2015. The company is the result of the 1999 merger of Thyssen AG and Krupp, and now has its operational headquarters in Essen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braun</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/braun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/braun/</guid>
      <description>Braun GmbH is a German consumer products company based in Kronberg. From 1984 until 2007, Braun was a wholly owned subsidiary of The Gillette Company, which had purchased a controlling interest in the company in 1967. Braun is now a wholly owned subsidiary of Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, which acquired Gillette in 2005. On 16 April 2012, De&amp;rsquo;Longhi bought perpetual rights to manufacture Braun branded products from Procter &amp;amp; Gamble in the small appliance segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSW</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jsw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jsw/</guid>
      <description> Japan Steel Works, Ltd. is a steel manufacturer founded in Muroran
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitsui</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mitsui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mitsui/</guid>
      <description> Mitsui Group is one of the largest keiretsu in Japan and one of the largest corporate groups in the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitsui ES</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mitsui-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mitsui-es/</guid>
      <description> Mitsui Engineering &amp;amp; Shipbuilding is a Japanese company. It is listed on the Nikkei 225.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oji Paper</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/oji-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oji-paper/</guid>
      <description> Oji Holdings Corporation is a Japanese manufacturer of paper products. In 2012 the company was the third largest company in the global forest, paper and packaging industry. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock is listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange and the stock is constituent of the Nikkei 225 stock index.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3M</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/3m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/3m/</guid>
      <description>The 3M Company, formerly known as the Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company, is an American multinational conglomerate corporation operating in the fields of industry, worker safety, health care, and consumer goods. The company produces a variety of products, including adhesives, abrasives, laminates, passive fire protection, personal protective equipment, window films, paint protection films, dental and orthodontic products, electrical &amp;amp; electronic connecting and insulating materials, medical products, car-care products, electronic circuits, healthcare software and optical films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</guid>
      <description>HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
 Source Source In October 2014, the Hewlett-Packard Company announced its intention to split into two separate entities, signaling the largest corporate demerger in history. The two resulting companies would each remain Fortune 100 industry leaders—with HP, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/samsung/</guid>
      <description> Samsung is a South Korean multinational conglomerate headquartered in Samsung Town, Seoul. It comprises numerous affiliated businesses, most of them united under the Samsung brand, and is the largest South Korean chaebol (business conglomerate).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOTO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toto/</guid>
      <description> Toto Ltd.is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest toilet manufacturer. It was founded in 1917, and is known for developing the Washlet and derivative products. The company is based in Kitakyushu, Japan, and owns production facilities in nine countries. The name &amp;ldquo;Toto&amp;rdquo; is an abbreviation of the two Japanese words forming its full name, Tōyō Tōki (東洋陶器 Oriental Ceramics).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>