<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>M on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/m/</link>
    <description>Recent content in M on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/m/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel App</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</guid>
      <description>Marvel is a design, prototyping an collaboration application based in London, UK.
 Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/malaysia-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/malaysia-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Malaysia Airlines Berhad (MAB) is an airline operating flights from Kuala Lumpur International Airport and from secondary hubs in Kota Kinabalu and Kuching to destinations throughout Asia, Oceania and Europe. Malaysia Airlines is the flag carrier of Malaysia and a member of the oneworld airline alliance. The company headquarters are located at Kuala Lumpur International Airport. In August 2014, the Malaysian government&amp;rsquo;s sovereign wealth fund Khazanah Nasional—which then owned 69.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</guid>
      <description> Mercedes-Benz is a German global automobile marque and a division of Daimler AG. The brand is known for luxury vehicles, buses, coaches, and trucks. The headquarters is in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. The name first appeared in 1926 under Daimler-Benz. In 2018, Mercedes-Benz was the biggest selling premium vehicle brand in the world, having sold 2.31 million passenger cars.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Onenote</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-onenote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:02:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-onenote/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2018 Rebranding Microsoft Office (or simply Office) is a family of client software, server software, and services developed by Microsoft. It was first announced by Bill Gates on August 1, 1988, at COMDEX in Las Vegas. Initially a marketing term for an office suite (bundled set of productivity applications), the first version of Office contained Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, and Microsoft PowerPoint. Over the years, Office applications have grown substantially closer with shared features such as a common spell checker, OLE data integration and Visual Basic for Applications scripting language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:02:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2018 Rebranding Microsoft Office (or simply Office) is a family of client software, server software, and services developed by Microsoft. It was first announced by Bill Gates on August 1, 1988, at COMDEX in Las Vegas. Initially a marketing term for an office suite (bundled set of productivity applications), the first version of Office contained Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, and Microsoft PowerPoint. Over the years, Office applications have grown substantially closer with shared features such as a common spell checker, OLE data integration and Visual Basic for Applications scripting language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:02:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-teams/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2018 Rebranding Microsoft Office (or simply Office) is a family of client software, server software, and services developed by Microsoft. It was first announced by Bill Gates on August 1, 1988, at COMDEX in Las Vegas. Initially a marketing term for an office suite (bundled set of productivity applications), the first version of Office contained Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, and Microsoft PowerPoint. Over the years, Office applications have grown substantially closer with shared features such as a common spell checker, OLE data integration and Visual Basic for Applications scripting language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Word</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:01:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-word/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Word Screenshot  Microsoft Word (or simply Word) is a word processor developed by Microsoft. It was first released on October 25, 1983 under the name Multi-Tool Word for Xenix systems.Subsequent versions were later written for several other platforms including IBM PCs running DOS (1983), Apple Macintosh running the Classic Mac OS (1985), AT&amp;amp;T Unix PC (1985), Atari ST (1988), OS/2 (1989), Microsoft Windows (1989), SCO Unix (1994), and macOS (formerly OS X; 2001).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Powerpoint</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:01:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft PowerPoint Screenshot  Microsoft PowerPoint is a presentation program, created by Robert Gaskins and Dennis Austin at a software company named Forethought, Inc. It was released on April 20, 1987, initially for Macintosh computers only. Microsoft acquired PowerPoint for $14 million three months after it appeared. This was Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s first significant acquisition, and Microsoft set up a new business unit for PowerPoint in Silicon Valley where Forethought had been located.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:01:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft-excel/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Excel Screenshot  Microsoft Excel is a spreadsheet developed by Microsoft for Windows, macOS, Android and iOS. It features calculation, graphing tools, pivot tables, and a macro programming language called Visual Basic for Applications. It has been a very widely applied spreadsheet for these platforms, especially since version 5 in 1993, and it has replaced Lotus 1-2-3 as the industry standard for spreadsheets. Excel forms part of the Microsoft Office suite of software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Foundation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-foundation/</guid>
      <description>About Mozilla Foundation (from mozilla.org)
The Foundation is also the sole shareholder in the Mozilla Corporation, the maker of Firefox and other open source tools. Mozilla Corporation functions as a self-sustaining social enterprise – money earned through its products is reinvested into the organization. Mozilla Corporation, a wholly owned subsidiary of the Foundation, makes consumer Internet products that advance the same values outlined in the Mozilla Manifesto.
Firefox, our flagship product, gives increased choice, privacy and security to 100s of millions of people around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Maestro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Cirrus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</guid>
      <description>History of the MasterCard logo (from pentagram.com)
The iconic red and yellow intersecting circles of Mastercard are one of the world’s most recognized brands. Today the company launches an evolution of its brand identity featuring a new mark that highlights the connectivity and seamlessness of Mastercard and its payment systems. Designed by Pentagram, the identity brings simplicity and clarity with an increased emphasis on the interlocking circles, and is optimized for use in digital contexts, an increasingly important part of Mastercard’s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>