<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lippincott on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/lippincott/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lippincott on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/lippincott/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aer Lungus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</guid>
      <description>Aer Lingus is the flag carrier airline of Ireland and the second-largest airline in the country after Ryanair. Founded by the Irish government, it was privatised between 2006 and 2015 and it is now a wholly owned subsidiary of International Airlines Group (IAG), the parent company of British Airways and Iberia. The airline&amp;rsquo;s head office is on the grounds of Dublin Airport in Cloghran, County Dublin, Ireland.
 Source Aer Lingus tasked Lippincott with creating a brand that would reflect the radically different airline it had become, yet preserve the emotional bond with Ireland that it has always had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bain Capital</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</guid>
      <description> Bain Capital is a private investment firm based in Boston, Massachusetts. It specializes in private equity, venture capital, credit, public equity, impact investing, life sciences and real estate. Bain Capital invests across a range of industry sectors and geographic regions. As of 2018, the firm managed more than $105 billion of investor capital.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DuPont</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</guid>
      <description> DuPont de Nemours, Inc., commonly known as DuPont, is an American company formed by the merger of Dow Chemical and DuPont on August 31, 2017, and then subsequent spinoffs of Dow Inc. and Corteva. Prior to the spinoffs it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest chemical company in terms of sales.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nokia/</guid>
      <description>Nokia Corporation is a Finnish multinational telecommunications, information technology, and consumer electronics company, founded in 1865. Nokia&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Espoo, in the greater Helsinki metropolitan area. In 2018, Nokia employed approximately 103,000 people across over 100 countries, did business in more than 130 countries, and reported annual revenues of around €23 billion. Nokia is a public limited company listed on the Helsinki Stock Exchange and New York Stock Exchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/principal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/principal/</guid>
      <description>The Principal Financial Group is a global financial investment management and insurance company headquartered in Des Moines, Iowa
 Source Enter Lippincott, who, through leadership workshops, gained clarity on the vision and business objectives. We then conducted a global study of 1,200 employees to mine for perceived strengths and desired shifts in the brand evolution. Whether by geography, business unit or tenure, employees were calling for a strong signal about and recognition of the company’s next era — one that was already global, bolder, more collaborative, and more humanly and intellectually inclusive than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</guid>
      <description>Starbucks Corporation is an American coffee company and coffeehouse chain. Starbucks was founded in Seattle, Washington in 1971. As of early 2019, the company operates over 30,000 locations worldwide.
 Source The Starbucks History  Every day, we go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with our friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechnipFMC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</guid>
      <description> TechnipFMC plc is a UK-based company that provides complete project life cycle services (conception, feasibility study, front end engineering, detailed engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning, test runs, maintenance &amp;amp; decommissioning) for the energy industry. TechnipFMC was ranked 23rd among world&amp;rsquo;s Top 225 International Design Firms in the year 2017 by Engineering News-Record.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Versant Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walmart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</guid>
      <description>Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets, discount department stores, and grocery stores.
 Source The Walmart History  Walmart as we know it today evolved from Sam Walton’s goals for great value and great customer service. “Mr. Sam,” as he was known, believed in leadership through service. This belief that true leadership depends on willing service was the principle on which Walmart was built, and drove the decisions the company has made for the past 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ebay/</guid>
      <description>eBay Inc. (/ˈiːˌbeɪ/ EE-bay) is an American multinational e-commerce corporation based in San Jose, California that facilitates consumer-to-consumer and business-to-consumer sales through its website. eBay was founded by Pierre Omidyar in the autumn of 1995, and became a notable success story of the dot-com bubble. eBay is a multibillion-dollar business with operations in about 30 countries, as of 2011. The company manages the eBay website, an online auction and shopping website in which people and businesses buy and sell a wide variety of goods and services worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</guid>
      <description>History of the Bank of America logo (from Bank of America press release)
Bank of America today announced a new brand positioning focused on the question, “What would you like the power to do?” The positioning reflects the impact clients and communities can have when they have the power to achieve their goals, and the company’s role as a partner invested in their success. […]
The Flagscape logo is also getting its first update since being introduced in 1998, reflecting a more modern brand that delivers both cutting-edge technology and high-touch solutions for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>