<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Redhat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/redhat/</guid>
      <description> Red Hat, Inc. is an American multinational software company providing open-source software products to the enterprise community. Founded in 1993, Red Hat has its corporate headquarters in Raleigh, North Carolina, with other offices worldwide.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Royce</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce/</guid>
      <description>Rolls-Royce was a British luxury car and later an aero-engine manufacturing business established in 1904 by the partnership of Charles Rolls and Henry Royce. Building on Royce&amp;rsquo;s reputation established with his cranes they quickly developed a reputation for superior engineering by manufacturing the &amp;ldquo;best car in the world&amp;rdquo;. The First World War brought them into manufacturing aero-engines. Joint development of jet engines began in 1940 and they entered production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolls-Royce Motors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</guid>
      <description>Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited is a British luxury automobile maker. A wholly owned subsidiary of German group BMW, it was established in 1998 after BMW was licensed the rights to the Rolls-Royce brand name and logo from Rolls-Royce plc and acquired the rights to the Spirit of Ecstasy and Rolls-Royce grill shape trademarks from Volkswagen AG. Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited operates from purpose-built administrative and production facilities opened in 2003 across from the historic Goodwood Circuit in Goodwood, West Sussex, England, United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rotten Tomatoes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rotten-tomatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rotten-tomatoes/</guid>
      <description> Rotten Tomatoes is an American review-aggregation website for film and television. The company was launched in August 1998 by three undergraduate students at the University of California, Berkeley: Senh Duong, Patrick Y. Lee, and Stephen Wang.The name &amp;ldquo;Rotten Tomatoes&amp;rdquo; derives from the practice of audiences throwing rotten tomatoes when disapproving of a poor stage performance.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rambler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</guid>
      <description> Rambler (Russian: Рамблер) is a Russian search engine and one of the biggest Russian web portals. It is owned by the Rambler Media Group and Prof-Media since 2006. It was launched in 1996 by Stack Ltd, including Sergey Lysakov, Dmitry Kryukov, Vladimir Samoylov and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reebok</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/reebok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reebok/</guid>
      <description> Reebok (/ˈriːbɒk/) is an English footwear and apparel company, subsidiary of German sportsgiant Adidas since 2005. Reebok produces and distributes fitness, running and CrossFit sportswear including clothing and footwear. It is the official footwear and apparel sponsor for Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC), CrossFit, and Spartan Race.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remax</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/remax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/remax/</guid>
      <description> RE/MAX, short for &amp;ldquo; Real Estate Maximums,&amp;rdquo; is an American international real estate company that operates through a franchise system. Up until 2013, the company held the number one market share in the United States and Canada since 1999, as measured by residential transaction sides. RE/MAX has more than 100,000 agents in 6,800 offices. RE/MAX operates in about 100 countries.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rostelecom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</guid>
      <description> Rostelecom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s leading long-distance telephony provider. Domestic long distance service provides about 50% of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue; and international long distance calls provide about 25%.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Royal Bank of Canada</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 21:39:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RMA of Texas</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma-of-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:46:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma-of-texas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBS Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproductive Biology Associates</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/reproductive-biology-associates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reproductive-biology-associates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>