<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2016 on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/year/2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2016 on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0038</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0038</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</guid>
      <description>History of the MasterCard logo (from pentagram.com)
The iconic red and yellow intersecting circles of Mastercard are one of the world’s most recognized brands. Today the company launches an evolution of its brand identity featuring a new mark that highlights the connectivity and seamlessness of Mastercard and its payment systems. Designed by Pentagram, the identity brings simplicity and clarity with an increased emphasis on the interlocking circles, and is optimized for use in digital contexts, an increasingly important part of Mastercard’s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conceive Abilities</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</guid>
      <description> At ConceiveAbilities® Conceive Abilities believe that everyone who wants to become a parent, can. Conceive Abilities have helped build thousands of families for nearly 25 years. Whether you are an intended parent ready to fulfill your family destiny, a surrogate answering your calling or an egg donor wanting to expand what’s possible in your life—Conceive Abilities are your people.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DELL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dell/</guid>
      <description> Dell is a US multinational computer technology company that develops, sells, repairs, and supports computers and related products and services. Named after its founder, Michael Dell, the company is one of the largest technological corporations in the world, employing more than 145,000 people in the U.S. and around the world (Annual report 2018).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC United</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-united/</guid>
      <description>D.C. United is an American professional soccer club based in Washington, D.C. The club competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS), the top level of professional American soccer. The franchise began play in 1996 as one of the ten charter clubs of the league. The club was one of the most successful clubs in the early years of MLS, winning eight of its thirteen titles between 1996 and 1998 under then head coach Bruce Arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida Panthers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/florida-panthers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/florida-panthers/</guid>
      <description>The Florida Panthers are a professional ice hockey team based in the Miami metropolitan area. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team&amp;rsquo;s local broadcasting rights has been held by Fox Sports Florida (formerly SportsChannel Florida) since 1996. The team initially played their home games at Miami Arena, before moving to the BB&amp;amp;T Center in 1998. Located in Sunrise, Florida, the Panthers are the southernmost team in the NHL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Penguins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pittsburgh-penguins/</guid>
      <description>The Pittsburgh Penguins (colloquially known as the Pens) are a professional ice hockey team based in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Penguins are one of two NHL franchises in Pennsylvania, the other being the Philadelphia Flyers. The cities&amp;rsquo; proximity has led to a rivalry known as the &amp;ldquo;Battle of Pennsylvania&amp;rdquo;. The club is owned by Mario Lemieux and Ronald Burkle, who purchased the Penguins in 1999 and brought the club out of bankruptcy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utah Jazz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/utah-jazz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/utah-jazz/</guid>
      <description>The Utah Jazz are an American professional basketball team based in Salt Lake City, Utah. The Jazz compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference, Northwest Division. Since 1991, the team has played its home games at Vivint Smart Home Arena. The franchise began play as an expansion team in 1974 as the New Orleans Jazz (as a tribute to New Orleans&amp;rsquo; history of originating Jazz music).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</guid>
      <description> Enel S.p.A., or the Enel Group, is an Italian multinational energy company that is active in the sectors of electricity generation and distribution, as well as in the distribution of natural gas.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grubhub</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/grubhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/grubhub/</guid>
      <description> Grubhub Inc. is an American online and mobile food ordering and delivery marketplace that connects diners with local takeout restaurants. Based in Chicago, as of Q1 2019 the company has 19.9 million active users and 115,000 associated restaurants across 2,200 cities in the United States.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</guid>
      <description>Netflix, Inc. is an American media-services provider headquartered in Los Gatos, California, founded in 1997 by Reed Hastings and Marc Randolph in Scotts Valley, California. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its subscription-based streaming OTT service which offers online streaming of a library of films and television programs, including those produced in-house. As of April 2019, Netflix had over 148 million paid subscriptions worldwide, including 60 million in the United States, and over 154 million subscriptions total including free trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Met</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-met/</guid>
      <description> The Metropolitan Museum of Art of New York City, colloquially &amp;ldquo;the Met&amp;rdquo;, is the largest art museum in the United States. With 6,953,927 visitors to its three locations in 2018, it was the third most visited art museum in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21st Century Fox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</guid>
      <description> Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc., doing business as 21st Century Fox (21CF), was an American multinational mass media corporation that was based in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was one of the two companies formed from the 2013 spin-off of the publishing assets of News Corporation, as founded by Rupert Murdoch in 1980.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</guid>
      <description>Subway is an American privately held fast food restaurant franchise that primarily sells submarine sandwiches (subs) and salads. Subway is one of the fastest-growing franchises in the world and, as of June 2017, had approximately 42,000 stores located in more than 100 countries. More than half of the stores are located in the United States. It is the largest single-brand restaurant chain, and the largest restaurant operator, in the world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2016 Rio</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2016-rio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:33:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2016-rio/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citroen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</guid>
      <description> Citroën is a French automobile manufacturer, part of the PSA Peugeot Citroën group since 1976, founded in 1919 by French industrialist André-Gustave Citroën (1878–1935). In 1934, the firm established its reputation for innovative technology with the Traction Avant. This car was the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass-produced front wheel drive car, and also one of the first to feature a unitary type body, with no chassis supporting the mechanical components.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qantas Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Qantas Airways Limited (/ˈkwɒntəs/) is the flag carrier of Australia and its largest airline by fleet size, international flights and international destinations. It is the third oldest airline in the world, after KLM and Avianca having been founded in November 1920; it began international passenger flights in May 1935. The Qantas name comes from &amp;ldquo;QANTAS&amp;rdquo;, an acronym for its original name, &amp;ldquo;Queensland and Northern Territory Aerial Services&amp;rdquo;, and it is nicknamed &amp;ldquo;The Flying Kangaroo&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Maestro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Cirrus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IV Interactive</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</guid>
      <description>About IV interactive IV Interactive is a full-service interactive agency specializing in the four elements required for success in an increasingly digital world: innovative design, interactive marketing, technology implementation and strategic consulting. Using this multidisciplinary approach, IV Interactive provide results-driven, award-winning solutions to organizations of all sizes and disciplines. From Jones Apparel Group to Thomson Reuters, IV Interactive have helped IV Interactive clients identify and implement the elements necessary for success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>