<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>China on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in China on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CNOOC Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group/</guid>
      <description>China National Offshore Oil Corporation, or CNOOC Group (Chinese: 中国海洋石油总公司 Pinyin: Zhōngguó Háiyáng Shíyóu Zǒnggōngsī), is one of the largest national oil companies in China. It is the third-largest national oil company in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, after CNPC (parent of PetroChina) and China Petrochemical Corporation (parent of Sinopec).[citation needed] The CNOOC Group focuses on the exploitation, exploration and development of crude oil and natural gas in offshore China, alongwith its subsidiary COOEC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNPC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</guid>
      <description> The China National Petroleum Corporation (CNPC) is a major national oil and gas corporation of China PR and one of the largest integrated energy groups in the world. Its headquarters are in Dongcheng District, Beijing. CNPC was ranked fourth in 2017 Fortune Global 500, a global ranking of the largest corporations by revenue
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiktok</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tiktok/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tiktok/</guid>
      <description>TikTok is an iOS and Android social media video app for creating and sharing short lip-sync, comedy, and talent videos. The app was launched in 2017 by ByteDance, for markets outside of China. ByteDance has previously launched Douyin (Chinese: 抖音) for the China market in September 2016. TikTok and Douyin are the same, but run on different servers to comply with Chinese censorship restrictions. The application allows users to create short music and lip-sync videos of 3 to 15 seconds and short looping videos of 3 to 60 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2008 Beijing</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-china/</guid>
      <description> Air China Limited is the flag carrier and one of the major airlines of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, with its headquarters in Shunyi District, Beijing. Air China&amp;rsquo;s flight operations are based at Beijing Capital International Airport. In 2017, the airline carried 102 million domestic and international passengers with an average load factor of 81%.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Eastern</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern/</guid>
      <description> China Eastern Airlines Corporation Limited is an airline headquartered in the China Eastern Airlines Building, on the grounds of Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport in Changning District, Shanghai. It is a major Chinese airline operating international, domestic and regional routes. Its main hubs are at Shanghai Pudong International Airport and Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hainan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hainan Airlines is an airline headquartered in Haikou, Hainan, People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It is the largest civilian-run air transport company, the fourth-largest airline in terms of fleet size in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, and fourth-largest airline in Asia in terms of passengers carried. It operates scheduled domestic and international services on 500 routes from Hainan and nine locations on the mainland, as well as charter services. Its main base is Haikou Meilan International Airport, with hubs at Beijing Capital International Airport and Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport and several focus cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</guid>
      <description> Huawei Technologies Co. Ltd. is a Chinese multinational technology company that provides telecommunications equipment and sells consumer electronics, including smartphones, headquartered in Shenzhen, Guangdong.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sany</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</guid>
      <description> Sany Heavy Industry Co., Ltd. is a Chinese multinational heavy equipment manufacturing company headquartered in Changsha, Hunan Province. It is the sixth-largest heavy equipment manufacturer in the world, and the first in its industry in China to enter the FT Global 500 and the Forbes Global 2000 rankings. Its founder and main shareholder is Liang Wengen.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tencent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>