<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>China on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in China on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2008 Beijing</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Eastern</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern/</guid>
      <description> China Eastern Airlines Corporation Limited is an airline headquartered in the China Eastern Airlines Building, on the grounds of Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport in Changning District, Shanghai. It is a major Chinese airline operating international, domestic and regional routes. Its main hubs are at Shanghai Pudong International Airport and Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hainan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hainan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hainan Airlines is an airline headquartered in Haikou, Hainan, People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It is the largest civilian-run air transport company, the fourth-largest airline in terms of fleet size in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, and fourth-largest airline in Asia in terms of passengers carried. It operates scheduled domestic and international services on 500 routes from Hainan and nine locations on the mainland, as well as charter services. Its main base is Haikou Meilan International Airport, with hubs at Beijing Capital International Airport and Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport and several focus cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tencent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>