<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ireland on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/ireland/</link><description>Recent content in Ireland on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Allergan</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/allergan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/allergan/</guid><description>Allergan plc is an Irish-domiciled pharmaceutical company that acquires, develops, and markets brand name drugs, and in 2017 generated 80% net sales from the U.S. healthcare system. Allergan plc was formed in February 2015 when Irish–registered Actavis plc acquired U.S.–registered Allergan, Inc., and assumed the Allergan name. Actavis was a 2013 U.S. tax inversion that moved its legal domicile to Ireland to avoid U.S. taxes. Actavis used the Irish low-tax corporate system to acquire large U.</description></item><item><title>Guinness</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/guinness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/guinness/</guid><description>Guinness is a dark Irish dry stout that originated in the brewery of Arthur Guinness at St. James&amp;rsquo;s Gate, Dublin, Ireland, in 1759. It is one of the most successful beer brands worldwide, brewed in almost 50 countries, and available in over 120. Sales in 2011 amounted to 850 million litres (220,000,000 US gal). It is popular with the Irish, both in Ireland and abroad. In spite of declining consumption since 2001, it is still the best-selling alcoholic drink in Ireland where Guinness &amp;amp; Co.</description></item><item><title>Accenture</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/accenture/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/accenture/</guid><description>Accenture plc is a multinational professional services company that provides services in strategy, consulting, digital, technology and operations. A Fortune Global 500 company, it has been incorporated in Dublin, Ireland, since 1 September 2009. In 2018, the company reported net revenues of $39.6 billion, with more than 459,000 employees serving clients in more than 200 cities in 120 countries. In 2015, the company had about 150,000 employees in India, about 48,000 in the US, and about 50,000 in the Philippines.</description></item><item><title>Aer Lungus</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</guid><description>Aer Lingus is the flag carrier airline of Ireland and the second-largest airline in the country after Ryanair. Founded by the Irish government, it was privatised between 2006 and 2015 and it is now a wholly owned subsidiary of International Airlines Group (IAG), the parent company of British Airways and Iberia. The airline&amp;rsquo;s head office is on the grounds of Dublin Airport in Cloghran, County Dublin, Ireland.
Source Aer Lingus tasked Lippincott with creating a brand that would reflect the radically different airline it had become, yet preserve the emotional bond with Ireland that it has always had.</description></item></channel></rss>