<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>fashion on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/fashion/</link><description>Recent content in fashion on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/fashion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/off-white//file/off-white.svg</url><title>Off White Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Off White</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/off-white/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/off-white/</guid><description turbo="true">Off-White (stylized as OFF-WHITE c/o VIRGIL ABLOH) is an Italian luxury fashion label founded by American designer Virgil Abloh The company was incorporated in Milan in 2012.
The label has collaborated with Nike, Levi, Jimmy Choo, IKEA and Évian.
Source About Off White OFF-WHITE c/o VIRGIL ABLOH™ is a fashion label rooted in current culture at a taste-level particular to now. With a specific opinion and not necessarily same with vision seasonal men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s collections are offered.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/supreme//file/supreme.svg</url><title>Supreme Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Supreme</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/supreme/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/supreme/</guid><description turbo="true">Supreme is an American skateboarding shop and clothing brand established in New York City in April 1994.
The brand caters to the skateboarding and hip hop cultures as well as to youth culture in general. The brand produces clothes and accessories and also manufactures skateboards. Its shoes, clothing, and accessories are sold extensively in the secondary market.
The distinctive red box logo with &amp;ldquo;Supreme&amp;rdquo; in white Futura Heavy Oblique is largely based on Barbara Kruger&amp;rsquo;s propaganda art.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/versace//file/versace.svg</url><title>Versace Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Versace</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/versace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versace/</guid><description turbo="true">Gianni Versace , usually referred to simply as Versace, is an Italian luxury fashion company and trade name founded by Gianni Versace in 1978. The main collection of the brand is Versace, which produces upmarket Italian-made ready-to-wear and leather accessories. The Versace logo is the head of Medusa, a Greek mythological figure. The logo came from the floor of ruins in the area of Reggio Calabria that the Versace siblings played in as children.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/boss//file/boss.svg</url><title>Boss Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Boss</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/boss/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boss/</guid><description turbo="true">Hugo Boss AG, often styled as BOSS, is a German luxury fashion house headquartered in Metzingen. It was founded in 1924 by Hugo Boss and originally produced general purpose clothing. With the rise of the Nazi Party in the 1930s, Boss began to produce and sell Nazi uniforms. Boss would eventually supply the wartime German government with uniforms for organizations such as the Hitler Youth and Waffen-SS, resulting in a large boost in sales.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/capri//file/capri.svg</url><title>Capri Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Capri</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/capri/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/capri/</guid><description turbo="true">Capri Holdings Limited (formerly Michael Kors Holdings Limited) is a multinational fashion holding company, incorporated in the British Virgin Islands, with principal executive offices in London and operational headquarters in New York. It was founded in 1981 by American designer Michael Kors. The company sells clothes, shoes, watches, handbags, and other accessories. Michael Kors handbags have been a popular fashion trend among women of all ages. In 2015, the company had more than 550 stores and over 1500 in-store boutiques in various countries.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-shoes//file/dc-shoes.svg</url><title>DC Shoes Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">DC Shoes</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-shoes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-shoes/</guid><description turbo="true">DC Shoes is an American company that specializes in footwear for action sports, including skateboarding and snowboarding. The company also manufactures apparel, bags, accessories, hats, shirts, and posters.
Source About DC Shoes Founded in 1994, DC quickly grew to become a leader in performance skateboarding shoes and a renowned action sports brand. Today DC stands as a global brand whose product line has expanded to include men’s, women’s and kids’ skateboarding and lifestyle shoes, apparel, snowboards, snowboard boots, outerwear, and accessories.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/calvin-klein//file/calvin-klein.svg</url><title>Calvin Klein Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Calvin Klein</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/calvin-klein/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calvin-klein/</guid><description turbo="true"> Calvin Klein Inc. is an American fashion house established in 1968. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. The company has substantial market share in retail and commercial lines as well haute couture garments.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tommy-hilfiger//file/tommy-hilfiger.svg</url><title>Tommy Hilfiger Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tommy Hilfiger</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tommy-hilfiger/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tommy-hilfiger/</guid><description turbo="true">Tommy Hilfiger, formerly known as Tommy Hilfiger Corporation and Tommy Hilfiger Inc., is an American premium clothing company, manufacturing apparel, footwear, accessories, fragrances and home furnishings. The company was founded in 1985, and today is sold in department stores and over 1400 free-standing retail stores in 90 countries. In 2006, private equity firm Apax Partners acquired Tommy Hilfiger for approximately $1.6 billion, and in May 2004, PVH Corp. (NYSE: PVH) (then known as Philips van Heusen) bought the company.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry//file/burberry.svg</url><title>Burberry Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Burberry</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry/</guid><description turbo="true"> Burberry Group PLC is a British luxury fashion house headquartered in London, England. Its main fashion house focuses on and distributes trench coats (for which it is most famous), ready-to-wear outerwear, fashion accessories, fragrances, sunglasses, and cosmetics.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/prada//file/prada.svg</url><title>Prada Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Prada</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/prada/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prada/</guid><description turbo="true"> Prada S.p.A. is an Italian luxury fashion house, specializing in leather handbags, travel accessories, shoes, ready-to-wear, perfumes and other fashion accessories, founded in 1913 by Mario Prada.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good//file/fashion-for-good.svg</url><title>Fashion For Good Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Fashion For Good</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good/</guid><description turbo="true"> Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel//file/chanel.svg</url><title>Chanel Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chanel</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel/</guid><description turbo="true">Chanel S.A. is a French privately held company owned by Alain Wertheimer and Gérard Wertheimer, grandsons of Pierre Wertheimer, who was an early business partner of the couturière Coco Chanel. Chanel S.A. is a high fashion house that specializes in haute couture and ready-to-wear clothes, luxury goods, and fashion accessories. In her youth, Gabrielle Chanel gained the nickname Coco from her time as a chanteuse. As a fashion designer, Coco Chanel catered to women&amp;rsquo;s taste for elegance in dress, with blouses and suits, trousers and dresses, and jewellery (gemstone and bijouterie) of simple design, that replaced the opulent, over-designed, and constrictive clothes and accessories of 19th-century fashion.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior//file/dior.svg</url><title>Dior Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dior</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</guid><description turbo="true"> Christian Dior SE , commonly known as Dior, is a French luxury goods company controlled and chaired by French businessman Bernard Arnault, who also heads LVMH, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest luxury group. Dior itself holds 42.36% shares of and 59.01% voting rights within LVMH. Since 1997, the CEO is Sidney Toledano.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/gucci//file/gucci.svg</url><title>Gucci Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Gucci</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/gucci/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gucci/</guid><description turbo="true"> Gucci is an Italian luxury brand of fashion and leather goods. Gucci was founded by Guccio Gucci in Florence, Tuscany, in 1921. Gucci generated about €4.2 billion in revenue worldwide in 2008 according to BusinessWeek and climbed to 41st position in the magazine&amp;rsquo;s annual 2009 &amp;ldquo;Top Global 100 Brands&amp;rdquo; chart created by Interbrand; it retained that rank in Interbrand&amp;rsquo;s 2014 index. Gucci is also the highest-selling Italian brand.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo//file/kenzo.svg</url><title>Kenzo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Kenzo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kenzo/</guid><description turbo="true">Kenzo (stylized as KENZO) is a French luxury fashion house founded in 1970 by Japanese designer Kenzo Takada. Kenzo Takada was born in Japan and moved to Paris in 1964 to start his fashion career. He then became known for using Asian and Japanese influenced style with the construction of European fashion. He started out with a &amp;lsquo;Jungle Jap&amp;rsquo; boutique located in Paris and decorated in jungle inspired decor. He began with handmade women&amp;rsquo;s clothing, then in 1983 Kenzo started designing men and then kids and home collections in 1987.</description></item></channel></rss>