<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>T on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/t/</link>
    <description>Recent content in T on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/t/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Toshiba</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toshiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toshiba/</guid>
      <description> Toshiba Corporation is a Japanese multinational conglomerate headquartered in Tokyo, Japan. Its diversified products and services include information technology and communications equipment and systems, electronic components and materials, power systems, industrial and social infrastructure systems, consumer electronics, household appliances, medical equipment, office equipment, as well as lighting and logistics.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toys R Us</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</guid>
      <description> Toys &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; Us is an international toy, clothing, video game, and baby product retailer owned by Tru Kids, Inc. (d.b.a. Tru Kids Brands) and various others. It was founded in April 1948, with its headquarters located in Wayne, New Jersey, in the New York metropolitan area.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tap/</guid>
      <description>TAP Air Portugal is the flag carrier airline of Portugal, headquartered at Lisbon Airport which also serves as its hub. TAP – Transportes Aéreos Portugueses – has been a member of the Star Alliance since 2005 and operates on average 2,500 flights a week to 87 destinations in 34 countries worldwide. The company has a fleet of 90 airplanes, 68 of which were manufactured by Airbus and the remaining 22 by Embraer and ATR, operating on behalf of the regional airline TAP Express.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOTO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toto/</guid>
      <description> Toto Ltd.is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest toilet manufacturer. It was founded in 1917, and is known for developing the Washlet and derivative products. The company is based in Kitakyushu, Japan, and owns production facilities in nine countries. The name &amp;ldquo;Toto&amp;rdquo; is an abbreviation of the two Japanese words forming its full name, Tōyō Tōki (東洋陶器 Oriental Ceramics).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechnipFMC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</guid>
      <description> TechnipFMC plc is a UK-based company that provides complete project life cycle services (conception, feasibility study, front end engineering, detailed engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning, test runs, maintenance &amp;amp; decommissioning) for the energy industry. TechnipFMC was ranked 23rd among world&amp;rsquo;s Top 225 International Design Firms in the year 2017 by Engineering News-Record.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesla/</guid>
      <description>Tesla, Inc. (formerly Tesla Motors, Inc.) is an American automotive and energy company based in Palo Alto, California. The company specializes in electric car manufacturing and, through its SolarCity subsidiary, solar panel manufacturing. It operates multiple production and assembly plants, notably Gigafactory 1 near Reno, Nevada, and its main vehicle manufacturing facility at Tesla Factory in Fremont, California. As of March 2019, Tesla sells the Model S, Model X, and Model 3 automobiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripadvisor</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tripadvisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tripadvisor/</guid>
      <description> TripAdvisor, Inc. is an American travel and restaurant website company that shows hotel and restaurant reviews, accommodation bookings and other travel-related content. It also includes interactive travel forums.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkish-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/turkish-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Turkish Airlines (Turkish: Türk Hava Yolları) is the national flag carrier airline of Turkey. As of 2018, it operates scheduled services to 304 destinations in Europe, Asia, Africa, and the Americas, making it the largest carrier in the world by number of passenger destinations (excluding regional brands). It serves more destinations non-stop from a single airport than any other airline in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joint Commission</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</guid>
      <description>About The Joint Commission (from wikipedia.org)
The Joint Commission is a United States-based nonprofit tax-exempt 501&amp;copy; organization that accredits more than 21,000 US health care organizations and programs.The international branch accredits medical services from around the world. A majority of US state governments recognize Joint Commission accreditation as a condition of licensure for the receipt of Medicaid and Medicare reimbursements.
The Joint Commission was formerly the Joint Commission on Accreditation of healthcare Organizations (JCAHO) and previous to that the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals (JCAH)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</guid>
      <description>Target Corporation is the eighth-largest retailer in the United States, and is a component of the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index. Founded by George Dayton and headquartered in Minneapolis, the company was originally named Goodfellow Dry Goods in June 1902 before being renamed the Dayton&amp;rsquo;s Dry Goods Company in 1903 and later the Dayton Company in 1910. The first Target store opened in Roseville, Minnesota in 1962 while the parent company was renamed the Dayton Corporation in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-thunderbird/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-thunderbird/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</guid>
      <description>About the Toyota logo   The Toyota brand represents our tenets of quality, reliability and durability. It also stands as a symbol to inspire people around the world to go to the places and do the things they’ve always dreamed of.
 The staging platform is how we refer to the Toyota emblem when shown in the red surround. The staging platform allows the emblem to be anchored and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota F1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tencent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>