<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>T on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/t/</link>
    <description>Recent content in T on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/t/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechnipFMC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</guid>
      <description> TechnipFMC plc is a UK-based company that provides complete project life cycle services (conception, feasibility study, front end engineering, detailed engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning, test runs, maintenance &amp;amp; decommissioning) for the energy industry. TechnipFMC was ranked 23rd among world&amp;rsquo;s Top 225 International Design Firms in the year 2017 by Engineering News-Record.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joint Commission</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-joint-commission/</guid>
      <description>About The Joint Commission (from wikipedia.org)
The Joint Commission is a United States-based nonprofit tax-exempt 501&amp;copy; organization that accredits more than 21,000 US health care organizations and programs.The international branch accredits medical services from around the world. A majority of US state governments recognize Joint Commission accreditation as a condition of licensure for the receipt of Medicaid and Medicare reimbursements.
The Joint Commission was formerly the Joint Commission on Accreditation of healthcare Organizations (JCAHO) and previous to that the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals (JCAH)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-thunderbird/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-thunderbird/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</guid>
      <description>About the Toyota logo   The Toyota brand represents our tenets of quality, reliability and durability. It also stands as a symbol to inspire people around the world to go to the places and do the things they’ve always dreamed of.
 The staging platform is how we refer to the Toyota emblem when shown in the red surround. The staging platform allows the emblem to be anchored and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota F1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tencent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tencent/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>