<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/i/</link>
    <description>Recent content in I on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/i/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IOCL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl/</guid>
      <description>Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL), commonly known as IndianOil is an Indian state government owned oil and gas company headquartered in New Delhi. It is the largest commercial oil company in the country, with a net profit of INR 19,106 crore (USD 2,848 million) for the financial year 2016–17. It is ranked 1st in Fortune India 500 list for year 2016 and 137th in Fortune&amp;rsquo;s ‘Global 500’ list of world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies in the year 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/imagen/</guid>
      <description> Grupo Imagen is a Mexican media conglomerate, part of Grupo Empresarial Ángeles
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligencer Journal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/intelligencer-journal/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligencer Journal, known locally as the Intell, was the daily, morning newspaper published by Lancaster Newspapers, Inc in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. It is the 7th oldest newspaper in the United States and was one of the oldest newspapers to be continually published under the same name. The Intelligencer Journal&amp;rsquo;s editorial page generally leaned to the Democratic/liberal perspective. The Intelligencer merged with its sister newspaper, the Lancaster New Era, in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i24 News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/i24-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/i24-news/</guid>
      <description> i24NEWS is an Israeli international 24-hour news and current affairs television channel located in Jaffa Port, Tel Aviv, Israel. It broadcasts in French, English and Arabic. The channel&amp;rsquo;s owner is Patrick Drahi, and the CEO is Frank Melloul.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Pacers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-pacers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-pacers/</guid>
      <description>The Indiana Pacers are an American professional basketball team based in Indianapolis, Indiana. The Pacers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division. The Pacers were first established in 1967 as a member of the American Basketball Association (ABA) and became a member of the NBA in 1976 as a result of the ABA–NBA merger. They play their home games at Bankers Life Fieldhouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indianapolis Colts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indianapolis-colts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indianapolis-colts/</guid>
      <description>The Indianapolis Colts are an American football team based in Indianapolis, Indiana. The Colts compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) South division. Since the 2008 season, the Colts have played their games in Lucas Oil Stadium. Previously, the team had played for over two decades (1984–2007) at the RCA Dome. Since 1987, the Colts have been the host team for the NFL Scouting Combine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isetan Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/isetan-mitsukoshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/isetan-mitsukoshi/</guid>
      <description> Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings Ltd. is a solely owned holding company of the Mitsukoshi and Isetan department stores as the wholly owned subsidiaries.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ica/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IKEA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</guid>
      <description>IKEA is a Swedish-founded multinational group that designs and sells ready-to-assemble furniture, kitchen appliances and home products, among other useful goods and occasionally home services. It has been the world&amp;rsquo;s largest furniture Retail since at least 2008. It was founded in Sweden in 1943 by 17-year-old carpenter Ingvar Kamprad, who was listed by Forbes in 2015 as one of the ten richest people in the world, worth more than $40 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iberia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iberia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iberia/</guid>
      <description>Iberia is the flag carrier airline of Spain, founded in 1927. Based in Madrid, it operates an international network of services from its main base of Madrid-Barajas Airport. Iberia, with Iberia Regional (operated by an independent carrier Air Nostrum) and with Iberia Express, is a part of Iberia Group. In addition to transporting passengers and freight, Iberia Group carries out related activities, such as aircraft maintenance, handling in airports, IT systems and in-flight catering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icelandair</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/icelandair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/icelandair/</guid>
      <description>Icelandair is the flag carrier of Iceland, headquartered at Keflavík International Airport in Iceland. It is part of the Icelandair Group and as of April 2018, operated scheduled services to 48 cities in 16 countries on both sides of the Atlantic Ocean out of its hub at Keflavík International Airport. The geographical position of Iceland is convenient for one-stop transatlantic flights, which is one pillar of the airline&amp;rsquo;s business strategy, along with traffic to and from the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrator</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/illustrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/illustrator/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Illustrator is a vector graphics editor developed and marketed by Adobe Inc. Originally designed for the Apple Macintosh, development of Adobe Illustrator began in 1985. Along with Creative Cloud (Adobe&amp;rsquo;s shift to monthly or annual subscription service delivered over the Internet), Illustrator CC was released. The latest version, Illustrator CC 2019, was released in October 2018 and is the 23rd generation in the product line. Adobe Illustrator was reviewed as the best vector graphics editing program in 2018 by PC Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InDesign</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indesign/</guid>
      <description>Adobe InDesign is a desktop publishing and typesetting software application produced by Adobe Systems. It can be used to create works such as posters, flyers, brochures, magazines, newspapers, presentations, books and ebooks. InDesign can also publish content suitable for tablet devices in conjunction with Adobe Digital Publishing Suite. Graphic designers and production artists are the principal users, creating and laying out periodical publications, posters, and print media. It also supports export to EPUB and SWF formats to create e-books and digital publications, including digital magazines, and content suitable for consumption on tablet computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/instagram/</guid>
      <description>Instagram is a photo and video-sharing social networking service owned by Facebook, Inc. It was created by Kevin Systrom and Mike Krieger, and launched in October 2010 exclusively on iOS. A version for Android devices was released a year and half later, in April 2012, followed by a feature-limited website interface in November 2012, and apps for Windows 10 Mobile and Windows 10 in April 2016 and October 2016 respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/intel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/intel/</guid>
      <description>Intel Corporation is an American multinational corporation and technology company headquartered in Santa Clara, California, in the Silicon Valley. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest and second highest valued semiconductor chip manufacturer based on revenue after being overtaken by Samsung Electronics, and is the inventor of the x86 series of microprocessors, the processors found in most personal computers (PCs). Intel ranked No. 46 in the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love New York</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/i-love-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 01:06:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/i-love-new-york/</guid>
      <description>History of the I LOVE NY logo  One of the most widely distributed and imitated images in the world, the “I Love New York Logo”—consisting of an upper-case “I,” followed by a red heart symbol, and then the upper-case letters “N” and “Y,” set in the rounded slab serif typeface American Typewriter—was created by graphic designer Milton Glaser and first used in 1977 to promote the city and state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Surrogacy Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/illinois-surrogacy-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:49:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/illinois-surrogacy-center/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ibm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IV Interactive</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</guid>
      <description>About IV interactive IV Interactive is a full-service interactive agency specializing in the four elements required for success in an increasingly digital world: innovative design, interactive marketing, technology implementation and strategic consulting. Using this multidisciplinary approach, we provide results-driven, award-winning solutions to organizations of all sizes and disciplines. From Jones Apparel Group to Thomson Reuters, we have helped our clients identify and implement the elements necessary for success.
 Over 90% of our business comes through referrals from existing clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>