<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>Australia on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/australia/</link><description>Recent content in Australia on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/australia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/99designs//file/99designs.svg</url><title>99designs Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">99designs</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/99designs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/99designs/</guid><description turbo="true">99designs is a Melbourne, Australia, based company that operates a freelancer platform for connecting graphic designers and clients. The company was founded in 2008, and has a United States office in Oakland, California.
Source About 99designs We’re 99designs, the global creative platform that makes it easy for clients and designers to work together online. Since 2008, our freelance community has brought more than one million creative projects to life for thousands of genius entrepreneurs, savvy business owners, and brands with big ideas.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank//file/commonwealth-bank.svg</url><title>Commonwealth Bank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Commonwealth Bank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank/</guid><description turbo="true">The Commonwealth Bank of Australia (CBA), or CommBank, is an Australian multinational bank with businesses across New Zealand, Asia, the United States and the United Kingdom. It provides a variety of financial services including retail, business and institutional banking, funds management, superannuation, insurance, investment and broking services. The Commonwealth Bank is the largest Australian listed company on the Australian Securities Exchange as of August 2015 with brands including Bankwest, Colonial First State Investments, ASB Bank (New Zealand), Commonwealth Securities (CommSec) and Commonwealth Insurance (CommInsure).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/red-bull//file/red-bull.svg</url><title>Red Bull Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Red Bull</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/red-bull/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/red-bull/</guid><description turbo="true">Red Bull is an energy drink sold by Red Bull GmbH, an Austrian company created in 1987. Red Bull has the highest market share of any energy drink in the world, with 7.5 billion cans sold in a year (as of 2019).
Austrian entrepreneur Dietrich Mateschitz was inspired by an existing energy drink named Krating Daeng, which was first introduced and sold in Thailand by Chaleo Yoovidhya. He took this idea, modified the ingredients to suit the tastes of Westerners, and, in partnership with Chaleo, founded Red Bull GmbH in 1987 in Chakkapong, Thailand.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia//file/hearing-australia.svg</url><title>Hearing Australia Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hearing Australia</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hearing-australia/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hearing Australia is a statutory authority constituted under the Australian Hearing Services Act 1991, reporting to the Minister for Human Services, and is within the Department of Human Services portfolio. Hearing Australia is the largest Australian government-funded hearing aid dispensing company providing hearing care and technologies. One of their areas of interest is hearing testing and rehabilitation of children under the age of 26.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2000-sydney//file/olympics-2000-sydney.svg</url><title>Olympics 2000 Sydney Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Olympics 2000 Sydney</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2000-sydney/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:32 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2000-sydney/</guid><description turbo="true">About Olympic Games The Olympic flag The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc//file/abc.svg</url><title>ABC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ABC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/abc/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) is Australia&amp;rsquo;s national broadcaster founded in 1929. It is principally funded by the direct grants from the Australian government, but is expressly independent of government and partisan politics. The ABC plays a leading role in journalistic independence and is fundamental in the history of broadcasting in Australia.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines//file/qantas-airlines.svg</url><title>Qantas Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Qantas Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/qantas-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">Qantas Airways Limited (/ˈkwɒntəs/) is the flag carrier of Australia and its largest airline by fleet size, international flights and international destinations. It is the third oldest airline in the world, after KLM and Avianca having been founded in November 1920; it began international passenger flights in May 1935. The Qantas name comes from &amp;ldquo;QANTAS&amp;rdquo;, an acronym for its original name, &amp;ldquo;Queensland and Northern Territory Aerial Services&amp;rdquo;, and it is nicknamed &amp;ldquo;The Flying Kangaroo&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>