<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>social media on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in social media on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn is an American business and employment-oriented service that operates via websites and mobile apps. Founded on December 28, 2002, and launched on May 5, 2003, it is mainly used for professional networking, including employers posting jobs and job seekers posting their CVs. As of 2015, most of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue came from selling access to information about its members to recruiters and sales professionals. As of March 2019, LinkedIn had 610 million registered members in 200 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 22:48:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/youtube/</guid>
      <description>The YouTube logo is made of a red round-rectangular box with a white &amp;ldquo;play&amp;rdquo; button inside and the word &amp;ldquo;YouTube&amp;rdquo; written in black.
 2017 YouTube Logo Update The bright red cherry on top of this update sundae is a refreshed YouTube Logo and YouTube Icon. Designed for our multi-screen world, the updated Logo combines a cleaned up version of the YouTube wordmark and Icon, creating a more flexible design that works better across a variety of devices, even on the tiniest screens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/instagram/</guid>
      <description>Instagram is a photo and video-sharing social networking service owned by Facebook, Inc. It was created by Kevin Systrom and Mike Krieger, and launched in October 2010 exclusively on iOS. A version for Android devices was released a year and half later, in April 2012, followed by a feature-limited website interface in November 2012, and apps for Windows 10 Mobile and Windows 10 in April 2016 and October 2016 respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/snapchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/snapchat/</guid>
      <description> Snapchat is a multimedia messaging app used globally, created by Evan Spiegel, Bobby Murphy, and Reggie Brown, former students at Stanford University, and developed by Snap Inc., originally Snapchat Inc.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/twitter/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is an American online news and social networking service on which users post and interact with messages known as &amp;ldquo;tweets&amp;rdquo;. Tweets were originally restricted to 140 characters, but on November 7, 2017, this limit was doubled to 280 for all languages except Chinese, Japanese, and Korean. Registered users can post, like, and retweet tweets, but unregistered users can only read them. Users access Twitter through its website interface, through Short Message Service (SMS) or its mobile-device application software (&amp;ldquo;app&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook/</guid>
      <description>New Facebook Logo  The company unveiled its new logo Tuesday, April 30, 2019. The new logo retains the distinctive “f” letter, but replaces the rounded square container with a circle. In addition, the new look moves the “f” to the center of the icon, rather than the right side like in the old version. The “Facebook” logotype that has the full name of the company is now relegated to use only for the company — but not its services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Messenger</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook-messenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook-messenger/</guid>
      <description>Facebook Founded in 2004, Facebook’s mission is to give people the power to build community and bring the world closer together. People use Facebook to stay connected with friends and family, to discover what’s going on in the world, and to share and express what matters to them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>