<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>P on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/p/</link>
    <description>Recent content in P on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/p/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Porsche</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/porshe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/porshe/</guid>
      <description> Dr.-Ing. h.c. F. Porsche AG, usually shortened to Porsche AG, is a German automobile manufacturer specializing in high-performance sports cars, SUVs and sedans. Porsche AG is headquartered in Stuttgart, and is owned by Volkswagen AG, which is itself majority-owned by Porsche Automobil Holding SE. Porsche&amp;rsquo;s current lineup includes the 718 Boxster/Cayman, 911, Panamera, Macan and Cayenne.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penguin Books</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:31:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</guid>
      <description>Penguin Books Logo History Designed by Edward Young  In 1935, Edward Young designed Penguin’s famous “dignified but flippant” logo and the colour scheme for its book covers.
 It started with the simple logo and name, suggested, allegedly, by a typist who was earwigging the board meeting. Allen had already hit upon the idea of an animal logo, inspired by the template offered by the contemporary publishing house The Albatross Library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime Video</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prime-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:58:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prime-video/</guid>
      <description>About Amazon Prime Prime Video, also referred to as Amazon Prime Video, is an Internet video on demand service that is developed, owned, and operated by Amazon. It offers television shows and films for rent or purchase and Prime Video, a selection of Amazon Studios original content and licensed acquisitions included in the Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Prime subscription. In the UK, US, Germany, Sweden, and Austria, access to Prime Video is also available through a video-only membership, which does not require a full Prime subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper (from prosper.com)
Prosper was founded in 2005 as the first peer-to-peer lending marketplace in the United States. Since then, Prosper has facilitated more than $15 billion in loans to more than 910,000 people.
Through Prosper, people can invest in each other in a way that is financially and socially rewarding. Borrowers apply online for a fixed-rate, fixed-term loan between $2,000 and $40,000. Individuals and institutions can invest in the loans and earn attractive returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper healthcare (from prosperhealthcare.com)
Prosper healthcare Lending is a patient financing marketplace company headquartered in Salt Lake City, Utah at the heart of the “Silicon Slopes”. We sit at the intersection of the healthcare, technology, and financial services markets and we are using technology to bring innovative financial services solutions to a massive healthcare problem. Our patient financing platform allows healthcare providers nationwide to help Make healthcare Affordable™ for patients every day by referring patients with good credit to affordable installment loans offered through Prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Path2Parenthood</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</guid>
      <description>About Path2Parenthoods Path2Parenthood (P2P) is an inclusive organization committed to helping people create their families by providing leading-edge outreach programs and timely educational information. The scope of our work encompasses reproductive health, infertility prevention and treatment, and family-building options including adoption and third party solutions. P2P is a national, not-for-profit 501&amp;copy;(3) charitable organization headquartered in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patients Choice Award</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/patients-choice-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/patients-choice-award/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Makeup</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/puzzle-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 14:02:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/puzzle-makeup/</guid>
      <description> About Puzzle Makeup Puzzle cosmetics are great quality, composed of mineral ingredients and are talc and paraben free, with no harsh chemicals. All Puzzle cosmetics are cruelty free with no animal testing.
 At Puzzle Makeup, our natural, talc and paraben free cosmetics bring a healthy perspective to personal beauty at an honest price.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsico</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Cola</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Fertility Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</guid>
      <description>About Pacific Fertility Center Pacific Fertility Center®, located in Northern California&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco Bay Area, is an international destination for male and female fertility treatment and care. We also regularly see patients from surrounding areas in California, like Berkeley, Oakland, Palo Alto, and Marin County. For updated information about our fertility clinic, infertility treatment options, IVF success rates and more, read our infertility doctor blog or subscribe to Pacific Fertility Center&amp;rsquo;s Fertility Flash newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prelude Fertility</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 21:15:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</guid>
      <description>About Prelude (from Prelude brandbook)
Prelude Pagoda  Prelude is a network of top-tier fertility centers across the US offering comprehensive fertility care. Whether you’re hoping to build your family now or looking to preserve your options for the future, Prelude meets you where you are.
The story behind the logo The Pagoda plays a key role in the Prelude Network identity. It is a simple, functional device that communicates our mission yet allows for interpretation at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>