<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>P on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/p/</link>
    <description>Recent content in P on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/p/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper Healthcare (from prosperhealthcare.com)
Prosper Healthcare Lending is a patient financing marketplace company headquartered in Salt Lake City, Utah at the heart of the “Silicon Slopes”. We sit at the intersection of the healthcare, technology, and financial services markets and we are using technology to bring innovative financial services solutions to a massive healthcare problem. Our patient financing platform allows healthcare providers nationwide to help Make Healthcare Affordable™ for patients every day by referring patients with good credit to affordable installment loans offered through Prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Makeup</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/puzzle-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 14:02:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/puzzle-makeup/</guid>
      <description> About Puzzle Makeup Puzzle cosmetics are great quality, composed of mineral ingredients and are talc and paraben free, with no harsh chemicals. All Puzzle cosmetics are cruelty free with no animal testing.
 At Puzzle Makeup, our natural, talc and paraben free cosmetics bring a healthy perspective to personal beauty at an honest price.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsico</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Cola</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Fertility Center</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pacific-fertility-center/</guid>
      <description>About Pacific Fertility Center Pacific Fertility Center®, located in Northern California&amp;rsquo;s San Francisco Bay Area, is an international destination for male and female fertility treatment and care. We also regularly see patients from surrounding areas in California, like Berkeley, Oakland, Palo Alto, and Marin County. For updated information about our fertility clinic, infertility treatment options, IVF success rates and more, read our infertility doctor blog or subscribe to Pacific Fertility Center&amp;rsquo;s Fertility Flash newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prelude Fertility</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 21:15:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prelude-fertility/</guid>
      <description>About Prelude (from Prelude brandbook)
Prelude Pagoda  Prelude is a network of top-tier fertility centers across the US offering comprehensive fertility care. Whether you’re hoping to build your family now or looking to preserve your options for the future, Prelude meets you where you are.
The story behind the logo The Pagoda plays a key role in the Prelude Network identity. It is a simple, functional device that communicates our mission yet allows for interpretation at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>