<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>corporation on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/corporation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in corporation on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/corporation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Berkshire Hathaway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/berkshire-hathaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/berkshire-hathaway/</guid>
      <description>Berkshire Hathaway is an American multinational conglomerate holding company headquartered in Omaha, Nebraska, United States. The company wholly owns GEICO, Duracell, Dairy Queen, BNSF, Lubrizol, Fruit of the Loom, Helzberg Diamonds, Long &amp;amp; Foster, FlightSafety International, Pampered Chef, Forest River and NetJets, and also owns 38.6% of Pilot Flying J; 26.7% of the Kraft Heinz Company, and significant minority holdings in American Express (17.6%), Wells Fargo (9.9%), The Coca-Cola Company (9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cargill</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cargill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cargill/</guid>
      <description>Cargill, Incorporated is an American privately held global corporation based in Minnetonka, Minnesota, and incorporated in Wilmington, Delaware. Founded in 1865, it is the largest privately held corporation in the United States in terms of revenue. If it were a public company, it would rank, as of 2015, number 15 on the Fortune 500, behind McKesson and ahead of AT&amp;amp;T. Cargill has frequently been the subject of criticism related to the environment, human rights, finance, and other ethical considerations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jardines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jardines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jardines/</guid>
      <description>Jardine Matheson Holdings Limited (also known as Jardines) is a British conglomerate incorporated in Bermuda and headquartered in Hong Kong, with its primary listing on the London Stock Exchange and secondary listings on the Singapore Exchange and Bermuda Stock Exchange. The majority of its business interests are in Asia, and its subsidiaries include Jardine Pacific, Jardine Motors, Jardine Lloyd Thompson, Hongkong Land, Jardine Strategic Holdings, Dairy Farm, Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group, Jardine Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage and Astra International.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/trump/</guid>
      <description>The Trump Organization is the collective name for a group of approximately 500 business entities of which Donald Trump is the sole or principal owner. Approximately 250 entities use the Trump name. Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s grandmother, Elizabeth Christ Trump, and father, Fred Trump, founded the organization in 1923 as E. Trump &amp;amp; Son, and it was led from 1971 to 2017 by Donald Trump, who renamed the company around 1973.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DuPont</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</guid>
      <description> DuPont de Nemours, Inc., commonly known as DuPont, is an American company formed by the merger of Dow Chemical and DuPont on August 31, 2017, and then subsequent spinoffs of Dow Inc. and Corteva. Prior to the spinoffs it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest chemical company in terms of sales.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</guid>
      <description> Huawei Technologies Co. Ltd. is a Chinese multinational technology company that provides telecommunications equipment and sells consumer electronics, including smartphones, headquartered in Shenzhen, Guangdong.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siemens/</guid>
      <description> Siemens AG is a German multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Munich and the largest industrial manufacturing company in Europe with branch offices abroad.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Electric</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/general-electric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/general-electric/</guid>
      <description> General Electric Company (GE) is an American multinational conglomerate incorporated in New York City and headquartered in Boston. As of 2018, the company operates through the following segments: aviation, healthcare, power, renewable energy, digital industry, additive manufacturing, venture capital and finance, lighting, and oil and gas.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>