<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>corporation on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/corporation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in corporation on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/corporation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jardines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jardines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jardines/</guid>
      <description>Jardine Matheson Holdings Limited (also known as Jardines) is a British conglomerate incorporated in Bermuda and headquartered in Hong Kong, with its primary listing on the London Stock Exchange and secondary listings on the Singapore Exchange and Bermuda Stock Exchange. The majority of its business interests are in Asia, and its subsidiaries include Jardine Pacific, Jardine Motors, Jardine Lloyd Thompson, Hongkong Land, Jardine Strategic Holdings, Dairy Farm, Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group, Jardine Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage and Astra International.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DuPont</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</guid>
      <description> DuPont de Nemours, Inc., commonly known as DuPont, is an American company formed by the merger of Dow Chemical and DuPont on August 31, 2017, and then subsequent spinoffs of Dow Inc. and Corteva. Prior to the spinoffs it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest chemical company in terms of sales.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huawei/</guid>
      <description> Huawei Technologies Co. Ltd. is a Chinese multinational technology company that provides telecommunications equipment and sells consumer electronics, including smartphones, headquartered in Shenzhen, Guangdong.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siemens/</guid>
      <description> Siemens AG is a German multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Munich and the largest industrial manufacturing company in Europe with branch offices abroad.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Electric</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/general-electric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/general-electric/</guid>
      <description> General Electric Company (GE) is an American multinational conglomerate incorporated in New York City and headquartered in Boston. As of 2018, the company operates through the following segments: aviation, healthcare, power, renewable energy, digital industry, additive manufacturing, venture capital and finance, lighting, and oil and gas.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>