<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>1976 on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/year/1976/</link><description>Recent content in 1976 on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0001</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/1976/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple//file/apple.svg</url><title>Apple Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0001</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</guid><description turbo="true">History of Apple logo At the time of his initial meeting with Steve Jobs in early 1977, Apple Computer was still very much in its infancy, having been incorporated for less than a year. Apple’s offices were in a local strip mall, and consisted of just the three partners – Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Mike Markkula.
The initial identity development was to coincide with the introduction of the brand’s first personal computer, the Apple II.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-innsbruck//file/olympics-1976-innsbruck.svg</url><title>Olympics 1976 Innsbruck Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Olympics 1976 Innsbruck</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-innsbruck/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:28:09 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-innsbruck/</guid><description turbo="true">The 1976 Winter Olympics, officially known as the XII Olympic Winter Games (French: XIIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver, German: Olympische Winterspiele 1976), were a winter multi-sport event which was celebrated February 4–15, 1976 in Innsbruck, Austria. It was the second time the Tyrolean city hosted the Games, which were awarded to Innsbruck after Denver, the original host city, withdrew in 1972.
About Olympic Games The official poster of the 1976 Winter Olympics The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-montreal//file/olympics-1976-montreal.svg</url><title>Olympics 1976 Montreal Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Olympics 1976 Montreal</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-montreal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:31:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-montreal/</guid><description turbo="true">Préfontaine and Henderson lighting the Olympic Flame The 1976 Summer Olympics, officially called the Games of the XXI Olympiad (French: Les XXIes olympiques d&amp;rsquo;été), was an international multi-sport event in Montreal, Quebec, in 1976, and the first Olympic Games held in Canada. Montreal was awarded the rights to the 1976 Games on May 12, 1970, at the 69th IOC Session in Amsterdam, over the bids of Moscow and Los Angeles.</description></item></channel></rss>