<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>V on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/v/</link>
    <description>Recent content in V on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/v/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</guid>
      <description> VK (short for its original name VKontakte; Russian: ВКонта́кте, meaning InContact) is a Russian online social media and social networking service based in Saint Petersburg. VK is available in numerous languages but it is especially used by Russian-speakers. VK allows users to message each other publicly or privately; create groups, public pages, and events; share and tag images, audio, and video; and play browser-based games.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valero</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/valero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/valero/</guid>
      <description>Valero Energy Corporation is a Fortune 500 international manufacturer and marketer of transportation fuels, other petrochemical products, and power. It is headquartered in San Antonio, Texas, United States. Throughout the United States and Canada, the company owns and operates 15 refineries, and one in Wales, with a combined throughput capacity of approximately 3 million barrels (480,000 m3) per day, 11 ethanol plants with a combined production capacity of 1.2 billion US gallons (4,500,000 m3) per year, and a 50-megawatt wind farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</guid>
      <description> Vodafone plc /ˈvoʊdəfoʊn/ is a British multinational telecommunications conglomerate with headquarters in London and Newbury, Berkshire. It predominantly operates services in the regions of Asia, Africa, Europe, and Oceania. Among mobile operator groups globally, Vodafone ranked 4th (behind China Mobile, Bharti Airtel and Vodafone Idea) in the number of mobile customers (313 million) as of 2018
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Canucks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-canucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-canucks/</guid>
      <description> The Vancouver Canucks are a professional ice hockey team based in Vancouver, British Columbia. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Canucks play their home games at Rogers Arena, formerly known as General Motors Place, which has an official capacity of 18,910. Travis Green is the head coach and Jim Benning is the general manager.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Whitecaps FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-whitecaps-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vancouver-whitecaps-fc/</guid>
      <description>Vancouver Whitecaps FC is a Canadian professional soccer team based in Vancouver, British Columbia that competes in the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The Whitecaps were the 17th team to enter Major League Soccer and replaced the USSF Division 2 team of the same name in the city. The club has been owned and managed by the same group since their USSF days, having graduated to MLS after the conclusion of the USSF&amp;rsquo;s 2010 season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Golden Knights</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vegas-golden-knights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vegas-golden-knights/</guid>
      <description>The Vegas Golden Knights are a professional ice hockey team based in the Las Vegas metropolitan area that competes in the National Hockey League (NHL). They are members of the Pacific Division of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference, and began play in the 2017–18 NHL season. The team is owned by Black Knight Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment, a consortium led by Bill Foley and the Maloof family. The team plays its home games at T-Mobile Arena on the Las Vegas Strip in Paradise, Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</guid>
      <description>Virgin Media Limited is a British company which provides telephone, television and internet services in the United Kingdom. Its headquarters are in Hook, Hampshire. Since 2013, Virgin Media has been a subsidiary of Liberty Global plc, an international television and telecommunications company. The company was previously listed on the NASDAQ Stock Market and London Stock Exchange. Virgin Media is not a sister company of Virgin Mobile USA, which is owned by Sprint Corporation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verizon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</guid>
      <description> Verizon Communications Inc. is an American multinational telecommunications conglomerate and a corporate component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average. The company is based at 1095 Avenue of the Americas in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, but is incorporated in Delaware.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Versant Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Vietnam Airlines (Vietnamese: Hãng Hàng không Quốc gia Việt Nam) is the flag carrier of Vietnam. The airline was founded in 1956 and later established as a state-owned enterprise in April 1989. Vietnam Airlines is headquartered in Long Biên District, Hanoi, with hubs at Noi Bai International Airport and Tan Son Nhat International Airport. The airline flies to 64 destinations in 17 countries, excluding codeshared services.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/volkswagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volkswagen/</guid>
      <description> Volkswagen is a German automaker founded on 28 May 1937 by the German Labour Front, a Nazi labour union, and headquartered in Wolfsburg. It is the flagship marque of the Volkswagen Group, the largest automaker by worldwide sales in 2016 and 2017. The group&amp;rsquo;s biggest market is in China, which delivers 40% of its sales and profits.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volvo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</guid>
      <description> The Volvo Group (Swedish: Volvokoncernen; legally Aktiebolaget Volvo, shortened to AB Volvo) (stylized as VOLVO) is a Swedish multinational manufacturing company headquartered in Gothenburg. While its core activity is the production, distribution and sale of trucks, buses and construction equipment, Volvo also supplies marine and industrial drive systems and financial services. In 2016, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest manufacturer of heavy-duty trucks.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/visa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>