<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>Rugby on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/tags/rugby/</link><description>Recent content in Rugby on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/tags/rugby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Adams State Grizzlies Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/files525/adams-state-grizzlies.svg"/></figure></header>
The Adams State Grizzlies are the athletic teams that represent Adams State University, located in Alamosa, Colorado, in NCAA Division II intercollegiate sports. The Grizzlies compete as members of the Rocky Mountain Athletic Conference for all 19 varsity sports. Source<p>You can download theAdams State Grizzlieslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/files525/adams-state-grizzlies.svg</url><title>Adams State GrizzliesLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Adams State Grizzlies</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/adams-state-grizzlies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/adams-state-grizzlies/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Adams State Grizzlies are the athletic teams that represent Adams State University, located in Alamosa, Colorado, in NCAA Division II intercollegiate sports. The Grizzlies compete as members of the Rocky Mountain Athletic Conference for all 19 varsity sports. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Central Washington Wildcats Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/files525/central-washington-wildcats.svg"/></figure></header>
The Central Washington Wildcats are the 12 varsity athletic teams that represent Central Washington University, located in Ellensburg, Washington, in NCAA Division II intercollegiate sports. The Wildcats compete as members of the Great Northwest Athletic Conference. Source<p>You can download theCentral Washington Wildcatslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/files525/central-washington-wildcats.svg</url><title>Central Washington WildcatsLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Central Washington Wildcats</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/central-washington-wildcats/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/central-washington-wildcats/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Central Washington Wildcats are the 12 varsity athletic teams that represent Central Washington University, located in Ellensburg, Washington, in NCAA Division II intercollegiate sports. The Wildcats compete as members of the Great Northwest Athletic Conference. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Brown Bears Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/files525/brown-bears.svg"/></figure></header>
The Brown Bears are the sports teams that represent Brown University, an American university located in Providence, Rhode Island. The Bears are part of the Ivy League conference. Brown&amp;rsquo;s mascot is Bruno. Both the men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams share the name, competing in 28 National Collegiate Athletic Association Division I sports. In football, the Bears, along with all other the Ivy League teams, compete in the Football Championship Subdivision. Source<p>You can download theBrown Bearslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/files525/brown-bears.svg</url><title>Brown BearsLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Brown Bears</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/brown-bears/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown-bears/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Brown Bears are the sports teams that represent Brown University, an American university located in Providence, Rhode Island. The Bears are part of the Ivy League conference. Brown&amp;rsquo;s mascot is Bruno. Both the men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams share the name, competing in 28 National Collegiate Athletic Association Division I sports. In football, the Bears, along with all other the Ivy League teams, compete in the Football Championship Subdivision. Source</description></item></channel></rss>