<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japan on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/japan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Japan on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1998 Nagano</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1998-nagano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1998-nagano/</guid>
      <description>The 1998 Winter Olympics, officially the XVIII Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XVIIIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver)1, and commonly known as Nagano 1998, was a winter multi-sport event celebrated from 7 to 22 February 1998 that were centered in Nagano, Japan. The Games also took place in the nearby mountain communities of Hakuba, Karuizawa, Nozawa Onsen, and Yamanouuchi. The city of Nagano had previously been a candidate to host the 1940 Winter Olympics (which were later cancelled), as well as the 1972 Winter Olympics, but each time Nagano was eliminated at the national level by Sapporo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2020 Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2020-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:33:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2020-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acura</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acura/</guid>
      <description>Acura (/ˈækjʊrə/) is the American luxury vehicle marque of Japanese automaker Honda. The brand was launched in the United States and Canada on 27 March 1986, marketing luxury, performance, and high-performance vehicles. It was introduced to Hong Kong in 1991, Mexico in 2004, China in 2006, Russia in 2014 (no longer available in Russia) and Kuwait in 2015, and is also sold in Ukraine. Honda&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce Acura to the Japanese domestic market (JDM) in 2008 was delayed, due to economic reasons,[4] and later withheld as a result of the 2008 financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/honda/</guid>
      <description> Honda Motor Company, Ltd. is a Japanese public multinational conglomerate corporation primarily known as a manufacturer of automobiles, motorcycles, and power equipment.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Japan Airlines is an international airline, headquartered in Shinagawa Tokyo, Japan. Its main hubs are Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s Narita International Airport and Tokyo International Airport (Haneda Airport), as well as Osaka&amp;rsquo;s Kansai International Airport and Osaka International Airport. JAL group companies include Japan Airlines, J-Air, JAL Express, Japan Air Commuter, Japan Transocean Air, ZIPAIR Tokyo and Ryukyu Air Commuter for domestic feeder services, and JAL Cargo for cargo and mail services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mazda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mazda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mazda/</guid>
      <description> Mazda Motor Corporation (Japanese: マツダ株式会社 Hepburn: Matsuda Kabushiki-gaisha), commonly referred to as simply Mazda, is a Japanese multinational automaker based in Fuchū, Aki District, Hiroshima Prefecture, Japan.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subaru</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</guid>
      <description> Subaru is the automobile manufacturing division of Japanese transportation conglomerate Subaru Corporation (formerly known as Fuji Heavy Industries), the twenty-second largest automaker by production worldwide in 2012.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</guid>
      <description>About the Toyota logo   The Toyota brand represents our tenets of quality, reliability and durability. It also stands as a symbol to inspire people around the world to go to the places and do the things they’ve always dreamed of.
 The staging platform is how we refer to the Toyota emblem when shown in the red surround. The staging platform allows the emblem to be anchored and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota F1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scion</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lexus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>