<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>J on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/j/</link>
    <description>Recent content in J on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/j/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JC Penney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jc-penney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jc-penney/</guid>
      <description> J. C. Penney Company, is an American department store chain with 864 locations in 49 U.S. states and Puerto Rico. In addition to selling conventional merchandise, J. C. Penney stores often house several leased departments such as Sephora, Seattle&amp;rsquo;s Best Coffee, salons, auto centers, optical centers, portrait studios, and jewelry repair.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaguar</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jaguar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jaguar/</guid>
      <description> Jaguar is the luxury vehicle brand of Jaguar Land Rover, a British multinational car manufacturer with its headquarters in Whitley, Coventry, England. Jaguar Cars was the company that was responsible for the production of Jaguar cars until its operations were fully merged with those of Land Rover to form Jaguar Land Rover on 1 January 2013.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Japan Airlines is an international airline, headquartered in Shinagawa Tokyo, Japan. Its main hubs are Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s Narita International Airport and Tokyo International Airport (Haneda Airport), as well as Osaka&amp;rsquo;s Kansai International Airport and Osaka International Airport. JAL group companies include Japan Airlines, J-Air, JAL Express, Japan Air Commuter, Japan Transocean Air, ZIPAIR Tokyo and Ryukyu Air Commuter for domestic feeder services, and JAL Cargo for cargo and mail services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeep</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jeep/</guid>
      <description> Jeep is a brand of American automobile and division of FCA US LLC (formerly Chrysler Group, LLC), a wholly owned subsidiary of the Italian-American corporation Fiat Chrysler Automobiles. Jeep has been a part of Chrysler since 1987, when Chrysler acquired the Jeep brand, along with remaining assets, from its previous owner American Motors Corporation (AMC).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JetBlue</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetblue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jetblue/</guid>
      <description>JetBlue Airways Corporation, stylized as jetBlue, is an American low cost carrier scheduled passenger airline headquartered in New York City. A major air carrier and the sixth-largest airline in the United States, jetBlue is headquartered in the Long Island City neighborhood of the New York City borough of Queens, with its main base at John F. Kennedy International Airport. It also maintains corporate offices in Cottonwood Heights, Utah and Orlando, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>