<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>D on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in D on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DBS Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dbs-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dbs-bank/</guid>
      <description> DBS Bank is a Singaporean multinational banking and financial services corporation headquartered in Marina Bay Financial Centre Tower 3, Marina Bay, Singapore. The company was known as The Development Bank of Singapore Limited, before the present name was adopted on 21 July 2003 to reflect its changing role as a regional bank.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC Defenders</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-defenders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-defenders/</guid>
      <description>The DC Defenders are a professional American football team based in Washington, D.C. The team is an owned-and-operated member of the new XFL founded by Vince McMahon’s Alpha Entertainment and plays its home games at Audi Field, a soccer-specific stadium owned and originally built by Major League Soccer&amp;rsquo;s D.C. United, who leases the land from the District of Columbia. At 20,000 seats, Audi Field is the smallest stadium in the XFL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DQ</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</guid>
      <description> Dairy Queen (DQ) is an American multinational chain of soft serve ice cream and fast-food restaurants owned by International Dairy Queen, Inc., a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway. International Dairy Queen, Inc., also owns Orange Julius, and formerly owned Karmelkorn and Golden Skillet Fried Chicken.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DWH</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dwh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dwh/</guid>
      <description> We believe in a comprehensive approach to your healthcare - one that focuses on your emotional and practice needs as well as your medical status.
 Women today know that they play an important role in making treatment choices about their health care. We invite you to join us as partners in your healthcare decisions.
Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Renegades</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-renegades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-renegades/</guid>
      <description> The Dallas Renegades are a professional American football team based in Arlington, Texas. The team is an owned-and-operated member of the new XFL founded by Vince McMahon&amp;rsquo;s Alpha Entertainment and plays its home games at Globe Life Park in Arlington, which was re-purposed as a football venue after its previous tenant, Major League Baseball&amp;rsquo;s Texas Rangers, relocated to the newly built Globe Life Field.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decred</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/decred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/decred/</guid>
      <description> Decred (DCR) is an open-source, community-based cryptocurrency, similar to Bitcoin. Decred was launched in February 2016 by the bitcoin developers that engineered btcsuite, an alternative full-node Bitcoin implementation written in the Go (golang) programming language and is used by development projects such as Ethereum, Factom, BitGo, OpenBazaar, and the Lightning Network.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deezer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</guid>
      <description>Deezer is a French online music streaming service. It allows users to listen to music content from record labels, including Universal Music Group, Sony Music and Warner Music Group (owned by Deezer&amp;rsquo;s parent company Access Industries) on various devices online or offline. Created in Paris, France, Deezer currently has 56 million licensed tracks in its library, with over 30,000 radio channels, 14 million monthly active users, and 7 million paid subscribers as of January 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DiDi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/didi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/didi/</guid>
      <description>Didi Chuxing Technology Co., formerly Didi Kuaidi (Chinese: 滴滴快的), is a transportation company headquartered in Beijing. The company provides app-based transportation services, including taxi hailing, private car hailing, social ride-sharing and bike sharing; on-demand delivery services; and automobile services, including sales, leasing, financing, maintenance, fleet operation, electric vehicle charging and co-development of vehicles with automakers. In 2018, DiDi&amp;rsquo;s platform had more than 550 million users and tens of millions of drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docomo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/docomo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/docomo/</guid>
      <description>NTT Docomo Inc. is the predominant mobile phone operator in Japan. The name is officially an abbreviation of the phrase, &amp;ldquo;do communications over the mobile network&amp;rdquo;, and is also from a compound word dokomo, meaning &amp;ldquo;everywhere&amp;rdquo; in Japanese. Docomo provides phone, video phone (FOMA and Some PHS), i-mode (internet), and mail (i-mode mail, Short Mail, and SMS) services. The company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in the Sanno Park Tower, Nagatachō, Chiyoda, Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dogecoin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dogecoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dogecoin/</guid>
      <description> Dogecoin (DOGE, symbol: Ð and D) is a Litecoin-derived cryptocurrency featuring a Shiba Inu from the Doge Internet meme on its logo. The users themselves call it “joky”. One of the most popular uses of the coin is the reward of Internet users for interesting and quality content created or shared by them. It was introduced on December 8, 2013.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donor Concierge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/donor-concierge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/donor-concierge/</guid>
      <description>The Donor Concierge team is comprised of compassionate, educated, and knowledgeable case managers, with a track record of outstanding results to help families find the right donor/surrogate choice through the best industry connections. We have chosen each team member for her unique ability to relate to our clients. We have a multinational office with Canadian, Chinese, Filipino, and American case managers who speak a variety of languages including Mandarin, French, Tagalog, Spanish, and English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duracell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/duracell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/duracell/</guid>
      <description> Duracell Inc. is an American manufacturing company owned by Berkshire Hathaway that produces batteries and smart power systems. The company has its origins in the 1920s, through the work of Samuel Ruben and Philip Mallory, and the formation of the P.R. Mallory Company.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DXT</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</guid>
      <description> DXC Technology is an American multinational corporation that provides B2B IT services.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dash/</guid>
      <description> Dash is an open source cryptocurrency and is a form of decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) run by a subset of users, called &amp;ldquo;masternodes&amp;rdquo;. It is an altcoin that was forked from the Bitcoin protocol. The currency permits fast transactions that can be untraceable.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dazzler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dazzler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dazzler/</guid>
      <description> Featuring sleek decor and exceptional service, Dazzler Hotels represent an exciting synthesis of comfort and functional aesthetics. Centrally located in some of Latin America’s most vibrant neighborhoods, Dazzler offers easy access to local hotspots and top attractions.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deseret News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deseret-news/</guid>
      <description>The Deseret News is a newspaper published in Salt Lake City, Utah, United States. It is Utah&amp;rsquo;s oldest continuously published daily newspaper and has the largest Sunday circulation in the state and the second largest daily circulation behind The Salt Lake Tribune. The News is owned by Deseret News Publishing Company, a subsidiary of Deseret Management Corporation, a holding company owned by The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DigiTech</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/digitech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/digitech/</guid>
      <description> DigiTech is an American company which manufactures digital effects units.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolce</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dolce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dolce/</guid>
      <description> Dolce Hotels and Resorts’ awe-inspiring locations provide imaginative environments for guests to connect, create, and discover. State-of-the-art meeting spaces with advanced technology paired with our sophisticated food and beverage program, offer an ideal combination for stimulating creativity. Whether it’s an award-winning golf courses, rejuvenating spas, or close proximity to the world’s most famous wineries, guests are drawn to Dolce for meetings, celebrations, and memory-making getaways.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dribbble</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dribbble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dribbble/</guid>
      <description> Dribbble is a self-promotion and networking platform for digital designers of various disciplines, including graphic design, web design, UX/UI, web design, illustration, and branding.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microtel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/microtel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microtel/</guid>
      <description> The Microtel Inn &amp;amp; Suites brand is a chain of franchise hotels with 343 locations with 24,947 rooms as of December 31, 2018. The company has locations in Argentina, Canada, Mexico, the Philippines, and the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dbx</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dbx/</guid>
      <description> dbx, Inc. is an American producer of professional audio recording equipment owned by Harman International Industries, a subsidiary of South Korean firm Samsung Electronics. It was founded by David E. Blackmer in 1971.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DELL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dell/</guid>
      <description> Dell is a US multinational computer technology company that develops, sells, repairs, and supports computers and related products and services. Named after its founder, Michael Dell, the company is one of the largest technological corporations in the world, employing more than 145,000 people in the U.S. and around the world (Annual report 2018).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Hampshire Gazette</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daily-hampshire-gazette/</guid>
      <description> The Daily Hampshire Gazette is a six-day morning daily newspaper based in Northampton, Massachusetts, and covering all of Hampshire County and southern towns of Franklin County, Massachusetts. The newspaper prints Monday through Saturday, with the latter labeled &amp;ldquo;Weekend Edition&amp;rdquo;.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diageo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diageo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diageo/</guid>
      <description> Diageo plc is a British multinational alcoholic beverages company, with its headquarters in London, England and offices on six continents. It was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest distiller until being overtaken by China&amp;rsquo;s Kweichow Moutai on 9 April 2017.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/docker/</guid>
      <description> Docker is a set of platform-as-a-service (PaaS) products that use OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers. Containers are isolated from one another and bundle their own software, libraries and configuration files; they can communicate with each other through well-defined channels. All containers are run by a single operating-system kernel and are thus more lightweight than virtual machines.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominion Energy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</guid>
      <description> Dominion Energy, Inc., commonly referred to as Dominion, is an American power and energy company headquartered in Richmond, Virginia that supplies electricity in parts of Virginia, North Carolina, and South Carolina and supplies natural gas to parts of West Virginia, Ohio, Pennsylvania, North Carolina, South Carolina, and Georgia. Dominion also has generation facilities in Indiana, Illinois, Connecticut, and Rhode Island.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DoubleTree</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doubletree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doubletree/</guid>
      <description> DoubleTree by Hilton is an American hotel chain and a part of Hilton Worldwide. Most DoubleTree hotels are independently owned and operated by franchisees, but some are managed by Hilton Worldwide.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAngelo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dangelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dangelo/</guid>
      <description> D&amp;rsquo;Angelo Grilled Sandwiches is a chain of sandwich shops located throughout New England. It serves various kinds of hot and cold subs, wraps, and salads.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC United</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc-united/</guid>
      <description>D.C. United is an American professional soccer club based in Washington, D.C. The club competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS), the top level of professional American soccer. The franchise began play in 1996 as one of the ten charter clubs of the league. The club was one of the most successful clubs in the early years of MLS, winning eight of its thirteen titles between 1996 and 1998 under then head coach Bruce Arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Mavericks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-mavericks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-mavericks/</guid>
      <description> The Dallas Mavericks (often referred to as the Mavs) are an American professional basketball team based in Dallas, Texas. The Mavericks compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The team plays its home games at the American Airlines Center, which it shares with the National Hockey League&amp;rsquo;s Dallas Stars.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Stars</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-stars/</guid>
      <description>The Dallas Stars are a professional ice hockey team based in Dallas, Texas. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was founded during the 1967 NHL expansion as the Minnesota North Stars, based in Bloomington, Minnesota. Before the beginning of the 1978–79 NHL season, the team merged with the Cleveland Barons after the league granted them permission due to each team&amp;rsquo;s respective financial struggles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denver Nuggets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-nuggets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-nuggets/</guid>
      <description>The Denver Nuggets are an American professional basketball team based in Denver, Colorado. The Nuggets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Northwest Division. The team was founded as the Denver Larks in 1967 as a charter franchise of the American Basketball Association (ABA), but changed its name to Rockets before the first season. It changed its name again to the Nuggets in 1974.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Pistons</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-pistons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-pistons/</guid>
      <description>The Detroit Pistons are an American professional basketball team based in Detroit, Michigan. The Pistons compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division and plays its home games at Little Caesars Arena. The team was founded in Fort Wayne, Indiana as the Fort Wayne (Zollner) Pistons in 1941, a member of the National Basketball League (NBL) where it won two NBL championships: in 1944 and 1945.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Red Wings</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-red-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-red-wings/</guid>
      <description>The Detroit Red Wings are a professional ice hockey team based in Detroit. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL) and are one of the Original Six teams of the league. Founded in 1926, the team was known as the Detroit Cougars until 1930. For the 1930–31 and 1931–32 seasons the team was called the Detroit Falcons, and in 1932 changed their name to the Red Wings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Cowboys</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dallas-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>The Dallas Cowboys are a professional American football team based in the Dallas–Fort Worth metroplex. The Cowboys compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) East division. The team is headquartered in Frisco, Texas, and plays its home games at AT&amp;amp;T Stadium in Arlington, Texas, which opened for the 2009 season. The stadium took its current name prior to the 2013 season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denver Broncos</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-broncos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-broncos/</guid>
      <description>The Denver Broncos are a professional American football franchise based in Denver, Colorado. The Broncos compete as a member club of the National Football League (NFL)&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) West division. The team began play in 1960 as a charter member of the American Football League (AFL) and joined the NFL as part of the merger in 1970. The Broncos are owned by the Pat Bowlen trust and currently play home games at Broncos Stadium at Mile High (formerly known as Invesco Field at Mile High from 2001–2010 and Sports Authority Field at Mile High from 2011–2017).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Lions</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-lions/</guid>
      <description> The Detroit Lions are a professional American football team based in Detroit, Michigan. The Lions compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) North division. The team plays its home games at Ford Field in Downtown Detroit.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Tigers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-tigers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-tigers/</guid>
      <description>The Detroit Tigers are an American professional baseball team based in Detroit, Michigan. The Tigers compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member of the American League (AL) Central division. The club was founded as one of the AL&amp;rsquo;s eight charter franchises in 1901. The Tigers have won four World Series championships (1935, 1945, 1968, and 1984), 11 AL pennants (1907, 1908, 1909, 1934, 1935, 1940, 1945, 1968, 1984, 2006, 2012), and four AL Central division championships (2011, 2012, 2013, and 2014).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</guid>
      <description> DC Comics, Inc. is an American comic book publisher. It is the publishing unit of DC Entertainment, a subsidiary of Warner Bros. since 1967. DC Comics is one of the largest and oldest American comic book companies, and produces material featuring numerous culturally iconic heroic characters including: Superman, Batman, Wonder Woman, The Flash, Green Lantern, Aquaman, Shazam, Martian Manhunter, Nightwing, Green Arrow, Hawkman, Cyborg and Supergirl.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duane Reade</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/duane-reade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/duane-reade/</guid>
      <description> Duane Reade Inc. (/dweɪn ˈriːd/ dwayn-REED) is a chain of pharmacy and convenience stores owned by Walgreens Boots Alliance. They are primarily located in New York City, known for its high volume small store layouts in densely populated Manhattan locations. In 2012 the company headquarters was moved to 40 Wall Street in Lower Manhattan, the location of its newest flagship store.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cathay Dragon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited is a Hong Kong-based international regional airline, with its corporate headquarters, Cathay Dragon House, and main hub at Hong Kong International Airport. As of 30 October 2013, the airline operates a scheduled passenger network to 47 destinations in 14 countries and territories across Asia. Additionally, the airline has three codeshares on routes served by partner airlines. It has an all Airbus fleet of 48 aircraft, consisting of A320s, A321s and A330s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DHL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dhl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dhl/</guid>
      <description>DHL (Dalsey, Hillblom and Lynn) International GmbH is an American-founded German company which is now the international courier, parcel, and express mail division of the German logistics company Deutsche Post DHL. Deutsche Post DHL is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest logistics company, particularly in sea and air mail. The company delivers over 1.3 billion parcels per year
 Sourcel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daikin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</guid>
      <description> Daikin Industries, Ltd. (ダイキン工業株式会社 Daikin Kōgyō Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational air conditioning manufacturing company headquartered in Osaka. It has operations in the United States, Japan, China, Philippines, Australia, India, Southeast Asia, Europe, and South America.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daimler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</guid>
      <description> Daimler AG is a German multinational automotive corporation, headquartered in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. Daimler-Benz was formed with the merger of Benz &amp;amp; Cie and Daimler Motoren Gesellschaft in 1926. The company was renamed DaimlerChrysler upon acquiring the American automobile manufacturer Chrysler Corporation in 1998, and was again renamed Daimler upon divesting of Chrysler in 2007.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</guid>
      <description> Danone S.A. is a French multinational food-products corporation based in Paris and founded in Barcelona, Spain. The company is listed on Euronext Paris where it is a component of the CAC 40 stock market index. Some of the company’s products are branded Dannon in the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Days Inn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/days-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/days-inn/</guid>
      <description> Days Inn is a hotel chain headquartered in the United States. It was founded in 1970 by Cecil B. Day, who opened the first location in Tybee Island, Georgia. The brand is now a part of the Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, headquartered in Parsippany, New Jersey, which used to be a part of Cendant. As of December 31, 2018, Days Inn includes 1,728 locations worldwide with 137,678 rooms.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dior</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</guid>
      <description> Christian Dior SE , commonly known as Dior, is a French luxury goods company controlled and chaired by French businessman Bernard Arnault, who also heads LVMH, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest luxury group. Dior itself holds 42.36% shares of and 59.01% voting rights within LVMH. Since 1997, the CEO is Sidney Toledano.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</guid>
      <description>Discovery Channel is an American pay television network and flagship channel owned by Discovery, Inc., a publicly traded company run by CEO David Zaslav. As of June 2012, Discovery Channel is the third most widely distributed subscription channel in the United States, behind TBS and The Weather Channel; it is available in 409 million households worldwide, through its U.S. flagship channel and its various owned or licensed television channels internationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</guid>
      <description> Dodge is an American brand of automobile manufactured by FCA US LLC (formerly known as Fiat Chrysler Group LLC), based in Auburn Hills, Michigan. Dodge vehicles currently include performance cars, though for much of its existence Dodge was Chrysler&amp;rsquo;s mid-priced brand above Plymouth.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doosan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</guid>
      <description> Doosan Group is a South Korean conglomerate company. In 2009, the company was placed 471st in the Fortune Global 500. It has been included in the Forbes Global 2000 companies from 2007.[citation needed] It is the parent company of ŠKODA power. Doosan was ranked 4th among the “World&amp;rsquo;s Best 40 Companies 2009” list, released in the latest issue of BusinessWeek, the U.S. economics magazine in October 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreamweaver</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamweaver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamweaver/</guid>
      <description> Adobe Dreamweaver is a proprietary web development tool from Adobe Inc.. It was created by Macromedia in 1997 and developed by them until Macromedia was acquired by Adobe Systems in 2005.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DuPont</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</guid>
      <description> DuPont de Nemours, Inc., commonly known as DuPont, is an American company formed by the merger of Dow Chemical and DuPont on August 31, 2017, and then subsequent spinoffs of Dow Inc. and Corteva. Prior to the spinoffs it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest chemical company in terms of sales.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin Donuts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Dunkin&amp;rsquo; (formerly known as Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts from 1950 to 2019) is an American multinational coffee company and quick service restaurant. It was founded by William Rosenberg in Quincy, Massachusetts in 1950. The chain was acquired by Baskin-Robbins&amp;rsquo; holding company Allied Lyons in 1990; its acquisition of the Mister Donut chain and conversion to Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts facilitated the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth in North America that year. Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts and Baskin-Robbins have been subsidiaries of Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Brands, headquartered in Canton, Massachusetts, since 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discover/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet Coke</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>