<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>D on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in D on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daimler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</guid>
      <description> Daimler AG is a German multinational automotive corporation, headquartered in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. Daimler-Benz was formed with the merger of Benz &amp;amp; Cie and Daimler Motoren Gesellschaft in 1926. The company was renamed DaimlerChrysler upon acquiring the American automobile manufacturer Chrysler Corporation in 1998, and was again renamed Daimler upon divesting of Chrysler in 2007.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discover/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet Coke</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>