<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>D on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in D on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</guid>
      <description> DC Comics, Inc. is an American comic book publisher. It is the publishing unit of DC Entertainment, a subsidiary of Warner Bros. since 1967. DC Comics is one of the largest and oldest American comic book companies, and produces material featuring numerous culturally iconic heroic characters including: Superman, Batman, Wonder Woman, The Flash, Green Lantern, Aquaman, Shazam, Martian Manhunter, Nightwing, Green Arrow, Hawkman, Cyborg and Supergirl.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duane Reade</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/duane-reade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/duane-reade/</guid>
      <description> Duane Reade Inc. (/dweɪn ˈriːd/ dwayn-REED) is a chain of pharmacy and convenience stores owned by Walgreens Boots Alliance. They are primarily located in New York City, known for its high volume small store layouts in densely populated Manhattan locations. In 2012 the company headquarters was moved to 40 Wall Street in Lower Manhattan, the location of its newest flagship store.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cathay Dragon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited is a Hong Kong-based international regional airline, with its corporate headquarters, Cathay Dragon House, and main hub at Hong Kong International Airport. As of 30 October 2013, the airline operates a scheduled passenger network to 47 destinations in 14 countries and territories across Asia. Additionally, the airline has three codeshares on routes served by partner airlines. It has an all Airbus fleet of 48 aircraft, consisting of A320s, A321s and A330s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DHL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dhl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dhl/</guid>
      <description>DHL (Dalsey, Hillblom and Lynn) International GmbH is an American-founded German company which is now the international courier, parcel, and express mail division of the German logistics company Deutsche Post DHL. Deutsche Post DHL is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest logistics company, particularly in sea and air mail. The company delivers over 1.3 billion parcels per year
 Sourcel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daikin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daikin/</guid>
      <description> Daikin Industries, Ltd. (ダイキン工業株式会社 Daikin Kōgyō Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational air conditioning manufacturing company headquartered in Osaka. It has operations in the United States, Japan, China, Philippines, Australia, India, Southeast Asia, Europe, and South America.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daimler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</guid>
      <description> Daimler AG is a German multinational automotive corporation, headquartered in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. Daimler-Benz was formed with the merger of Benz &amp;amp; Cie and Daimler Motoren Gesellschaft in 1926. The company was renamed DaimlerChrysler upon acquiring the American automobile manufacturer Chrysler Corporation in 1998, and was again renamed Daimler upon divesting of Chrysler in 2007.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</guid>
      <description> Danone S.A. is a French multinational food-products corporation based in Paris and founded in Barcelona, Spain. The company is listed on Euronext Paris where it is a component of the CAC 40 stock market index. Some of the company’s products are branded Dannon in the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/delta-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. (NYSE: DAL), typically referred as Delta, is a major American airline, with its headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia. The airline, along with its subsidiaries and regional affiliates, operates over 5,400 flights daily and serves an extensive domestic and international network that includes 304 destinations in 52 countries on six continents, as of October 2018. Delta is a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance. Regional service is operated under the brand name Delta Connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dior</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dior/</guid>
      <description> Christian Dior SE , commonly known as Dior, is a French luxury goods company controlled and chaired by French businessman Bernard Arnault, who also heads LVMH, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest luxury group. Dior itself holds 42.36% shares of and 59.01% voting rights within LVMH. Since 1997, the CEO is Sidney Toledano.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discovery/</guid>
      <description>Discovery Channel is an American pay television network and flagship channel owned by Discovery, Inc., a publicly traded company run by CEO David Zaslav. As of June 2012, Discovery Channel is the third most widely distributed subscription channel in the United States, behind TBS and The Weather Channel; it is available in 409 million households worldwide, through its U.S. flagship channel and its various owned or licensed television channels internationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dodge/</guid>
      <description> Dodge is an American brand of automobile manufactured by FCA US LLC (formerly known as Fiat Chrysler Group LLC), based in Auburn Hills, Michigan. Dodge vehicles currently include performance cars, though for much of its existence Dodge was Chrysler&amp;rsquo;s mid-priced brand above Plymouth.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doosan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doosan/</guid>
      <description> Doosan Group is a South Korean conglomerate company. In 2009, the company was placed 471st in the Fortune Global 500. It has been included in the Forbes Global 2000 companies from 2007.[citation needed] It is the parent company of ŠKODA power. Doosan was ranked 4th among the “World&amp;rsquo;s Best 40 Companies 2009” list, released in the latest issue of BusinessWeek, the U.S. economics magazine in October 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreamweaver</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamweaver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamweaver/</guid>
      <description> Adobe Dreamweaver is a proprietary web development tool from Adobe Inc.. It was created by Macromedia in 1997 and developed by them until Macromedia was acquired by Adobe Systems in 2005.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DuPont</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dupont/</guid>
      <description> DuPont de Nemours, Inc., commonly known as DuPont, is an American company formed by the merger of Dow Chemical and DuPont on August 31, 2017, and then subsequent spinoffs of Dow Inc. and Corteva. Prior to the spinoffs it was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest chemical company in terms of sales.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin Donuts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Dunkin&amp;rsquo; (formerly known as Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts from 1950 to 2019) is an American multinational coffee company and quick service restaurant. It was founded by William Rosenberg in Quincy, Massachusetts in 1950. The chain was acquired by Baskin-Robbins&amp;rsquo; holding company Allied Lyons in 1990; its acquisition of the Mister Donut chain and conversion to Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts facilitated the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth in North America that year. Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts and Baskin-Robbins have been subsidiaries of Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Brands, headquartered in Canton, Massachusetts, since 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/discover/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet Coke</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>