<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pharmaceuticals on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/pharmaceuticals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pharmaceuticals on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/pharmaceuticals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</guid>
      <description> GlaxoSmithKline plc (GSK) is a British multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Brentford, London. Established in 2000 by a merger of Glaxo Wellcome and SmithKline Beecham, GSK was the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth largest pharmaceutical company as of 2015, after Pfizer, Novartis, Merck, Hoffmann-La Roche and Sanofi.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merck</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/merck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/merck/</guid>
      <description> Merck KGaA (also called as the Merck Group), branded and commonly known as Merck, is a German multinational pharmaceutical, chemical and life sciences company headquartered in Darmstadt, with around 50,000 employees in around 70 countries. Merck was founded in 1668 and is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest operating chemical and pharmaceutical company, as well as one of the largest pharmaceutical companies in the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanofi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanofi/</guid>
      <description> Sanofi S.A. is a French multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Paris, France, as of 2013 the world&amp;rsquo;s fifth-largest by prescription sales. The company was formed as Sanofi-Aventis in 2004 by the merger of Aventis and Sanofi-Synthélabo, which were each the product of several previous mergers. It changed its name to Sanofi in May 2011. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>