<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>2011 on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/year/2011/</link><description>Recent content in 2011 on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0037</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/2011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks//file/starbucks.svg</url><title>Starbucks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Starbucks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0037</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</guid><description turbo="true">Starbucks Corporation is an American coffee company and coffeehouse chain. Starbucks was founded in Seattle, Washington in 1971. As of early 2019, the company operates over 30,000 locations worldwide.
Source The Starbucks History Every day, Starbucks go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with Starbucks friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv//file/ctv.svg</url><title>CTV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CTV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv/</guid><description turbo="true"> CTV News Channel is a Canadian discretionary service that is owned by Bell Media (a wholly owned subsidiary of Bell Canada). It broadcasts national and international news headlines, breaking news, and information. The channel is headquartered at 9 Channel Nine Court in the Agincourt neighbourhood of Scarborough in the city of Toronto.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news//file/nbc-news.svg</url><title>NBC News Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NBC News</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news/</guid><description turbo="true"> NBC News is the news division of the American broadcast television network NBC. The division operates under NBCUniversal Broadcast, Cable, Sports and News, a subsidiary of NBCUniversal, in turn a subsidiary of Comcast. The group&amp;rsquo;s various operations report to the president of NBC News, Noah Oppenheim.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings//file/los-angeles-kings.svg</url><title>Los Angeles Kings Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Los Angeles Kings</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/los-angeles-kings/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Kings are a professional ice hockey team based in Los Angeles. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was founded on June 5, 1967, after Jack Kent Cooke was awarded an NHL expansion franchise for Los Angeles on February 9, 1966, becoming one of the six teams that began play as part of the 1967 NHL expansion.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators//file/nashville-predators.svg</url><title>Nashville Predators Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nashville Predators</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Nashville Predators are a professional ice hockey team based in Nashville, Tennessee. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Predators&amp;rsquo; television broadcasting rights are held by Fox Sports Tennessee, whereas radio broadcasting rights are held by WPRT-FM. The Predators have played their home games at Bridgestone Arena since 1998.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-lightning//file/tampa-bay-lightning.svg</url><title>Tampa Bay Lightning Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tampa Bay Lightning</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-lightning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-lightning/</guid><description turbo="true">The Tampa Bay Lightning are a professional ice hockey team based in Tampa, Florida. The Lightning compete as a member of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The club has won one Stanley Cup championship in their history, in 2003–04. The team is often referred to as the Bolts, and the nickname was used on the former third jerseys. The Lightning plays home games in Amalie Arena in Tampa.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/wnnipeg-jets//file/winnipeg-jets.svg</url><title>Winnipeg Jets Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Winnipeg Jets</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/wnnipeg-jets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wnnipeg-jets/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Winnipeg Jets are a professional ice hockey team based in Winnipeg, Manitoba. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team is owned by True North Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment and plays its home games at Bell MTS Place.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy//file/codecademy.svg</url><title>Codecademy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Codecademy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy/</guid><description turbo="true"> Codecademy is an online interactive platform that offers free coding classes in 12 different programming languages including Python, Java, JavaScript (jQuery, AngularJS, React.js), Ruby, SQL, C++, and Sass, as well as markup languages HTML and CSS. The site also offers a paid &amp;ldquo;pro&amp;rdquo; option that gives users access to a personalized learning plan, quizzes, realistic projects, and live help from advisors.[
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks//file/nyc-parks.svg</url><title>NYC Parks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NYC Parks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks/</guid><description turbo="true"> The New York City Department of Parks and Recreation, also called the Parks Department or NYC Parks, is the department of the government of New York City responsible for maintaining the city&amp;rsquo;s parks system, preserving and maintaining the ecological diversity of the city&amp;rsquo;s natural areas, and furnishing recreational opportunities for city&amp;rsquo;s residents and visitors.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot//file/aeroflot.svg</url><title>Aeroflot Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aeroflot</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</guid><description turbo="true"> Aeroflot – Russian Airlines is the flag carrier and largest airline of the Russian Federation. The carrier is an open joint stock company that operates domestic and international passenger and services, mainly from its hub at Sheremetyevo International Airport.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines//file/japan-airlines.svg</url><title>Japan Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Japan Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/japan-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true">Japan Airlines is an international airline, headquartered in Shinagawa Tokyo, Japan. Its main hubs are Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s Narita International Airport and Tokyo International Airport (Haneda Airport), as well as Osaka&amp;rsquo;s Kansai International Airport and Osaka International Airport. JAL group companies include Japan Airlines, J-Air, JAL Express, Japan Air Commuter, Japan Transocean Air, ZIPAIR Tokyo and Ryukyu Air Commuter for domestic feeder services, and JAL Cargo for cargo and mail services.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap//file/sap.svg</url><title>SAP Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">SAP</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</guid><description turbo="true">SAP SE is a German multinational software corporation that makes enterprise software to manage business operations and customer relations. SAP is headquartered in Walldorf, Baden-Württemberg, Germany with regional offices in 180 countries. The company has over 425,000 customers in over 180 countries and is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
Source Subtle enhancements to the SAP logo make it feel more contemporary. Designed to live in the digital world, the new mark springs vividly from the screen, on any background, connecting with both large-scale business clients and individual consumers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines//file/swiss-airlines.svg</url><title>Swiss Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Swiss Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true"> Swiss International Air Lines is the national airline of Switzerland, operating scheduled services in Europe and to North America, South America, Africa and Asia. Zurich Airport is its hub, Geneva Airport is a focus city. The airline was formed following the bankruptcy in 2002 of Swissair, Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s then flag carrier.
Source</description></item></channel></rss>