<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>Hong Kong on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/hong-kong/</link><description>Recent content in Hong Kong on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/hong-kong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn//file/hkbn.svg</url><title>HKBN Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HKBN</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hkbn/</guid><description turbo="true"> HKBN Limited (Chinese: 香港寬頻有限公司), commonly known for its subsidiary Hong Kong Broadband Network Limited (Chinese: 香港寬頻網絡), is a Hong Kong-based telecommunication company. Hong Kong Broadband Network Limited was established on 23 August 1999, is one of the largest residential broadband and telecommunications service providers in Hong Kong. HKBN operates in both Hong Kong and Guangzhou, and employs about 2,900 personnel
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/phoenix-infonews//file/phoenix-infonews.svg</url><title>Phoenix InfoNews Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Phoenix InfoNews</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/phoenix-infonews/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/phoenix-infonews/</guid><description turbo="true"> Phoenix InfoNews Channel is a Hongkonger pay television news channel owned by Phoenix Television. It is the first channel to report news across the Greater China region, which includes Mainland China, Macau, Taiwan and Hong Kong. This channel was established on 1 January 2001, delivering news and financial updates around the clock. Analysts also provide comments and analysis on current issues and topics.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon//file/cathay-dragon.svg</url><title>Cathay Dragon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cathay Dragon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cathay-dragon/</guid><description turbo="true">Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited is a Hong Kong-based international regional airline, with its corporate headquarters, Cathay Dragon House, and main hub at Hong Kong International Airport. As of 30 October 2013, the airline operates a scheduled passenger network to 47 destinations in 14 countries and territories across Asia. Additionally, the airline has three codeshares on routes served by partner airlines. It has an all Airbus fleet of 48 aircraft, consisting of A320s, A321s and A330s.</description></item></channel></rss>