<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>orange on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/colors/orange/</link>
    <description>Recent content in orange on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/colors/orange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avast</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/avast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/avast/</guid>
      <description>Avast Software s.r.o. is a Czech multinational cybersecurity software company headquartered in Prague, Czech Republic that researches and develops computer security software, machine learning and artificial intelligence. Avast has more than 435 million monthly active users and the second largest market share among anti-malware application vendors worldwide as of April 2020. The company has approximately 1,700 employees across its 25 offices worldwide.
 Avast was founded by Pavel Baudiš and Eduard Kučera in 1988 as a cooperative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanwha Eagles</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles/</guid>
      <description>The Hanwha Eagles (Korean: 한화 이글스) is a South Korean professional baseball club based in the city of Daejeon. They are a member of the KBO League. The Eagles&amp;rsquo; home ballpark is Daejeon Hanbat Baseball Stadium. The Eagles have won the Korean Series once, in 1999, and the league pennant twice. As of 2020, the Eagles have played in the postseason 13 times, being the runner-up in the Korean Series five times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutoh</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mutoh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mutoh/</guid>
      <description> Whatever wide format digital print solution you are looking for, Mutoh has it ! Quality is the thread that runs through every Mutoh wide format product. Mutoh offer wide format piezo drop on demand inkjet printers and sign cutting plotters for sign &amp;amp; display, specialty/industrial, dye sublimation &amp;amp; direct textile applications !
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaws</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shaws/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shaws/</guid>
      <description>Shaw&amp;rsquo;s and Star Market are two American grocery store chains under united management based in West Bridgewater, Massachusetts, employing about 30,000 associates in 154 total stores. 133 stores are operated under the Shaw&amp;rsquo;s banner in Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Rhode Island, and Vermont; while Star Market operates 21 stores in Massachusetts, most of which are in or near Boston. Until 2010, Shaw&amp;rsquo;s operated stores in all six New England states, and as of 2017 Shaw&amp;rsquo;s remained the only supermarket chain with stores in five of the six, after it sold its Connecticut operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sina Weibo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sina-weibo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sina-weibo/</guid>
      <description>Sina Weibo is a Chinese microblogging (weibo) website. Launched by Sina Corporation on 14 August 2009, it is one of the biggest social media platforms in China, with over 445 million monthly active users as of Q3 2018. The platform has been a huge financial success, with surging stocks, lucrative advertising sales and high revenue and total earnings per quarter. At the start of 2018, it surpassed the US$30 billion market valuation mark for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SK Wyverns</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sk-wyverns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sk-wyverns/</guid>
      <description> SK Wyverns (Korean: SK 와이번스) is a South Korean professional baseball team founded in 2000. They are a member of the KBO League. Based in Incheon, they play their home games at Munhak Baseball Stadium.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoundCloud</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcloud/</guid>
      <description>SoundCloud is an online audio distribution platform and music sharing website based in Berlin, Germany, that enables its users to upload, promote, and share audio. Started in 2007 by Alexander Ljung and Eric Wahlforss, SoundCloud has grown to be one of the largest music streaming services reaching over 175 million monthly users worldwide. SoundCloud offers both free and paid membership on the platform, available for desktop and mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrator</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/illustrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/illustrator/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Illustrator is a vector graphics editor developed and marketed by Adobe Inc. Originally designed for the Apple Macintosh, development of Adobe Illustrator began in 1985. Along with Creative Cloud (Adobe&amp;rsquo;s shift to monthly or annual subscription service delivered over the Internet), Illustrator CC was released. The latest version, Illustrator CC 2019, was released in October 2018 and is the 23rd generation in the product line. Adobe Illustrator was reviewed as the best vector graphics editing program in 2018 by PC Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doordash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doordash/</guid>
      <description>DoorDash Inc. is a San Francisco-based on-demand prepared food delivery service founded in 2013 by Stanford students Tony Xu, Stanley Tang, Andy Fang and Evan Moore. A Y Combinator–backed company, DoorDash is one of several technology companies that uses logistics services to offer food delivery from restaurants on-demand. DoorDash launched in Palo Alto and, as of May 2019, had expanded to more than 4,000 cities and offers a selection of 340,000 stores across the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G2A</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/g2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/g2a/</guid>
      <description>G2A.COM Limited (commonly referred to as G2A) is a global digital marketplace which specializes in the resale of gaming products by the use of redemption keys. It is headquartered in the Netherlands and has offices in various countries including Poland and Hong Kong. The site has over 20 million customers, 400,000 sellers from 200 countries, 75,000 digital products and 600 employees throughout all locations. The main product offering on G2A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instacart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/instacart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/instacart/</guid>
      <description>Instacart, headquartered in San Francisco, operates a grocery delivery and pick-up service in the United States and Canada. The company offers service via a website and mobile app in 5,500 cities in all 50 U.S. states and Canadian provinces in partnership with over 350 retailers that have more than 25,000 grocery stores including Albertsons, Aldi, Costco, CVS Health, Eataly, H-E-B, Kroger, Loblaw Companies, Petco, Publix, Safeway Inc., Sam&amp;rsquo;s Club, Sprouts Farmers Market, Target Corporation, Total Wine &amp;amp; More, and Wegmans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kayak</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kayak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kayak/</guid>
      <description>Kayak.com, sometimes styled as KAYAK, is a travel agency and metasearch engine owned and operated by Booking Holdings. The company also runs travel search engines checkfelix, Mundi, Hotels Combined, and swoodoo.
 Kayak&amp;rsquo;s website and mobile apps are currently available in over 18 languages and more than 30 countries, including the United States, the United Kingdom, India, China, France, Germany, Italy, Spain, Russia, Switzerland, Norway, Sweden, Finland, the Netherlands, Australia, Ireland, Mexico, New Zealand, Belgium, Hong Kong, Taiwan, Korea, Japan, and Singapore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loblaws</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws/</guid>
      <description>Loblaws Inc. is a Canadian supermarket chain with stores located in the provinces of British Columbia, Saskatchewan, Alberta, Ontario and Quebec. Headquartered in Brampton, Ontario, Loblaws is a subsidiary of Loblaw Companies Limited, Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest food distributor.
  Source About Loblaws Since the beginning, Loblaws love of food has driven us to find innovative ways to bring customers closer to their favourite products. In 1919, founders of the first Loblaw Groceterias were told their self-serve, cash-and-carry model would never work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McKesson</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mckesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mckesson/</guid>
      <description>McKesson Corporation is an American company distributing pharmaceuticals and providing health information technology, medical supplies, and care management tools. The company had revenues of $208.4 billion in 2018.
 McKesson is based in Irving, Texas and distributes health care systems, medical supplies and pharmaceutical products. Additionally, McKesson provides extensive network infrastructure for the health care industry; also, it was an early adopter of technologies like bar-code scanning for distribution, pharmacy robotics, and RFID tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molson Coors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors/</guid>
      <description>The Molson Coors Beverage Company is a multinational brewing company, formed in 2005 by the merger of Molson of Canada, and Coors of the United States. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s seventh largest brewer by volume.
 While the company is incorporated in the United States, it is traded on stock exchanges in both the United States and Canada, and control is equally shared between the Molson and Coors families. The company is headquartered at 1801 California Street, a 1,372,179-square-foot (127,479.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Jr</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr/</guid>
      <description>Nick Jr. is an American pay television channel run by Nickelodeon Group, a unit of the ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division of ViacomCBS, the channel&amp;rsquo;s ultimate owner headquartered in New York City. It launched on September 28, 2009 as a spin-off of Nickelodeon&amp;rsquo;s long-running preschool programming block of the same name, which had aired since 1988. The channel, which is aimed at children under 6, features a mix of originally-produced programming, and series previously and concurrently aired on the Nick Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nickelodeon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon/</guid>
      <description>Nickelodeon (often shortened to Nick) is an American pay television channel which was first tested on December 1, 1977, before relaunching on April 1, 1979 as the first cable channel for children. It is owned by ViacomCBS through its domestic networks division and is based in New York City. The network&amp;rsquo;s programming is primarily aimed at children and adolescents aged 2–17, while some of its program blocks target a broader family audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/origin/</guid>
      <description>Origin is a digital distribution platform developed by Electronic Arts for purchasing and playing video games. The platform&amp;rsquo;s software client is available for personal computer and mobile platforms.
 Origin contains social features such as profile management, networking with friends with chat and direct game joining along with an in-game overlay, streaming via Twitch and sharing of game library and community integration with networking sites like Facebook, Xbox Live, PlayStation Network, and Nintendo Network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reuters</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters/</guid>
      <description>Reuters (About this soundpronunciation ; /ˈrɔɪtərz/) is an international news organization owned by Thomson Reuters. Until 2008, the Reuters news agency formed part of an independent company, Reuters Group plc, which was also a provider of financial market data. Since the acquisition of Reuters Group by the Thomson Corporation in 2008, the Reuters news agency has been a part of Thomson Reuters, making up the media division. It was established in 1851.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sling TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sling-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sling-tv/</guid>
      <description>Sling Television, commonly known as Sling TV, is an American over-the-top internet television service owned by Dish Network and legally operated by Sling TV LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of Dish Network. Unveiled on January 5, 2015, at the Consumer Electronics Show, the virtual multichannel video programming distributor aims to complement subscription video on demand services for cord cutters, offering a selection of major cable channels and OTT-originated services that can be streamed through smart TVs, digital media players and apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akamai</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/akamai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/akamai/</guid>
      <description>Akamai Technologies, Inc. is an American content delivery network (CDN), cybersecurity, and cloud service provider headquartered in Cambridge, Massachusetts, in the United States. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s content delivery network is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest distributed computing platforms, responsible for serving between 15% and 30% of all web traffic. The company operates a network of servers around the world and rents out capacity on these servers to customers who want their websites to work faster by distributing content from locations close to the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alibaba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alibaba/</guid>
      <description>Alibaba Group Holding Limited (also known as Alibaba Group and as Alibaba) is a Chinese multinational technology company specializing in e-commerce, retail, Internet, and technology. Founded on 4 April 1999 in Hangzhou, Zhejiang, the company provides consumer-to-consumer (C2C), business-to-consumer (B2C), and business-to-business (B2B) sales services via web portals, as well as electronic payment services, shopping search engines and cloud computing services. It owns and operates a diverse array of businesses around the world in numerous sectors, and is named as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most admired companies by Fortune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billboard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard/</guid>
      <description>Billboard, stylized as billboard, is an American entertainment media brand owned by the Billboard-Hollywood Reporter Media Group, a division of Eldridge Industries. It publishes pieces involving news, video, opinion, reviews, events, and style, and is also known for its music charts, including the Hot 100 and Billboard 200, tracking the most popular songs and albums in different genres. It also hosts events, owns a publishing firm, and operates several TV shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comcast</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast/</guid>
      <description>Comcast Corporation (formerly registered as Comcast Holdings)[note 1] is an American telecommunications conglomerate headquartered in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. It is the second-largest broadcasting and cable television company in the world by revenue and the largest pay-TV company, the largest cable TV company and largest home Internet service provider in the United States, and the nation&amp;rsquo;s third-largest home telephone service provider. Comcast services U.S. residential and commercial customers in 40 states and in the District of Columbia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deezer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deezer/</guid>
      <description>Deezer is a French online music streaming service. It allows users to listen to music content from record labels, including Universal Music Group, Sony Music and Warner Music Group (owned by Deezer&amp;rsquo;s parent company Access Industries) on various devices online or offline. Created in Paris, France, Deezer currently has 56 million licensed tracks in its library, with over 30,000 radio channels, 14 million monthly active users, and 7 million paid subscribers as of January 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DiDi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/didi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/didi/</guid>
      <description>Didi Chuxing Technology Co., formerly Didi Kuaidi (Chinese: 滴滴快的), is a transportation company headquartered in Beijing. The company provides app-based transportation services, including taxi hailing, private car hailing, social ride-sharing and bike sharing; on-demand delivery services; and automobile services, including sales, leasing, financing, maintenance, fleet operation, electric vehicle charging and co-development of vehicles with automakers. In 2018, DiDi&amp;rsquo;s platform had more than 550 million users and tens of millions of drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DQ</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</guid>
      <description> Dairy Queen (DQ) is an American multinational chain of soft serve ice cream and fast-food restaurants owned by International Dairy Queen, Inc., a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway. International Dairy Queen, Inc., also owns Orange Julius, and formerly owned Karmelkorn and Golden Skillet Fried Chicken.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Wildcats</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-wildcats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-wildcats/</guid>
      <description> The Los Angeles Wildcats (LA Wildcats) are a professional American football team based in the Los Angeles suburb of Carson, California. The team is a franchise of the new XFL founded by Vince McMahon’s Alpha Entertainment and plays its home games at the Dignity Health Sports Park, which is also home to the MLS’s LA Galaxy.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</guid>
      <description> NEM is a peer-to-peer blockchain platform for app developers. Its native cryptocurrency is the XEM. Its code was created from scratch in Java by the New Economy Movement (NEM), which seeks to build &amp;ldquo;a new economy based on the principles of financial freedom, decentralization, equality and solidarity&amp;rdquo;.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ping An</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ping-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ping-an/</guid>
      <description> Ping An Insurance known also as Ping An of China (Chinese: 中国平安; pinyin: Zhōngguó Píng Ān), full name Ping An Insurance (Group) Company of China, Ltd. is a Chinese holding conglomerate whose subsidiaries mainly deal with insurance, banking, and financial services. The company was founded in 1988 and has its headquarters in Shenzhen. &amp;ldquo;Ping An&amp;rdquo; literally means &amp;ldquo;safe and well&amp;rdquo;.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resolve</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/resolve/</guid>
      <description> RESOLVE is a non-profit, 501(c)(3) organization certified under the National Health Council Standards of Excellence and America’s Best Charities as well as earned the Guidestar Gold Seal of Transparency.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Cash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017. In 2018 Bitcoin Cash subsequently split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash, and Bitcoin SV. Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coinomi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</guid>
      <description> Coinomi – is one of the first, and most trusted, cryptocurrency multiwallets. Coinomi is a non-custodial multiwallet and your private keys are stored securely encrypted on your device at all times. The wallet is available on all platforms and the only official download sources are listed on the Coinomi website. Coinomi currently supports more than 125 blockchains and has FULL support for all Ethereum Tokens.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howard Johnson</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/howard-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/howard-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Howard Johnson&amp;rsquo;s, or Howard Johnson by Wyndham, is an American chain of hotels and motels located primarily throughout the United States and Canada. It had also once been a chain of restaurants for over 90 years and its name was widely known for that alone. Founded by Howard Deering Johnson, it was the largest restaurant chain in the U.S. throughout the 1960s and 1970s, with more than 1,000 combined company-owned and franchised outlets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HubSpot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot/</guid>
      <description> HubSpot is a developer and marketer of software products for inbound marketing and sales. It was founded by Brian Halligan and Dharmesh Shah in 2006. Its products and services aim to provide tools for social media marketing, content management, web analytics and search engine optimization.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monero</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</guid>
      <description> Monero is an open-source cryptocurrency created in April 2014 that focuses on fungibility, privacy and decentralization. Monero uses an obfuscated public ledger, meaning anybody can broadcast or send transactions, but no outside observer can tell the source, amount or destination. Monero uses a Proof of Work mechanism to issue new coins and incentivize miners to secure the network and validate transactions.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zcash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</guid>
      <description> Zcash is a cryptocurrency aimed at using cryptography to provide enhanced privacy for its users compared to other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc/</guid>
      <description>CNBC is an American pay television business news channel that is owned by NBCUniversal Broadcast, Cable, Sports and News, a division of NBCUniversal, with both being ultimately owned by Comcast. Headquartered in Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey, the network primarily carries business day coverage of U.S. and international financial markets; following the end of the business day and on non-trading days, CNBC primarily carries financial and business-themed documentaries and reality shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNPC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</guid>
      <description> The China National Petroleum Corporation (CNPC) is a major national oil and gas corporation of China PR and one of the largest integrated energy groups in the world. Its headquarters are in Dongcheng District, Beijing. CNPC was ranked fourth in 2017 Fortune Global 500, a global ranking of the largest corporations by revenue
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conduent</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</guid>
      <description> Conduent Inc. is a technology-led business process services company headquartered in New Jersey. It was formed in 2017 as a divestiture from Xerox.The company offers digital platforms for businesses and governments. It has 85,000 employees in more than 40 countries.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etsy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/etsy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/etsy/</guid>
      <description>Etsy is an e-commerce website (etsy.com) focused on handmade or vintage items and craft supplies. These items fall under a wide range of categories, including jewelry, bags, clothing, home décor and furniture, toys, art, as well as craft supplies and tools. All vintage items must be at least 20 years old. The site follows in the tradition of open craft fairs, giving sellers personal storefronts where they list their goods for a fee of US$0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</guid>
      <description> GlaxoSmithKline plc (GSK) is a British multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Brentford, London. Established in 2000 by a merger of Glaxo Wellcome and SmithKline Beecham, GSK was the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth largest pharmaceutical company as of 2015, after Pfizer, Novartis, Merck, Hoffmann-La Roche and Sanofi.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOCL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl/</guid>
      <description>Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL), commonly known as IndianOil is an Indian state government owned oil and gas company headquartered in New Delhi. It is the largest commercial oil company in the country, with a net profit of INR 19,106 crore (USD 2,848 million) for the financial year 2016–17. It is ranked 1st in Fortune India 500 list for year 2016 and 137th in Fortune&amp;rsquo;s ‘Global 500’ list of world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies in the year 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/msnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/msnbc/</guid>
      <description>MSNBC is an American pay television network that provides news coverage and political commentary from NBC News on current events. MSNBC is owned by the NBCUniversal News Group, a unit of the NBCUniversal Television Group division of NBCUniversal (all of which are ultimately owned by Comcast). MSNBC and its website were founded in 1996 under a partnership between Microsoft and General Electric&amp;rsquo;s NBC unit, hence the network&amp;rsquo;s naming. Although they had the same name, msnbc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news/</guid>
      <description> NBC News is the news division of the American broadcast television network NBC. The division operates under NBCUniversal Broadcast, Cable, Sports and News, a subsidiary of NBCUniversal, in turn a subsidiary of Comcast. The group&amp;rsquo;s various operations report to the president of NBC News, Noah Oppenheim.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novartis</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/novartis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/novartis/</guid>
      <description> Novartis International AG is a Swiss multinational pharmaceutical company based in Basel, Switzerland. It is one of the largest pharmaceutical companies by both market capitalization and sales.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prague Zoo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo/</guid>
      <description>Prague Zoological Garden is a zoo in Prague, Czech Republic. It was opened in 1931 with the goal to &amp;ldquo;advance the study of zoology, protect wildlife, and educate the public&amp;rdquo; in the district of Troja in the north of Prague. In 2013, the zoo occupied 58 hectares (140 acres) with 50 hectares (120 acres) in use for exhibits, and housed around 5,000 animals from just 676 species, including 132 species listed as threatened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princeton University Press</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/princeton-university-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/princeton-university-press/</guid>
      <description> Princeton University Press is an independent publisher with close connections to Princeton University. Its mission is to disseminate scholarship within academia and society at large.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Gems</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</guid>
      <description> Screen Gems, Inc. is an American film production and distribution studio that is a division of Sony Pictures&amp;rsquo;s Motion Picture Group, a subsidiary of Japanese multinational conglomerate Sony.[1] It has served several different purposes for its parent companies over the decades since its incorporation. The label currently specializes in genre films, mainly horror.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonatrach</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach/</guid>
      <description> Sonatrach (Arabic:سوناطراك) (Société Nationale pour la Recherche, la Production, le Transport, la Transformation, et la Commercialisation des Hydrocarbures) is an Algerian government-owned company formed to explore the hydrocarbon resources of the country. It has some concessions in Libya, Mauritania, Peru, Yemen and Venezuela. Its diversified activities cover all aspects of production: exploration, extraction, transport, and refining. It has diversified into petrochemistry and the desalination of seawater.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tinder</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tinder/</guid>
      <description>Tinder is a location-based social search mobile app and Web application most often used as a dating service, that allows users to use a swiping motion to like (swipe right) or dislike (swipe left) other users, and allows users to chat if both parties like each other (a “match”). Information available to users is based on pictures, a short biography, and, optionally, a linked Instagram, Facebook or Spotify account. Tinder originally required access to a Facebook account of the user of Tinder but, as of 2019‑08‑17, Tinder allows users to register using a telephone number and without access to a Facebook account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total SA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa/</guid>
      <description> Total S.A. is a French multinational integrated oil and gas company founded in 1924 and one of the seven &amp;ldquo;Supermajor&amp;rdquo; oil companies in the world. Its businesses cover the entire oil and gas chain, from crude oil and natural gas exploration and production to power generation, transportation, refining, petroleum product marketing, and international crude oil and product trading. Total is also a large scale chemicals manufacturer.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</guid>
      <description> Vodafone plc /ˈvoʊdəfoʊn/ is a British multinational telecommunications conglomerate with headquarters in London and Newbury, Berkshire. It predominantly operates services in the regions of Asia, Africa, Europe, and Oceania. Among mobile operator groups globally, Vodafone ranked 4th (behind China Mobile, Bharti Airtel and Vodafone Idea) in the number of mobile customers (313 million) as of 2018
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y Combinator</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/y-combinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/y-combinator/</guid>
      <description> Y Combinator is an American seed accelerator which was launched in March 2005. Y Combinator is consistently ranked at the top of U.S. accelerators.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoshinoya</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</guid>
      <description> Yoshinoya is a Japanese multinational fast food chain, and the second-largest chain of gyūdon (beef bowl) restaurants. The chain was established in Japan in 1899. Its motto is &amp;ldquo;Tasty, low-priced, and quick&amp;rdquo;.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anaheim Ducks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/anaheim-ducks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/anaheim-ducks/</guid>
      <description> The Anaheim Ducks are a professional ice hockey team based in Anaheim, California. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). Since their inception, the Ducks have played their home games at the Honda Center.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AW Root Beer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</guid>
      <description> A&amp;amp;W Root Beer is a root beer brand primarily available in the United States and Canada, started in 1919 by Roy W. Allen. In 1922, Allen partnered with Frank Wright. They combined their initials to create the brand &amp;ldquo;A&amp;amp;W&amp;rdquo; and inspired a restaurant chain, founded in 1922. Originally, A&amp;amp;W root beer drinks sold for five cents.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edmonton Oilers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/edmonton-oilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/edmonton-oilers/</guid>
      <description> The Edmonton Oilers are a professional ice hockey team based in Edmonton, Alberta. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FC Cincinnati</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-cincinnati/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-cincinnati/</guid>
      <description>FC Cincinnati is an American professional soccer club based in Cincinnati, Ohio that plays in the Eastern Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The team succeeded the lower-division team of the same name and was announced on May 29, 2018, when MLS awarded an expansion franchise to Cincinnati. The team began MLS play on March 2, 2019 with its first match against Seattle Sounders FC. The club&amp;rsquo;s ownership group is led by Carl H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Dynamo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-dynamo/</guid>
      <description>Houston Dynamo are an American professional soccer club based in Houston, Texas. The franchise competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), as a member of the Western Conference. The Dynamo had first played their home games at Robertson Stadium on the University of Houston campus until 2011. Since 2012, the Dynamo has played home matches at BBVA Stadium, a soccer-specific stadium located in Houston. The team&amp;rsquo;s head coach is Wilmer Cabrera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Islanders</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-islanders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-islanders/</guid>
      <description>The New York Islanders are a professional ice hockey team based in the New York metropolitan area. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team splits its home games between Barclays Center in the borough of Brooklyn and Nassau Coliseum in Uniondale, New York. The Islanders are one of three NHL franchises in the New York metropolitan area, along with the New Jersey Devils and New York Rangers, and their fan base resides primarily on Long Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-fc/</guid>
      <description> New York City Football Club is an American professional soccer club based in New York City that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), the highest level of American soccer, as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Okc Thunder</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/okc-thunder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/okc-thunder/</guid>
      <description> The Oklahoma City Thunder are an American professional basketball team based in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. The Thunder compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Northwest Division. The team plays its home games at Chesapeake Energy Arena
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Flyers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-flyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/philadelphia-flyers/</guid>
      <description> The Philadelphia Flyers are a professional ice hockey team based in Philadelphia. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). Part of the 1967 NHL Expansion, the Flyers were the first expansion team in the post–Original Six era to win the Stanley Cup, victorious in 1973–74 and again in 1974–75.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Suns</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/phoenix-suns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/phoenix-suns/</guid>
      <description> The Phoenix Suns are an American professional basketball team based in Phoenix, Arizona. The Suns compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Pacific Division, and are the only team in their division not based in California. The Suns play their home games at the Talking Stick Resort Arena.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Jose Sharks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-jose-sharks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-jose-sharks/</guid>
      <description>The San Jose Sharks are a professional ice hockey team based in San Jose, California. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The franchise is owned by San Jose Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment Enterprises. Beginning play in the 1991–92 season, the Sharks initially played their home games at the Cow Palace, before they moved to their present home, now named SAP Center at San Jose, in 1993.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tide</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tide/</guid>
      <description> Tide is a laundry detergent owned and produced by American multinational Procter &amp;amp; Gamble. Introduced in 1946, it is the highest selling detergent brand in the world, with an estimated 14.3 percent of the global market.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Orioles</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-orioles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-orioles/</guid>
      <description>The Baltimore Orioles are an American professional baseball team based in Baltimore, Maryland. As one of the American League&amp;rsquo;s eight charter teams in 1901, this particular franchise spent its first year as a major league club in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, as the Milwaukee Brewers (not related to the second current Brewers franchise there) before moving to St. Louis, Missouri, to become the St. Louis Browns. After 52 often-beleaguered years in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Bengals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-bengals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-bengals/</guid>
      <description> The Cincinnati Bengals are a professional American football franchise based in Cincinnati, Ohio. The Bengals compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) North division. Their home stadium is Paul Brown Stadium in downtown Cincinnati. Their divisional opponents are the Pittsburgh Steelers, Cleveland Browns, and the Baltimore Ravens.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland Browns</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns/</guid>
      <description>The Cleveland Browns are a professional American football team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Browns compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) North division. The Browns play their home games at FirstEnergy Stadium, which opened in 1999, with administrative offices and training facilities in Berea, Ohio. The Browns&amp;rsquo; official colors are brown, orange, and white. They are unique among the 32 member franchises of the NFL in that they do not have a logo on their helmets</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denver Broncos</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-broncos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/denver-broncos/</guid>
      <description>The Denver Broncos are a professional American football franchise based in Denver, Colorado. The Broncos compete as a member club of the National Football League (NFL)&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) West division. The team began play in 1960 as a charter member of the American Football League (AFL) and joined the NFL as part of the merger in 1970. The Broncos are owned by the Pat Bowlen trust and currently play home games at Broncos Stadium at Mile High (formerly known as Invesco Field at Mile High from 2001–2010 and Sports Authority Field at Mile High from 2011–2017).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Astros</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-astros/</guid>
      <description> The Houston Astros are an American professional baseball team based in Houston, Texas. The Astros compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West division, having moved to the division in 2013 after spending their first 51 seasons in the National League (NL). The Astros have played their home games at Minute Maid Park since 2000.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Dolphins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/miami-dolphins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/miami-dolphins/</guid>
      <description>The Miami Dolphins are a professional American football team based in the Miami metropolitan area. The Dolphins compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The Dolphins play their home games at Hard Rock Stadium in the northern suburb of Miami Gardens, Florida, and are headquartered in Davie, Florida. The Dolphins are Florida&amp;rsquo;s oldest professional sports team. Of the four AFC East teams, they are the only team in the division that was not a charter member of the American Football League (AFL).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Mets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-mets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-mets/</guid>
      <description> The New York Mets are an American professional baseball team based in the New York City borough of Queens. The Mets compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) East division. The Mets are one of two Major League clubs based in New York City; the other is the New York Yankees of the American League East.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Bay Buccaneers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-buccaneers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tampa-bay-buccaneers/</guid>
      <description>The Tampa Bay Buccaneers are a professional American football franchise based in Tampa, Florida. The Buccaneers currently compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The club joined the NFL in 1976 as an expansion team, along with the Seattle Seahawks. Tampa Bay played its first season in the American Football Conference (AFC) West division as part of the 1976 expansion plan, whereby each new franchise would play every other franchise over the first two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</guid>
      <description> Home Depot is an American home improvement supplies retailing company that sells tools, construction products, and services. The company is headquartered at the Atlanta Store Support Center in unincorporated Cobb County, Georgia (with an Atlanta mailing address).
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</guid>
      <description> Popeyes is an American multinational chain of fried chicken fast food restaurants founded in 1972 in New Orleans, Louisiana and headquartered in Miami, Florida. Since 2008, its full brand name is Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen, Inc., and it was formerly named Popeyes Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits and Popeyes Famous Fried Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits. It is currently a subsidiary of Toronto-based Restaurant Brands International.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rotten Tomatoes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rotten-tomatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rotten-tomatoes/</guid>
      <description> Rotten Tomatoes is an American review-aggregation website for film and television. The company was launched in August 1998 by three undergraduate students at the University of California, Berkeley: Senh Duong, Patrick Y. Lee, and Stephen Wang.The name &amp;ldquo;Rotten Tomatoes&amp;rdquo; derives from the practice of audiences throwing rotten tomatoes when disapproving of a poor stage performance.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toys R Us</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</guid>
      <description> Toys &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; Us is an international toy, clothing, video game, and baby product Retail owned by Tru Kids, Inc. (d.b.a. Tru Kids Brands) and various others. It was founded in April 1948, with its headquarters located in Wayne, New Jersey, in the New York metropolitan area.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7-eleven</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</guid>
      <description>7-Eleven Inc. is a Japanese-owned American international chain of convenience stores, headquartered in Dallas, Texas. The chain was founded in 1927 as Tote&amp;rsquo;m Stores until it was renamed in 1946. Its parent company since 2005, Seven-Eleven Japan Co., Ltd., operates, franchises, and licenses 68,236 stores in 17 countries as of June 2019. Seven-Eleven Japan is headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo and held by Seven &amp;amp; I Holdings Co., Ltd.. The most recent franchise agreement gives up to 59% of a franchise&amp;rsquo;s gross profit to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin Donuts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Dunkin&amp;rsquo; (formerly known as Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts from 1950 to 2019) is an American multinational coffee company and quick service restaurant. It was founded by William Rosenberg in Quincy, Massachusetts in 1950. The chain was acquired by Baskin-Robbins&amp;rsquo; holding company Allied Lyons in 1990; its acquisition of the Mister Donut chain and conversion to Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts facilitated the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth in North America that year. Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts and Baskin-Robbins have been subsidiaries of Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Brands, headquartered in Canton, Massachusetts, since 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FedEx</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fedex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fedex/</guid>
      <description>FedEx Corporation is an American multinational courier delivery services company headquartered in Memphis, Tennessee. The name &amp;ldquo;FedEx&amp;rdquo; is a syllabic abbreviation of the name of the company&amp;rsquo;s original air division, Federal Express (now FedEx Express), which was used from 1973 until 2000. The company is known for its overnight shipping service and pioneering a system that could track packages and provide real-time updates on package location (to help in finding lost packages), a feature that has now been implemented by most other carrier services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harley</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/harley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/harley/</guid>
      <description>Harley-Davidson, Inc., H-D, or Harley, is an American motorcycle manufacturer founded in 1903 in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. It was one of two major American motorcycle manufacturers to survive the Great Depression, along with Indian. The company has survived numerous ownership arrangements, subsidiary arrangements, periods of poor economic health and product quality, and intense global competition to become one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest motorcycle manufacturers and an iconic brand widely known for its loyal following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hawaiian-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is the flag carrier and the largest airline in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It is the tenth-largest commercial airline in the US, and is based in Honolulu, Hawaii. The airline operates its main hub at Daniel K. Inouye International Airport on the island of Oʻahu and a secondary hub out of Kahului Airport on the island of Maui. Hawaiian Airlines operates flights to Asia, American Samoa, Australia, French Polynesia, Hawaii, New Zealand, and the United States mainland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</guid>
      <description> Hermès International S.A., or simply Hermès is a French high fashion luxury goods manufacturer established in 1837. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. Its logo, since the 1950s, is of a Duc carriage with horse. Nadège Vanhee-Cybulski is the current creative director.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutterfly</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shutterfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shutterfly/</guid>
      <description> Shutterfly, Inc. is an American Internet-based company, headquartered in Redwood City, California, and specializing in image-publishing services. Shutterfly&amp;rsquo;s flagship product is its photo book line. The company, founded in 1999, is currently led by Christopher North. The company went public in 2006. The Shutterfly customer base is heavily skewed toward women, who accounted for 80% of customers as reported in 2013.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Money</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</guid>
      <description> Yandex.Money is Russia’s largest electronic payment service according to a 2016 survey by TNS. It is an online payment service that works with two types of clients — individual users and merchants.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMCA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</guid>
      <description> YMCA, sometimes regionally called the Y, is a worldwide organisation based in Geneva, Switzerland, with more than 64 million beneficiaries from 120 national associations. It was founded on 6 June 1844 by Sir George Williams in London, originally as the Young Men&amp;rsquo;s Christian Association and aims to put Christian principles into practice by developing a healthy &amp;ldquo;body, mind, and spirit&amp;rdquo;.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penguin Books</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:31:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</guid>
      <description>Penguin Books Logo History Designed by Edward Young  In 1935, Edward Young designed Penguin’s famous “dignified but flippant” logo and the colour scheme for its book covers.
 It started with the simple logo and name, suggested, allegedly, by a typist who was earwigging the board meeting. Allen had already hit upon the idea of an animal logo, inspired by the template offered by the contemporary publishing house The Albatross Library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper (from prosper.com)
Prosper was founded in 2005 as the first peer-to-peer lending marketplace in the United States. Since then, Prosper has facilitated more than $15 billion in loans to more than 910,000 people.
Through Prosper, people can invest in each other in a way that is financially and socially rewarding. Borrowers apply online for a fixed-rate, fixed-term loan between $2,000 and $40,000. Individuals and institutions can invest in the loans and earn attractive returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Fire</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kindle-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:04:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kindle-fire/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Firefox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-firefox/</guid>
      <description>New Firefor Logo  The “Firefox” you’ve always known as a browser is stretching to cover a family of products and services united by putting you and your privacy first. Firefox is a browser AND an encrypted service to send huge files. It’s an easy way to protect your passwords on every device AND an early warning if your email has been part of a data breach. Safe, private, eye-opening. That’s just the beginning of the new Firefox family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amalgamated Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:52:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Amalgamated Bank logo Amalgamated Bank is the leading financial institution dedicated to providing affordable banking services to working people, unions, and progressive organizations and businesses. Established in 1923 as New York City’s first labor bank, Amalgamated is now the largest union-owned bank in the United States, with locations across the city, as well as in Washington DC, New Jersey, Nevada and California. Pentagram has designed a new brand identity for the bank that updates its look while also honoring its legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Knicks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-knicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 21:38:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-knicks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IV Interactive</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</guid>
      <description>About IV interactive IV Interactive is a full-service interactive agency specializing in the four elements required for success in an increasingly digital world: innovative design, interactive marketing, technology implementation and strategic consulting. Using this multidisciplinary approach, IV Interactive provide results-driven, award-winning solutions to organizations of all sizes and disciplines. From Jones Apparel Group to Thomson Reuters, IV Interactive have helped IV Interactive clients identify and implement the elements necessary for success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>