<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>apparel on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/apparel/</link><description>Recent content in apparel on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0013</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/apparel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nike//file/nike.svg</url><title>Nike Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nike</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nike/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0013</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nike/</guid><description turbo="true">Nike, Inc. is an American multinational corporation that is engaged in the design, development, manufacturing, and worldwide marketing and sales of footwear, apparel, equipment, accessories, and services. The company is headquartered near Beaverton, Oregon, in the Portland metropolitan area. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest supplier of athletic shoes and apparel and a major manufacturer of sports equipment, with revenue in excess of US$24.1 billion in its fiscal year 2012 (ending May 31, 2012).</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fila//file/fila.svg</url><title>Fila Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Fila</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fila/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fila/</guid><description turbo="true">Fila Holdings Corp. (d/b/a Fila) is a South Korean corporation that designs and manufactures shoes and apparel, taking its current name after the acquisition of the Italian company Fila in 2007 and therefore the rights to the brand name. It is the largest South Korean sportswear manufacturer. Fila was originally founded by Ettore and Giansevero Fila in 1911 in Biella, Piedmont, Italy. In 2003, it was sold to United States-based Sports Brand International.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker//file/foot-locker.svg</url><title>Foot Locker Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Foot Locker</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker/</guid><description turbo="true">Foot Locker Retail, Inc. is an American sportswear and footwear retailer, with its headquarters in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, and operating in 28 countries.
Although established in 1974, and founded as a separate company in 1988, Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s roots date to 1879, as it is a successor corporation to the F. W. Woolworth Company (“Woolworth&amp;rsquo;s”), as many of its freestanding stores were originally Kinney Shoes and Woolworth&amp;rsquo;s locations.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/puma//file/puma.svg</url><title>Puma Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Puma</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/puma/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/puma/</guid><description turbo="true">Puma SE, branded as Puma, is a German multinational corporation that designs and manufactures athletic and casual footwear, apparel and accessories, which is headquartered in Herzogenaurach, Bavaria, Germany. Puma is the third largest sportswear manufacturer in the world. The company was founded in 1948 by Rudolf Dassler. In 1924, Rudolf and his brother Adolf Dassler had jointly formed the company Gebrüder Dassler Schuhfabrik (Dassler Brothers Shoe Factory). The relationship between the two brothers deteriorated until the two agreed to split in 1948, forming two separate entities, Adidas and Puma.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-jordan//file/air-jordan.svg</url><title>Air Jordan Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Air Jordan</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/air-jordan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-jordan/</guid><description turbo="true"> Air Jordan is a brand of basketball shoes, athletic, casual, and style clothing produced by Nike. It was created for former NBA player and 6 time NBA Finals MVP Michael Jordan. The original Air Jordan sneakers were produced exclusively for Michael Jordan in early 1984, and released to the public in late 1984. The shoes were designed for Nike by Peter Moore, Tinker Hatfield, and Bruce Kilgore.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/reebok//file/reebok.svg</url><title>Reebok Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Reebok</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/reebok/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reebok/</guid><description turbo="true">Reebok (/ˈriːbɒk/) is an English footwear and apparel company, subsidiary of German sportsgiant Adidas since 2005. Reebok produces and distributes fitness, running and CrossFit sportswear including clothing and footwear. It is the official footwear and apparel sponsor for Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC), CrossFit, and Spartan Race. Source History Established in 1895 in the small England village of Holcombe as J.W. Foster and Sons, Reebok, as it was renamed in 1958 (after “rhebok”, a type of African gazelle) is a “worldwide designer, marketer and distributor of fitness and lifestyle footwear, apparel and equipment.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/crocs//file/crocs.svg</url><title>Crocs Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Crocs</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/crocs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crocs/</guid><description turbo="true"> Crocs, Inc. is an American company, based in Niwot, Colorado, that distributes and once manufactured a foam clog shoe.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/northface//file/northface.svg</url><title>Northface Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Northface</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/northface/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/northface/</guid><description turbo="true"> The North Face is an American outdoor recreation product company. The North Face produces clothing, footwear, and outdoor equipment.
Source</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/adidas//file/adidas.svg</url><title>Adidas Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Adidas</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/adidas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/adidas/</guid><description turbo="true">Adidas AG is a multinational corporation, founded and headquartered in Herzogenaurach, Germany, that designs and manufactures shoes, clothing and accessories. It is the largest sportswear manufacturer in Europe, and the second largest in the world, after Nike. It is the holding company for the Adidas Group, which consists of the Reebok sportswear company, TaylorMade golf company (including Ashworth), Runtastic, an Austrian fitness technology company and 8.33% of German football club Bayern Munich.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;![CDATA[<image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/asics//file/asics.svg</url><title>Asics Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Asics</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/asics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/asics/</guid><description turbo="true">ASICS (アシックス Ashikkusu) (stylized in all lowercase and italicized) is a Japanese multinational corporation which produces footwear and sports equipment designed for a wide range of sports, generally in the upper price range. The name is an acronym for the Latin phrase anima sana in corpore sano, which translates as &amp;ldquo;Healthy soul in a healthy body&amp;rdquo;. In recent years their running shoes have often been ranked among the top performance footwear in the market.</description>
]] ></turbo:content></item></channel></rss>