<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Norway on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/norway/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Norway on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/norway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Equinor</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor/</guid>
      <description>Equinor ASA (OSE: EQNR, formerly Statoil and StatoilHydro) is a Norwegian multinational energy company headquartered in Stavanger, Norway. It is a petroleum and wind energy company with operations in thirty-six countries. By revenue, while under Statoil name, Equinor was ranked by Forbes Magazine (2013) as the world&amp;rsquo;s eleventh largest oil and gas company and the twenty-sixth largest company, regardless of industry, by profit in the world. The company has about 20,200 employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1994 Lillehammer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1994-lillehammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:28:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1994-lillehammer/</guid>
      <description>The 1994 Winter Olympics (Norwegian: Olympiske vinterleker 1994), officially known as the XVII Olympic Winter Games, was a winter multi-sport event celebrated from 12 to 27 February 1994 in and around Lillehammer, Norway.
 Lillehammer failed to win the bid for the 1992 event, losing to Albertville. Lillehammer was awarded the 1994 Winter Olympics in 1988, after beating Anchorage, United States; Östersund, Sweden; and Sofia, Bulgaria. Lillehammer is the northernmost city to ever host the Winter Games and the Olympic Games overall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opera Mini</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-mini/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-mini/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opera News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opera Software</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-software/</guid>
      <description>About Opera Software AG Opera Software AS is a Norwegian software company, primarily known for its desktop Opera web browser, and mobile web browser Opera Mini. It was demerged from its parent company Otello Corporation as part of the latter&amp;rsquo;s divestiture of its web browser business. Opera browsers have more than 350 million users worldwide across multiple platforms.
Opera is also involved in promoting Web standards through participation in the W3C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opera Touch</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-touch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>