<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Canada on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/canada/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Canada on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/canada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2010 Vancouver</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2010-vancouver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2010-vancouver/</guid>
      <description>The 2010 Winter Olympics, officially known as the XXI Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XXIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver) and commonly known as Vancouver 2010, informally the 21st Winter Olympics, was an international winter multi-sport event that was held from 12 to 28 February 2010 in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, with some events held in the surrounding suburbs of Richmond, West Vancouver and the University Endowment Lands, and in the nearby resort town of Whistler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1988 Calgary</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1988-calgary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:28:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1988-calgary/</guid>
      <description>The 1988 Winter Olympics, officially known as the XV Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XVes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver), was a Winter Olympics multi-sport event celebrated in and around Calgary, Alberta, Canada, between February 13 and 28, 1988 and were the first Winter Olympics to be held over a whole two week period. The host city was selected in 1981 over Falun, Sweden, and Cortina d&amp;rsquo;Ampezzo, Italy. Most events took place in Calgary while several skiing events were held in the mountain resorts of Nakiska and Canmore, west of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1976 Montreal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-montreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:31:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1976-montreal/</guid>
      <description>Préfontaine and Henderson lighting the Olympic Flame   The 1976 Summer Olympics, officially called the Games of the XXI Olympiad (French: Les XXIes olympiques d&amp;rsquo;été), was an international multi-sport event in Montreal, Quebec, in 1976, and the first Olympic Games held in Canada. Montreal was awarded the rights to the 1976 Games on May 12, 1970, at the 69th IOC Session in Amsterdam, over the bids of Moscow and Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Canada</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/air-canada/</guid>
      <description>Air Canada is the flag carrier and the largest airline of Canada by fleet size and passengers carried. The airline, founded in 1937, provides scheduled and charter air transport for passengers and cargo to 207 destinations worldwide. It is a founding member of the Star Alliance. Air Canada&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters are in Montreal, Quebec, while its largest hub is at Toronto Pearson International Airport. The airline&amp;rsquo;s regional service is Air Canada Express.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Royal Bank of Canada</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 21:39:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>