<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>messaging on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/tags/messaging/</link><description>Recent content in messaging on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/tags/messaging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Telegram Messenger Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/files/telegram.svg"/></figure></header>
Telegram is a cloud-based instant messaging and voice over IP service. Telegram client apps are available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any type. Source<p>You can download theTelegramlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/files/telegram.svg</url><title>TelegramLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Telegram</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</guid><description turbo="true"> Telegram is a cloud-based instant messaging and voice over IP service. Telegram client apps are available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any type. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> VKontakte (ВКонтакте) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/files/vk.svg"/></figure></header>
VK (short for its original name VKontakte; Russian: ВКонта́кте, meaning InContact) is a Russian online social media and social networking service based in Saint Petersburg. VK is available in numerous languages but it is especially used by Russian-speakers. VK allows users to message each other publicly or privately; create groups, public pages, and events; share and tag images, audio, and video; and play browser-based games. Source<p>You can download theVKlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/files/vk.svg</url><title>VKLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">VK</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</guid><description turbo="true"> VK (short for its original name VKontakte; Russian: ВКонта́кте, meaning InContact) is a Russian online social media and social networking service based in Saint Petersburg. VK is available in numerous languages but it is especially used by Russian-speakers. VK allows users to message each other publicly or privately; create groups, public pages, and events; share and tag images, audio, and video; and play browser-based games. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> WhatsApp Messenger Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/files/whatsapp.svg"/></figure></header>
WhatsApp Messenger is a freeware, cross-platform messaging and Voice over IP (VoIP) service owned by Facebook. It allows users to send text messages and voice messages, make voice and video calls, and share images, documents, user locations, and other media. WhatsApp&amp;rsquo;s client application runs on mobile devices, but is also accessible from Windows and Mac desktop computers, as long as the user&amp;rsquo;s mobile device remains connected to the Internet while they use the desktop app.<p>You can download theWhatsApplogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/files/whatsapp.svg</url><title>WhatsAppLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">WhatsApp</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/whatsapp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/whatsapp/</guid><description turbo="true">WhatsApp Messenger is a freeware, cross-platform messaging and Voice over IP (VoIP) service owned by Facebook. It allows users to send text messages and voice messages, make voice and video calls, and share images, documents, user locations, and other media. WhatsApp&amp;rsquo;s client application runs on mobile devices, but is also accessible from Windows and Mac desktop computers, as long as the user&amp;rsquo;s mobile device remains connected to the Internet while they use the desktop app.</description></item></channel></rss>