<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>2015 on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/year/2015/</link><description>Recent content in 2015 on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0017</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon//file/verizon.svg</url><title>Verizon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Verizon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0017</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/verizon/</guid><description turbo="true"> Verizon Communications Inc. is an American multinational telecommunications conglomerate and a corporate component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average. The company is based at 1095 Avenue of the Americas in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, but is incorporated in Delaware.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/google//file/google.svg</url><title>Google Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Google</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/google/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0002</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/google/</guid><description turbo="true">About Google Google is an American multinational technology company that specializes in Internet-related services and products. These include online advertising technologies, search, cloud computing, software, and hardware. Google was founded in 1998 by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while they were Ph.D. students at Stanford University in California.
The current Google logo was released on Sept 1 2015. A sans serif logotype retains google’s distinct multi-color sequence, and a compact version of the Google icon works in small contexts.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonos//file/sonos.svg</url><title>Sonos Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sonos</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sonos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonos/</guid><description turbo="true"> Sonos is an American consumer electronics company based in Santa Barbara, California. It was founded in 2002 by John MacFarlane, Craig Shelburne, Tom Cullen, and Trung Mai, and is currently run by Patrick Spence. Sonos is widely known for the smart speakers it develops and manufactures. Sonos products are designed to allow speakers to play music simultaneously in multiple rooms.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge//file/university-of-cambridge.svg</url><title>University of Cambridge Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">University of Cambridge</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</guid><description turbo="true">The University of Cambridge (legally The Chancellor, Masters, and Scholars of the University of Cambridge) is a collegiate public research university in Cambridge, United Kingdom. Founded in 1209 and granted a royal charter by King Henry III in 1231, Cambridge is the second-oldest university in the English-speaking world and the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-oldest surviving university. The university grew out of an association of scholars who left the University of Oxford after a dispute with the townspeople.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1//file/fs1.svg</url><title>FS1 Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">FS1</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</guid><description turbo="true">Fox Sports 1 (FS1) is an American pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation.[1] FS1 replaced the motorsports network Speed on August 17, 2013, at the same time that its companion channel Fox Sports 2 replaced Fuel TV.[2] Both FS1 and FS2 absorbed most of the sports programming from its predecessors, as well as content from Fox Soccer, which was replaced by the entertainment-based channel FXX on September 2, 2013.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2//file/fs2.svg</url><title>FS2 Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">FS2</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</guid><description turbo="true"> Fox Sports 2 (FS2) is an American sports-oriented pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation. The channel is based at the Fox Sports division&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in the Westwood section of Los Angeles, California.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/msnbc//file/msnbc.svg</url><title>MSNBC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MSNBC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/msnbc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/msnbc/</guid><description turbo="true">MSNBC is an American pay television network that provides news coverage and political commentary from NBC News on current events. MSNBC is owned by the NBCUniversal News Group, a unit of the NBCUniversal Television Group division of NBCUniversal (all of which are ultimately owned by Comcast). MSNBC and its website were founded in 1996 under a partnership between Microsoft and General Electric&amp;rsquo;s NBC unit, hence the network&amp;rsquo;s naming. Although they had the same name, msnbc.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/thyssenkrupp//file/thyssenkrupp.svg</url><title>ThyssenKrupp Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ThyssenKrupp</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/thyssenkrupp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/thyssenkrupp/</guid><description turbo="true">thyssenkrupp AG /ˈtɪsɛn.krʊp/ is a German multinational conglomerate with focus on industrial engineering and steel production. The company is based in Duisburg and Essen and divided into 670 subsidiaries worldwide. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest steel producers; it was ranked tenth-largest worldwide by revenue in 2015. The company is the result of the 1999 merger of Thyssen AG and Krupp, and now has its operational headquarters in Essen.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers//file/la-clippers.svg</url><title>LA Clippers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LA Clippers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-clippers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Clippers (branded as the LA Clippers) are an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles. The Clippers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of Pacific Division of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference. The Clippers play their home games at the Staples Center, an arena they share with fellow NBA team the Los Angeles Lakers, as well as the Los Angeles Sparks of the Women&amp;rsquo;s National Basketball Association (WNBA) and the Los Angeles Kings of the National Hockey League (NHL).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker//file/johnnie-walker.svg</url><title>Johnnie Walker Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Johnnie Walker</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker/</guid><description turbo="true"> Johnnie Walker is a brand of Scotch whisky now owned by Diageo that originated in the Scottish town of Kilmarnock, East Ayrshire. The brand was first established by grocer John Walker. It is the most widely distributed brand of blended Scotch whisky in the world, sold in almost every country, with annual sales of the equivalent of over 223.7 million 700 ml bottles in 2016 (156.6 million litres)
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ufc//file/ufc.svg</url><title>UFC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">UFC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ufc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ufc/</guid><description turbo="true">The Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) is an American mixed martial arts promotion company based in Las Vegas, Nevada, that is owned and operated by parent company William Morris Endeavor. It is the largest MMA promotion company in the world and features the highest-level fighters on the roster. The UFC produces events worldwide that showcase twelve weight divisions and abide by the Unified Rules of Mixed Martial Arts. As of 2018, the UFC has held over 400 events.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens//file/walgreens.svg</url><title>Walgreens Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Walgreens</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens/</guid><description turbo="true">Walgreen Company or simply Walgreens is an American company that operates as the second-largest pharmacy store chain in the United States behind CVS Health. It specializes in filling prescriptions, health and wellness products, health information, and photo services. As of August 31, 2018, the company operated 9,560 stores in all 50 states, the District of Columbia and the US territories of Puerto Rico and the U.S. Virgin Islands. It was founded in Chicago, Illinois, in 1901.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines//file/vietnam-airlines.svg</url><title>Vietnam Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Vietnam Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vietnam-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true"> Vietnam Airlines (Vietnamese: Hãng Hàng không Quốc gia Việt Nam) is the flag carrier of Vietnam. The airline was founded in 1956 and later established as a state-owned enterprise in April 1989. Vietnam Airlines is headquartered in Long Biên District, Hanoi, with hubs at Noi Bai International Airport and Tan Son Nhat International Airport. The airline flies to 64 destinations in 17 countries, excluding codeshared services.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune//file/san-diego-union-tribune.svg</url><title>San Diego Union Tribune Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">San Diego Union Tribune</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</guid><description turbo="true">About San Diego Union Tribune The San Diego Union-Tribune is San Diego’s largest media company and its oldest business, dating back to the founding of the Union in 1868.
Today, Union-Tribune publications reach more than 96 percent of San Diego County households each week. The company portfolio includes its Pulitzer Prize-winning newspaper, The San Diego Union-Tribune; the region’s leading website, SanDiegoUnionTribune.com; weekly entertainment guide Night + Day; lifestyle magazine Pacific San Diego; Spanish-language weekly Hoy San Diego; and nine community newspapers: the La Jolla Light; Del Mar Times; Encinitas Advocate; Solana Beach Sun; Carmel Valley Times; Poway News Chieftain; Rancho Santa Fe Review; Ramona Sentinel and Rancho Bernardo News Journal.</description></item></channel></rss>