<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Germany on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/germany/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Germany on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:31:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/germany/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 1972 Munchen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1972-munchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:31:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-1972-munchen/</guid>
      <description>The 1972 Summer Olympics (German: Olympische Sommerspiele 1972), officially known as the Games of the XX Olympiad, was an international multi-sport event held in Munich, West Germany, from August 26 to September 11, 1972. The sporting nature of the event was largely overshadowed by the Munich massacre in the second week, in which eleven Israeli athletes and coaches and a West German police officer at Olympic village were killed by Black September terrorists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amg/</guid>
      <description> Mercedes-AMG GmbH, commonly known as AMG, is the high-performance brand used by Mercedes-Benz. AMG independently hires engineers and contracts with manufacturers to customize Mercedes-Benz AMG vehicles. Mercedes-AMG is headquartered in Affalterbach, Baden-Württemberg, Germany.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpina</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alpina/</guid>
      <description>Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners. For instance, the Alpina B7 is produced at the same assembly line in Dingolfing, Germany (BMW Plant Dingolfing), as BMW&amp;rsquo;s own 7 Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/audi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/audi/</guid>
      <description>Alpina Burkard Bovensiepen GmbH &amp;amp; Co. KG is an automobile manufacturing company based in Buchloe, in the Ostallgäu district of Bavaria, Germany that develops and sells high-performance versions of BMW cars. Alpina works closely with BMW and their processes are integrated into BMW&amp;rsquo;s production lines, thus Alpina is recognized by the German Ministry of Transport as an automobile manufacturer, in contrast to other performance specialists which are aftermarket tuners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMW</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</guid>
      <description> BMW AG (German originally an initialism for Bayerische Motoren Werke in German, or Bavarian Motor Works in English) is a German multinational company which currently produces automobiles and motorcycles, and also produced aircraft engines until 1945.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daimler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/daimler/</guid>
      <description> Daimler AG is a German multinational automotive corporation, headquartered in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. Daimler-Benz was formed with the merger of Benz &amp;amp; Cie and Daimler Motoren Gesellschaft in 1926. The company was renamed DaimlerChrysler upon acquiring the American automobile manufacturer Chrysler Corporation in 1998, and was again renamed Daimler upon divesting of Chrysler in 2007.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</guid>
      <description> Mercedes-Benz is a German global automobile marque and a division of Daimler AG. The brand is known for luxury vehicles, buses, coaches, and trucks. The headquarters is in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. The name first appeared in 1926 under Daimler-Benz. In 2018, Mercedes-Benz was the biggest selling premium vehicle brand in the world, having sold 2.31 million passenger cars.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opel</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/opel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opel/</guid>
      <description> Opel is a German automobile manufacturer, a subsidiary of French automaker Groupe PSA since August 2017. From 1929 until 2017, Opel was owned by American automaker General Motors. Opel vehicles are sold in England under the Vauxhall brand. Some Opel vehicles are badge-engineered in Australasia under the Holden brand, and in North America and China under the Buick brand.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porsche</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/porshe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/porshe/</guid>
      <description> Dr.-Ing. h.c. F. Porsche AG, usually shortened to Porsche AG, is a German automobile manufacturer specializing in high-performance sports cars, SUVs and sedans. Porsche AG is headquartered in Stuttgart, and is owned by Volkswagen AG, which is itself majority-owned by Porsche Automobil Holding SE. Porsche&amp;rsquo;s current lineup includes the 718 Boxster/Cayman, 911, Panamera, Macan and Cayenne.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</guid>
      <description> Smart (stylized as smart) is a German automotive brand and division of Daimler AG. The company is based in Böblingen, Germany. It produces microcars and subcompacts, primarily the Fortwo and Forfour. The primary assembly plants is the Smartville in Hambach, France. A second plant exists in Novo Mesto, Slovenia. Marketed in 46 countries around the world, production of the Fortwo had surpassed 1.7 million units by early 2015.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/volkswagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volkswagen/</guid>
      <description> Volkswagen is a German automaker founded on 28 May 1937 by the German Labour Front, a Nazi labour union, and headquartered in Wolfsburg. It is the flagship marque of the Volkswagen Group, the largest automaker by worldwide sales in 2016 and 2017. The group&amp;rsquo;s biggest market is in China, which delivers 40% of its sales and profits.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>