<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>U on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/u/</link>
    <description>Recent content in U on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/u/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft/</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft Entertainment is a French video game company headquartered in Montreuil with several development studios across the world. It publishes games for several video game franchises, including Rayman, Raving Rabbids, Prince of Persia, Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed, Far Cry, Just Dance, and the Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s series. As of March 2018, Ubisoft is the fifth largest publicly traded game company in the Americas and Europe in terms of revenue and market capitalisation, after Activision Blizzard, Electronic Arts, Take-Two Interactive and CD Projekt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udemy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/udemy/</guid>
      <description>Udemy, Inc. is an American massive open online course (MOOC) provider aimed at professional adults and students. It was founded in May 2010 by Eren Bali, Gagan Biyani, and Oktay Caglar.
 As of Jan 2020, the platform has more than 35 million students and 57,000 instructors teaching courses in over 65 languages. There have been over 400 million course enrollments. Students and instructors come from 180+ countries and 2/3 of the students are located outside of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under Armour</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/under-armour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/under-armour/</guid>
      <description>Under Armour, Inc. is an American company that manufactures footwear, sports, and casual apparel. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters are located in Baltimore, Maryland with additional offices located in Amsterdam (European headquarters), Austin, Guangzhou, Hong Kong, Houston, Jakarta, London, Mexico City, Munich, New York City, Panama City (international headquarters), Paris, Pittsburgh, Portland, San Francisco, São Paulo, Santiago, Seoul, Shanghai (Greater Chinese headquarters), and Toronto.
 Source About Under Armour Under Armour’s vision is to inspire you with performance solutions you never knew you needed and can’t imagine living without.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Technologies</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-technologies/</guid>
      <description>United Technologies Corporation (UTC) was an American multinational conglomerate headquartered in Farmington, Connecticut. It merged with the Raytheon Company in April 2020 to form Raytheon Technologies. It researched, developed, and manufactured products in numerous areas, including aircraft engines, aerospace systems, HVAC, elevators and escalators, fire and security, building automation, and industrial products, among others. UTC was also a large military contractor, getting about 10% of its revenue from the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealth</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unitedhealth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unitedhealth/</guid>
      <description>UnitedHealth Group Incorporated is an American for-profit managed health care company based in Minnetonka, Minnesota. It offers health care products and insurance services. It is the largest healthcare company in the world by revenue, with 2019 revenue of $242.2 billion. UnitedHealthcare revenues comprise 80% of the Group&amp;rsquo;s overall revenue.
 The company is ranked 7th on the 2020 Fortune 500.
Source About UnitedHealth UnitedHealth Group is committed to leading the development of a more modern, progressive and effective health system that provides extraordinary value for society — building healthier communities and improving the quality of life for those we serve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unity/</guid>
      <description>Unity is a cross-platform game engine developed by Unity Technologies, first announced and released in June 2005 at Apple Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Developers Conference as a Mac OS X-exclusive game engine. As of 2018, the engine had been extended to support more than 25 platforms. The engine can be used to create three-dimensional, two-dimensional, virtual reality, and augmented reality games, as well as simulations and other experiences. The engine has been adopted by industries outside video gaming, such as film, automotive, architecture, engineering and construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universal Kids</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/universal-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/universal-kids/</guid>
      <description>Universal Kids (formerly PBS Kids Sprout and Sprout as the logo used to be) is an American pay television channel owned by the NBCUniversal Television and Streaming division of NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast.
 The channel first launched on September 26, 2005, originally a joint venture between PBS, Comcast, Sesame Workshop, and HIT Entertainment, devoted to children&amp;rsquo;s television programming aimed at a preschool audience. Following Comcast&amp;rsquo;s purchase of NBCUniversal, the company gradually bought out the remaining owners&amp;rsquo; shares in the channel, reaching full ownership in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universal Pictures</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/universal-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/universal-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Universal Pictures (legally Universal City Studios LLC, also known as Universal Studios, and formerly named Universal Film Manufacturing Company and Universal-International Pictures Inc.) is an American film studio owned by Comcast through the NBCUniversal Film and Entertainment division of its wholly owned subsidiary NBCUniversal.
 Founded in 1912 by Carl Laemmle, Mark Dintenfass, Charles O. Baumann, Adam Kessel, Pat Powers, William Swanson, David Horsley, Robert H. Cochrane, and Jules Brulatour, it is the oldest surviving film studio in the United States; the world&amp;rsquo;s fifth oldest after Gaumont, Pathé, Titanus, and Nordisk Film; and the oldest member of Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Big Five&amp;rdquo; studios in terms of the overall film market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engine</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unreal-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unreal-engine/</guid>
      <description>The Unreal Engine is a game engine developed by Epic Games, first showcased in the 1998 first-person shooter game Unreal. Although initially developed for first-person shooters, it has been used in a variety of other genres, including platformers, fighting games, MMORPGs, and other RPGs. Written in C++, the Unreal Engine features a high degree of portability, supporting a wide range of platforms.
 The latest release is Unreal Engine 4, which launched in 2014 under a subscription model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Network</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-network/</guid>
      <description>USA Network (on-air simply as USA, stylized as usa since 2005) is an American basic cable channel owned by the NBCUniversal Television and Streaming division of NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast. It was originally launched in 1977 as Madison Square Garden Sports Network, one of the first national sports cable television channels, before being relaunched as USA Network in 1980. Once a minor player in basic-tier pay television, USA has steadily gained popularity due to its original programming; it is one of four major subscription-television networks (with TBS, TNT and FX) that also broadcasts syndicated reruns of current and former network television series and theatrically-released feature films, as well as limited sports programming and WWE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Cambridge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</guid>
      <description>The University of Cambridge (legally The Chancellor, Masters, and Scholars of the University of Cambridge) is a collegiate public research university in Cambridge, United Kingdom. Founded in 1209 and granted a royal charter by King Henry III in 1231, Cambridge is the second-oldest university in the English-speaking world and the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-oldest surviving university. The university grew out of an association of scholars who left the University of Oxford after a dispute with the townspeople.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNDP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/undp/</guid>
      <description> The United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) is the United Nations&amp;rsquo; global development network. It advocates for change and connects countries to knowledge, experience and resources to help people build a better life for themselves. It provides expert advice, training and grants support to developing countries, with increasing emphasis on assistance to the least developed countries. It promotes technical and investment cooperation among nations.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNH</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/unh/</guid>
      <description> The University of New Hampshire (UNH) is a public research university with its main campus in Durham, New Hampshire. It was founded and incorporated in 1866 as a land grant college in Hanover in connection with Dartmouth College. In 1893, UNH moved to Durham.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universidad Tecmilenio</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/universidad-tecmilenio/</guid>
      <description>The Universidad TecMilenio (UTM) (TecMilenio University) is a private institution of higher education. The institution is part of Monterrey Institute of Technology and Higher Education TecMilenio University ITESM System, an educational system with national and international levels, through 30 campus and an online campus with a unique and innovative educational model that forms professionals with the skills needed by modern businesses and organizations. For-profit schools that have entered the country in recent years, the university serves some 21,000 students on its own at high school, undergraduate and postgraduate level, frequently through distance learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Univision Networks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/univision-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/univision-networks/</guid>
      <description> The graphic identification for this large Spanish-language television network features a bold abstract letter “U”, which, with the upper left quadrant turned, also suggests an exuberantly colorful bird.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Bicentennial</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-bicentennial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-bicentennial/</guid>
      <description> The United States Bicentennial was a series of celebrations and observances during the mid-1970s that paid tribute to historical events leading up to the creation of the United States of America as an independent republic. It was a central event in the memory of the American Revolution. The Bicentennial culminated on Sunday, July 4, 1976, with the 200th anniversary of the adoption of the Declaration of Independence.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Open</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/us-open/</guid>
      <description> The United States Open Tennis Championships is a hard court tennis tournament. The tournament is the modern version of one of the oldest tennis championships in the world, the U.S. National Championship, for which men&amp;rsquo;s singles and men&amp;rsquo;s doubles were first played in 1881.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utah Jazz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/utah-jazz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/utah-jazz/</guid>
      <description>The Utah Jazz are an American professional basketball team based in Salt Lake City, Utah. The Jazz compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference, Northwest Division. Since 1991, the team has played its home games at Vivint Smart Home Arena. The franchise began play as an expansion team in 1974 as the New Orleans Jazz (as a tribute to New Orleans&amp;rsquo; history of originating Jazz music).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UFC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ufc/</guid>
      <description>The Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) is an American mixed martial arts promotion company based in Las Vegas, Nevada, that is owned and operated by parent company William Morris Endeavor. It is the largest MMA promotion company in the world and features the highest-level fighters on the roster. The UFC produces events worldwide that showcase twelve weight divisions and abide by the Unified Rules of Mixed Martial Arts. As of 2018, the UFC has held over 400 events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uniliver</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniliver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniliver/</guid>
      <description> Unilever is a British-Dutch transnational consumer goods company co-headquartered in London, United Kingdom, and Rotterdam, Netherlands. Its products include food and beverages (about 40 per cent of its revenue), cleaning agents, beauty products, and personal care products. It is Europe’s seventh most valuable company. Unilever is one of the oldest multinational companies; its products are available in around 190 countries.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>USA Today is an internationally distributed American daily, middle-market newspaper that serves as the flagship publication of its owner, the Gannett Company. The newspaper has a generally centrist audience.[3] Founded by Al Neuharth on September 15, 1982, it operates from Gannett&amp;rsquo;s corporate headquarters on Jones Branch Drive, in McLean, Virginia.[4] It is printed at 37 sites across the United States and at five additional sites internationally. Its dynamic design influenced the style of local, regional, and national newspapers worldwide, through its use of concise reports, colorized images, informational graphics, and inclusion of popular culture stories, among other distinct features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uber/</guid>
      <description>Uber Technologies Inc. is an American multinational transportation network company (TNC) offering services that include peer-to-peer ridesharing, ride service hailing, food delivery, and a bicycle-sharing system. The company is based in San Francisco and has operations in 785 metropolitan areas worldwide. Its platforms can be accessed via its websites and mobile apps.
 Source Uber typography is as unique and easy to use as Uber are. Inspired by the world’s best used transportation examples, it was designed to maximize its impact across all applications while keeping it easy to read, ownable, and highly recognizable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-airlines/</guid>
      <description>United Airlines, Inc. is a major American airline headquartered at Willis Tower in Chicago, Illinois. United operates a large domestic and international route network, with an extensive presence in the Asia-Pacific region. United is a founding member of the Star Alliance, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline alliance with a total of 28 member airlines. Regional service is operated by independent carriers under the brand name United Express. United was established by the amalgamation of several airlines in the late 1920s, the oldest of these being Varney Air Lines, which was founded in 1926.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ups/</guid>
      <description> United Parcel Service (UPS) is an American multinational package delivery and supply chain management company.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>