<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>U on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/u/</link>
    <description>Recent content in U on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/u/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UPS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ups/</guid>
      <description> United Parcel Service (UPS) is an American multinational package delivery and supply chain management company.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uber/</guid>
      <description>Uber Technologies Inc. is an American multinational transportation network company (TNC) offering services that include peer-to-peer ridesharing, ride service hailing, food delivery, and a bicycle-sharing system. The company is based in San Francisco and has operations in 785 metropolitan areas worldwide. Its platforms can be accessed via its websites and mobile apps.
 Source Our typography is as unique and easy to use as we are. Inspired by the world’s best used transportation examples, it was designed to maximize its impact across all applications while keeping it easy to read, ownable, and highly recognizable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-airlines/</guid>
      <description>United Airlines, Inc. is a major American airline headquartered at Willis Tower in Chicago, Illinois. United operates a large domestic and international route network, with an extensive presence in the Asia-Pacific region. United is a founding member of the Star Alliance, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest airline alliance with a total of 28 member airlines. Regional service is operated by independent carriers under the brand name United Express. United was established by the amalgamation of several airlines in the late 1920s, the oldest of these being Varney Air Lines, which was founded in 1926.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>