<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Siegel &#43; Gale on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/siegel-&#43;-gale/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Siegel &#43; Gale on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/siegel-+-gale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Apron</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</guid>
      <description> Blue Apron Inc. is an American ingredient-and-recipe meal kit service. It exclusively operates in the United States. The weekly boxes contain ingredients and also include suggested recipes that must be cooked by hand by the customer using the pre-ordered ingredients.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DXT</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</guid>
      <description> DXC Technology is an American multinational corporation that provides B2B IT services.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HMH</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</guid>
      <description> Houghton Mifflin Harcourt is a publisher of textbooks, instructional technology materials, assessments, reference works, and fiction and non-fiction for both young readers and adults.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount Sinai</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mount-sinai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mount-sinai/</guid>
      <description>Mount Sinai Hospital, founded in 1852, is one of the oldest and largest teaching hospitals in the United States. It is located on the Upper East Side in the New York City borough of Manhattan, on the eastern border of Central Park stretching along Fifth Avenue, between East 98th Street and East 103rd Street. The entire Mount Sinai health system has over 7,400 physicians, as well as 3,815 beds, and delivers over 16,000 babies a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</guid>
      <description>National Oilwell Varco (NOV) is an American multinational corporation based in Houston, Texas. It is a leading worldwide provider of equipment and components used in oil and gas drilling and production operations, oilfield services, and supply chain integration services to the upstream oil and gas industry. The company conducts operations in more than 600 locations across six continents, operating through three reporting segments: Rig Technologies, Wellbore Technologies, and Completion &amp;amp; Production Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nexford</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</guid>
      <description> Nexford University is a private for-profit online university headquartered in Washington, DC. It was founded in 2018 by Fadl Al Tarzi. The University offers programs through the process of online distance learning. Nexford is licensed to issue degrees by the Higher Education Licensure Commission (HELC) in Washington DC. Nexford is accredited by ASIC, an UK-based International accreditation agency operating in 60+ countries.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super 8</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</guid>
      <description> With more than 2,800 hotels on four continents, the newly redesigned Super 8 offers affordable, innovative lodging on the open road. As your ultimate roadside companion, every location also offers free WiFi and a complimentary SuperStart Breakfast to get you recharged and refueled for the day ahead.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMCA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</guid>
      <description> YMCA, sometimes regionally called the Y, is a worldwide organisation based in Geneva, Switzerland, with more than 64 million beneficiaries from 120 national associations. It was founded on 6 June 1844 by Sir George Williams in London, originally as the Young Men&amp;rsquo;s Christian Association and aims to put Christian principles into practice by developing a healthy &amp;ldquo;body, mind, and spirit&amp;rdquo;.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</guid>
      <description>CVS Pharmacy is a subsidiary of the American retail and health care company CVS Health, headquartered in Woonsocket, Rhode Island. It was also known as, and originally named, the Consumer Value Store and was founded in Lowell, Massachusetts, in 1963. The chain was owned by its original holding company Melville Corporation since its inception until its current parent company (CVS Health) was spun off into its own company in 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aetna</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aetna/</guid>
      <description> Aetna Inc. is an American managed health care company that sells traditional and consumer directed health care insurance and related services, such as medical, pharmaceutical, dental, behavioral health, long-term care, and disability plans, primarily through employer-paid (fully or partly) insurance and benefit programs, and through Medicare. Since November 28, 2018, the company has been a subsidiary of CVS Health.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</guid>
      <description>HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
 Source Source In October 2014, the Hewlett-Packard Company announced its intention to split into two separate entities, signaling the largest corporate demerger in history. The two resulting companies would each remain Fortune 100 industry leaders—with HP, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</guid>
      <description>SAP SE is a German multinational software corporation that makes enterprise software to manage business operations and customer relations. SAP is headquartered in Walldorf, Baden-Württemberg, Germany with regional offices in 180 countries. The company has over 425,000 customers in over 180 countries and is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source  Subtle enhancements to the SAP logo make it feel more contemporary. Designed to live in the digital world, the new mark springs vividly from the screen, on any background, connecting with both large-scale business clients and individual consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</guid>
      <description>About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>