<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Siegel &#43; Gale on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/siegel-&#43;-gale/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Siegel &#43; Gale on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/siegel-+-gale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</guid>
      <description>CVS Pharmacy is a subsidiary of the American retail and health care company CVS Health, headquartered in Woonsocket, Rhode Island. It was also known as, and originally named, the Consumer Value Store and was founded in Lowell, Massachusetts, in 1963. The chain was owned by its original holding company Melville Corporation since its inception until its current parent company (CVS Health) was spun off into its own company in 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hpe/</guid>
      <description>HP Inc. (also known as HP and stylized as hp) is an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California, United States. It develops personal computers (PCs), printers and related supplies, as well as 3D printing solutions.
 Source Source In October 2014, the Hewlett-Packard Company announced its intention to split into two separate entities, signaling the largest corporate demerger in history. The two resulting companies would each remain Fortune 100 industry leaders—with HP, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</guid>
      <description>SAP SE is a German multinational software corporation that makes enterprise software to manage business operations and customer relations. SAP is headquartered in Walldorf, Baden-Württemberg, Germany with regional offices in 180 countries. The company has over 425,000 customers in over 180 countries and is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source  Subtle enhancements to the SAP logo make it feel more contemporary. Designed to live in the digital world, the new mark springs vividly from the screen, on any background, connecting with both large-scale business clients and individual consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</guid>
      <description>About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>