<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>energy on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/energy/</link><description>Recent content in energy on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apache//file/apache.svg</url><title>Apache Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apache</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apache/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apache/</guid><description turbo="true"> Apache Corporation is a company engaged in hydrocarbon exploration. It is organized in Delaware and headquartered in Houston. The company is ranked 411th on the Fortune 500.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov//file/nov.svg</url><title>NOV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NOV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</guid><description turbo="true">National Oilwell Varco (NOV) is an American multinational corporation based in Houston, Texas. It is a leading worldwide provider of equipment and components used in oil and gas drilling and production operations, oilfield services, and supply chain integration services to the upstream oil and gas industry. The company conducts operations in more than 600 locations across six continents, operating through three reporting segments: Rig Technologies, Wellbore Technologies, and Completion &amp;amp; Production Solutions.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp//file/bp.svg</url><title>BP Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">BP</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</guid><description turbo="true">BP plc (formerly The British Petroleum Company plc and BP Amoco plc) is a British multinational oil and gas company headquartered in London, United Kingdom. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s seven oil and gas &amp;ldquo;supermajors&amp;rdquo;, whose performance in 2012 made it the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth-largest oil and gas company, the sixth-largest energy company by market capitalization and the company with the world&amp;rsquo;s 12th-largest revenue (turnover). It is a vertically integrated company operating in all areas of the oil and gas industry, including exploration and production, refining, distribution and marketing, petrochemicals, power generation and trading.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chevron//file/chevron.svg</url><title>Chevron Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chevron</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chevron/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chevron/</guid><description turbo="true">Chevron Corporation is an American multinational energy corporation. One of the successor companies of Standard Oil, it is headquartered in San Ramon, California, and active in more than 180 countries. Chevron is engaged in every aspect of the oil, natural gas, and geothermal energy industries, including hydrocarbon exploration and production; refining, marketing and transport; chemicals manufacturing and sales; and power generation. Chevron is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest oil companies; as of 2019, it ranked eleventh in the Fortune 500 list of the top US closely held and public corporations and 28th on the Fortune Global 500 list of the top 500 corporations worldwide.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group//file/cnooc-group.svg</url><title>CNOOC Group Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNOOC Group</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group/</guid><description turbo="true">China National Offshore Oil Corporation, or CNOOC Group (Chinese: 中国海洋石油总公司 Pinyin: Zhōngguó Háiyáng Shíyóu Zǒnggōngsī), is one of the largest national oil companies in China. It is the third-largest national oil company in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, after CNPC (parent of PetroChina) and China Petrochemical Corporation (parent of Sinopec).[citation needed] The CNOOC Group focuses on the exploitation, exploration and development of crude oil and natural gas in offshore China, alongwith its subsidiary COOEC.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc//file/cnpc.svg</url><title>CNPC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNPC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</guid><description turbo="true"> The China National Petroleum Corporation (CNPC) is a major national oil and gas corporation of China PR and one of the largest integrated energy groups in the world. Its headquarters are in Dongcheng District, Beijing. CNPC was ranked fourth in 2017 Fortune Global 500, a global ranking of the largest corporations by revenue
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/conocophillips//file/conocophillips.svg</url><title>ConocoPhillips Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ConocoPhillips</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/conocophillips/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conocophillips/</guid><description turbo="true">ConocoPhillips is an American multinational energy corporation with its headquarters located in the Energy Corridor district of Houston, Texas in the United States. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest independent pure-play exploration and production company and the company ranked No. 95 in the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue. ConocoPhillips was created through the merger of American oil companies Conoco Inc. and Phillips Petroleum Co.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy//file/dominion-energy.svg</url><title>Dominion Energy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dominion Energy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dominion-energy/</guid><description turbo="true"> Dominion Energy, Inc., commonly referred to as Dominion, is an American power and energy company headquartered in Richmond, Virginia that supplies electricity in parts of Virginia, North Carolina, and South Carolina and supplies natural gas to parts of West Virginia, Ohio, Pennsylvania, North Carolina, South Carolina, and Georgia. Dominion also has generation facilities in Indiana, Illinois, Connecticut, and Rhode Island.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni//file/eni.svg</url><title>Eni Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Eni</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eni/</guid><description turbo="true">Eni S.p.A. is an Italian multinational oil and gas company headquartered in Rome. Considered one of the global supermajors, it has operations in 79 countries, and is currently world&amp;rsquo;s 11th largest industrial company with a market capitalization of 68 billion euros (US$ 90 billion), as of August 14, 2013 The Italian government owns a 30.303% golden share in the company, 3.934% held through the state Treasury and 26.369% held through the Cassa Depositi e Prestiti.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor//file/equinor.svg</url><title>Equinor Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Equinor</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/equinor/</guid><description turbo="true">Equinor ASA (OSE: EQNR, formerly Statoil and StatoilHydro) is a Norwegian multinational energy company headquartered in Stavanger, Norway. It is a petroleum and wind energy company with operations in thirty-six countries. By revenue, while under Statoil name, Equinor was ranked by Forbes Magazine (2013) as the world&amp;rsquo;s eleventh largest oil and gas company and the twenty-sixth largest company, regardless of industry, by profit in the world. The company has about 20,200 employees.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/exxonmobil//file/exxonmobil.svg</url><title>ExxonMobil Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ExxonMobil</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/exxonmobil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/exxonmobil/</guid><description turbo="true">Exxon Mobil Corporation, doing business as ExxonMobil, is an American multinational oil and gas corporation headquartered in Irving, Texas. It is the largest direct descendant of John D. Rockefeller&amp;rsquo;s Standard Oil Company, and was formed on November 30, 1999 by the merger of Exxon (formerly the Standard Oil Company of New Jersey) and Mobil (formerly the Standard Oil Company of New York). ExxonMobil&amp;rsquo;s primary brands are Exxon, Mobil, Esso, and ExxonMobil Chemical.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom//file/gazprom.svg</url><title>Gazprom Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Gazprom</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom/</guid><description turbo="true">Public Joint Stock Company Gazprom is a large Russian company founded in 1989, which carries on the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of natural gas. The company is majority owned by the Government of Russia, via the Federal Agency for State Property Management and Rosneftegaz. The remaining shares are listed on public stock markets of Moscow, London and Frankfurt. The Gazprom name is a portmanteau of the Russian words Gazovaya Promyshlennost (Russian: га́зовая промы́шленность - gas industry).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hellenic-petroleum//file/hellenic-petroleum.svg</url><title>Hellenic Petroleum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hellenic Petroleum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hellenic-petroleum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hellenic-petroleum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Hellenic Petroleum S.A. is one of the largest oil companies in the Balkans and with its roots dating to 1958 with the establishment of the first oil refinery in Greece (Aspropyrgos).
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl//file/iocl.svg</url><title>IOCL Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">IOCL</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iocl/</guid><description turbo="true">Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL), commonly known as IndianOil is an Indian state government owned oil and gas company headquartered in New Delhi. It is the largest commercial oil company in the country, with a net profit of INR 19,106 crore (USD 2,848 million) for the financial year 2016–17. It is ranked 1st in Fortune India 500 list for year 2016 and 137th in Fortune&amp;rsquo;s ‘Global 500’ list of world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies in the year 2018.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/jxtg//file/jxtg.svg</url><title>JXTG Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">JXTG</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/jxtg/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jxtg/</guid><description turbo="true"> JXTG Holdings (JXTGホールディングス株式会社) is a Japanese petroleum and metals conglomerate headquartered in Tokyo, Japan. In 2012 the multinational corporation consisted of 24,691 employees worldwide and, as of March 2013, JX Holdings was the forty third largest company in the world by revenue. Since April 2017, JX Holdings and TonenGeneral Sekiyu K.K. integrated their businesses into the JXTG Group.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/kuwait-petroleum//file/kuwait-petroleum.svg</url><title>Kuwait Petroleum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Kuwait Petroleum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/kuwait-petroleum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kuwait-petroleum/</guid><description turbo="true">Kuwait Petroleum Corporation (Arabic: مؤسسة البترول الكويتية‎) is Kuwait&amp;rsquo;s national oil company, headquartered in Kuwait City. The activities of Kuwait Petroleum Corporation (KPC) are focused on petroleum exploration, production, petrochemicals, refining, marketing, and transportation. KPC produces about 7% of the world&amp;rsquo;s total crude oil. KPC plans are to achieve crude oil production capacities in Kuwait of 3.0 million barrels per day by 2010, 3.5 million barrels per day by 2015 and 4.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil//file/lukoil.svg</url><title>Lukoil Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lukoil</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</guid><description turbo="true">The PJSC Lukoil Oil Company is a Russian multinational energy corporation headquartered in Moscow, specializing in the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of petroleum, natural gas, and petroleum products. It was formed in 1991 when three state-run, western Siberian companies named after the respective town in Khanty–Mansi Autonomous Okrug that each was based in, Langepasneftegaz, Urayneftegaz, and Kogalymneftegaz, merged. Its name is the combination of the acronym LUK (initials of the oil-producing cities of Langepas, Uray, Kogalym) and the English word &amp;ldquo;oil&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/marathon-petroleum//file/marathon-petroleum.svg</url><title>Marathon Petroleum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Marathon Petroleum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/marathon-petroleum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marathon-petroleum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Marathon Petroleum Corporation is an American petroleum refining, marketing, and transportation company headquartered in Findlay, Ohio. The company was a wholly owned subsidiary of Marathon Oil until a corporate spin-off in 2011.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ongc//file/ongc.svg</url><title>ONGC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ONGC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ongc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ongc/</guid><description turbo="true">Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) is an Indian multinational oil and gas company. Its registered office is now at New Delhi, India. It is a Public Sector Undertaking (PSU) of the Government of India, under the administrative control of the Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas. It is India&amp;rsquo;s largest oil and gas exploration and production company. It produces around 70% of India&amp;rsquo;s crude oil (equivalent to around 30% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total demand) and around 62% of its natural gas.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/pdvsa//file/pdvsa.svg</url><title>PDVSA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">PDVSA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/pdvsa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pdvsa/</guid><description turbo="true"> Petróleos de Venezuela, S.A. (English: Petroleum of Venezuela) is the Venezuelan state-owned oil and natural gas company. It has activities in exploration, production, refining and exporting oil as well as exploration and production of natural gas. Since its founding on 1 January 1976 with the nationalization of the Venezuelan oil industry, PDVSA has dominated the oil industry of Venezuela, the world&amp;rsquo;s fifth largest oil exporter.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/pemex//file/pemex.svg</url><title>Pemex Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Pemex</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/pemex/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pemex/</guid><description turbo="true">Petróleos Mexicanos, which translates to Mexican Petroleum, but is trademarked and better known as Pemex, is the Mexican state-owned petroleum company, created in 1938 by nationalization or expropriation of all private, foreign, and domestic oil companies at that time. Pemex had total assets worth $415.75 billion, and was the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest non-publicly listed company by total market value (in December 2005), and Latin America&amp;rsquo;s second-largest enterprise by annual revenue as of 2009, surpassed only by Petrobras (the Brazilian National Oil Company).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/pertamina//file/pertamina.svg</url><title>Pertamina Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Pertamina</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/pertamina/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pertamina/</guid><description turbo="true">PT Pertamina (Persero) or Pertamina (was Perusahaan Pertambangan Minyak dan Gas Bumi Negara, lit. &amp;lsquo;State Oil and Natural Gas Mining Company&amp;rsquo;) is an Indonesian state-owned oil and natural gas corporation based in Jakarta. It was created in August 1968 by the merger of Pertamin (established 1961) and Permina (established 1957). The firm is currently (2013) the second-largest crude oil producer in Indonesia behind the US-based Chevron Pacific Indonesia. In 2013 for the first time, Pertamina ranked no.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/petrobras//file/petrobras.svg</url><title>Petrobras Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Petrobras</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/petrobras/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/petrobras/</guid><description turbo="true"> Petróleo Brasileiro S.A. — Petrobras, more commonly known as simply Petrobras (Portuguese pronunciation: [ˌpɛtɾoˈbɾas ]), is a semi-public Brazilian multinational corporation in the petroleum industry headquartered in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil. The company&amp;rsquo;s name translates to Brazilian Petroleum Corporation — Petrobras.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/phillips-66//file/phillips-66.svg</url><title>Phillips 66 Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Phillips 66</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/phillips-66/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/phillips-66/</guid><description turbo="true">The Phillips 66 Company is an American multinational energy company headquartered in Westchase, Houston, Texas. It debuted as an independent energy company when ConocoPhillips executed a spin-off of its downstream and midstream assets. Taking its name from the 1927 &amp;ldquo;Phillips 66&amp;rdquo; trademark of ConocoPhillips predecessor Phillips Petroleum Company, Phillips 66 began trading on the New York Stock Exchange on May 1, 2012, under the ticker PSX. The company is engaged in producing natural gas liquids (NGL) and petrochemicals.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ptt//file/ptt.svg</url><title>PTT Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">PTT</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ptt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ptt/</guid><description turbo="true"> PTT Public Company Limited or simply PTT (Thai: ปตท) is a Thai state-owned SET-listed oil and gas company. Formerly known as the Petroleum Authority of Thailand, it owns extensive submarine gas pipelines in the Gulf of Thailand, a network of LPG terminals throughout the kingdom, and is involved in electricity generation, petrochemical products, oil and gas exploration and production, and gasoline retailing businesses.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ril//file/ril.svg</url><title>RIL Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">RIL</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ril/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ril/</guid><description turbo="true">Reliance Industries Limited (RIL) is an Indian multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. Reliance owns businesses across India engaged in energy, petrochemicals, textiles, natural resources, retail, and telecommunications. Reliance is one of the most profitable companies in India, the largest publicly traded company in India by market capitalization, and the largest company in India as measured by revenue after recently surpassing the government-controlled Indian Oil Corporation. On 18 October 2007, Reliance Industries became the first Indian company to breach $100 billion market capitalization.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/rosneft//file/rosneft.svg</url><title>Rosneft Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Rosneft</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/rosneft/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rosneft/</guid><description turbo="true">PJSC Rosneft Oil Company (Russian: Росне́фть, tr. Rosnéft&amp;rsquo;, IPA: stylized as ROSNEFT) is a Russian integrated energy company headquartered in the Russian capital of Moscow. It is specializing on exploration, extraction, production, refinement, transport, and sale of petroleum, natural gas, and petroleum products. The company is controlled by the Russian government through the Rosneftegaz holding company. Its name is a portmanteau of the Russian words Rossiyskaya neft&amp;rsquo; (Russian: Российская нефть - Russian oil).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach//file/sonatrach.svg</url><title>Sonatrach Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sonatrach</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach/</guid><description turbo="true"> Sonatrach (Arabic:سوناطراك) (Société Nationale pour la Recherche, la Production, le Transport, la Transformation, et la Commercialisation des Hydrocarbures) is an Algerian government-owned company formed to explore the hydrocarbon resources of the country. It has some concessions in Libya, Mauritania, Peru, Yemen and Venezuela. Its diversified activities cover all aspects of production: exploration, extraction, transport, and refining. It has diversified into petrochemistry and the desalination of seawater.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa//file/total-sa.svg</url><title>Total SA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Total SA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/total-sa/</guid><description turbo="true"> Total S.A. is a French multinational integrated oil and gas company founded in 1924 and one of the seven &amp;ldquo;Supermajor&amp;rdquo; oil companies in the world. Its businesses cover the entire oil and gas chain, from crude oil and natural gas exploration and production to power generation, transportation, refining, petroleum product marketing, and international crude oil and product trading. Total is also a large scale chemicals manufacturer.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/valero//file/valero.svg</url><title>Valero Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Valero</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/valero/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/valero/</guid><description turbo="true">Valero Energy Corporation is a Fortune 500 international manufacturer and marketer of transportation fuels, other petrochemical products, and power. It is headquartered in San Antonio, Texas, United States. Throughout the United States and Canada, the company owns and operates 15 refineries, and one in Wales, with a combined throughput capacity of approximately 3 million barrels (480,000 m3) per day, 11 ethanol plants with a combined production capacity of 1.2 billion US gallons (4,500,000 m3) per year, and a 50-megawatt wind farm.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel//file/enel.svg</url><title>Enel Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Enel</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/enel/</guid><description turbo="true"> Enel S.p.A., or the Enel Group, is an Italian multinational energy company that is active in the sectors of electricity generation and distribution, as well as in the distribution of natural gas.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/shell//file/shell.svg</url><title>Shell Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Shell</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/shell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shell/</guid><description turbo="true">Shell Oil Company is the United States-based wholly owned subsidiary of Royal Dutch Shell, transnational corporation &amp;ldquo;oil major&amp;rdquo; of Anglo-Dutch origins, which is amongst the largest oil companies in the world. Approximately 22,000 Shell employees are based in the U.S. The U.S. headquarters are in Houston, Texas. The current president is Bruce Culpepper, a graduate of the University of Alabama. Shell Oil Company, including its consolidated companies and its share in equity companies, is one of America&amp;rsquo;s largest oil and natural gas producers, natural gas marketers, gasoline marketers and petrochemical manufacturers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc//file/technipfmc.svg</url><title>TechnipFMC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">TechnipFMC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</guid><description turbo="true"> TechnipFMC plc is a UK-based company that provides complete project life cycle services (conception, feasibility study, front end engineering, detailed engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning, test runs, maintenance &amp;amp; decommissioning) for the energy industry. TechnipFMC was ranked 23rd among world&amp;rsquo;s Top 225 International Design Firms in the year 2017 by Engineering News-Record.
Source Source</description></item></channel></rss>