<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retailer on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/retailer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retailer on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/retailer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BJs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</guid>
      <description> BJ&amp;rsquo;s Wholesale Club Holdings, Inc., commonly referred as BJ&amp;rsquo;s, is an American membership-only warehouse club chain operating on the East Coast of the United States and the state of Ohio.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costco</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/costco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/costco/</guid>
      <description>Costco Wholesale Corporation, doing business as Costco, is an American multinational corporation which operates a chain of membership-only warehouse clubs. As of 2015, Costco was the second largest retailer in the world after Walmart, and as of 2016, Costco was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer of choice and prime beef, organic foods, rotisserie chicken, and wine. Costco is ranked #15 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isetan Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/isetan-mitsukoshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/isetan-mitsukoshi/</guid>
      <description> Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings Ltd. is a solely owned holding company of the Mitsukoshi and Isetan department stores as the wholly owned subsidiaries.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Knowhow</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/team-knowhow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/team-knowhow/</guid>
      <description> We believe everyone has the right to expert help with all technology. That’s why, whatever it is and wherever you bought it, we’ll help you get more from the kit that matters most to you.
 When you’re looking for something new, our nationwide team of in-store experts offers friendly, impartial advice – and we’ll help you get it home and set it up with no fuss.
Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</guid>
      <description> Home Depot is an American home improvement supplies retailing company that sells tools, construction products, and services. The company is headquartered at the Atlanta Store Support Center in unincorporated Cobb County, Georgia (with an Atlanta mailing address).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leroy-Merlin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</guid>
      <description> Leroy Merlin (French: [ləʁwa mɛʁlɛ̃]) is a French headquartered home improvement and gardening Retail serving several countries in Europe, Asia, South America, and Africa.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toys R Us</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toys-r-us/</guid>
      <description> Toys &amp;ldquo;R&amp;rdquo; Us is an international toy, clothing, video game, and baby product Retail owned by Tru Kids, Inc. (d.b.a. Tru Kids Brands) and various others. It was founded in April 1948, with its headquarters located in Wayne, New Jersey, in the New York metropolitan area.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7-eleven</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</guid>
      <description>7-Eleven Inc. is a Japanese-owned American international chain of convenience stores, headquartered in Dallas, Texas. The chain was founded in 1927 as Tote&amp;rsquo;m Stores until it was renamed in 1946. Its parent company since 2005, Seven-Eleven Japan Co., Ltd., operates, franchises, and licenses 68,236 stores in 17 countries as of June 2019. Seven-Eleven Japan is headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo and held by Seven &amp;amp; I Holdings Co., Ltd.. The most recent franchise agreement gives up to 59% of a franchise&amp;rsquo;s gross profit to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-buy/</guid>
      <description> Best Buy Co., Inc. is an American multinational consumer electronics Retail headquartered in Richfield, Minnesota. It was originally founded by Richard M. Schulze and James Wheeler in 1966 as an audio specialty store called Sound of Music. In 1983, it was re-branded under its current name with an emphasis placed on consumer electronics.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gap/</guid>
      <description>Gap was founded in 1969 by Donald Fisher and Doris F. Fisher and is headquartered in San Francisco, California. The company operates six primary divisions: Gap (the namesake banner), Banana Republic, Old Navy, Intermix, Hill City, and Athleta . Gap Inc. is the largest specialty Retail in the United States, and is 3rd in total international locations, behind Inditex Group and H&amp;amp;M. As of September 2008, the company has approximately 135,000 employees and operates 3,727 stores worldwide, of which 2,406 are located in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>H&amp;M</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</guid>
      <description>Hennes &amp;amp; Mauritz AB is a Swedish multinational clothing-retail company known for its fast-fashion clothing for men, women, teenagers and children. H&amp;amp;M and its associated companies operate in 62 countries with over 4,500 stores and as of 2015 employed around 132,000 people. It is the second-largest global clothing Retail, just behind Spain-based Inditex (parent company of Zara). The company has a significant online presence, with online shopping available in 33 countries:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</guid>
      <description> Hermès International S.A., or simply Hermès is a French high fashion luxury goods manufacturer established in 1837. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. Its logo, since the 1950s, is of a Duc carriage with horse. Nadège Vanhee-Cybulski is the current creative director.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IKEA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</guid>
      <description>IKEA is a Swedish-founded multinational group that designs and sells ready-to-assemble furniture, kitchen appliances and home products, among other useful goods and occasionally home services. It has been the world&amp;rsquo;s largest furniture Retail since at least 2008. It was founded in Sweden in 1943 by 17-year-old carpenter Ingvar Kamprad, who was listed by Forbes in 2015 as one of the ten richest people in the world, worth more than $40 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JC Penney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jc-penney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jc-penney/</guid>
      <description> J. C. Penney Company, is an American department store chain with 864 locations in 49 U.S. states and Puerto Rico. In addition to selling conventional merchandise, J. C. Penney stores often house several leased departments such as Sephora, Seattle&amp;rsquo;s Best Coffee, salons, auto centers, optical centers, portrait studios, and jewelry repair.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MUJI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/muji/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/muji/</guid>
      <description> Muji is a Japanese retail company which sells a wide variety of household and consumer goods.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staples</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/staples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/staples/</guid>
      <description>Staples Inc. is a Massachusetts-based retail company. It is primarily involved in the sale of office supplies and related products, via retail channels and business-to-business (B2B)-oriented delivery operations.
 Source The new logo takes the old staple, opens it up, and turns into a table, or at least that’s my interpretation based on the chair graphic used in multiple other places.
Still, with Staples placing more emphasis on its B2B operation, the redesign will have its biggest impact there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniqlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniqlo/</guid>
      <description> Uniqlo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese casual wear designer, manufacturer and Retail. The company is a wholly owned subsidiary of Fast Retailing Co., Ltd. The company operates in Japan and several other countries.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zara</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</guid>
      <description>Zara SA is a Spanish fast fashion (clothing and accessories) Retail based in Arteixo (A Coruña) in Galicia. The company was founded in 1975 by Amancio Ortega and Rosalía Mera. It is the main brand of the Inditex group, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel Retail. The fashion group also owns brands such as Massimo Dutti, Pull&amp;amp;Bear, Bershka, Stradivarius, Oysho, Zara Home, and Uterqüe. Zara as of 2017 manages up to 20 clothing collections a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zuca</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zuca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 22:43:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zuca/</guid>
      <description>About Zuca  ZÜCA has been on a roll since 2004, making lives better—and making people smile—with our patented, super-durable and versatile, fashionable carry–all bags. We have revolutionized how people transport their belongings by helping them get around in a healthy way. Kids can transport all of their books without straining their backs, and they can grab a seat anywhere. Professionals can organize and protect their tools and samples on the go—and look totally put together for every client meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walmart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</guid>
      <description>Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets, discount department stores, and grocery stores.
 Source The Walmart History  Walmart as we know it today evolved from Sam Walton’s goals for great value and great customer service. “Mr. Sam,” as he was known, believed in leadership through service. This belief that true leadership depends on willing service was the principle on which Walmart was built, and drove the decisions the company has made for the past 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</guid>
      <description>Target Corporation is the eighth-largest Retail in the United States, and is a component of the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index. Founded by George Dayton and headquartered in Minneapolis, the company was originally named Goodfellow Dry Goods in June 1902 before being renamed the Dayton&amp;rsquo;s Dry Goods Company in 1903 and later the Dayton Company in 1910. The first Target store opened in Roseville, Minnesota in 1962 while the parent company was renamed the Dayton Corporation in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>