<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retailer on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/retailer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retailer on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/retailer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggen</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/haggen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/haggen/</guid>
      <description>Haggen Food &amp;amp; Pharmacy is a grocery retailer in Washington state.
 Haggen is headquartered in Bellingham, Washington, where it started in 1933 when Ben Haggen, Dorothy Haggen, and Doug Clark opened the first store on Bay Street in Bellingham. For many years, Haggen was the largest independent grocery retailer in the Pacific Northwest, with locations in Washington and Oregon. From 1982 through 2014, Haggen also operated Top Food &amp;amp; Drug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instacart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/instacart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/instacart/</guid>
      <description>Instacart, headquartered in San Francisco, operates a grocery delivery and pick-up service in the United States and Canada. The company offers service via a website and mobile app in 5,500 cities in all 50 U.S. states and Canadian provinces in partnership with over 350 retailers that have more than 25,000 grocery stores including Albertsons, Aldi, Costco, CVS Health, Eataly, H-E-B, Kroger, Loblaw Companies, Petco, Publix, Safeway Inc., Sam&amp;rsquo;s Club, Sprouts Farmers Market, Target Corporation, Total Wine &amp;amp; More, and Wegmans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel-Osco</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jewel-osco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jewel-osco/</guid>
      <description>Jewel-Osco is a supermarket chain in the Greater Chicago area, headquartered in Itasca, a western suburb. Jewel-Osco currently has 188 stores across northern, central, and western Illinois; eastern Iowa; and portions of northwest Indiana. Jewel-Osco and Jewel are currently wholly owned subsidiaries of Boise, Idaho-based Albertsons. The company originally started as a door-to-door coffee delivery service before it expanded into delivering non-perishable groceries and later into grocery stores, and supermarkets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kroger</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kroger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kroger/</guid>
      <description>The Kroger Company, or simply Kroger, is an American retail company founded by Bernard Kroger in 1883 in Cincinnati, Ohio. It is the United States&amp;rsquo; largest supermarket by revenue ($121.16 billion for fiscal year 2019), the second-largest general retailer (behind Walmart). Kroger is also the fifth-largest retailer in the world and the fourth largest American-owned private employer in the United States. Kroger is ranked #20 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lacoste</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lacoste/</guid>
      <description>Lacoste is a French company, founded in 1933 by tennis player René Lacoste and André Gillier. It sells clothing, footwear, sportswear, eyewear, leather goods, perfume, towels and watches. The company can be recognised by its green crocodile logo. René Lacoste, the company&amp;rsquo;s founder, was nicknamed &amp;ldquo;the Crocodile&amp;rdquo; by fans because of his tenacity on the tennis court. In November 2012 Lacoste was bought outright by Swiss family-held group Maus Frères.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loblaws</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/loblaws/</guid>
      <description>Loblaws Inc. is a Canadian supermarket chain with stores located in the provinces of British Columbia, Saskatchewan, Alberta, Ontario and Quebec. Headquartered in Brampton, Ontario, Loblaws is a subsidiary of Loblaw Companies Limited, Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest food distributor.
 Source About Loblaws Since the beginning, Loblaws love of food has driven us to find innovative ways to bring customers closer to their favourite products. In 1919, founders of the first Loblaw Groceterias were told their self-serve, cash-and-carry model would never work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lowe’s</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lowes/</guid>
      <description>Lowe&amp;rsquo;s Companies, Inc. (/loʊz/), doing business as Lowe&amp;rsquo;s, is an American retail company specializing in home improvement. Headquartered in Mooresville, North Carolina, the company operates a chain of retail stores in the United States and Canada. As of November 2018, Lowe&amp;rsquo;s and its related businesses operate 2,015 home improvement and hardware stores in North America.
 Lowe&amp;rsquo;s is the second-largest hardware chain in the United States behind rival The Home Depot and ahead of Menards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucky</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucky/</guid>
      <description>Lucky Stores is an American supermarket chain founded in San Leandro, California, in 1935. Lucky is currently operated by Save Mart Supermarkets in Northern California.
 In 1998, Lucky&amp;rsquo;s parent company, American Stores, was taken over by Albertsons, and by 1999 the Lucky brand had disappeared. On January 23, 2006, SuperValu, CVS Pharmacy and an investment group led by Cerberus Capital Management announced they had agreed to acquire Albertsons for $17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/michelin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/michelin/</guid>
      <description>Michelin (/ˈmɪʃəlɪn, -læ̃/; full name: Compagnie Générale des Établissements Michelin SCA) is a French multinational tyre manufacturer based in Clermont-Ferrand in the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes région of France. It is the second largest tyre manufacturer in the world after Bridgestone and larger than both Goodyear and Continental. In addition to the Michelin brand, it also owns the Kléber tyres company, Uniroyal-Goodrich Tire Company, SASCAR, Bookatable and Camso brands. Michelin is also notable for its Red and Green travel guides, its roadmaps, the Michelin stars that the Red Guide awards to restaurants for their cooking, and for its company mascot Bibendum, colloquially known as the Michelin Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget Markets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nugget-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nugget-markets/</guid>
      <description>Nugget Markets is a family-owned upscale supermarket chain operating within the greater Sacramento metropolitan area. It is headquartered in Woodland, California. As of October 2019, the company operates twelve of its flagship Nugget Markets-brand stores, as well as Sonoma Market in Sonoma, Fork Lift by Nugget Markets in Cameron Park and Food 4 Less in Woodland.
 Source Nugget Markets Nugget Markets is a family-owned-and-operated company based in Northern California dedicated to creating an extraordinary grocery experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/publix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/publix/</guid>
      <description>Publix Super Markets, Inc., commonly known as Publix, is an employee-owned, American supermarket chain headquartered in Lakeland, Florida. Founded in 1930 by George W. Jenkins, Publix is a private corporation that is wholly owned by present and past employees and members of the Jenkins family. Publix operates throughout the Southeastern United States, with locations in Florida (809), Georgia (188), Alabama (77), South Carolina (63), Tennessee (46), North Carolina (46), and Virginia (15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roche Bros</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/roche-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/roche-bros/</guid>
      <description>Roche Bros. Supermarkets, Inc. is a chain of supermarkets based in Wellesley, Massachusetts. The company&amp;rsquo;s stores are primarily located in the Boston Metro Area. Roche Bros. also operates the supermarket chain Sudbury Farms.
 A third banner, Brothers Marketplace, primarily the next-generation concept of the brothers Ed and Rick Roche, has five locations. The first one was opened in Weston, Massachusetts and a second in Medfield, Massachusetts, both in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/safeway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/safeway/</guid>
      <description>Safeway is an American supermarket chain founded in April 1915 in American Falls, Idaho by Marion Barton Skaggs. It is a subsidiary of Albertsons after being acquired by private equity investors led by Cerberus Capital Management in January 2015. Safeway&amp;rsquo;s primary base of operations is in the west [1] with some stores located in the Mid-Atlantic region of the Eastern Seaboard. The subsidiary is headquartered in Pleasanton, California, with its parent company headquartered in Boise, Idaho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shopify/</guid>
      <description>Shopify Inc. is a Canadian multinational e-commerce company headquartered in Ottawa, Ontario. It is also the name of its proprietary e-commerce platform for online stores and retail point-of-sale systems. Shopify offers online retailers a suite of services &amp;ldquo;including payments, marketing, shipping and customer engagement tools to simplify the process of running an online store for small merchants.&amp;rdquo;
 The company reported that it had more than 1,000,000 businesses in approximately 175 countries using its platform as of June 2019, with total gross merchandise volume exceeding $41.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACME</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/acme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/acme/</guid>
      <description> Acme Markets Inc. is a supermarket chain operating 164 stores throughout Connecticut, Delaware, Maryland, New Jersey, New York, and Pennsylvania and, as of 1999, is a subsidiary of Albertsons, and part of its presence in the Northeast. It is headquartered in East Whiteland Township, Pennsylvania, near Malvern, a Philadelphia suburb.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advance Auto Parts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/advance-auto-parts/</guid>
      <description>Advance Auto Parts, Inc. (Advance) is an American automotive aftermarket parts provider. Headquartered in Raleigh, North Carolina, it serves both professional installer and do-it-yourself (DIY) customers. As of July 13, 2019, Advance operated 4,912 stores and 150 Worldpac branches in the United States and Canada. The Company also serves 1,250 independently owned Carquest branded stores across these locations in addition to Mexico, the Bahamas, Turks and Caicos and British Virgin Islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albertsons</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/albertsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/albertsons/</guid>
      <description>Albertsons Companies, Inc. is an American grocery company founded and headquartered in Boise, Idaho. It is privately owned and operated by investors, including Cerberus Capital Management.
 With 2,260 stores as of the third quarter of fiscal 2019 and 267,000 employees as of fiscal 2018, the company is the second-largest supermarket chain in North America after Kroger, which has 2,758 stores. Albertsons ranked 53rd in the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fanatics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fanatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fanatics/</guid>
      <description>Fanatics, Inc. is an American online retailer of licensed sportswear, sports equipment, and merchandise, formed in 1995 and headquartered in Jacksonville, Florida. Fanatics offers product via its Fanatics and FansEdge brands, as well as sports collectibles and memorabilia through Fanatics Authentic and SportsMemorabilia.com. Fanatics also currently operates the e-commerce websites of major professional sports leagues (MLB, NASCAR, NBA, NFL, NHL, PGA, MLS, and UFC), major media brands (CBS Sports, FOX Sports, and NBC Sports), and over 150 collegiate and professional team properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lawson</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lawson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lawson/</guid>
      <description> Lawson, Inc. (株式会社ローソン Kabushiki Kaisha Rōson, TYO: 2651) is a convenience store franchise chain in Japan. The store originated in Cuyahoga Falls, Ohio, but exists today as a Japanese company.
 The Japanese company has its headquarters in East Tower of Gate City Ohsaki in Ōsaki, Shinagawa, Tokyo.
Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marui</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marui/</guid>
      <description> Marui Co., Ltd. (株式会社丸井, Kabushiki-gaisha Marui) (TYO: 8252) is a Japanese retail company which operates a chain of department stores in Tokyo as well in other major Japanese cities. They are best known for their women&amp;rsquo;s fashion and accessories, which are aimed at the 25–35 age range.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macys</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/macys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/macys/</guid>
      <description>Macy&amp;rsquo;s (originally R. H. Macy &amp;amp; Co., stylized as macy*s) is an American department store chain founded in 1858 by Rowland Hussey Macy. It became a division of the Cincinnati-based Federated Department Stores in 1994 (later renamed as Macy&amp;rsquo;s, Inc. in 2007), as a Bloomingdale&amp;rsquo;s department store chain affiliate. As of 2015, Macy&amp;rsquo;s was the largest U.S. department store company by retail sales. As of February 2019, there were 584 full-line stores with the Macy&amp;rsquo;s nameplate in operation throughout the United States, Puerto Rico, and Guam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</guid>
      <description> BJ&amp;rsquo;s Wholesale Club Holdings, Inc., commonly referred as BJ&amp;rsquo;s, is an American membership-only warehouse club chain operating on the East Coast of the United States and the state of Ohio.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costco</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/costco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/costco/</guid>
      <description>Costco Wholesale Corporation, doing business as Costco, is an American multinational corporation which operates a chain of membership-only warehouse clubs. As of 2015, Costco was the second largest retailer in the world after Walmart, and as of 2016, Costco was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer of choice and prime beef, organic foods, rotisserie chicken, and wine. Costco is ranked #15 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinsegae</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</guid>
      <description> Shinsegae (Korean: 신세계, KRX: 004170) is a South Korean department store franchise, along with several other businesses, headquartered in Seoul, South Korea. The name Shinsegae literally means &amp;ldquo;New World&amp;rdquo; in Korean. Its flagship store in Centum City, Busan, was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest department store at 3,163,000 square feet (293,900 m2), surpassing Macy&amp;rsquo;s flagship Herald Square in New York City in 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isetan Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/isetan-mitsukoshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/isetan-mitsukoshi/</guid>
      <description> Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings Ltd. is a solely owned holding company of the Mitsukoshi and Isetan department stores as the wholly owned subsidiaries.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Knowhow</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/team-knowhow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/team-knowhow/</guid>
      <description>Team Knowhow believe everyone has the right to expert help with all technology. That’s why, whatever it is and wherever you bought it, we’ll help you get more from the kit that matters most to you.
 When you’re looking for something new, Team Knowhow nationwide team of in-store experts offers friendly, impartial advice – and Team Knowhow’ll help you get it home and set it up with no fuss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/home-depot/</guid>
      <description> Home Depot is an American home improvement supplies retailing company that sells tools, construction products, and services. The company is headquartered at the Atlanta Store Support Center in unincorporated Cobb County, Georgia (with an Atlanta mailing address).
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leroy-Merlin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/leroy-merlin/</guid>
      <description> Leroy Merlin (French: [ləʁwa mɛʁlɛ̃]) is a French headquartered home improvement and gardening Retail serving several countries in Europe, Asia, South America, and Africa.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7-eleven</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/7-eleven/</guid>
      <description>7-Eleven Inc. is a Japanese-owned American international chain of convenience stores, headquartered in Dallas, Texas. The chain was founded in 1927 as Tote&amp;rsquo;m Stores until it was renamed in 1946. Its parent company since 2005, Seven-Eleven Japan Co., Ltd., operates, franchises, and licenses 68,236 stores in 17 countries as of June 2019. Seven-Eleven Japan is headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo and held by Seven &amp;amp; I Holdings Co., Ltd.. The most recent franchise agreement gives up to 59% of a franchise&amp;rsquo;s gross profit to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-buy/</guid>
      <description> Best Buy Co., Inc. is an American multinational consumer electronics Retail headquartered in Richfield, Minnesota. It was originally founded by Richard M. Schulze and James Wheeler in 1966 as an audio specialty store called Sound of Music. In 1983, it was re-branded under its current name with an emphasis placed on consumer electronics.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gap/</guid>
      <description>Gap was founded in 1969 by Donald Fisher and Doris F. Fisher and is headquartered in San Francisco, California. The company operates six primary divisions: Gap (the namesake banner), Banana Republic, Old Navy, Intermix, Hill City, and Athleta . Gap Inc. is the largest specialty Retail in the United States, and is 3rd in total international locations, behind Inditex Group and H&amp;amp;M. As of September 2008, the company has approximately 135,000 employees and operates 3,727 stores worldwide, of which 2,406 are located in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>H&amp;M</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</guid>
      <description>Hennes &amp;amp; Mauritz AB is a Swedish multinational clothing-retail company known for its fast-fashion clothing for men, women, teenagers and children. H&amp;amp;M and its associated companies operate in 62 countries with over 4,500 stores and as of 2015 employed around 132,000 people. It is the second-largest global clothing Retail, just behind Spain-based Inditex (parent company of Zara). The company has a significant online presence, with online shopping available in 33 countries:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hermes/</guid>
      <description> Hermès International S.A., or simply Hermès is a French high fashion luxury goods manufacturer established in 1837. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. Its logo, since the 1950s, is of a Duc carriage with horse. Nadège Vanhee-Cybulski is the current creative director.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JC Penney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jc-penney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jc-penney/</guid>
      <description> J. C. Penney Company, is an American department store chain with 864 locations in 49 U.S. states and Puerto Rico. In addition to selling conventional merchandise, J. C. Penney stores often house several leased departments such as Sephora, Seattle&amp;rsquo;s Best Coffee, salons, auto centers, optical centers, portrait studios, and jewelry repair.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MUJI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/muji/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/muji/</guid>
      <description> Muji is a Japanese retail company which sells a wide variety of household and consumer goods.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staples</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/staples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/staples/</guid>
      <description>Staples Inc. is a Massachusetts-based retail company. It is primarily involved in the sale of office supplies and related products, via retail channels and business-to-business (B2B)-oriented delivery operations.
 Source The new logo takes the old staple, opens it up, and turns into a table, or at least that’s my interpretation based on the chair graphic used in multiple other places.
Still, with Staples placing more emphasis on its B2B operation, the redesign will have its biggest impact there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniqlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniqlo/</guid>
      <description> Uniqlo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese casual wear designer, manufacturer and Retail. The company is a wholly owned subsidiary of Fast Retailing Co., Ltd. The company operates in Japan and several other countries.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zara</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zara/</guid>
      <description>Zara SA is a Spanish fast fashion (clothing and accessories) Retail based in Arteixo (A Coruña) in Galicia. The company was founded in 1975 by Amancio Ortega and Rosalía Mera. It is the main brand of the Inditex group, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel Retail. The fashion group also owns brands such as Massimo Dutti, Pull&amp;amp;Bear, Bershka, Stradivarius, Oysho, Zara Home, and Uterqüe. Zara as of 2017 manages up to 20 clothing collections a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zuca</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/zuca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 22:43:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zuca/</guid>
      <description>About Zuca  ZÜCA has been on a roll since 2004, making lives better—and making people smile—with Zuca patented, super-durable and versatile, fashionable carry–all bags. Zuca have revolutionized how people transport their belongings by helping them get around in a healthy way. Kids can transport all of their books without straining their backs, and they can grab a seat anywhere. Professionals can organize and protect their tools and samples on the go—and look totally put together for every client meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walmart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</guid>
      <description>Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets, discount department stores, and grocery stores.
 Source The Walmart History  Walmart as Walmart know it today evolved from Sam Walton’s goals for great value and great customer service. “Mr. Sam,” as he was known, believed in leadership through service. This belief that true leadership depends on willing service was the principle on which Walmart was built, and drove the decisions the company has made for the past 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/target/</guid>
      <description>Target Corporation is the eighth-largest Retail in the United States, and is a component of the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index. Founded by George Dayton and headquartered in Minneapolis, the company was originally named Goodfellow Dry Goods in June 1902 before being renamed the Dayton&amp;rsquo;s Dry Goods Company in 1903 and later the Dayton Company in 1910. The first Target store opened in Roseville, Minnesota in 1962 while the parent company was renamed the Dayton Corporation in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>