<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>United Kingdom on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/united-kingdom/</link><description>Recent content in United Kingdom on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/united-kingdom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JCB</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jcb/</guid><description>JCB is a manufacturer of equipment for construction, agriculture, waste handling, and demolition, based in Rocester, Staffordshire, England. It produces over 300 types of machines, including diggers (backhoes), excavators, tractors, and diesel engines, across 22 factories spanning Asia, Europe, North America, and South America; its products are sold in over 150 countries.
Joseph Cyril Bamford Excavators Ltd. was founded in 1945 by Joseph Cyril Bamford and continues to be owned by the Bamford family.</description></item><item><title>Tesco</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesco/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tesco/</guid><description>Tesco plc (/ˈtɛs.koʊ/), trading as Tesco, is a British multinational groceries and general merchandise retailer with headquarters in Welwyn Garden City, Hertfordshire, England, United Kingdom. It is the third-largest retailer in the world measured by gross revenues and the ninth-largest in the world measured by revenues. It has shops in seven countries across Asia and Europe, and is the market leader of groceries in the UK (where it has a market share of around 28.</description></item><item><title>Deloitte</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deloitte/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deloitte/</guid><description>Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu Limited /dəˈlɔɪt ˈtuːʃ toʊˈmɑːtsuː/, commonly referred to as Deloitte, is a multinational professional services network. Deloitte is one of the &amp;ldquo;Big Four&amp;rdquo; accounting organizations and the largest professional services network in the world by revenue and number of professionals with headquarters in London, United Kingdom.
Source About Deloitte “Deloitte” is the brand under which approximately 286,000 dedicated professionals in independent firms throughout the world collaborate to provide audit &amp;amp; assurance, consulting, financial advisory, risk advisory, tax and related services to select clients.</description></item><item><title>London Underground</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/london-underground/</guid><description>The London Underground (also known simply as the Underground, or by its nickname the Tube) is a public rapid transit system serving London region, England and some parts of the adjacent counties of Buckinghamshire, Essex and Hertfordshire in the United Kingdom.
The Underground has its origins in the Metropolitan Railway, the world&amp;rsquo;s first underground passenger railway. Opened in January 1863, it is now part of the Circle, Hammersmith &amp;amp; City and Metropolitan lines; the first line to operate underground electric traction trains, the City &amp;amp; South London Railway in 1890, is now part of the Northern line.</description></item><item><title>Reuters</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters/</guid><description>Reuters (About this soundpronunciation ; /ˈrɔɪtərz/) is an international news organization owned by Thomson Reuters. Until 2008, the Reuters news agency formed part of an independent company, Reuters Group plc, which was also a provider of financial market data. Since the acquisition of Reuters Group by the Thomson Corporation in 2008, the Reuters news agency has been a part of Thomson Reuters, making up the media division. It was established in 1851.</description></item><item><title>Sophos</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sophos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sophos/</guid><description>Sophos Group plc is a British security software and hardware company. Sophos develops products for communication endpoint, encryption, network security, email security, mobile security and unified threat management. Sophos is primarily focused on providing security software to the mid market and pragmatic enterprise from 100- to 5,000-seat organizations. While not a primary focus, Sophos also protects home users, through free and paid antivirus solutions (Sophos Home/Home Premium) intended to demonstrate product functionality.</description></item><item><title>BBC</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</guid><description>The British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) is a British public service broadcaster. Its headquarters are at Broadcasting House in Westminster, London. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest national broadcaster, and the largest broadcaster in the world by number of employees. It employs over 22,000 staff in total, more than 16,000 of whom are in public sector broadcasting. The total number of staff is 35,402 when part-time, flexible, and fixed-contract staff are included.</description></item><item><title>Lotus</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus/</guid><description>Lotus Cars Limited is a British automotive company that manufactures sports cars and racing cars with headquarters in Hethel, England. Lotus cars include the Esprit, Elan, Europa, Elise, Exige, Evora and Evija sports cars and it had motor racing success with Team Lotus in Formula One. Lotus Cars are based at the former site of RAF Hethel, a World War II airfield in Norfolk. The company designs and builds race and production automobiles of light weight and fine handling characteristics.</description></item><item><title>Human Appeal</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/human-appeal/</guid><description> Human Appeal is a British international development and relief charity based in Manchester. It was established in 1991. It runs targeted poverty relief programmes in emergency response and sustainable development. In the past, the charity was known as Human Appeal International but was restyled in 2018. It is now known as Human Appeal.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>Nexford</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</guid><description> Nexford University is a private for-profit online university headquartered in Washington, DC. It was founded in 2018 by Fadl Al Tarzi. The University offers programs through the process of online distance learning. Nexford is licensed to issue degrees by the Higher Education Licensure Commission (HELC) in Washington DC. Nexford is accredited by ASIC, an UK-based International accreditation agency operating in 60+ countries.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>Shelter</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shelter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shelter/</guid><description>Shelter is a registered charity that campaigns to end homelessness and bad housing in England and Scotland. It gives advice, information and advocacy to people in need, and tackles the root causes of bad housing by lobbying government and local authorities for new laws and policies to improve the lives of homeless and badly housed people. It works in partnership with Shelter Cymru in Wales and the Housing Rights Service in Northern Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Soundcraft</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft/</guid><description> Soundcraft is a British designer and importer (formerly a manufacturer) of mixing consoles and other professional audio equipment. It is a subsidiary of Harman International Industries, which is owned by South Korean company Samsung Electronics. It was founded by sound engineer Phil Dudderidge and electronics designer Graham Blyth in 1973.
Source</description></item><item><title>Teach First</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/teach-first/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/teach-first/</guid><description> Teach First is a social enterprise registered as a charity which aims to address educational disadvantage in England and Wales. Teach First coordinates an employment-based teaching training programme whereby participants achieve Qualified Teacher Status through the participation in a two-year training programme that involves the completion of a PGDE along with wider leadership skills training and an optional master&amp;rsquo;s degree.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>University of Cambridge</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/university-of-cambridge/</guid><description>The University of Cambridge (legally The Chancellor, Masters, and Scholars of the University of Cambridge) is a collegiate public research university in Cambridge, United Kingdom. Founded in 1209 and granted a royal charter by King Henry III in 1231, Cambridge is the second-oldest university in the English-speaking world and the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-oldest surviving university. The university grew out of an association of scholars who left the University of Oxford after a dispute with the townspeople.</description></item><item><title>Virgin Atlantic</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-atlantic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-atlantic/</guid><description>Virgin Atlantic, a trading name of Virgin Atlantic Airways Limited and Virgin Atlantic International Limited, is a British airline with its head office in Crawley, England. The airline was established in 1984 as British Atlantic Airways, and was originally planned by its co-founders Randolph Fields and Alan Hellary to fly between London and the Falkland Islands. Soon after changing the name to Virgin Atlantic Airways, Fields sold his shares in the company after disagreements with Sir Richard Branson over the management of the company.</description></item><item><title>BBC News</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</guid><description>BBC News is an operational business division of the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) responsible for the gathering and broadcasting of news and current affairs. The department is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest broadcast news organisation and generates about 120 hours of radio and television output each day, as well as online news coverage. The service maintains 50 foreign news bureaux with more than 250 correspondents around the world. Fran Unsworth has been Director of News and Current Affairs since January 2018.</description></item><item><title>BBC World News</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</guid><description>BBC World News is the BBC&amp;rsquo;s international news and current affairs television channel. It has the largest audience of any channel, with an estimated 121 million viewers weekly in 2016/2017, part of the estimated 372 million weekly audience of the BBC&amp;rsquo;s four main international news services. Launched on 11 March 1991 as BBC World Service Television outside Europe, its name was changed to BBC World on 16 January 1995 and to BBC World News on 21 April 2008.</description></item><item><title>BP</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</guid><description>BP plc (formerly The British Petroleum Company plc and BP Amoco plc) is a British multinational oil and gas company headquartered in London, United Kingdom. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s seven oil and gas &amp;ldquo;supermajors&amp;rdquo;, whose performance in 2012 made it the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth-largest oil and gas company, the sixth-largest energy company by market capitalization and the company with the world&amp;rsquo;s 12th-largest revenue (turnover). It is a vertically integrated company operating in all areas of the oil and gas industry, including exploration and production, refining, distribution and marketing, petrochemicals, power generation and trading.</description></item><item><title>British Council</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-council/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-council/</guid><description> The British Council is a British organisation specialising in international cultural and educational opportunities. It works in over 100 countries: promoting a wider knowledge of the United Kingdom and the English language; encouraging cultural, scientific, technological and educational co-operation with the United Kingdom.
Source</description></item><item><title>Diageo</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diageo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diageo/</guid><description> Diageo plc is a British multinational alcoholic beverages company, with its headquarters in London, England and offices on six continents. It was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest distiller until being overtaken by China&amp;rsquo;s Kweichow Moutai on 9 April 2017.
Source</description></item><item><title>GSK</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gsk/</guid><description> GlaxoSmithKline plc (GSK) is a British multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Brentford, London. Established in 2000 by a merger of Glaxo Wellcome and SmithKline Beecham, GSK was the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth largest pharmaceutical company as of 2015, after Pfizer, Novartis, Merck, Hoffmann-La Roche and Sanofi.
Source</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/holiday-inn/</guid><description> Holiday Inn is a British-owned American brand of hotels, and a subsidiary of InterContinental Hotels Group. Founded as a U.S. motel chain, it has grown to be one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest hotel chains, with 1,173 active hotels and over 214,000 bedrooms as of September 30, 2018. The hotel chain&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Denham, Buckinghamshire.
Source</description></item><item><title>Jardines</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jardines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jardines/</guid><description>Jardine Matheson Holdings Limited (also known as Jardines) is a British conglomerate incorporated in Bermuda and headquartered in Hong Kong, with its primary listing on the London Stock Exchange and secondary listings on the Singapore Exchange and Bermuda Stock Exchange. The majority of its business interests are in Asia, and its subsidiaries include Jardine Pacific, Jardine Motors, Jardine Lloyd Thompson, Hongkong Land, Jardine Strategic Holdings, Dairy Farm, Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group, Jardine Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage and Astra International.</description></item><item><title>Smirnoff</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smirnoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smirnoff/</guid><description>Smirnoff is a brand of vodka owned and produced by the British company Diageo. The Smirnoff brand began with a vodka distillery founded in Moscow by Pyotr Arsenievich Smirnov (1831–1898). It is now distributed in 130 countries[citation needed] and produced in several countries including Albania, Brazil, Honduras, India, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Mongolia, the Philippines, the United Kingdom and the United States[citation needed]. Smirnoff products include vodka, flavoured vodka, and malt beverages.</description></item><item><title>Vodafone</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vodafone/</guid><description> Vodafone plc /ˈvoʊdəfoʊn/ is a British multinational telecommunications conglomerate with headquarters in London and Newbury, Berkshire. It predominantly operates services in the regions of Asia, Africa, Europe, and Oceania. Among mobile operator groups globally, Vodafone ranked 4th (behind China Mobile, Bharti Airtel and Vodafone Idea) in the number of mobile customers (313 million) as of 2018
Source</description></item><item><title>BHF</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</guid><description> The British Heart Foundation (BHF) is a charity organisation in the United Kingdom. It funds research to beat heartbreak from heart and circulatory diseases and their risk factors.
Source</description></item><item><title>Boots UK</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boots-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boots-uk/</guid><description> Boots UK Ltd., trading as Boots, is a health and beauty Retail and pharmacy chain in the United Kingdom and other territories including Ireland and Thailand
Source</description></item><item><title>Burberry</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry/</guid><description> Burberry Group PLC is a British luxury fashion house headquartered in London, England. Its main fashion house focuses on and distributes trench coats (for which it is most famous), ready-to-wear outerwear, fashion accessories, fragrances, sunglasses, and cosmetics.
Source</description></item><item><title>Johnnie Walker</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/johnnie-walker/</guid><description> Johnnie Walker is a brand of Scotch whisky now owned by Diageo that originated in the Scottish town of Kilmarnock, East Ayrshire. The brand was first established by grocer John Walker. It is the most widely distributed brand of blended Scotch whisky in the world, sold in almost every country, with annual sales of the equivalent of over 223.7 million 700 ml bottles in 2016 (156.6 million litres)
Source Source</description></item><item><title>Team Knowhow</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/team-knowhow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/team-knowhow/</guid><description>Team Knowhow believe everyone has the right to expert help with all technology. That’s why, whatever it is and wherever you bought it, we’ll help you get more from the kit that matters most to you.
When you’re looking for something new, Team Knowhow nationwide team of in-store experts offers friendly, impartial advice – and Team Knowhow’ll help you get it home and set it up with no fuss.</description></item><item><title>Virgin Media</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/virgin-media/</guid><description>Virgin Media Limited is a British company which provides telephone, television and internet services in the United Kingdom. Its headquarters are in Hook, Hampshire. Since 2013, Virgin Media has been a subsidiary of Liberty Global plc, an international television and telecommunications company. The company was previously listed on the NASDAQ Stock Market and London Stock Exchange. Virgin Media is not a sister company of Virgin Mobile USA, which is owned by Sprint Corporation</description></item><item><title>Rolls-Royce</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce/</guid><description>Rolls-Royce was a British luxury car and later an aero-engine manufacturing business established in 1904 by the partnership of Charles Rolls and Henry Royce. Building on Royce&amp;rsquo;s reputation established with his cranes they quickly developed a reputation for superior engineering by manufacturing the &amp;ldquo;best car in the world&amp;rdquo;. The First World War brought them into manufacturing aero-engines. Joint development of jet engines began in 1940 and they entered production.</description></item><item><title>Rolls-Royce Motors</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rolls-royce-motors/</guid><description>Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited is a British luxury automobile maker. A wholly owned subsidiary of German group BMW, it was established in 1998 after BMW was licensed the rights to the Rolls-Royce brand name and logo from Rolls-Royce plc and acquired the rights to the Spirit of Ecstasy and Rolls-Royce grill shape trademarks from Volkswagen AG. Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited operates from purpose-built administrative and production facilities opened in 2003 across from the historic Goodwood Circuit in Goodwood, West Sussex, England, United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Marvel App</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</guid><description>Marvel is a design, prototyping an collaboration application based in London, UK.
Source</description></item><item><title>Olympics 2012 London</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2012-london/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:33:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2012-london/</guid><description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description></item><item><title>Affinity Designer</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-designer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-designer/</guid><description> Affinity Designer is a vector graphics editor developed by Serif for macOS, iOS, and Microsoft Windows. It is part of the &amp;ldquo;Affinity trinity&amp;rdquo; alongside Affinity Photo and Affinity Publisher. Affinity Designer is available for purchase directly from the company website and in the Mac App Store, iOS App Store, and the Microsoft Store.
Source</description></item><item><title>Affinity Photo</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-photo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-photo/</guid><description> Affinity Photo is a raster graphics editor developed by Serif for macOS, iOS and Windows. It is part of the &amp;ldquo;Affinity trinity&amp;rdquo; alongside Affinity Designer and Affinity Publisher. Affinity Photo is available for purchase in the Mac App Store, iOS App Store, and the Microsoft Store.
Source</description></item><item><title>Affinity Publisher</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-publisher/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/affinity-publisher/</guid><description> Affinity Publisher is a desktop publishing application developed by Serif for macOS and Microsoft Windows. It is a part of the Affinity product line along with Affinity Photo and Affinity Designer.
Source</description></item><item><title>Aston-Martin</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aston-martin/</guid><description>Aston Martin Lagonda Global Holdings plc is a British independent manufacturer of luxury sports cars and grand tourers. It was founded in 1913 by Lionel Martin and Robert Bamford. Steered from 1947 by David Brown, it became associated with expensive grand touring cars in the 1950s and 1960s, and with the fictional character James Bond following his use of a DB5 model in the 1964 film Goldfinger. Their sports cars are regarded as a British cultural icon.</description></item><item><title>Bentley</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</guid><description> Bentley Motors Limited is a British manufacturer and marketer of luxury cars and SUVs—and a subsidiary of the Volkswagen Group since 1998.
Source</description></item><item><title>British Airways</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-airways/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-airways/</guid><description>British Airways (BA) is the flag carrier airline of the United Kingdom, headquartered at Waterside, Harmondsworth. It is the second largest airline in the United Kingdom, based on fleet size and passengers carried, behind easyJet. The airline is based in Waterside near its main hub at London Heathrow Airport. In January 2011 BA merged with Iberia, creating the International Airlines Group (IAG), a holding company registered in Madrid, Spain. IAG is the world&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline group in terms of annual revenue and the second-largest in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Hummer</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</guid><description> Hummer was a brand of trucks and SUVs, first marketed in 1992 when AM General began selling a civilian version of the M998 Humvee. In 1998, General Motors (GM) purchased the brand name from AM General and marketed three vehicles: the original Hummer H1, based on the military Humvee, as well as the new H2 and H3 models that were based on smaller, civilian-market GM platforms.
Source</description></item><item><title>Jaguar</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jaguar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jaguar/</guid><description> Jaguar is the luxury vehicle brand of Jaguar Land Rover, a British multinational car manufacturer with its headquarters in Whitley, Coventry, England. Jaguar Cars was the company that was responsible for the production of Jaguar cars until its operations were fully merged with those of Land Rover to form Jaguar Land Rover on 1 January 2013.
Source</description></item><item><title>Mini</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mini/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mini/</guid><description>Mini (stylised as MINI) is a British automotive marque, owned by BMW since 2000, and used by them for a range of small cars. The word Mini has been used in car model names since 1959, and in 1969 it became a marque in its own right when the name &amp;ldquo;Mini&amp;rdquo; replaced the separate &amp;ldquo;Austin Mini&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Morris Mini&amp;rdquo; car model names. BMW acquired the marque in 1994 when it bought Rover Group (formerly British Leyland), which owned Mini, among other brands.</description></item><item><title>TechnipFMC</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</guid><description> TechnipFMC plc is a UK-based company that provides complete project life cycle services (conception, feasibility study, front end engineering, detailed engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning, test runs, maintenance &amp;amp; decommissioning) for the energy industry. TechnipFMC was ranked 23rd among world&amp;rsquo;s Top 225 International Design Firms in the year 2017 by Engineering News-Record.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>YMCA</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ymca/</guid><description> YMCA, sometimes regionally called the Y, is a worldwide organisation based in Geneva, Switzerland, with more than 64 million beneficiaries from 120 national associations. It was founded on 6 June 1844 by Sir George Williams in London, originally as the Young Men&amp;rsquo;s Christian Association and aims to put Christian principles into practice by developing a healthy &amp;ldquo;body, mind, and spirit&amp;rdquo;.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>Penguin Books</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:31:07 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</guid><description>Penguin Books Logo History Designed by Edward Young In 1935, Edward Young designed Penguin’s famous “dignified but flippant” logo and the colour scheme for its book covers.
It started with the simple logo and name, suggested, allegedly, by a typist who was earwigging the board meeting. Allen had already hit upon the idea of an animal logo, inspired by the template offered by the contemporary publishing house The Albatross Library.</description></item><item><title>UBS</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:37 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>RBS Group</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:57 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hsbc Bank</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</guid><description>About HSBC Bank The HSBC brand is recognised worldwide. Hsbc Bank latest advertising illustrates Hsbc Bank role in helping people, businesses and communities to thrive.
HSBC is one of the largest banking and financial services organisations in the world, with operations in 66 countries and territories. Hsbc Bank aim to be where the growth is, enabling businesses to thrive and economies to prosper, and, ultimately, helping people to fulfil their hopes and realise their ambitions.</description></item><item><title>Barclays</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:42:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>