<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>United Kingdom on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/united-kingdom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in United Kingdom on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/united-kingdom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel App</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 18:03:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-app/</guid>
      <description>Marvel is a design, prototyping an collaboration application based in London, UK.
 Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2012 London</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2012-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:33:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2012-london/</guid>
      <description>About Olympic Games The Olympic flag  The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Airways</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-airways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-airways/</guid>
      <description>British Airways (BA) is the flag carrier airline of the United Kingdom, headquartered at Waterside, Harmondsworth. It is the second largest airline in the United Kingdom, based on fleet size and passengers carried, behind easyJet. The airline is based in Waterside near its main hub at London Heathrow Airport. In January 2011 BA merged with Iberia, creating the International Airlines Group (IAG), a holding company registered in Madrid, Spain. IAG is the world&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline group in terms of annual revenue and the second-largest in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hummer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hummer/</guid>
      <description> Hummer was a brand of trucks and SUVs, first marketed in 1992 when AM General began selling a civilian version of the M998 Humvee. In 1998, General Motors (GM) purchased the brand name from AM General and marketed three vehicles: the original Hummer H1, based on the military Humvee, as well as the new H2 and H3 models that were based on smaller, civilian-market GM platforms.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechnipFMC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/technipfmc/</guid>
      <description> TechnipFMC plc is a UK-based company that provides complete project life cycle services (conception, feasibility study, front end engineering, detailed engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning, test runs, maintenance &amp;amp; decommissioning) for the energy industry. TechnipFMC was ranked 23rd among world&amp;rsquo;s Top 225 International Design Firms in the year 2017 by Engineering News-Record.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penguin Books</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:31:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/penguin-books/</guid>
      <description>Penguin Books Logo History Designed by Edward Young  In 1935, Edward Young designed Penguin’s famous “dignified but flippant” logo and the colour scheme for its book covers.
 It started with the simple logo and name, suggested, allegedly, by a typist who was earwigging the board meeting. Allen had already hit upon the idea of an animal logo, inspired by the template offered by the contemporary publishing house The Albatross Library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBS Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hsbc Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</guid>
      <description>About HSBC Bank  The HSBC brand is recognised worldwide. Our latest advertising illustrates our role in helping people, businesses and communities to thrive.
 HSBC is one of the largest banking and financial services organisations in the world, with operations in 66 countries and territories. We aim to be where the growth is, enabling businesses to thrive and economies to prosper, and, ultimately, helping people to fulfil their hopes and realise their ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barclays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:42:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>