<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>F on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/f/</link>
    <description>Recent content in F on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/f/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferrari</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ferrari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ferrari/</guid>
      <description>Ferrari is an Italian luxury sports car manufacturer based in Maranello. Founded by Enzo Ferrari in 1939 out of Alfa Romeo&amp;rsquo;s race division as Auto Avio Costruzioni, the company built its first car in 1940. However, the company&amp;rsquo;s inception as an auto manufacturer is usually recognized in 1947, when the first Ferrari-badged car was completed.
 In 2014 Ferrari was rated the world&amp;rsquo;s most powerful brand by Brand Finance. In June 2018, the 1964 250 GTO became the most expensive car in history, setting an all-time record selling price of $70 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity Investments</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fidelity-investments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fidelity-investments/</guid>
      <description>Fidelity Investments Inc., commonly referred to as Fidelity, earlier as Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research or FMR, is an American multinational financial services corporation based in Boston, Massachusetts.
 It is one of the largest asset managers in the world with $2.46 trillion in assets under management as of March 2018 and a combined total customer asset value number of $6.7 trillion. Fidelity Investments operates a brokerage firm, manages a large family of mutual funds, provides fund distribution and investment advice, retirement services, Index funds, wealth management, cryptocurrency, securities execution and clearance, and life insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIFA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fifa/</guid>
      <description>The Fédération Internationale de Football Association (FIFA /ˈfiːfə/ FEE-fə; French for &amp;lsquo;International Federation of Association Football&amp;rsquo;; Spanish: Federación Internacional de Fútbol Asociación; German: Internationaler Verband des Association Football) is a non-profit organization which describes itself as an international governing body of association football, fútsal, beach soccer, and efootball. It is the highest governing body of football.
 FIFA was founded in 1904 to oversee international competition among the national associations of Belgium, Denmark, France, Germany, the Netherlands, Spain, Sweden, and Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fila</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fila/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fila/</guid>
      <description>Fila Holdings Corp. (d/b/a Fila) is a South Korean corporation that designs and manufactures shoes and apparel, taking its current name after the acquisition of the Italian company Fila in 2007 and therefore the rights to the brand name. It is the largest South Korean sportswear manufacturer. Fila was originally founded by Ettore and Giansevero Fila in 1911 in Biella, Piedmont, Italy. In 2003, it was sold to United States-based Sports Brand International.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fitbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fitbit/</guid>
      <description>Fitbit, Inc. is an American company headquartered in San Francisco, California. Its products are activity trackers, smartwatches, wireless-enabled wearable technology devices that measure data such as the number of steps walked, heart rate, quality of sleep, steps climbed, and other personal metrics involved in fitness. Before October 2007, the company was previously named Healthy Metrics Research, Inc. While these devices appear to increase physical activities, there is little evidence that they improve health outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Locker</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/foot-locker/</guid>
      <description>Foot Locker Retail, Inc. is an American sportswear and footwear retailer, with its headquarters in Midtown Manhattan, New York City, and operating in 28 countries.
 Although established in 1974, and founded as a separate company in 1988, Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s roots date to 1879, as it is a successor corporation to the F. W. Woolworth Company (“Woolworth&amp;rsquo;s”), as many of its freestanding stores were originally Kinney Shoes and Woolworth&amp;rsquo;s locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite/</guid>
      <description>Fortnite is an online video game developed by Epic Games and released in 2017. It is available in three distinct game mode versions that otherwise share the same general gameplay and game engine: Fortnite: Save the World, a cooperative shooter-survival game for up to four players to fight off zombie-like creatures and defend objects with fortifications they can build; Fortnite Battle Royale, a free-to-play battle royale game where up to 100 players fight to be the last person standing; and Fortnite Creative, where players are given complete freedom to create worlds and battle arenas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fujifilm</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujifilm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujifilm/</guid>
      <description>Fujifilm Holdings Corporation (富士フイルム株式会社, Fujifuirumu Kabushiki-kaisha), trading as Fujifilm (stylized as FUJiFILM), or simply Fuji, is a Japanese multinational photography and imaging company headquartered in Tokyo.
 Fujifilm&amp;rsquo;s principal activities are the development, production, sale and servicing of business document solutions, medical imaging and diagnostics equipment, cosmetics, regenerative medicine, stem cells, biologics manufacturing, optical films for flat panel displays, optical devices, photocopiers and printers, digital cameras, color film, color paper, photofinishing equipment, photofinishing chemicals, graphic arts equipment and materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fanatics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fanatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fanatics/</guid>
      <description>Fanatics, Inc. is an American online retailer of licensed sportswear, sports equipment, and merchandise, formed in 1995 and headquartered in Jacksonville, Florida. Fanatics offers product via its Fanatics and FansEdge brands, as well as sports collectibles and memorabilia through Fanatics Authentic and SportsMemorabilia.com. Fanatics also currently operates the e-commerce websites of major professional sports leagues (MLB, NASCAR, NBA, NFL, NHL, PGA, MLS, and UFC), major media brands (CBS Sports, FOX Sports, and NBC Sports), and over 150 collegiate and professional team properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fertility Solutions</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertility-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertility-solutions/</guid>
      <description> Fertility Solutions is a patient-centered practice that provides a full spectrum of infertility diagnosis and treatment. From lifestyle modifications to the latest in assisted reproductive technology, Fertility Solutions offer a decidedly different, more personal approach to fertility care.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flatiron Health</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/flatiron-health/</guid>
      <description> Flatiron is a healthcare technology company providing software and data analytics services to the FDA, cancer researchers, and care providers. Flatiron’s Learning Oncology Platform supports over 260 community oncology practices across the U.S, 10 of the top 12 life science companies and three major academic research centers. Early investors include Google Ventures, First Round Capital, Roche and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/forbes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/forbes/</guid>
      <description>Forbes is an American business magazine. Published bi-weekly, it features original articles on finance, industry, investing, and marketing topics. Forbes also reports on related subjects such as technology, communications, science, politics, and law. Its headquarters is located in Jersey City, New Jersey. Primary competitors in the national business magazine category include Fortune and Bloomberg Businessweek. The magazine is well known for its lists and rankings, including of the richest Americans (the Forbes 400), of the world&amp;rsquo;s top companies (the Forbes Global 2000), and The World&amp;rsquo;s Billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Business</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-business/</guid>
      <description>Fox Business Network (also known as Fox Business) is an American pay television business news channel that is owned by the Fox News Group division of Fox Corporation. The network discusses business and financial news. Day-to-day operations are run by Kevin Magee, executive vice president of Fox News; Neil Cavuto manages content and business news coverage. As of February 2015, Fox Business Network is available to approximately 74,224,000 pay television households (63.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Corporation</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Fox Corporation (abbreviated Fox Corp. and informally &amp;ldquo;New Fox&amp;rdquo;) is an American television broadcasting company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was formed from the 2019 acquisition of 21st Century Fox (itself formed from the 2013 split of News Corporation) by The Walt Disney Company. Fox Corp. was spun off from 21st Century Fox and its stock began trading on March 19, 2019. It is owned by the Murdoch family via a family trust with 39% interest; Rupert Murdoch is co-executive chairman, while his son Lachlan Murdoch is chairman and CEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-news/</guid>
      <description>Fox News (officially Fox News Channel and abbreviated FNC) is an American pay television news channel. It is owned by the Fox News Group, which itself was owned by News Corporation from 1996–2013, 21st Century Fox from 2013–2019, and Fox Corporation since 2019. The channel broadcasts primarily from studios at 1211 Avenue of the Americas in New York City. Fox News is provided in 86 countries or overseas territories worldwide, with international broadcasts featuring Fox Extra segments during ad breaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-sports/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports is the brand name for a number of sports channels, broadcast divisions, programming, and other media around the world that are either controlled or partially owned by the family of Rupert Murdoch. These assets are held mainly by Fox Corporation, with the exceptions of the operations in Australia, which are part of News Corp Australia and rest of the international Fox Sports channels and Fox Sports Networks which are owned by The Walt Disney Company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</guid>
      <description> Fox Television Stations, LLC (FTS; alternately Fox Television Stations Group, LLC), is a group of television stations located within the United States which are owned-and-operated by the Fox Broadcasting Company, a subsidiary of the Fox Corporation.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France 24</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/france-24/</guid>
      <description> France 24 (pronounced &amp;ldquo;France vingt-quatre&amp;rdquo;) is a state-owned international news and current affairs television network based in Paris. Its channels broadcast in French, English, Arabic, and Spanish and are aimed at the overseas market, similar to DD News, BBC World News, DW and RT.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs1/</guid>
      <description>Fox Sports 1 (FS1) is an American pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation.[1] FS1 replaced the motorsports network Speed on August 17, 2013, at the same time that its companion channel Fox Sports 2 replaced Fuel TV.[2] Both FS1 and FS2 absorbed most of the sports programming from its predecessors, as well as content from Fox Soccer, which was replaced by the entertainment-based channel FXX on September 2, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS2</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fs2/</guid>
      <description> Fox Sports 2 (FS2) is an American sports-oriented pay television channel that is owned by the Fox Sports Media Group, a unit of Fox Corporation. The channel is based at the Fox Sports division&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in the Westwood section of Los Angeles, California.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FC Cincinnati</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-cincinnati/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-cincinnati/</guid>
      <description>FC Cincinnati is an American professional soccer club based in Cincinnati, Ohio that plays in the Eastern Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The team succeeded the lower-division team of the same name and was announced on May 29, 2018, when MLS awarded an expansion franchise to Cincinnati. The team began MLS play on March 2, 2019 with its first match against Seattle Sounders FC. The club&amp;rsquo;s ownership group is led by Carl H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FC Dallas</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fc-dallas/</guid>
      <description> FC Dallas is an American professional soccer club based in the Dallas suburb of Frisco, Texas. The club competes as a member of Major League Soccer (MLS). The franchise began play in 1996 as a charter club of the league. The club was founded in 1995 as the Dallas Burn before adopting its current name in 2004.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida Panthers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/florida-panthers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/florida-panthers/</guid>
      <description>The Florida Panthers are a professional ice hockey team based in the Miami metropolitan area. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team&amp;rsquo;s local broadcasting rights has been held by Fox Sports Florida (formerly SportsChannel Florida) since 1996. The team initially played their home games at Miami Arena, before moving to the BB&amp;amp;T Center in 1998. Located in Sunrise, Florida, the Panthers are the southernmost team in the NHL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion For Good</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good/</guid>
      <description>Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F1</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/f1/</guid>
      <description>Formula One (also Formula 1 or F1) is the highest class of single-seater auto racing sanctioned by the Fédération Internationale de l&amp;rsquo;Automobile (FIA) and owned by the Formula One Group. The FIA Formula One World Championship has been one of the premier forms of racing around the world since its inaugural season in 1950. The word &amp;ldquo;formula&amp;rdquo; in the name refers to the set of rules to which all participants&amp;rsquo; cars must conform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FedEx</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fedex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fedex/</guid>
      <description>FedEx Corporation is an American multinational courier delivery services company headquartered in Memphis, Tennessee. The name &amp;ldquo;FedEx&amp;rdquo; is a syllabic abbreviation of the name of the company&amp;rsquo;s original air division, Federal Express (now FedEx Express), which was used from 1973 until 2000. The company is known for its overnight shipping service and pioneering a system that could track packages and provide real-time updates on package location (to help in finding lost packages), a feature that has now been implemented by most other carrier services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fiat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fiat/</guid>
      <description> Fiat Automobiles is an Italian automobile manufacturer, a subsidiary of FCA Italy S.p.A., which is part of Fiat Chrysler Automobiles (previously Fiat S.p.A.). Fiat Automobiles was formed in January 2007 when Fiat reorganized its automobile business, and traces its history back to 1899 when the first Fiat automobile, the Fiat 4 HP, was produced.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ford</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ford/</guid>
      <description>Ford Motor Company is an American multinational automaker that has its main headquarter in Dearborn, Michigan, a suburb of Detroit. It was founded by Henry Ford and incorporated on June 16, 1903. The company sells automobiles and commercial vehicles under the Ford brand and most luxury cars under the Lincoln brand. Ford also owns Brazilian SUV manufacturer Troller, an 8% stake in Aston Martin of the United Kingdom and a 32% stake in Jiangling Motors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fujitsu</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujitsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujitsu/</guid>
      <description> Fujitsu Ltd. is a Japanese multinational information technology equipment and services company headquartered in Tokyo, Japan. In 2015, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-largest IT services provider measured by IT services revenue (after IBM, HP and Accenture). Fortune named Fujitsu as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most admired companies and a Global 500 company.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FertileHope</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertilehope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fertilehope/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fda/</guid>
      <description>About FDA (from wikipedia.org)
The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or USFDA) is a federal agency of the United States Department of Health and Human Services, one of the United States federal executive departments. The FDA is responsible for protecting and promoting public health through the control and supervision of food safety, tobacco products, dietary supplements, prescription and over-the-counter pharmaceutical drugs (medications), vaccines, biopharmaceuticals, blood transfusions, medical devices, electromagnetic radiation emitting devices (ERED), cosmetics, animal foods &amp;amp; feed and veterinary products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook/</guid>
      <description>New Facebook Logo  The company unveiled its new logo Tuesday, April 30, 2019. The new logo retains the distinctive “f” letter, but replaces the rounded square container with a circle. In addition, the new look moves the “f” to the center of the icon, rather than the right side like in the old version. The “Facebook” logotype that has the full name of the company is now relegated to use only for the company — but not its services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Developer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/firefox-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/firefox-developer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Focus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/firefox-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/firefox-focus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Nightly</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/firefox-nightly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/firefox-nightly/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Firefox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-firefox/</guid>
      <description>New Firefor Logo  The “Firefox” you’ve always known as a browser is stretching to cover a family of products and services united by putting you and your privacy first. Firefox is a browser AND an encrypted service to send huge files. It’s an easy way to protect your passwords on every device AND an early warning if your email has been part of a data breach. Safe, private, eye-opening. That’s just the beginning of the new Firefox family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocket</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pocket/</guid>
      <description>About Pocket (from getpocket.com)
Pocket was founded in 2007 by Nate Weiner to help people save interesting articles, videos and more from the web for later enjoyment. Once saved to Pocket, the list of content is visible on any device — phone, tablet or computer. It can be viewed while waiting in line, on the couch, during commutes or travel — even offline.
The world&amp;rsquo;s leading save-for-later service currently has more than 30 million registered users and is integrated into more than 1500 apps including Flipboard, Twitter and Zite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Messenger</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook-messenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook-messenger/</guid>
      <description>Facebook Founded in 2004, Facebook’s mission is to give people the power to build community and bring the world closer together. People use Facebook to stay connected with friends and family, to discover what’s going on in the world, and to share and express what matters to them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>