<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>S on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/s/</link>
    <description>Recent content in S on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/s/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Doctors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-doctors/</guid>
      <description>About Super Doctors (from superdoctors.com)
Super Doctors is a listing of outstanding doctors from more than 40 medical specialties who have attained a high degree of peer recognition or professional achievement. Super Doctors is published as a special supplement in leading newspapers and city and regional magazines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SREI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/srei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/srei/</guid>
      <description>About the Society for Reproductive Endocrinology and Infertility (from socrei.org)
Reproductive Endocrinologists are Obstetrician-Gynecologists with advanced education, research and professional skills in Reproductive Endocrinology &amp;amp; Infertility. These highly trained and qualified physicians treat Reproductive Disorders that affect children, women, men, the mature woman, and infertility in both men and women.
SREI Membership requires certification by the American Board of Obstetrics and Gynecology in both Obstetrics and Gynecology and the subspecialty of Reproductive Endocrinology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Sharp HealthCare (from sharp.org)
Sharp HealthCare is San Diego&amp;rsquo;s health care leader with hospitals in San Diego, affiliated medical groups, urgent care centers and a health plan. Sharp provides medical services in virtually all fields of medicine, including primary care, heart care, cancer treatment, orthopedics and women&amp;rsquo;s health.
 Sharp is not for profit, but for people, which means all of our resources are dedicated to delivering the highest quality patient-centered care, the latest medical technology and superior service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Union Tribune</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</guid>
      <description>About San Diego Union Tribune The San Diego Union-Tribune is San Diego’s largest media company and its oldest business, dating back to the founding of the Union in 1868.
Today, Union-Tribune publications reach more than 96 percent of San Diego County households each week. The company portfolio includes its Pulitzer Prize-winning newspaper, The San Diego Union-Tribune; the region’s leading website, SanDiegoUnionTribune.com; weekly entertainment guide Night + Day; lifestyle magazine Pacific San Diego; Spanish-language weekly Hoy San Diego; and nine community newspapers: the La Jolla Light; Del Mar Times; Encinitas Advocate; Solana Beach Sun; Carmel Valley Times; Poway News Chieftain; Rancho Santa Fe Review; Ramona Sentinel and Rancho Bernardo News Journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scion</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>