<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>S on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/s/</link>
    <description>Recent content in S on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/s/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schiotz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/schiotz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/schiotz/</guid>
      <description> A common interest in good beet was a vital element in the brewery’s history. And that was the special ingredient that made Albani into one of the most important breweries of the day with interesting recipes and skilled, dedicated brewery workers as the crucial factors.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelter</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shelter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shelter/</guid>
      <description>Shelter is a registered charity that campaigns to end homelessness and bad housing in England and Scotland. It gives advice, information and advocacy to people in need, and tackles the root causes of bad housing by lobbying government and local authorities for new laws and policies to improve the lives of homeless and badly housed people. It works in partnership with Shelter Cymru in Wales and the Housing Rights Service in Northern Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shure</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shure/</guid>
      <description> Shure Incorporated is an American audio products corporation. It was founded by Sidney N. Shure in Chicago, Illinois in 1925 as a supplier of radio parts kits. The company became a consumer and professional audio-electronics manufacturer of microphones, wireless microphone systems, phonograph cartridges, discussion systems, mixers, and digital signal processing. The company also manufactures listening products, including headphones, high-end earphones, and personal monitor systems.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonos</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonos/</guid>
      <description> Sonos is an American consumer electronics company based in Santa Barbara, California. It was founded in 2002 by John MacFarlane, Craig Shelburne, Tom Cullen, and Trung Mai, and is currently run by Patrick Spence. Sonos is widely known for the smart speakers it develops and manufactures. Sonos products are designed to allow speakers to play music simultaneously in multiple rooms.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soundcraft</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft/</guid>
      <description> Soundcraft is a British designer and importer (formerly a manufacturer) of mixing consoles and other professional audio equipment. It is a subsidiary of Harman International Industries, which is owned by South Korean company Samsung Electronics. It was founded by sound engineer Phil Dudderidge and electronics designer Graham Blyth in 1973.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sourcetree</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sourcetree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sourcetree/</guid>
      <description> Sourcetree simplifies how you interact with your Git repositories so you can focus on coding. Visualize and manage your repositories through Sourcetree&amp;rsquo;s simple Git GUI.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statuspage</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/statuspage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/statuspage/</guid>
      <description> Statuspage is the communication piece of your incident management process. Statuspage integrates with your favorite monitoring, alerting, chat, and help desk tools for efficient response every time.
   Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steam</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/steam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/steam/</guid>
      <description>Steam is a video game digital distribution service platform developed by Valve Corporation. It was launched in September 2003 as a way for Valve to provide automatic updates for their games, but eventually expanded to include games from third-party publishers. Initially launched as a software client component to help keep Valve&amp;rsquo;s games up-to-date, the Steam service has expanded to include web- and mobile-based interfaces for consumers and developers for third-party games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stellar</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar/</guid>
      <description> Stellar is an open source, decentralized protocol for digital currency to fiat money transfers which allows cross-border transactions between any pair of currencies. The Stellar protocol is supported by a 501&amp;copy;3 nonprofit, the Stellar Development Foundation.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/studer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/studer/</guid>
      <description> Studer is a Swiss designer and manufacturer of audio equipment for recording studios and broadcasters. The company was founded in Zürich, Switzerland, in 1948 by Willi Studer. It initially became known in the 1950s for its professional tape recorders. In the 1990s the company moved into the manufacture of mixing consoles.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super 8</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</guid>
      <description> With more than 2,800 hotels on four continents, the newly redesigned Super 8 offers affordable, innovative lodging on the open road. As your ultimate roadside companion, every location also offers free WiFi and a complimentary SuperStart Breakfast to get you recharged and refueled for the day ahead.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SABC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sabc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sabc/</guid>
      <description> The South African Broadcasting Corporation (SABC) is the public broadcaster in South Africa, and provides 19 radio stations (AM/FM) as well as five television broadcasts to the general public. It is one of the largest of South Africa&amp;rsquo;s state-owned enterprises.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Gobain</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/saint-gobain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/saint-gobain/</guid>
      <description> Compagnie de Saint-Gobain S.A. is a French multinational corporation, founded in 1665 in Paris and headquartered on the outskirts of Paris, at La Défense and in Courbevoie. Originally a mirror manufacturer, it now also produces a variety of construction and high-performance materials. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanofi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanofi/</guid>
      <description> Sanofi S.A. is a French multinational pharmaceutical company headquartered in Paris, France, as of 2013 the world&amp;rsquo;s fifth-largest by prescription sales. The company was formed as Sanofi-Aventis in 2004 by the merger of Aventis and Sanofi-Synthélabo, which were each the product of several previous mergers. It changed its name to Sanofi in May 2011. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Gems</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</guid>
      <description> Screen Gems, Inc. is an American film production and distribution studio that is a division of Sony Pictures&amp;rsquo;s Motion Picture Group, a subsidiary of Japanese multinational conglomerate Sony.[1] It has served several different purposes for its parent companies over the decades since its incorporation. The label currently specializes in genre films, mainly horror.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sheraton</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sheraton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sheraton/</guid>
      <description> Sheraton Hotels and Resorts is an international hotel chain owned by Marriott International. As of December 31, 2018, Sheraton operates 441 hotels with 155,617 rooms globally, including locations in North America, Africa, Asia Pacific, Central and South America, Europe, the Middle East and the Caribbean.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinsegae</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shinsegae/</guid>
      <description> Shinsegae (Korean: 신세계, KRX: 004170) is a South Korean department store franchise, along with several other businesses, headquartered in Seoul, South Korea. The name Shinsegae literally means &amp;ldquo;New World&amp;rdquo; in Korean. Its flagship store in Centum City, Busan, was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest department store at 3,163,000 square feet (293,900 m2), surpassing Macy&amp;rsquo;s flagship Herald Square in New York City in 2009.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showtime</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime/</guid>
      <description> Showtime Networks Inc. (SNI) is an American entertainment company that oversees the company&amp;rsquo;s premium cable television channels, including its flagship service Showtime. It is a subsidiary of media conglomerate CBS Corporation.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siberia Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</guid>
      <description> S7 Airlines, legally JSC Siberia Airlines (Russian: АО «Авиакомпания &amp;ldquo;Сибирь&amp;rdquo;», &amp;ldquo;АО Aviakompania Sibir&amp;rdquo;), is an airline headquartered in Ob, Novosibirsk Oblast, Russia, with offices in Moscow. As of 2008, it is Russia&amp;rsquo;s biggest domestic airline, with its main bases at Domodedovo International Airport and Tolmachevo Airport
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smirnoff</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smirnoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smirnoff/</guid>
      <description>Smirnoff is a brand of vodka owned and produced by the British company Diageo. The Smirnoff brand began with a vodka distillery founded in Moscow by Pyotr Arsenievich Smirnov (1831–1898). It is now distributed in 130 countries[citation needed] and produced in several countries including Albania, Brazil, Honduras, India, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Mongolia, the Philippines, the United Kingdom and the United States[citation needed]. Smirnoff products include vodka, flavoured vodka, and malt beverages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smithsonian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smithsonian/</guid>
      <description>The Smithsonian Institution (/smɪθˈsoʊniən/ smith-SOH-nee-ən), also known simply as the Smithsonian, is a group of museums and research centers administered by the Government of the United States. It was founded on August 10, 1846, &amp;ldquo;for the increase and diffusion of knowledge&amp;rdquo;.[= The institution is named after its founding donor, British scientist James Smithson. It was originally organized as the &amp;ldquo;United States National Museum&amp;rdquo;, but that name ceased to exist as an administrative entity in 1967.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonatrach</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sonatrach/</guid>
      <description> Sonatrach (Arabic:سوناطراك) (Société Nationale pour la Recherche, la Production, le Transport, la Transformation, et la Commercialisation des Hydrocarbures) is an Algerian government-owned company formed to explore the hydrocarbon resources of the country. It has some concessions in Libya, Mauritania, Peru, Yemen and Venezuela. Its diversified activities cover all aspects of production: exploration, extraction, transport, and refining. It has diversified into petrochemistry and the desalination of seawater.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SJ Earthquakes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sj-earthquakes/</guid>
      <description>The San Jose Earthquakes are an American professional soccer team based in San Jose, California, United States, that competes as a member of the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The franchise began play in 1996 (originally as the San Jose Clash) as one of the charter clubs of the league. The Earthquakes took part in the first game in MLS history, defeating D.C. United 1–0. The Earthquakes have won two MLS Cup titles, in 2001 and 2003, and two Supporters&amp;rsquo; Shields in 2005 and 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento Kings</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sacramento-kings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sacramento-kings/</guid>
      <description>The Sacramento Kings are an American professional basketball team based in Sacramento, California. The Kings compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the Western Conference&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Division. The Kings are the only team in the major professional North American sports leagues located in Sacramento. The team plays its home games at the Golden 1 Center. Their best seasons to date in the city were in the early 2000s, including the 2001–02 season when they had the best record in the NBA at 61–21 (a winning percentage of .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Jose Sharks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-jose-sharks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-jose-sharks/</guid>
      <description>The San Jose Sharks are a professional ice hockey team based in San Jose, California. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The franchise is owned by San Jose Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment Enterprises. Beginning play in the 1991–92 season, the Sharks initially played their home games at the Cow Palace, before they moved to their present home, now named SAP Center at San Jose, in 1993.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Sounders FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-sounders-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-sounders-fc/</guid>
      <description>Seattle Sounders FC is an American professional soccer club based in Seattle, Washington. The Sounders compete as a member of the Western Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The club was established on November 13, 2007, and began play in 2009 as an MLS expansion team. The Sounders are a phoenix club, carrying the same name as the original franchise that competed in the North American Soccer League from 1974 to 1983.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sporting KC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc/</guid>
      <description> Sporting Kansas City is an American professional soccer club in Kansas City, Kansas, with its main office and historic location in Kansas City, Missouri. The club competes as a member of the Western Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS), having returned in 2015 after spending ten seasons in the Eastern Conference.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spurs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/spurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spurs/</guid>
      <description> The San Antonio Spurs are an American professional basketball team based in San Antonio, Texas. The Spurs compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The team plays its home games at the AT&amp;amp;T Center in San Antonio.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis Blues</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-blues/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Blues are a professional ice hockey team based in St. Louis, Missouri. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The franchise was founded in 1967 as one of the six teams from the 1967 NHL expansion and is named after the W. C. Handy song &amp;ldquo;Saint Louis Blues&amp;rdquo;. The Blues play their home games at the 19,150-seat Enterprise Center in downtown St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>49ers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/49ers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/49ers/</guid>
      <description>The San Francisco 49ers are a professional American football team located in the San Francisco Bay Area. They compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) West division. The team currently plays its home games at Levi&amp;rsquo;s Stadium in Santa Clara, California, located 45 miles (72 km) southeast of San Francisco in the heart of Silicon Valley. Since 1988, the 49ers have been headquartered in Santa Clara</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMFG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smfg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smfg/</guid>
      <description> Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group, Inc. (SMFG; 株式会社三井住友フィナンシャルグループ Kabushiki kaisha Mitsui Sumitomo Finansharu Gurūpu) is a Japanese bank holding / financial services company established by Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation, the second largest bank in Japan by market value (as of November 2009).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Padres</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-padres/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-padres/</guid>
      <description>The San Diego Padres are an American professional baseball team based in San Diego, California. The Padres compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) West division. Founded in 1969, the Padres have won two NL pennants — in 1984 and 1998, losing in the World Series both years. As of 2018, they have had 14 winning seasons in franchise history. The Padres are one of two Major League Baseball teams (the other being the Los Angeles Angels) in California to originate from that state; the Athletics were originally from Philadelphia (and moved to the state from Kansas City), and the Dodgers and Giants are originally from two New York City boroughs – Brooklyn and Manhattan, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sapporo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sapporo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sapporo/</guid>
      <description> Sapporo Breweries Ltd. (サッポロビール株式会社 Sapporo Bīru Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese beer brewing company founded in 1876. Sapporo is the oldest brand of beer in Japan. It was first brewed in Sapporo, Japan, in 1876 by brewer Seibei Nakagawa. The world headquarters of Sapporo Breweries is in Ebisu, Shibuya, Tokyo. The company purchased the Canadian company Sleeman Breweries in 2006.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Mariners</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-mariners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-mariners/</guid>
      <description>The Seattle Mariners are an American professional baseball team based in Seattle, Washington. The Mariners compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West Division. The team joined the American League as an expansion team in 1977 playing their home games in the Kingdome. Since July 1999, the Mariners&amp;rsquo; home ballpark has been T-Mobile Park (formerly Safeco Field), located in the SoDo neighborhood of Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Seahawks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-seahawks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-seahawks/</guid>
      <description>The Seattle Seahawks are a professional American football franchise based in Seattle, Washington. The Seahawks compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) West division. They joined the NFL in 1976 as an expansion team. The Seahawks are coached by Pete Carroll. Since 2002, they have played their home games at CenturyLink Field (formerly Qwest Field), located south of downtown Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprite</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprite/</guid>
      <description> Sprite is a colorless, caffeine-free, lemon and lime-flavored soft drink created by The Coca-Cola Company. It was first developed in West Germany in 1959 as Fanta Klare Zitrone (“Clear Lemon Fanta”) and was introduced in the United States under the current brand name Sprite in 1961 as a competitor to 7 Up.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis Cardinals</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-cardinals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/st-louis-cardinals/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals are an American professional baseball team based in St. Louis, Missouri. The Cardinals compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. Busch Stadium has been their home ballpark since 2006. One of the most successful franchises in baseball history, the Cardinals have won 11 World Series championships, the second-most in Major League Baseball (behind the New York Yankees) and the most in the National League.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumitomo Mitsui</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sumitomo-mitsui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sumitomo-mitsui/</guid>
      <description> Sumitomo Mitsui Trust Holdings, Inc. is a Japanese financial holding company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo. It provides an assortment of financial products to retail and wholesale customers, with a focus on asset management, financial brokerage and real estate services.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/slack/</guid>
      <description>Slack is an American cloud-based set of proprietary team collaboration tools and services, founded by Stewart Butterfield. Slack began as an internal tool used by his company, Tiny Speck, in the development of Glitch, a now defunct online game.[ The name is an acronym for &amp;ldquo;Searchable Log of All Conversation and Knowledge&amp;rdquo;.
 Source   Source The new logo does away with the direct representation of the hash tag — referred to by both Pentagram and Slack as “octothorpe” — and its rotation which, yes, was a big part of its equity but can be a problematic feature for wide and mainstream implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Alliance</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/star-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/star-alliance/</guid>
      <description> Star Alliance is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest global airline alliances. Founded on 14 May 1997, its current CEO is Jeffrey Goh and its headquarters is located in Frankfurt am Main, Germany. As of April 2018, Star Alliance is the second largest global alliance by passenger count with 728 million, behind SkyTeam (730 million) and ahead of Oneworld (528 million). Its slogan is &amp;ldquo;The Way The Earth Connects&amp;rdquo;.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</guid>
      <description>Subway is an American privately held fast food restaurant franchise that primarily sells submarine sandwiches (subs) and salads. Subway is one of the fastest-growing franchises in the world and, as of June 2017, had approximately 42,000 stores located in more than 100 countries. More than half of the stores are located in the United States. It is the largest single-brand restaurant chain, and the largest restaurant operator, in the world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sap/</guid>
      <description>SAP SE is a German multinational software corporation that makes enterprise software to manage business operations and customer relations. SAP is headquartered in Walldorf, Baden-Württemberg, Germany with regional offices in 180 countries. The company has over 425,000 customers in over 180 countries and is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index.
 Source  Subtle enhancements to the SAP logo make it feel more contemporary. Designed to live in the digital world, the new mark springs vividly from the screen, on any background, connecting with both large-scale business clients and individual consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SONY</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony/</guid>
      <description>Sony Corporation is a Japanese multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Kōnan, Minato, Tokyo. Its diversified business includes consumer and professional electronics, gaming, entertainment and financial services. The company owns the largest music entertainment business in the world the largest video game console business and one of the largest video game publishing businesses, and is one of the leading manufacturers of electronic products for the consumer and professional markets, and a leading player in the film and television entertainment industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/salesforce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/salesforce/</guid>
      <description> Salesforce.com, Inc. (usually abbreviated as SF or SFDC) is an American cloud-based software company headquartered in San Francisco, California. Though the bulk of its revenue comes from its customer-relationship management (CRM) service, Salesforce training also sells a complementary suite of enterprise applications focused on customer service, marketing automation, analytics and application development.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/samsung/</guid>
      <description> Samsung is a South Korean multinational conglomerate headquartered in Samsung Town, Seoul. It comprises numerous affiliated businesses, most of them united under the Samsung brand, and is the largest South Korean chaebol (business conglomerate).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santander</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/santander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/santander/</guid>
      <description>Banco Santander, S.A., doing business as Santander Group (/ˌsɑːntɑːnˈdɛər/), is a Spanish multinational commercial bank and financial services company founded and based in Santander, Spain. In addition to hubs in Madrid and Barcelona, Santander maintains a presence in all global financial centres as the largest Spanish banking institution in the world. Although known for its European banking operations, it has extended operations across North and South America, and more recently in continental Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sany</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</guid>
      <description> Sany Heavy Industry Co., Ltd. is a Chinese multinational heavy equipment manufacturing company headquartered in Changsha, Hunan Province. It is the sixth-largest heavy equipment manufacturer in the world, and the first in its industry in China to enter the FT Global 500 and the Forbes Global 2000 rankings. Its founder and main shareholder is Liang Wengen.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanyo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanyo/</guid>
      <description> Sanyo Electric Co., Ltd. (三洋電機株式会社 San&amp;rsquo;yō Denki Kabushiki-gaisha) (stylized as SANYO) was a Japanese major electronics company and formerly a member of the Fortune Global 500 whose headquarters was located in Moriguchi, Osaka prefecture, Japan. Sanyo had over 230 subsidiaries and affiliates. Sanyo was founded by Toshio Iue.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seiko</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seiko/</guid>
      <description> Seiko Holdings Corporation is a Japanese holding company that has subsidiaries which manufactures and sells watches, clocks, electronic devices, semiconductors, jewelries, and optical products.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shell/</guid>
      <description>Shell Oil Company is the United States-based wholly owned subsidiary of Royal Dutch Shell, transnational corporation &amp;ldquo;oil major&amp;rdquo; of Anglo-Dutch origins, which is amongst the largest oil companies in the world. Approximately 22,000 Shell employees are based in the U.S. The U.S. headquarters are in Houston, Texas. The current president is Bruce Culpepper, a graduate of the University of Alabama. Shell Oil Company, including its consolidated companies and its share in equity companies, is one of America&amp;rsquo;s largest oil and natural gas producers, natural gas marketers, gasoline marketers and petrochemical manufacturers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiseido</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shiseido/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shiseido/</guid>
      <description>Shiseido Company, Limited is a Japanese multinational personal care company, that is a skin care, hair care, cosmetics and fragrance producer. It is one of the oldest cosmetics companies in the world. Founded in 1872, it celebrated its 140th anniversary in 2012. It is the largest cosmetic firm in Japan and the fifth largest cosmetics company in the world.[Shiseido is only available at cosmetic counters at selected department stores or pharmacists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutterfly</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/shutterfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/shutterfly/</guid>
      <description> Shutterfly, Inc. is an American Internet-based company, headquartered in Redwood City, California, and specializing in image-publishing services. Shutterfly&amp;rsquo;s flagship product is its photo book line. The company, founded in 1999, is currently led by Christopher North. The company went public in 2006. The Shutterfly customer base is heavily skewed toward women, who accounted for 80% of customers as reported in 2013.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siemens/</guid>
      <description> Siemens AG is a German multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Munich and the largest industrial manufacturing company in Europe with branch offices abroad.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/singapore-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/singapore-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Singapore Airlines Limited (SIA) is the flag carrier airline of Singapore with its hub at Singapore Changi Airport. The airline uses the Singapore Girl as its central figure in corporate branding. It is ranked as the world&amp;rsquo;s best airline, since 2018, while winning the top spot in three other categories in the same year including &amp;ldquo;Best First Class&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Best First Class Airline Seat&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Best Airline in Asia&amp;rdquo;. In 2018, the airline was placed 18th on the top 50 most admired companies worldwide, first in Asia and the only airline on the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skoda</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/skoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/skoda/</guid>
      <description> ŠKODA AUTO is a Czech automobile manufacturer founded in 1895 as Laurin &amp;amp; Klement. Its headquarters are in Mladá Boleslav, Czech Republic.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</guid>
      <description> Smart (stylized as smart) is a German automotive brand and division of Daimler AG. The company is based in Böblingen, Germany. It produces microcars and subcompacts, primarily the Fortwo and Forfour. The primary assembly plants is the Smartville in Hambach, France. A second plant exists in Novo Mesto, Slovenia. Marketed in 46 countries around the world, production of the Fortwo had surpassed 1.7 million units by early 2015.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/snapchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/snapchat/</guid>
      <description> Snapchat is a multimedia messaging app used globally, created by Evan Spiegel, Bobby Murphy, and Reggie Brown, former students at Stanford University, and developed by Snap Inc., originally Snapchat Inc.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South African Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/south-african-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/south-african-airlines/</guid>
      <description>South African Airways (SAA) is the flag carrier airline of South Africa. Its headquarters are in Airways Park on the grounds of O. R. Tambo International Airport in Kempton Park, Ekurhuleni, Gauteng. In partnership with SA Express, SA Airlink and its low-cost carrier, Mango, the airline flies to 56 destinations in South Africa, continental Africa and around the world from its Johannesburg hub, using a fleet of 47 aircraft. Vuyani Jarana has been CEO since November 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</guid>
      <description> Spotify Technology S.A. (/ˈspɒtɪfaɪ/) is a Swedish media-services provider founded in 2006. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its audio streaming platform that provides DRM-protected music and podcasts from record labels and media companies. As a freemium service, basic features are free with advertisements or automatic music videos, while additional features, such as improved streaming quality, are offered via paid subscriptions.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staples</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/staples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/staples/</guid>
      <description>Staples Inc. is a Massachusetts-based retail company. It is primarily involved in the sale of office supplies and related products, via retail channels and business-to-business (B2B)-oriented delivery operations.
 Source The new logo takes the old staple, opens it up, and turns into a table, or at least that’s my interpretation based on the chair graphic used in multiple other places.
Still, with Staples placing more emphasis on its B2B operation, the redesign will have its biggest impact there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subaru</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subaru/</guid>
      <description> Subaru is the automobile manufacturing division of Japanese transportation conglomerate Subaru Corporation (formerly known as Fuji Heavy Industries), the twenty-second largest automaker by production worldwide in 2012.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Swiss International Air Lines is the national airline of Switzerland, operating scheduled services in Europe and to North America, South America, Africa and Asia. Zurich Airport is its hub, Geneva Airport is a focus city. The airline was formed following the bankruptcy in 2002 of Swissair, Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s then flag carrier.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Doctors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-doctors/</guid>
      <description> Super Doctors is a listing of outstanding doctors from more than 40 medical specialties who have attained a high degree of peer recognition or professional achievement. Super Doctors is published as a special supplement in leading newspapers and city and regional magazines.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SREI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/srei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/srei/</guid>
      <description>About the Society for Reproductive Endocrinology and Infertility (from socrei.org)
Reproductive Endocrinologists are Obstetrician-Gynecologists with advanced education, research and professional skills in Reproductive Endocrinology &amp;amp; Infertility. These highly trained and qualified physicians treat Reproductive Disorders that affect children, women, men, the mature woman, and infertility in both men and women.
SREI Membership requires certification by the American Board of Obstetrics and Gynecology in both Obstetrics and Gynecology and the subspecialty of Reproductive Endocrinology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Sharp healthcare (from sharp.org)
Sharp healthcare is San Diego&amp;rsquo;s health care leader with hospitals in San Diego, affiliated medical groups, urgent care centers and a health plan. Sharp provides medical services in virtually all fields of medicine, including primary care, heart care, cancer treatment, orthopedics and women&amp;rsquo;s health.
 Sharp is not for profit, but for people, which means all of our resources are dedicated to delivering the highest quality patient-centered care, the latest medical technology and superior service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SART</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Union Tribune</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</guid>
      <description>About San Diego Union Tribune The San Diego Union-Tribune is San Diego’s largest media company and its oldest business, dating back to the founding of the Union in 1868.
Today, Union-Tribune publications reach more than 96 percent of San Diego County households each week. The company portfolio includes its Pulitzer Prize-winning newspaper, The San Diego Union-Tribune; the region’s leading website, SanDiegoUnionTribune.com; weekly entertainment guide Night + Day; lifestyle magazine Pacific San Diego; Spanish-language weekly Hoy San Diego; and nine community newspapers: the La Jolla Light; Del Mar Times; Encinitas Advocate; Solana Beach Sun; Carmel Valley Times; Poway News Chieftain; Rancho Santa Fe Review; Ramona Sentinel and Rancho Bernardo News Journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</guid>
      <description>Starbucks Corporation is an American coffee company and coffeehouse chain. Starbucks was founded in Seattle, Washington in 1971. As of early 2019, the company operates over 30,000 locations worldwide.
 Source The Starbucks History  Every day, we go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with our friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scion</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>