<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>S on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/s/</link>
    <description>Recent content in S on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/s/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/singapore-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/singapore-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Singapore Airlines Limited (SIA) is the flag carrier airline of Singapore with its hub at Singapore Changi Airport. The airline uses the Singapore Girl as its central figure in corporate branding. It is ranked as the world&amp;rsquo;s best airline, since 2018, while winning the top spot in three other categories in the same year including &amp;ldquo;Best First Class&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Best First Class Airline Seat&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Best Airline in Asia&amp;rdquo;. In 2018, the airline was placed 18th on the top 50 most admired companies worldwide, first in Asia and the only airline on the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</guid>
      <description> Smart (stylized as smart) is a German automotive brand and division of Daimler AG. The company is based in Böblingen, Germany. It produces microcars and subcompacts, primarily the Fortwo and Forfour. The primary assembly plants is the Smartville in Hambach, France. A second plant exists in Novo Mesto, Slovenia. Marketed in 46 countries around the world, production of the Fortwo had surpassed 1.7 million units by early 2015.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South African Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/south-african-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/south-african-airlines/</guid>
      <description>South African Airways (SAA) is the flag carrier airline of South Africa. Its headquarters are in Airways Park on the grounds of O. R. Tambo International Airport in Kempton Park, Ekurhuleni, Gauteng. In partnership with SA Express, SA Airlink and its low-cost carrier, Mango, the airline flies to 56 destinations in South Africa, continental Africa and around the world from its Johannesburg hub, using a fleet of 47 aircraft. Vuyani Jarana has been CEO since November 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/southwest-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. is a major American airline headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest low-cost carrier. The airline was established on March 15, 1967 by Herb Kelleher as Air Southwest Co. and adopted its current name, Southwest Airlines Co., in 1971, when it began operating as an intrastate airline wholly within the state of Texas, first flying between Dallas and San Antonio. The airline has about 58,000 employees as of September 2018 and operates about 4,000 departures a day during peak travel season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/starbucks/</guid>
      <description>Starbucks Corporation is an American coffee company and coffeehouse chain. Starbucks was founded in Seattle, Washington in 1971. As of early 2019, the company operates over 30,000 locations worldwide.
 Source The Starbucks History  Every day, we go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with our friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/swiss-airlines/</guid>
      <description> Swiss International Air Lines is the national airline of Switzerland, operating scheduled services in Europe and to North America, South America, Africa and Asia. Zurich Airport is its hub, Geneva Airport is a focus city. The airline was formed following the bankruptcy in 2002 of Swissair, Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s then flag carrier.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Doctors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:28:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-doctors/</guid>
      <description> Super Doctors is a listing of outstanding doctors from more than 40 medical specialties who have attained a high degree of peer recognition or professional achievement. Super Doctors is published as a special supplement in leading newspapers and city and regional magazines.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SREI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/srei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/srei/</guid>
      <description>About the Society for Reproductive Endocrinology and Infertility (from socrei.org)
Reproductive Endocrinologists are Obstetrician-Gynecologists with advanced education, research and professional skills in Reproductive Endocrinology &amp;amp; Infertility. These highly trained and qualified physicians treat Reproductive Disorders that affect children, women, men, the mature woman, and infertility in both men and women.
SREI Membership requires certification by the American Board of Obstetrics and Gynecology in both Obstetrics and Gynecology and the subspecialty of Reproductive Endocrinology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sharp-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>About Sharp healthcare (from sharp.org)
Sharp healthcare is San Diego&amp;rsquo;s health care leader with hospitals in San Diego, affiliated medical groups, urgent care centers and a health plan. Sharp provides medical services in virtually all fields of medicine, including primary care, heart care, cancer treatment, orthopedics and women&amp;rsquo;s health.
 Sharp is not for profit, but for people, which means all of our resources are dedicated to delivering the highest quality patient-centered care, the latest medical technology and superior service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SART</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sart/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Union Tribune</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/san-diego-union-tribune/</guid>
      <description>About San Diego Union Tribune The San Diego Union-Tribune is San Diego’s largest media company and its oldest business, dating back to the founding of the Union in 1868.
Today, Union-Tribune publications reach more than 96 percent of San Diego County households each week. The company portfolio includes its Pulitzer Prize-winning newspaper, The San Diego Union-Tribune; the region’s leading website, SanDiegoUnionTribune.com; weekly entertainment guide Night + Day; lifestyle magazine Pacific San Diego; Spanish-language weekly Hoy San Diego; and nine community newspapers: the La Jolla Light; Del Mar Times; Encinitas Advocate; Solana Beach Sun; Carmel Valley Times; Poway News Chieftain; Rancho Santa Fe Review; Ramona Sentinel and Rancho Bernardo News Journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scion</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/scion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>