<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>banking &amp; finances on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finances/</link>
    <description>Recent content in banking &amp; finances on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finances/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SMFG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smfg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smfg/</guid>
      <description> Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group, Inc. (SMFG; 株式会社三井住友フィナンシャルグループ Kabushiki kaisha Mitsui Sumitomo Finansharu Gurūpu) is a Japanese bank holding / financial services company established by Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation, the second largest bank in Japan by market value (as of November 2009).
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumitomo Mitsui</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sumitomo-mitsui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sumitomo-mitsui/</guid>
      <description> Sumitomo Mitsui Trust Holdings, Inc. is a Japanese financial holding company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo. It provides an assortment of financial products to retail and wholesale customers, with a focus on asset management, financial brokerage and real estate services.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PayPal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/paypal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/paypal/</guid>
      <description>PayPal Holdings, Inc. is an American company operating a worldwide online payments system that supports online money transfers and serves as an electronic alternative to traditional paper methods like checks and money orders. The company operates as a payment processor for online vendors, auction sites, and many other commercial users, for which it charges a fee in exchange for benefits such as one-click transactions and password memory. PayPal&amp;rsquo;s payment system, also called PayPal, is considered a type of payment rail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>