<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IV Interactive on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/agency/iv-interactive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IV Interactive on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/agency/iv-interactive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conceive Abilities</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</guid>
      <description> At ConceiveAbilities® Conceive Abilities believe that everyone who wants to become a parent, can. Conceive Abilities have helped build thousands of families for nearly 25 years. Whether you are an intended parent ready to fulfill your family destiny, a surrogate answering your calling or an egg donor wanting to expand what’s possible in your life—Conceive Abilities are your people.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donor Concierge</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/donor-concierge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/donor-concierge/</guid>
      <description>The Donor Concierge team is comprised of compassionate, educated, and knowledgeable case managers, with a track record of outstanding results to help families find the right donor/surrogate choice through the best industry connections. Donor Concierge have chosen each team member for her unique ability to relate to Donor Concierge clients. Donor Concierge have a multinational office with Canadian, Chinese, Filipino, and American case managers who speak a variety of languages including Mandarin, French, Tagalog, Spanish, and English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O3 TSI</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/o3-tsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/o3-tsi/</guid>
      <description> O3 Technology Solutions is a leading provider of Services, Software, and Solutions to financial services and capital market participants.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>