<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/doordash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/doordash/</guid>
      <description>DoorDash Inc. is a San Francisco-based on-demand prepared food delivery service founded in 2013 by Stanford students Tony Xu, Stanley Tang, Andy Fang and Evan Moore. A Y Combinator–backed company, DoorDash is one of several technology companies that uses logistics services to offer food delivery from restaurants on-demand. DoorDash launched in Palo Alto and, as of May 2019, had expanded to more than 4,000 cities and offers a selection of 340,000 stores across the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heinz</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/heinz/</guid>
      <description>The H. J. Heinz Company, better known as Heinz, is an American food processing company headquartered at One PPG Place in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, part of the Kraft Heinz Company. The company was founded by Henry John Heinz in 1869. Heinz manufactures thousands of food products in plants on six continents, and markets these products in more than 200 countries and territories. The company claims to have 150 number-one or number-two brands worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Flying J</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pilot-flying-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pilot-flying-j/</guid>
      <description>Pilot Travel Centers LLC, doing business as Pilot Flying J, is a North American chain of truck stops in the United States and Canada. The company is based in Knoxville, Tennessee, where Pilot Corporation, the majority owner, is based. The company is owned by Pilot, FJ Management, and Berkshire Hathaway. The company operates truck stops under the Pilot Travel Centers, Flying J Travel Plaza, and Mr. Fuel brands.
 Source About Pilot Flying J Pilot Flying J is the largest operator of travel centers in North America with more than 750 locations in 44 states and six Canadian provinces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Bull</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/red-bull/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/red-bull/</guid>
      <description>Red Bull is an energy drink sold by Red Bull GmbH, an Austrian company created in 1987. Red Bull has the highest market share of any energy drink in the world, with 7.5 billion cans sold in a year (as of 2019).
 Austrian entrepreneur Dietrich Mateschitz was inspired by an existing energy drink named Krating Daeng, which was first introduced and sold in Thailand by Chaleo Yoovidhya. He took this idea, modified the ingredients to suit the tastes of Westerners, and, in partnership with Chaleo, founded Red Bull GmbH in 1987 in Chakkapong, Thailand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carlsberg</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/carlsberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/carlsberg/</guid>
      <description>Carlsberg A/S is a global brewer. Founded in 1847 by J. C. Jacobsen, the company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters is located in Copenhagen, Denmark. Since Jacobsen&amp;rsquo;s death in 1887, the majority owner of the company has been the Carlsberg Foundation. The company&amp;rsquo;s flagship brand is Carlsberg (named after Jacobsen&amp;rsquo;s son Carl). It also brews Tuborg, Kronenbourg, Somersby cider, Russia&amp;rsquo;s best-selling beer Baltika, Belgian Grimbergen abbey beers, and more than 500 local beers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DQ</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dq/</guid>
      <description> Dairy Queen (DQ) is an American multinational chain of soft serve ice cream and fast-food restaurants owned by International Dairy Queen, Inc., a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway. International Dairy Queen, Inc., also owns Orange Julius, and formerly owned Karmelkorn and Golden Skillet Fried Chicken.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lotte</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotte/</guid>
      <description> Lotte Corporation (Korean: 롯데 그룹 lotte geurup) is a South Korean multinational conglomerate. Lotte began its history on June 28, 1948, by Korean businessman Shin Kyuk-ho in Tokyo. Shin expanded Lotte to his ancestral country, South Korea, with the establishment of Lotte Confectionery in Seoul on April 3, 1967. Lotte eventually grew to become South Korea&amp;rsquo;s fifth largest business conglomerate.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Apron</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</guid>
      <description> Blue Apron Inc. is an American ingredient-and-recipe meal kit service. It exclusively operates in the United States. The weekly boxes contain ingredients and also include suggested recipes that must be cooked by hand by the customer using the pre-ordered ingredients.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panera Bread</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/panera-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/panera-bread/</guid>
      <description> Panera Bread Company is an American chain store of bakery-café fast casual restaurants with over 2,000 locations, all of which are in the United States and Canada. Its headquarters are in Sunset Hills, Missouri, a suburb of St. Louis. The company operates as Saint Louis Bread Company in Greater St. Louis, where it has over 100 locations Offerings include soups, salads, pasta, sandwiches, specialty drinks, and bakery items.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyson</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tyson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tyson/</guid>
      <description>Tyson Foods, Inc. is an American multinational corporation based in Springdale, Arkansas, that operates in the food industry. The company is the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest processor and marketer of chicken, beef, and pork after JBS S.A. and annually exports the largest percentage of beef out of the United States. Together with its subsidiaries, it operates major food brands, including Jimmy Dean, Hillshire Farm, Sara Lee, Ball Park, Wright Brand, Aidells, and State Fair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoshinoya</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yoshinoya/</guid>
      <description> Yoshinoya is a Japanese multinational fast food chain, and the second-largest chain of gyūdon (beef bowl) restaurants. The chain was established in Japan in 1899. Its motto is &amp;ldquo;Tasty, low-priced, and quick&amp;rdquo;.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AW Restaurants</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-restaurants/</guid>
      <description>A&amp;amp;W Restaurants, Inc. is a chain of fast-food restaurants distinguished by its draft root beer, root beer floats and burgers. Its origins date back to 1919 when Roy W. Allen opened a walk-up root beer stand in Lodi, California. Allen&amp;rsquo;s employee Frank Wright partnered with him and they founded their first restaurant in Sacramento, California, in 1923. The company name was taken respectively from the initials of their last names—Allen and Wright.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AW Root Beer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aw-root-beer/</guid>
      <description> A&amp;amp;W Root Beer is a root beer brand primarily available in the United States and Canada, started in 1919 by Roy W. Allen. In 1922, Allen partnered with Frank Wright. They combined their initials to create the brand &amp;ldquo;A&amp;amp;W&amp;rdquo; and inspired a restaurant chain, founded in 1922. Originally, A&amp;amp;W root beer drinks sold for five cents.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAngelo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dangelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dangelo/</guid>
      <description> D&amp;rsquo;Angelo Grilled Sandwiches is a chain of sandwich shops located throughout New England. It serves various kinds of hot and cold subs, wraps, and salads.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KFC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kfc/</guid>
      <description> KFC is an American fast food restaurant chain headquartered in Louisville, Kentucky, that specializes in fried chicken. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest restaurant chain (as measured by sales) after McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, with 22,621 locations globally in 136 countries as of December 2018. The chain is a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, a restaurant company that also owns the Pizza Hut, Taco Bell, and WingStreet chains
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papa Gino</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/papa-gino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/papa-gino/</guid>
      <description> Papa Gino&amp;rsquo;s, Inc. is a restaurant chain based in Dedham, Massachusetts, specializing in American-style pizza along with pasta, subs, salads, and a variety of appetizers. There are 97 Papa Gino&amp;rsquo;s locations in Connecticut, Massachusetts, New Hampshire and Rhode Island. In November 2018, the chain&amp;rsquo;s parent company, PGHC Holdings, filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yum! Brands</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yum-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yum-brands/</guid>
      <description> Yum! Brands, Inc., or Yum! and formerly Tricon Global Restaurants, Inc., is an American fast food company. A Fortune 500 corporation, Yum! operates the brands Taco Bell, KFC, Pizza Hut, and WingStreet worldwide, except in China, where the brands are operated by a separate company, Yum China. Prior to 2011, Yum! owned Long John Silver&amp;rsquo;s and A&amp;amp;W Restaurants.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grubhub</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/grubhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/grubhub/</guid>
      <description> Grubhub Inc. is an American online and mobile food ordering and delivery marketplace that connects diners with local takeout restaurants. Based in Chicago, as of Q1 2019 the company has 19.9 million active users and 115,000 associated restaurants across 2,200 cities in the United States.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprite</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sprite/</guid>
      <description> Sprite is a colorless, caffeine-free, lemon and lime-flavored soft drink created by The Coca-Cola Company. It was first developed in West Germany in 1959 as Fanta Klare Zitrone (“Clear Lemon Fanta”) and was introduced in the United States under the current brand name Sprite in 1961 as a competitor to 7 Up.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Hortons</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tim-hortons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tim-hortons/</guid>
      <description> Tim Hortons Inc. (known as Tim Hortons Cafe and Bake Shop in some countries) is a fast food restaurant chain, specializing in coffee and donut items. It is Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest quick service restaurant chain; as of December 31, 2018, it had a total of 4,846 restaurants in 14 countries. The company has its headquarters in Toronto.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger King</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/burger-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/burger-king/</guid>
      <description> Burger King (BK) is an American global chain of hamburger fast food restaurants. Headquartered in the unincorporated area of Miami-Dade County, Florida, the company was founded in 1953 as Insta-Burger King, a Jacksonville, Florida–based restaurant chain. After Insta-Burger King ran into financial difficulties in 1954, its two Miami-based franchisees David Edgerton and James McLamore purchased the company and renamed it &amp;ldquo;Burger King&amp;rdquo;.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle/</guid>
      <description> Chipotle Mexican Grill, Inc. is an American chain of fast casual restaurants in the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, Germany, and France, specializing in tacos and Mission-style burritos. Its name derives from chipotle, the Nahuatl name for a smoked and dried jalapeño chili pepper. The company trades on the New York Stock Exchange under the ticker symbol CMG.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chobani</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani/</guid>
      <description> Chobani is an American dairy processor specializing in strained yogurt. The company was founded in 2005 when Hamdi Ulukaya bought a plant in the town of South Edmeston, New York, that was being closed by Kraft Foods. Ulukaya hired several of the former Kraft employees as well as a &amp;ldquo;yogurt master&amp;rdquo; and launched his brand in 2007.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Hut</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pizza-hut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pizza-hut/</guid>
      <description>Pizza Hut is an American restaurant chain and international franchise which was founded in 1958 by Dan and Frank Carney. The company is known for its Italian-American cuisine menu, including pizza and pasta, as well as side dishes and desserts. Pizza Hut has 18,431 restaurants worldwide as of December 31, 2018, making it the world&amp;rsquo;s largest pizza chain in terms of locations. It is a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</guid>
      <description> Popeyes is an American multinational chain of fried chicken fast food restaurants founded in 1972 in New Orleans, Louisiana and headquartered in Miami, Florida. Since 2008, its full brand name is Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen, Inc., and it was formerly named Popeyes Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits and Popeyes Famous Fried Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits. It is currently a subsidiary of Toronto-based Restaurant Brands International.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</guid>
      <description>Subway is an American privately held fast food restaurant franchise that primarily sells submarine sandwiches (subs) and salads. Subway is one of the fastest-growing franchises in the world and, as of June 2017, had approximately 42,000 stores located in more than 100 countries. More than half of the stores are located in the United States. It is the largest single-brand restaurant chain, and the largest restaurant operator, in the world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</guid>
      <description> Danone S.A. is a French multinational food-products corporation based in Paris and founded in Barcelona, Spain. The company is listed on Euronext Paris where it is a component of the CAC 40 stock market index. Some of the company’s products are branded Dannon in the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin Donuts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Dunkin&amp;rsquo; (formerly known as Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts from 1950 to 2019) is an American multinational coffee company and quick service restaurant. It was founded by William Rosenberg in Quincy, Massachusetts in 1950. The chain was acquired by Baskin-Robbins&amp;rsquo; holding company Allied Lyons in 1990; its acquisition of the Mister Donut chain and conversion to Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts facilitated the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth in North America that year. Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts and Baskin-Robbins have been subsidiaries of Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Brands, headquartered in Canton, Massachusetts, since 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelloggs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kelloggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kelloggs/</guid>
      <description> The Kellogg Company, doing business as Kellogg&amp;rsquo;s, is an American multinational food manufacturing company headquartered in Battle Creek, Michigan, United States. Kellogg&amp;rsquo;s produces cereal and convenience foods, including cookies, crackers, and toaster pastries and markets their products by several well known brands including Corn Flakes, Frosted Flakes, Keebler, Pringles, Eggo, and Cheez-It. Kellogg&amp;rsquo;s mission statement is &amp;ldquo;Nourishing families so they can flourish and thrive.&amp;rdquo;
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nestle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</guid>
      <description> Nestlé S.A. is a Swiss multinational food and drink company headquartered in Vevey, Vaud, Switzerland. It is the largest food company in the world, measured by revenues and other metrics, since 2014. It ranked No. 64 on the Fortune Global 500 in 2017 and No. 33 on the 2016 edition of the Forbes Global 2000 list of largest public companies.[
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coca Cola</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsico</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Cola</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet Coke</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coca Cola Light</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coca Cola Life</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McDonalds</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s is an American fast food company, founded in 1940 as a restaurant operated by Richard and Maurice McDonald, in San Bernardino, California, United States. They rechristened their business as a hamburger stand, and later turned the company into a franchise, with the Golden Arches logo being introduced in 1953 at a location in Phoenix, Arizona. In 1955, Ray Kroc, a businessman, joined the company as a franchise agent and proceeded to purchase the chain from the McDonald brothers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>