<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger King</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/burger-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/burger-king/</guid>
      <description> Burger King (BK) is an American global chain of hamburger fast food restaurants. Headquartered in the unincorporated area of Miami-Dade County, Florida, the company was founded in 1953 as Insta-Burger King, a Jacksonville, Florida–based restaurant chain. After Insta-Burger King ran into financial difficulties in 1954, its two Miami-based franchisees David Edgerton and James McLamore purchased the company and renamed it &amp;ldquo;Burger King&amp;rdquo;.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle/</guid>
      <description> Chipotle Mexican Grill, Inc. is an American chain of fast casual restaurants in the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, Germany, and France, specializing in tacos and Mission-style burritos. Its name derives from chipotle, the Nahuatl name for a smoked and dried jalapeño chili pepper. The company trades on the New York Stock Exchange under the ticker symbol CMG.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chobani</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani/</guid>
      <description> Chobani is an American dairy processor specializing in strained yogurt. The company was founded in 2005 when Hamdi Ulukaya bought a plant in the town of South Edmeston, New York, that was being closed by Kraft Foods. Ulukaya hired several of the former Kraft employees as well as a &amp;ldquo;yogurt master&amp;rdquo; and launched his brand in 2007.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Hut</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pizza-hut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pizza-hut/</guid>
      <description>Pizza Hut is an American restaurant chain and international franchise which was founded in 1958 by Dan and Frank Carney. The company is known for its Italian-American cuisine menu, including pizza and pasta, as well as side dishes and desserts. Pizza Hut has 18,431 restaurants worldwide as of December 31, 2018, making it the world&amp;rsquo;s largest pizza chain in terms of locations. It is a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/popeyes/</guid>
      <description> Popeyes is an American multinational chain of fried chicken fast food restaurants founded in 1972 in New Orleans, Louisiana and headquartered in Miami, Florida. Since 2008, its full brand name is Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen, Inc., and it was formerly named Popeyes Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits and Popeyes Famous Fried Chicken &amp;amp; Biscuits. It is currently a subsidiary of Toronto-based Restaurant Brands International.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/subway/</guid>
      <description>Subway is an American privately held fast food restaurant franchise that primarily sells submarine sandwiches (subs) and salads. Subway is one of the fastest-growing franchises in the world and, as of June 2017, had approximately 42,000 stores located in more than 100 countries. More than half of the stores are located in the United States. It is the largest single-brand restaurant chain, and the largest restaurant operator, in the world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/danone/</guid>
      <description> Danone S.A. is a French multinational food-products corporation based in Paris and founded in Barcelona, Spain. The company is listed on Euronext Paris where it is a component of the CAC 40 stock market index. Some of the company’s products are branded Dannon in the United States.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin Donuts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Dunkin&amp;rsquo; (formerly known as Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts from 1950 to 2019) is an American multinational coffee company and quick service restaurant. It was founded by William Rosenberg in Quincy, Massachusetts in 1950. The chain was acquired by Baskin-Robbins&amp;rsquo; holding company Allied Lyons in 1990; its acquisition of the Mister Donut chain and conversion to Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts facilitated the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth in North America that year. Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts and Baskin-Robbins have been subsidiaries of Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Brands, headquartered in Canton, Massachusetts, since 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelloggs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kelloggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kelloggs/</guid>
      <description> The Kellogg Company, doing business as Kellogg&amp;rsquo;s, is an American multinational food manufacturing company headquartered in Battle Creek, Michigan, United States. Kellogg&amp;rsquo;s produces cereal and convenience foods, including cookies, crackers, and toaster pastries and markets their products by several well known brands including Corn Flakes, Frosted Flakes, Keebler, Pringles, Eggo, and Cheez-It. Kellogg&amp;rsquo;s mission statement is &amp;ldquo;Nourishing families so they can flourish and thrive.&amp;rdquo;
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nestle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</guid>
      <description> Nestlé S.A. is a Swiss multinational food and drink company headquartered in Vevey, Vaud, Switzerland. It is the largest food company in the world, measured by revenues and other metrics, since 2014. It ranked No. 64 on the Fortune Global 500 in 2017 and No. 33 on the 2016 edition of the Forbes Global 2000 list of largest public companies.[
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Bell</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/taco-bell/</guid>
      <description>Taco Bell is an American chain of fast food restaurants based out of Irvine, California and a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc. The restaurants serve a variety of Mexican inspired foods that include tacos, burritos, quesadillas, nachos, novelty and specialty items, and a variety of &amp;ldquo;value menu&amp;rdquo; items. As of 2018, Taco Bell serves more than 2 billion customers each year at 7,072 restaurants, more than 93 percent of which are owned and operated by independent franchisees and licensees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coca Cola</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsico</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsico/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Cola</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pepsi-cola/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet Coke</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/diet-coke/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coca Cola Light</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coca Cola Life</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McDonalds</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s is an American fast food company, founded in 1940 as a restaurant operated by Richard and Maurice McDonald, in San Bernardino, California, United States. They rechristened their business as a hamburger stand, and later turned the company into a franchise, with the Golden Arches logo being introduced in 1953 at a location in Phoenix, Arizona. In 1955, Ray Kroc, a businessman, joined the company as a franchise agent and proceeded to purchase the chain from the McDonald brothers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>