<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Emirates on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/emirates/</link><description>Recent content in Emirates on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/emirates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad Airways</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/etihad-airways/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/etihad-airways/</guid><description>Etihad Airways (Arabic: شَرِكَة ٱلْاِتِّحَاد لِلطَّيْرَان‎, romanized: sharikat al-ittiḥād li-ṭ-ṭayarān) is the flag carrier of the UAE and the second-largest airline in the country (after Emirates). Its head office is in Khalifa City, Abu Dhabi, near Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s International Airport. Etihad commenced operations in November 2003.
The airline operates more than 1,000 flights per week to over 120 passenger and cargo destinations in the Middle East, Africa, Europe, Asia, Australia, and North America, with a fleet of 102 Airbus and Boeing aircraft as of February 2020.</description></item><item><title>Meraas</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/meraas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/meraas/</guid><description> Meraas is a holding company based in Dubai with operations and assets in the United Arab Emirates.
Source Source</description></item><item><title>Emirates Airlines</title><link>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/emirates-airlines/</guid><description>Emirates is an airline based in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. The airline is a subsidiary of The Emirates Group, which is wholly owned by the government of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Investment Corporation of Dubai. It is the largest airline in the Middle East, operating over 3,600 flights per week from its hub at Dubai International Airport, to more than 150 cities in 80 countries across six continents. Cargo activities are undertaken by Emirates SkyCargo.</description></item></channel></rss>