<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>C on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/c/</link><description>Recent content in C on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/c/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cory-booker//file/cory-booker.svg</url><title>Cory Booker Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cory Booker</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cory-booker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cory-booker/</guid><description turbo="true"> The 2020 Presidential Campaign of U.S. Senator Cory Booker was announced on February 1, 2019, when a video titled &amp;ldquo;We Will Rise&amp;rdquo; was posted on Booker&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel. He intentionally chose the first day of Black History Month to announce his candidacy. Booker suspended his campaign on January 13, 2020.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cisco//file/cisco.svg</url><title>Cisco Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cisco</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cisco/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0015</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cisco/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cisco Systems, Inc. is an American multinational technology conglomerate headquartered in San Jose, California, in the center of Silicon Valley. Cisco develops, manufactures and sells networking hardware, telecommunications equipment and other high-technology services and products. Through its numerous acquired subsidiaries, such as OpenDNS, WebEx, Jabber and Jasper, Cisco specializes into specific tech markets, such as Internet of Things (IoT), domain security and energy management.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola//file/coca-cola.svg</url><title>Coca-Cola Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coca-Cola</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0006</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coca-Cola, or Coke, is a carbonated soft drink manufactured by The Coca-Cola Company. Originally marketed as a temperance drink and intended as a patent medicine, it was invented in the late 19th century by John Stith Pemberton and was bought out by businessman Asa Griggs Candler, whose marketing tactics led Coca-Cola to its dominance of the world soft-drink market throughout the 20th century.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/c-sharp//file/c-sharp.svg</url><title>C-sharp Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">C-sharp</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/c-sharp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/c-sharp/</guid><description turbo="true">C# is a general-purpose, multi-paradigm programming language encompassing strong typing, lexically scoped, imperative, declarative, functional, generic, object-oriented (class-based), and component-oriented programming disciplines. It was developed around 2000 by Microsoft as part of its .NET initiative and later approved as an international standard by Ecma (ECMA-334) in 2002 and ISO (ISO/IEC 23270) in 2003. Mono is the name of the free and open-source project to develop a compiler and runtime for the language.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank//file/commonwealth-bank.svg</url><title>Commonwealth Bank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Commonwealth Bank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank/</guid><description turbo="true">The Commonwealth Bank of Australia (CBA), or CommBank, is an Australian multinational bank with businesses across New Zealand, Asia, the United States and the United Kingdom. It provides a variety of financial services including retail, business and institutional banking, funds management, superannuation, insurance, investment and broking services. The Commonwealth Bank is the largest Australian listed company on the Australian Securities Exchange as of August 2015 with brands including Bankwest, Colonial First State Investments, ASB Bank (New Zealand), Commonwealth Securities (CommSec) and Commonwealth Insurance (CommInsure).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/creative-cloud//file/creative-cloud.svg</url><title>Creative Cloud Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Creative Cloud</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/creative-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/creative-cloud/</guid><description turbo="true">Adobe Creative Cloud is a set of applications and services from Adobe Inc. that gives subscribers access to a collection of software used for graphic design, video editing, web development, photography, along with a set of mobile applications and also some optional cloud services.
Source About Adobe Creative Cloud Suite Creative Cloud is a collection of 20+ desktop and mobile apps and services for photography, design, video, web, UX and more.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/capri//file/capri.svg</url><title>Capri Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Capri</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/capri/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/capri/</guid><description turbo="true">Capri Holdings Limited (formerly Michael Kors Holdings Limited) is a multinational fashion holding company, incorporated in the British Virgin Islands, with principal executive offices in London and operational headquarters in New York. It was founded in 1981 by American designer Michael Kors. The company sells clothes, shoes, watches, handbags, and other accessories. Michael Kors handbags have been a popular fashion trend among women of all ages. In 2015, the company had more than 550 stores and over 1500 in-store boutiques in various countries.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc//file/cdc.svg</url><title>CDC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CDC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 22:22:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cdc/</guid><description turbo="true">CDC is responding to the novel coronavirus outbreak. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is the leading national public health institute of the United States. The CDC is a United States federal agency under the Department of Health and Human Services and is headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/calvin-klein//file/calvin-klein.svg</url><title>Calvin Klein Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Calvin Klein</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/calvin-klein/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calvin-klein/</guid><description turbo="true"> Calvin Klein Inc. is an American fashion house established in 1968. It specializes in leather, lifestyle accessories, home furnishings, perfumery, jewellery, watches and ready-to-wear. The company has substantial market share in retail and commercial lines as well haute couture garments.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cargill//file/cargill.svg</url><title>Cargill Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cargill</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cargill/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cargill/</guid><description turbo="true">Cargill, Incorporated is an American privately held global corporation based in Minnetonka, Minnesota, and incorporated in Wilmington, Delaware. Founded in 1865, it is the largest privately held corporation in the United States in terms of revenue. If it were a public company, it would rank, as of 2015, number 15 on the Fortune 500, behind McKesson and ahead of AT&amp;amp;T. Cargill has frequently been the subject of criticism related to the environment, human rights, finance, and other ethical considerations.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/carlsberg//file/carlsberg.svg</url><title>Carlsberg Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Carlsberg</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/carlsberg/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/carlsberg/</guid><description turbo="true">Carlsberg A/S is a global brewer. Founded in 1847 by J. C. Jacobsen, the company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters is located in Copenhagen, Denmark. Since Jacobsen&amp;rsquo;s death in 1887, the majority owner of the company has been the Carlsberg Foundation. The company&amp;rsquo;s flagship brand is Carlsberg (named after Jacobsen&amp;rsquo;s son Carl). It also brews Tuborg, Kronenbourg, Somersby cider, Russia&amp;rsquo;s best-selling beer Baltika, Belgian Grimbergen abbey beers, and more than 500 local beers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network//file/cartoon-network.svg</url><title>Cartoon Network Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cartoon Network</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network/</guid><description turbo="true">Cartoon Network is an American pay television channel owned by Warner Bros. Entertainment, a division of AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. The channel was launched on October 1, 1992, and primarily broadcasts animated television series, mostly children&amp;rsquo;s programming, ranging from action to animated comedy. It operates usually from 6:00 AM to 8:00 PM (ET/PT) and is targeted at children between ages 7 and 15. Its overnight daypart block Adult Swim is aimed at adults and is treated as a separate entity for promotional purposes and as a separate channel by Nielsen for ratings purposes.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs//file/cbs.svg</url><title>CBS Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CBS</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbs/</guid><description turbo="true">CBS (an initialism of the network&amp;rsquo;s former name, the Columbia Broadcasting System) is an American English-language commercial broadcast television and radio network that is the flagship property of the CBS Entertainment Group division of ViacomCBS. The company is headquartered at the CBS Building in New York City with major production facilities and operations in New York City (at the CBS Broadcast Center) and Los Angeles (at CBS Television City and the CBS Studio Center).</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/claro//file/claro.svg</url><title>Claro Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Claro</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/claro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/claro/</guid><description turbo="true"> Claro Americas is a Brazilian company part of América Móvil, a Mexican telecom group. Claro serves clients in Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, the Dominican Republic, Ecuador, El Salvador, Guatemala, Honduras, Nicaragua, Panama, Paraguay, Peru, Puerto Rico and Uruguay. The company&amp;rsquo;s name means &amp;ldquo;bright&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;clear&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo; in Portuguese and Spanish.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast//file/comcast.svg</url><title>Comcast Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Comcast</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/comcast/</guid><description turbo="true">Comcast Corporation (formerly registered as Comcast Holdings)[note 1] is an American telecommunications conglomerate headquartered in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. It is the second-largest broadcasting and cable television company in the world by revenue and the largest pay-TV company, the largest cable TV company and largest home Internet service provider in the United States, and the nation&amp;rsquo;s third-largest home telephone service provider. Comcast services U.S. residential and commercial customers in 40 states and in the District of Columbia.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/comedy-central//file/comedy-central.svg</url><title>Comedy Central Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Comedy Central</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/comedy-central/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/comedy-central/</guid><description turbo="true"> Comedy Central is an American pay television channel owned by ViacomCBS through its ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division&amp;rsquo;s Entertainment &amp;amp; Youth Group unit, based in Manhattan. The channel is geared for mature audiences and carries comedy programming in the form of both original, licensed, and syndicated series, stand-up comedy specials, and feature films.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/compass//file/compass.svg</url><title>Compass Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Compass</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/compass/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/compass/</guid><description turbo="true">Compass is a licensed real estate broker that utilizes the Internet as a marketing medium with the use of real estate technology. Compass employs more than 10,000 agents who earn a percentage of the selling price and give 15 to 30 percent on each sale to Compass. The Company specializes in high-margin, luxury homes in upscale, coastal markets. Founded in 2012, the company is headquartered in New York City. The company provides software to real estate agents.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities//file/conceive-abilities.svg</url><title>Conceive Abilities Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Conceive Abilities</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conceive-abilities/</guid><description turbo="true"> At ConceiveAbilities® Conceive Abilities believe that everyone who wants to become a parent, can. Conceive Abilities have helped build thousands of families for nearly 25 years. Whether you are an intended parent ready to fulfill your family destiny, a surrogate answering your calling or an egg donor wanting to expand what’s possible in your life—Conceive Abilities are your people.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle//file/crown-castle.svg</url><title>Crown Castle Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Crown Castle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle/</guid><description turbo="true">Crown Castle is a real estate investment trust and the largest provider of shared communications infrastructure in the United States, with more than 40,000 cell towers and approximately 70,000 route miles of fiber supporting small cells and fiber solutions.
Source s</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cruise//file/cruise.svg</url><title>Cruise Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cruise</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cruise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cruise/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cruise LLC, commonly referred to as Cruise, is an American self-driving car company headquartered in San Francisco, California. Founded in 2013 by Kyle Vogt and Dan Kan, Cruise tests and develops autonomous car technology.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-company//file/coca-cola-company.svg</url><title>Coca-Cola Company Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coca-Cola Company</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0006</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-company/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Coca-Cola Company is an American multinational beverage corporation incorporated under Delaware&amp;rsquo;s General Corporation Law and headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia. The Coca-Cola Company has interests in the manufacturing, retailing, and marketing of nonalcoholic beverage concentrates and syrups.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/capexmd//file/capexmd.svg</url><title>CapexMD Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CapexMD</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/capexmd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/capexmd/</guid><description turbo="true">CAPEXMD specializes in providing patient financing services for all fertility treatment options. CapexMD easy, convenient loan process and competitive rates ensures that the financial aspects of treatment are not an obstacle to achieving your dream of a family. CAPEXMD offers a wide variety of loan options, allowing you to attain the necessary financing required to make your treatment affordable. Each loan program is designed to fit your individual circumstances and once approved, CapexMD Fertility Loan Specialists will work closely with CapexMD fertility center partners to ensure the funds are secured prior to the commencement of your treatment.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano//file/cardano.svg</url><title>Cardano Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cardano</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cardano is een open source cryptovaluta blockchain platform waarop slimme contracten kunnen draaien.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/circle//file/circle.svg</url><title>Circle Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Circle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/circle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/circle/</guid><description turbo="true">Circle is a peer-to-peer payments technology company. It was founded by Jeremy Allaire and Sean Neville in October 2013. Circle&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment platform, Circle Pay, allows users to hold, send, and receive traditional fiat currencies . In September 2015, Circle received the first BitLicense issued from the New York State Department of Financial Services. In April 2016, the British government approved the first virtual currency licensure to Circle. Circle is headquartered in Boston, Massachusetts.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase//file/coinbase.svg</url><title>Coinbase Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coinbase</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coinbase is a digital currency exchange headquartered in San Francisco, California. They broker exchanges of Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic, and Litecoin with fiat currencies in approximately 32 countries, and bitcoin transactions and storage in 190 countries worldwide.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi//file/coinomi.svg</url><title>Coinomi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coinomi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coinomi – is one of the first, and most trusted, cryptocurrency multiwallets. Coinomi is a non-custodial multiwallet and your private keys are stored securely encrypted on your device at all times. The wallet is available on all platforms and the only official download sources are listed on the Coinomi website. Coinomi currently supports more than 125 blockchains and has FULL support for all Ethereum Tokens.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/confluence//file/confluence.svg</url><title>Confluence Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Confluence</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/confluence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/confluence/</guid><description turbo="true"> Confluence is your collaborative workspace where teams and knowledge meet to achieve great things.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-audio//file/crown-audio.svg</url><title>Crown Audio Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Crown Audio</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-audio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-audio/</guid><description turbo="true"> Crown International, or Crown Audio, is an American manufacturer of audio electronics, and is a subsidiary of Harman International Industries, which has been part of South Korea-based Samsung Electronics since 2017. Today, the company is known primarily for its power amplifiers, but has also manufactured microphones, a line of commercial audio products as well as digital audio networking products.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health//file/cardinal-health.svg</url><title>Cardinal Health Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cardinal Health</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardinal-health/</guid><description turbo="true">Cardinal Health, Inc. is an American multinational health care services company, and the 14th highest revenue generating company in the United States. Its headquarters are based in Dublin, Ohio and Dublin, Ireland (EMEA). The company specializes in distribution of pharmaceuticals and medical products, serving more than 100,000 locations. The company also manufactures medical and surgical products, including gloves, surgical apparel and fluid management products. In addition, it operates the largest network of radiopharmacies in the U.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news//file/cbc-news.svg</url><title>CBC News Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CBC News</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</guid><description turbo="true">CBC News is the division of the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation responsible for the news gathering and production of news programs on the corporation&amp;rsquo;s English-language operations, namely CBC Television, CBC Radio, CBC News Network, and CBC.ca. Founded in 1941, CBC News is the largest news broadcaster in Canada and has local, regional and national broadcasts and stations. It frequently collaborates with its French-language counterpart, Radio-Canada Info, although the two are organizationally separate.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre//file/cbre.svg</url><title>CBRE Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CBRE</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</guid><description turbo="true"> CBRE Group, Inc., is an American commercial real estate services and investment firm. The abbreviation CBRE stands for Coldwell Banker Richard Ellis. As of 2018, it is the largest commercial real estate services company in the world.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute//file/cfa-institute.svg</url><title>CFA Institute Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CFA Institute</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</guid><description turbo="true"> The organization offers the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) designation, the Certificate in Investment Performance Measurement (CIPM) designation, and the Investment Foundations Certificate. It provides continuing education conferences, seminars, webcasts, and publications to allow members and other participants to stay current on developments in the investment industry. CFA Institute also oversees the CFA Institute Research Challenge for university students and the Research Foundation of CFA Institute.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chevron//file/chevron.svg</url><title>Chevron Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chevron</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chevron/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chevron/</guid><description turbo="true">Chevron Corporation is an American multinational energy corporation. One of the successor companies of Standard Oil, it is headquartered in San Ramon, California, and active in more than 180 countries. Chevron is engaged in every aspect of the oil, natural gas, and geothermal energy industries, including hydrocarbon exploration and production; refining, marketing and transport; chemicals manufacturing and sales; and power generation. Chevron is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest oil companies; as of 2019, it ranked eleventh in the Fortune 500 list of the top US closely held and public corporations and 28th on the Fortune Global 500 list of the top 500 corporations worldwide.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci//file/ci.svg</url><title>CI Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CI</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ci/</guid><description turbo="true"> Conservation International (CI) is an American nonprofit environmental organization headquartered in Arlington, Virginia. Its goal is to protect nature as a source of food, fresh water, livelihoods and a stable climate.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil//file/cirque-du-soleil.svg</url><title>Cirque du Soleil Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cirque du Soleil</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cirque du Soleil (French: [sɪʁk dzy sɔ.lɛj], &amp;ldquo;Circus of the Sun&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Sun Circus&amp;rdquo;) is a Canadian (Quebecois) entertainment company and the largest theatrical producer in the world. Based in Montreal, Quebec, Canada, and located in the inner-city area of Saint-Michel, it was founded in Baie-Saint-Paul on 7 July 1984, by two former street performers, Guy Laliberté and Gilles Ste-Croix.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/citizens//file/citizens.svg</url><title>Citizens Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Citizens</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/citizens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citizens/</guid><description turbo="true"> Citizens Financial Group, Inc. is an American bank headquartered in Providence, Rhode Island, which operates in the states of Connecticut, Delaware, Maine, Massachusetts, Michigan, New Hampshire, New Jersey, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island and Vermont.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cna//file/cna.svg</url><title>cna Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">cna</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cna/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cna/</guid><description turbo="true"> CNA is an English language news channel based in Singapore. It broadcasts free-to-air domestically and as a subscription network to 29 territories across Asia and Australia.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc//file/cnbc.svg</url><title>CNBC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNBC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnbc/</guid><description turbo="true">CNBC is an American pay television business news channel that is owned by NBCUniversal Broadcast, Cable, Sports and News, a division of NBCUniversal, with both being ultimately owned by Comcast. Headquartered in Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey, the network primarily carries business day coverage of U.S. and international financial markets; following the end of the business day and on non-trading days, CNBC primarily carries financial and business-themed documentaries and reality shows.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn//file/cnn.svg</url><title>CNN Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNN</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cable News Network (CNN) is an American news-based pay television channel owned by AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. CNN was founded in 1980 by American media proprietor Ted Turner as a 24-hour cable news channel. Upon its launch, CNN was the first television channel to provide 24-hour news coverage, and was the first all-news television channel in the United States.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport//file/cnn-airport.svg</url><title>CNN Airport Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNN Airport</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-airport/</guid><description turbo="true"> CNN Airport is an American out-of-home television network operated by CNN. The service broadcasts general news, weather, stock market updates, entertainment, and travel content to airports across the United States. The founding management was led by Jon Petrovich and Scott Weiss. Deborah Cooper was the inaugural vice president/general manager, and continues in the role today.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol//file/cnn-en-espanol.svg</url><title>CNN en Espanol Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNN en Espanol</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnn-en-espanol/</guid><description turbo="true"> CNN en Español (stylized as CN͠N) is a Pan-American Spanish-language news channel, owned by WarnerMedia. It was launched on pay television, on 17 March 1997.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus//file/cnnplus.svg</url><title>CNNplus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNNplus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</guid><description turbo="true"> CNN+ (CNN Plus) was a Spanish 24-hour television news channel. Launched in 1999 as a joint venture by Sogecable and Turner Broadcasting, a unit of Time Warner that owns CNN, it went off the air at the end of 28 December 2010. The management announced that CNN+ would be closed on 31 December 2010.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group//file/cnooc-group.svg</url><title>CNOOC Group Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNOOC Group</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnooc-group/</guid><description turbo="true">China National Offshore Oil Corporation, or CNOOC Group (Chinese: 中国海洋石油总公司 Pinyin: Zhōngguó Háiyáng Shíyóu Zǒnggōngsī), is one of the largest national oil companies in China. It is the third-largest national oil company in the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, after CNPC (parent of PetroChina) and China Petrochemical Corporation (parent of Sinopec).[citation needed] The CNOOC Group focuses on the exploitation, exploration and development of crude oil and natural gas in offshore China, alongwith its subsidiary COOEC.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc//file/cnpc.svg</url><title>CNPC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNPC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnpc/</guid><description turbo="true"> The China National Petroleum Corporation (CNPC) is a major national oil and gas corporation of China PR and one of the largest integrated energy groups in the world. Its headquarters are in Dongcheng District, Beijing. CNPC was ranked fourth in 2017 Fortune Global 500, a global ranking of the largest corporations by revenue
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent//file/conduent.svg</url><title>Conduent Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Conduent</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conduent/</guid><description turbo="true"> Conduent Inc. is a technology-led business process services company headquartered in New Jersey. It was formed in 2017 as a divestiture from Xerox.The company offers digital platforms for businesses and governments. It has 85,000 employees in more than 40 countries.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/conocophillips//file/conocophillips.svg</url><title>ConocoPhillips Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ConocoPhillips</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/conocophillips/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conocophillips/</guid><description turbo="true">ConocoPhillips is an American multinational energy corporation with its headquarters located in the Energy Corridor district of Houston, Texas in the United States. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest independent pure-play exploration and production company and the company ranked No. 95 in the 2018 Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue. ConocoPhillips was created through the merger of American oil companies Conoco Inc. and Phillips Petroleum Co.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels//file/conrad-hotels.svg</url><title>Conrad Hotels Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Conrad Hotels</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/conrad-hotels/</guid><description turbo="true">Conrad Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is an international brand of luxury hotels and resorts owned and operated by Hilton Worldwide. Conrad was considered the luxury flagship brand in the Hilton Family of Brands, named after company founder Conrad Hilton, until being supplanted by The Waldorf-Astoria Collection in 2006. As of December 31, 2018, it as 33 locations with 10,625 rooms, including two that are owned or leased with 778 rooms, 29 that are managed with 8,874 rooms, and two that are franchised with 973 rooms.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell//file/cornell.svg</url><title>Cornell Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cornell</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cornell/</guid><description turbo="true">Cornell University (/kɔːrˈnɛl/ kor-NEL) is a private and statutory Ivy League research university in Ithaca, New York. Founded in 1865 by Ezra Cornell and Andrew Dickson White, the university was intended to teach and make contributions in all fields of knowledge—from the classics to the sciences, and from the theoretical to the applied. These ideals, unconventional for the time, are captured in Cornell&amp;rsquo;s founding principle, a popular 1868 Ezra Cornell quotation: &amp;ldquo;I would found an institution where any person can find instruction in any study.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/costco//file/costco.svg</url><title>Costco Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Costco</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/costco/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/costco/</guid><description turbo="true">Costco Wholesale Corporation, doing business as Costco, is an American multinational corporation which operates a chain of membership-only warehouse clubs. As of 2015, Costco was the second largest retailer in the world after Walmart, and as of 2016, Costco was the world&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer of choice and prime beef, organic foods, rotisserie chicken, and wine. Costco is ranked #15 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero//file/course-hero.svg</url><title>Course Hero Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Course Hero</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/course-hero/</guid><description turbo="true">Course Hero is an education technology website company based in Redwood City, California, which operates an online learning platform for students to access course-specific study resources contributed by a community of students and educators. The crowdsourced learning platform contains practice problems, study guides, infographics, class notes, step-by-step explanations, essays, lab reports, videos, user-submitted questions paired with answers from tutors, and original materials created and uploaded by educators. Users either buy a subscription or upload original documents to receive unlocks that are used to view and download full Course Hero documents.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/crocs//file/crocs.svg</url><title>Crocs Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Crocs</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/crocs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crocs/</guid><description turbo="true"> Crocs, Inc. is an American company, based in Niwot, Colorado, that distributes and once manufactured a foam clog shoe.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/csu//file/csu.svg</url><title>CSU Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CSU</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/csu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/csu/</guid><description turbo="true"> Colorado State University (also referred to as Colorado State, State, and CSU) is a public research university in Fort Collins, Colorado. The university is the state&amp;rsquo;s land grant university and the flagship university of the Colorado State University System.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv//file/ctv.svg</url><title>CTV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CTV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ctv/</guid><description turbo="true"> CTV News Channel is a Canadian discretionary service that is owned by Bell Media (a wholly owned subsidiary of Bell Canada). It broadcasts national and international news headlines, breaking news, and information. The channel is headquartered at 9 Channel Nine Court in the Agincourt neighbourhood of Scarborough in the city of Toronto.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/calgary-flames//file/calgary-flames.svg</url><title>Calgary Flames Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Calgary Flames</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/calgary-flames/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calgary-flames/</guid><description turbo="true">The Calgary Flames are a professional ice hockey team based in Calgary, Alberta. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The club is the third major-professional ice hockey team to represent the city of Calgary, following the Calgary Tigers (1921–1927) and Calgary Cowboys (1975–1977). The Flames are one of two NHL franchises in Alberta; the other is the Edmonton Oilers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-hurricanes//file/carolina-hurricanes.svg</url><title>Carolina Hurricanes Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Carolina Hurricanes</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-hurricanes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-hurricanes/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Carolina Hurricanes are a professional ice hockey team based in Raleigh, North Carolina. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Hurricanes play their home games at the 18,680-seat PNC Arena.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets//file/charlotte-hornets.svg</url><title>Charlotte Hornets Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Charlotte Hornets</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Charlotte Hornets are an American professional basketball team based in Charlotte, North Carolina. The Hornets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Southeast Division. The team is largely owned by retired NBA player Michael Jordan, who acquired controlling interest in the team in 2010. The Hornets play their home games at the Spectrum Center in Uptown Charlotte.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-blackhawks//file/chicago-blackhawks.svg</url><title>Chicago Blackhawks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Blackhawks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-blackhawks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-blackhawks/</guid><description turbo="true">The Chicago Blackhawks (spelled Black Hawks until 1986, and known colloquially as the Hawks) are a professional ice hockey team based in Chicago, Illinois. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). They have won six Stanley Cup championships since their founding in 1926. The Blackhawks are one of the &amp;ldquo;Original Six&amp;rdquo; NHL teams along with the Detroit Red Wings, Montreal Canadiens, Toronto Maple Leafs, Boston Bruins and New York Rangers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bulls//file/chicago-bulls.svg</url><title>Chicago Bulls Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Bulls</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bulls/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bulls/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Chicago Bulls are an American professional basketball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The Bulls compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division. The team was founded on January 16, 1966. The team plays its home games at the United Center, an arena shared with the Chicago Blackhawks of the National Hockey League (NHL).
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc//file/chicago-fire-fc.svg</url><title>Chicago Fire FC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Fire FC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc/</guid><description turbo="true">Chicago Fire Football Club is an American professional soccer club based in Chicago, Illinois. The team competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the league’s Eastern Conference, having moved to the conference in 2002. The franchise is named after the Great Chicago Fire of 1871, and was founded as the Chicago Fire Soccer Club on October 8, 1997, the event’s 126th anniversary. The team began play in 1998 as one of the league’s first expansion teams.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-cavaliers//file/cleveland-cavaliers.svg</url><title>Cleveland Cavaliers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cleveland Cavaliers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-cavaliers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-cavaliers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Cleveland Cavaliers, often referred to as the Cavs, are an American professional basketball team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Cavs compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division. The team began play as an expansion team in 1970, along with the Portland Trail Blazers and Buffalo Braves. Home games were first held at Cleveland Arena from 1970 to 1974, followed by the Richfield Coliseum from 1974 to 1994.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-avalanche//file/colorado-avalanche.svg</url><title>Colorado Avalanche Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Colorado Avalanche</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-avalanche/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-avalanche/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Colorado Avalanche are a professional ice hockey team based in Denver, Colorado. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Avalanche are the only team in their division not based in the Central Time Zone; the team is situated in the Mountain Time Zone. Their home arena is Pepsi Center. Their general manager is Joe Sakic.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rapids//file/colorado-rapids.svg</url><title>Colorado Rapids Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Colorado Rapids</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rapids/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rapids/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Colorado Rapids are an American professional soccer club based in the Denver suburb of Commerce City, Colorado. The Rapids compete in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the Western Conference. The franchise began play in 1996 as one of the charter clubs in MLS.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-blue-jackets//file/columbus-blue-jackets.svg</url><title>Columbus Blue Jackets Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Columbus Blue Jackets</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-blue-jackets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-blue-jackets/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Columbus Blue Jackets are a professional ice hockey team based in Columbus, Ohio. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL).
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-crew-sc//file/columbus-crew-sc.svg</url><title>Columbus Crew SC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Columbus Crew SC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-crew-sc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/columbus-crew-sc/</guid><description turbo="true">Columbus Crew Soccer Club is an American professional soccer club based in Columbus, Ohio. The Crew competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference and began play in 1996 as one of the ten charter clubs of the league. The team is currently being operated by an ownership group led by the Haslam family and former team doctor Pete Edwards. The Haslam/Edwards group is the third owner in club history.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-panthers//file/carolina-panthers.svg</url><title>Carolina Panthers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Carolina Panthers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-panthers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-panthers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Carolina Panthers are a professional American football team based in Charlotte, North Carolina. The Panthers compete in the National Football League (NFL), as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The team is headquartered in Bank of America Stadium in uptown Charlotte; the stadium also serves as the team&amp;rsquo;s home field. They are one of the few NFL teams to own the stadium they play in, which is legally registered as Panthers Stadium, LLC.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bears//file/chicago-bears.svg</url><title>Chicago Bears Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Bears</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bears/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-bears/</guid><description turbo="true">The Chicago Bears are a professional American football team based in Chicago, Illinois. The Bears compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) North division. The Bears have won nine NFL Championships, including one Super Bowl, and hold the NFL record for the most enshrinees in the Pro Football Hall of Fame and the most retired jersey numbers. The Bears have also recorded more victories than any other NFL franchise.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-cubs//file/chicago-cubs.svg</url><title>Chicago Cubs Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Cubs</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-cubs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-cubs/</guid><description turbo="true">The Chicago Cubs are an American professional baseball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The Cubs compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. The team plays its home games at Wrigley Field, located on the city&amp;rsquo;s North Side. The Cubs are one of two major league teams in Chicago; the other, the Chicago White Sox, is a member of the American League (AL) Central division.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox//file/chicago-white-sox.svg</url><title>Chicago White Sox Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago White Sox</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox/</guid><description turbo="true">The Chicago White Sox are an American professional baseball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The White Sox compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) Central division. The White Sox are owned by Jerry Reinsdorf, and play their home games at Guaranteed Rate Field, located on the city&amp;rsquo;s South Side. They are one of two major league clubs in Chicago; the other is the Chicago Cubs, who are a member of the National League (NL) Central division.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-bengals//file/cincinnati-bengals.svg</url><title>Cincinnati Bengals Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cincinnati Bengals</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-bengals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-bengals/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Cincinnati Bengals are a professional American football franchise based in Cincinnati, Ohio. The Bengals compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) North division. Their home stadium is Paul Brown Stadium in downtown Cincinnati. Their divisional opponents are the Pittsburgh Steelers, Cleveland Browns, and the Baltimore Ravens.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-reds//file/cincinnati-reds.svg</url><title>Cincinnati Reds Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cincinnati Reds</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-reds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cincinnati-reds/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Cincinnati Reds are an American professional baseball team based in Cincinnati, Ohio. The Reds compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) Central division. They were a charter member of the American Association in 1882 and joined the NL in 1890.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns//file/cleveland-browns.svg</url><title>Cleveland Browns Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cleveland Browns</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-browns/</guid><description turbo="true">The Cleveland Browns are a professional American football team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Browns compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) North division. The Browns play their home games at FirstEnergy Stadium, which opened in 1999, with administrative offices and training facilities in Berea, Ohio. The Browns&amp;rsquo; official colors are brown, orange, and white. They are unique among the 32 member franchises of the NFL in that they do not have a logo on their helmets</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians//file/cleveland-indians.svg</url><title>Cleveland Indians Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cleveland Indians</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cleveland-indians/</guid><description turbo="true">The Cleveland Indians are an American professional baseball team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Indians compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) Central division. Since 1994, they have played at Progressive Field. The team&amp;rsquo;s spring training facility is at Goodyear Ballpark in Goodyear, Arizona. Since their establishment as a major league franchise in 1901, the Indians have won two World Series championships: in 1920 and 1948, along with 10 Central Division titles and six American League pennants.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rockies//file/colorado-rockies.svg</url><title>Colorado Rockies Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Colorado Rockies</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rockies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colorado-rockies/</guid><description turbo="true">he Colorado Rockies are an American professional baseball team based in Denver, Colorado. The Rockies compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) West division. The team&amp;rsquo;s home venue is Coors Field, located in the Lower Downtown area of Denver. The Rockies won their first National League championship in 2007, after having won 14 of their final 15 games in order to secure a Wild Card position.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/casio//file/casio.svg</url><title>Casio Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Casio</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/casio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/casio/</guid><description turbo="true">Casio Computer Co., Ltd. (カシオ計算機株式会社 Kashio Keisanki Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational consumer electronics and commercial electronics manufacturing company headquartered in Shibuya, Tokyo, Japan. Its products include calculators, mobile phones, digital cameras, electronic musical instruments, and analogue and digital watches. It was founded in 1946, and in 1957 introduced the world&amp;rsquo;s first entirely electric compact calculator. It was an early digital camera innovator, and during the 1980s and 1990s, the company developed numerous affordable home electronic keyboards for musicians along with introducing the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass produced digital watches.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle//file/chipotle.svg</url><title>Chipotle Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chipotle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chipotle/</guid><description turbo="true"> Chipotle Mexican Grill, Inc. is an American chain of fast casual restaurants in the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, Germany, and France, specializing in tacos and Mission-style burritos. Its name derives from chipotle, the Nahuatl name for a smoked and dried jalapeño chili pepper. The company trades on the New York Stock Exchange under the ticker symbol CMG.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani//file/chobani.svg</url><title>Chobani Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chobani</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chobani/</guid><description turbo="true"> Chobani is an American dairy processor specializing in strained yogurt. The company was founded in 2005 when Hamdi Ulukaya bought a plant in the town of South Edmeston, New York, that was being closed by Kraft Foods. Ulukaya hired several of the former Kraft employees as well as a &amp;ldquo;yogurt master&amp;rdquo; and launched his brand in 2007.
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy//file/codecademy.svg</url><title>Codecademy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Codecademy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/codecademy/</guid><description turbo="true"> Codecademy is an online interactive platform that offers free coding classes in 12 different programming languages including Python, Java, JavaScript (jQuery, AngularJS, React.js), Ruby, SQL, C++, and Sass, as well as markup languages HTML and CSS. The site also offers a paid &amp;ldquo;pro&amp;rdquo; option that gives users access to a personalized learning plan, quizzes, realistic projects, and live help from advisors.[
Source Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs//file/cvs.svg</url><title>CVS Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CVS</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</guid><description turbo="true">CVS Pharmacy is a subsidiary of the American retail and health care company CVS Health, headquartered in Woonsocket, Rhode Island. It was also known as, and originally named, the Consumer Value Store and was founded in Lowell, Massachusetts, in 1963. The chain was owned by its original holding company Melville Corporation since its inception until its current parent company (CVS Health) was spun off into its own company in 1996.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac//file/cadillac.svg</url><title>Cadillac Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cadillac</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cadillac/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cadillac /ˈkædɪlæk/ is a division of the American automobile manufacturer General Motors (GM) that designs and builds luxury vehicles. Its major markets are the United States, Canada, and China. Cadillac vehicles are distributed in 34 additional markets worldwide. Cadillac automobiles are at the top of the luxury field within the United States. In 2017, Cadillac&amp;rsquo;s U.S. sales were 156,440 vehicles and its global sales were 356,467 vehicles.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/canon//file/canon.svg</url><title>Canon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Canon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/canon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/canon/</guid><description turbo="true"> Canon Inc. (キヤノン株式会社 Kiyanon Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational corporation specializing in the manufacture of imaging and optical products, including cameras, camcorders, photocopiers, steppers, computer printers and medical equipment. It&amp;rsquo;s headquartered in Ōta, Tokyo, Japan.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartier//file/cartier.svg</url><title>Cartier Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cartier</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cartier/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartier/</guid><description turbo="true">CARTIER International SNC, or simply Cartier is a French luxury goods conglomerate which designs, manufactures, distributes, and sells jewellery and watches. Founded by Louis-François Cartier in Paris in 1847, the company remained under family control until 1964. The company maintains its headquarters in Paris, although it has been a wholly owned subsidiary of the Swiss Richemont Group. Cartier operates more than 200 stores in 125 countries, with three Temples (Historical Maison) in London, New York, and Paris.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/caterpillar//file/caterpillar.svg</url><title>Caterpillar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Caterpillar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/caterpillar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/caterpillar/</guid><description turbo="true"> Caterpillar Inc. is an American Fortune 100 corporation which designs, develops, engineers, manufactures, markets and sells machinery, engines, financial products and insurance to customers via a worldwide dealer network. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest construction equipment manufacturer. In 2018, Caterpillar was ranked #65 on the Fortune 500 list and #238 on the Global Fortune 500 list. Caterpillar stock is a component of the Dow Jones Industrial Average.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel//file/chanel.svg</url><title>Chanel Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chanel</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chanel/</guid><description turbo="true">Chanel S.A. is a French privately held company owned by Alain Wertheimer and Gérard Wertheimer, grandsons of Pierre Wertheimer, who was an early business partner of the couturière Coco Chanel. Chanel S.A. is a high fashion house that specializes in haute couture and ready-to-wear clothes, luxury goods, and fashion accessories. In her youth, Gabrielle Chanel gained the nickname Coco from her time as a chanteuse. As a fashion designer, Coco Chanel catered to women&amp;rsquo;s taste for elegance in dress, with blouses and suits, trousers and dresses, and jewellery (gemstone and bijouterie) of simple design, that replaced the opulent, over-designed, and constrictive clothes and accessories of 19th-century fashion.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern//file/china-eastern.svg</url><title>China Eastern Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">China Eastern</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/china-eastern/</guid><description turbo="true"> China Eastern Airlines Corporation Limited is an airline headquartered in the China Eastern Airlines Building, on the grounds of Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport in Changning District, Shanghai. It is a major Chinese airline operating international, domestic and regional routes. Its main hubs are at Shanghai Pudong International Airport and Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chrysler//file/chrysler.svg</url><title>Chrysler Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chrysler</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chrysler/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chrysler/</guid><description turbo="true">Chrysler is one of the &amp;ldquo;Big Three&amp;rdquo; automobile manufacturers in the United States, headquartered in Auburn Hills, Michigan. The original Chrysler Corporation was founded in 1925 by Walter Chrysler from the remains of the Maxwell Motor Company. In 1998, it was acquired by Daimler-Benz, and the holding company was renamed DaimlerChrysler. After Daimler divested Chrysler in 2007, the company existed as Chrysler LLC (2007–2009) and Chrysler Group LLC (2009–2014) before merging in 2014 with Italian holding company Fiat S.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen//file/citroen.svg</url><title>Citroen Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Citroen</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</guid><description turbo="true"> Citroën is a French automobile manufacturer, part of the PSA Peugeot Citroën group since 1976, founded in 1919 by French industrialist André-Gustave Citroën (1878–1935). In 1934, the firm established its reputation for innovative technology with the Traction Avant. This car was the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass-produced front wheel drive car, and also one of the first to feature a unitary type body, with no chassis supporting the mechanical components.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate//file/colgate.svg</url><title>Colgate Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Colgate</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate/</guid><description turbo="true"> Colgate is an umbrella brand principally used for oral hygiene products such as toothpastes, toothbrushes, mouthwashes and dental floss. Manufactured by the American consumer-goods conglomerate Colgate-Palmolive, Colgate oral hygiene products were first sold by the company in 1873, sixteen years after the death of the founder, William Colgate. The company originally sold soap.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate-palmolive//file/colgate-palmolive.svg</url><title>Colgate-Palmolive Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Colgate-Palmolive</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate-palmolive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/colgate-palmolive/</guid><description turbo="true"> Colgate-Palmolive Company is an American worldwide consumer products company focused on the production, distribution and provision of household, health care, and personal care products. Under its &amp;ldquo;Hill&amp;rsquo;s Pet Nutrition&amp;rdquo; brand, it is also a manufacturer of veterinary products. The company&amp;rsquo;s corporate offices are on Park Avenue in Midtown Manhattan, New York City.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra//file/corona-extra.svg</url><title>Corona Extra Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Corona Extra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/corona-extra/</guid><description turbo="true">Corona Extra is a pale lager produced by Cervecería Modelo in Mexico for domestic distribution and export to all other countries besides the United States, and by Constellation Brands in Mexico for export to the United States. The Corona brand is one of the top-selling beers worldwide. Outside Mexico, Corona is commonly served with a wedge of lime or lemon in the neck of the bottle to add tartness and flavor.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/commercial-bank-of-kuwait//file/commercial-bank-of-kuwait.svg</url><title>Commercial Bank of Kuwait Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Commercial Bank of Kuwait</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/commercial-bank-of-kuwait/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:58:49 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/commercial-bank-of-kuwait/</guid><description turbo="true">History of the Commercial Bank of Kuwait logo The new Commercial Bank symbol is an amalgamation of calligraphy and image. the words commercial and bank are rendered in kufic, a geometric script, to make a decorative star, recognizable by anyone as a distinctive pattern and, additionally, readable to an Arab. The dual language identity has English type in Paul Renner’s Futura with a compatible Arabic script especially drawn by Ahmed Mustafa.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/clia//file/clia.svg</url><title>CLIA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CLIA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/clia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:22:27 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/clia/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists//file/college-of-american-pathologists.svg</url><title>College of American Pathologists Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">College of American Pathologists</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:21:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</guid><description turbo="true"> The College of American Pathologists is a member-based physician organization founded in 1946 comprising approximately 18,000 board-certified pathologists. It serves patients, pathologists, and the public by fostering and advocating best practices in pathology and laboratory medicine.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/castle-colony-top-doctors//file/castle-colony-top-doctors.svg</url><title>Castle Colony Top Doctors Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Castle Colony Top Doctors</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/castle-colony-top-doctors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:21:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/castle-colony-top-doctors/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Castle Connolly physician-led research team reviews and screens all nominated physicians before selecting those regarded as the most outstanding healthcare providers to be Top Doctors. Physicians do not and cannot pay to be selected as a Castle Connolly Top Doctor.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf//file/chicago-ivf.svg</url><title>Chicago IVF Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago IVF</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:32:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-ivf/</guid><description turbo="true">About Chicago IFV (from chicagoivf.com)
Chicago IVF’s offices and state-of-the-art facilities are conveniently located throughout Chicagoland and eastward into the state of Indiana, in close proximity to domestic and international airports. The fertility and surrogacy-friendly legal environment of Illinois makes the location of Chicago IVF practice an ideal destination for treatment.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one//file/capital-one.svg</url><title>Capital One Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Capital One</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:42:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one/</guid><description turbo="true">About Capital One (from capitalone.com)
Capital One Financial Corporation is a financial holding company whose subsidiaries, which include Capital One, N.A., and Capital One Bank (USA), N.A., had $249.8 billion in deposits and $372.5 billion in total assets as of December 31, 2018. Headquartered in McLean, Virginia, Capital One offers a broad spectrum of financial products and services to consumers, small businesses and commercial clients through a variety of channels. Capital One, N.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra//file/calibra.svg</url><title>Calibra Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Calibra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</guid><description turbo="true">About Calibra Calibra is from Facebook. Making it easy to use in your favorite apps. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency that will make money work better for all of us.
Calibra was founded in 2019 with the mission of making money work for everyone. Calibra believe that all people, all over the world should have equal, easy and educated access to financial services. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light//file/coca-cola-light.svg</url><title>Coca Cola Light Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coca Cola Light</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:51 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-light/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life//file/coca-cola-life.svg</url><title>Coca Cola Life Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coca Cola Life</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:42 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coca-cola-life/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi//file/citi.svg</url><title>Citi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Citi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</guid><description turbo="true">History of the Citi Group logo (from pentagram.com and medium.com)
Citi Group In Spring of 1998, Citi announced a merger with Travelers Insurance. At the time, it was the largest merger in the world and the brands needed to be unified to reflect that.
After a brief negotiation the budget for the brand overhaul was pegged at almost $10m, with the design of the logo itself making up $1.5m of that.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank//file/citibank.svg</url><title>Citibank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Citibank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</guid><description turbo="true">History of the Citi Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
In 1998 financial giants Citicorp and Travelers Group merged to create Citigroup, the largest financial company in the world. After having designed the now ubiquitous identity for the newly formed entity, a three dimensional extension of the brand in the form of Citibank branch interiors and fascias was developed and implemented worldwide.
A visual language and colors and materials palette were developed to represent the new brand.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chase//file/chase.svg</url><title>Chase Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chase</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chase/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chase/</guid><description turbo="true"/></item></channel></rss>