<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>gray on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/colors/gray/</link><description>Recent content in gray on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0011</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/colors/gray/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota//file/toyota.svg</url><title>Toyota Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Toyota</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0011</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</guid><description turbo="true">About the Toyota logo The Toyota brand represents Toyota tenets of quality, reliability and durability. It also stands as a symbol to inspire people around the world to go to the places and do the things they’ve always dreamed of.
The staging platform is how Toyota refer to the Toyota emblem when shown in the red surround. The staging platform allows the emblem to be anchored and impactful.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft//file/microsoft.svg</url><title>Microsoft Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Microsoft</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0003</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/microsoft/</guid><description turbo="true"> Microsoft Corporation is an American multinational technology company with headquarters in Redmond, Washington. It develops, manufactures, licenses, supports, and sells computer software, consumer electronics, personal computers, and related services.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple//file/apple.svg</url><title>Apple Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Apple</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0001</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</guid><description turbo="true">History of Apple logo At the time of his initial meeting with Steve Jobs in early 1977, Apple Computer was still very much in its infancy, having been incorporated for less than a year. Apple’s offices were in a local strip mall, and consisted of just the three partners – Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Mike Markkula.
The initial identity development was to coincide with the introduction of the brand’s first personal computer, the Apple II.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/99designs//file/99designs.svg</url><title>99designs Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">99designs</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/99designs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/99designs/</guid><description turbo="true">99designs is a Melbourne, Australia, based company that operates a freelancer platform for connecting graphic designers and clients. The company was founded in 2008, and has a United States office in Oakland, California.
Source About 99designs We’re 99designs, the global creative platform that makes it easy for clients and designers to work together online. Since 2008, our freelance community has brought more than one million creative projects to life for thousands of genius entrepreneurs, savvy business owners, and brands with big ideas.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles//file/hanwha-eagles.svg</url><title>Hanwha Eagles Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hanwha Eagles</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hanwha-eagles/</guid><description turbo="true">The Hanwha Eagles (Korean: 한화 이글스) is a South Korean professional baseball club based in the city of Daejeon. They are a member of the KBO League. The Eagles&amp;rsquo; home ballpark is Daejeon Hanbat Baseball Stadium. The Eagles have won the Korean Series once, in 1999, and the league pennant twice. As of 2020, the Eagles have played in the postseason 13 times, being the runner-up in the Korean Series five times.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lg-twins//file/lg-twins.svg</url><title>LG Twins Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LG Twins</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lg-twins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lg-twins/</guid><description turbo="true">LG Twins (Korean: LG 트윈스) is a South Korean professional baseball team based in Seoul, South Korea. They are a member of the KBO League. The Twins play their home games at Jamsil Baseball Stadium, which they share with their rival, the Doosan Bears; the stadium is known as &amp;ldquo;Two families under one roof.&amp;rdquo;
The LG Twins are one of the most popular baseball teams in Korea.[citation needed] They gained many fans in the 1980s–2000s, most of whom live in Seoul.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexen-heroes//file/nexen-heroes.svg</url><title>Nexen Heroes Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nexen Heroes</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nexen-heroes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexen-heroes/</guid><description turbo="true">Kiwoom Heroes (Korean: 키움 히어로즈) is a South Korean professional baseball team based in Seoul. They are a member of the KBO League. The Heroes mascot is Teokdori (턱돌이; Mr. Jaw). Like other baseball teams in South Korea, the team is known primarily by the name of the sponsor, occasionally as their nickname, and never as the city in which they are based. The Heroes play their home games at Gocheok Sky Dome in Gocheok-dong, a neighborhood located in the southwestern part of Seoul.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/vmware//file/vmware.svg</url><title>VMware Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">VMware</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/vmware/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vmware/</guid><description turbo="true">VMware, Inc. is an American publicly traded software company from California, USA. It provides cloud computing and virtualization software and services. It was one of the first commercially successful companies to virtualize the x86 architecture.
VMware&amp;rsquo;s desktop software runs on Microsoft Windows, Linux, and macOS, while its enterprise software hypervisor for servers, VMware ESXi, is a bare-metal hypervisor that runs directly on server hardware without requiring an additional underlying operating system.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/g2a//file/g2a.svg</url><title>G2A Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">G2A</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/g2a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/g2a/</guid><description turbo="true">G2A.COM Limited (commonly referred to as G2A) is a global digital marketplace which specializes in the resale of gaming products by the use of redemption keys. It is headquartered in the Netherlands and has offices in various countries including Poland and Hong Kong. The site has over 20 million customers, 400,000 sellers from 200 countries, 75,000 digital products and 600 employees throughout all locations. The main product offering on G2A.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors//file/molson-coors.svg</url><title>Molson Coors Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Molson Coors</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/molson-coors/</guid><description turbo="true">The Molson Coors Beverage Company is a multinational brewing company, formed in 2005 by the merger of Molson of Canada, and Coors of the United States. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s seventh largest brewer by volume.
While the company is incorporated in the United States, it is traded on stock exchanges in both the United States and Canada, and control is equally shared between the Molson and Coors families. The company is headquartered at 1801 California Street, a 1,372,179-square-foot (127,479.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters//file/reuters.svg</url><title>Reuters Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Reuters</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/reuters/</guid><description turbo="true">Reuters (About this soundpronunciation ; /ˈrɔɪtərz/) is an international news organization owned by Thomson Reuters. Until 2008, the Reuters news agency formed part of an independent company, Reuters Group plc, which was also a provider of financial market data. Since the acquisition of Reuters Group by the Thomson Corporation in 2008, the Reuters news agency has been a part of Thomson Reuters, making up the media division. It was established in 1851.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ring//file/ring.svg</url><title>Ring Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ring</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ring/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ring/</guid><description turbo="true">Ring Inc. (formerly Doorbot) is a home security and smart home company owned by Amazon. Ring manufactures home security products that incorporate outdoor motion-detecting cameras, including Ring Video Doorbell. It hosts an app, Neighbors, for online social sharing of captured footage among users. Ring also provides video footage from its cameras and data from its Neighbors app to law enforcement agencies on request. Its police partnerships have been criticized by civil rights advocacy groups as building an invasive private surveillance network.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/softbank//file/softbank.svg</url><title>Softbank Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Softbank</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/softbank/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/softbank/</guid><description turbo="true">SoftBank Group Corp. is a Japanese multinational conglomerate holding company headquartered in Tokyo. The company owns stakes in Softbank Corp. (ja), Softbank Vision Fund (ja), Arm Holdings, Fortress Investment Group, Boston Dynamics, Sprint (85%), Alibaba (29.5%), Yahoo Japan (48.17%), Brightstar (87.1%), Uber (15%), Didi Chuxing (ca.20%), Ola (ca.30%), Renren (42.9%), InMobi (45%), Hike (25.8%), Snapdeal (ca.30%), Fanatics (ca.22%), Improbable Worlds (ca.50%), Paytm (ca.20%), OYO (42%), Ping An Insurance (7.41%), Slack Technologies (ca.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar//file/brightstar.svg</url><title>Brightstar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Brightstar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar/</guid><description turbo="true">Brightstar Corp., an American privately held corporation founded in 1997, distributes mobile phones and other devices, serving more than 200 carriers, 40,000+ retailers, and 15,000+ enterprise customers in more than 100 countries. It provides specialized global wireless distribution and services, serving mobile device manufacturers, wireless operators and retailers. Brightstar offers value-added device and accessories distribution, supply chain, handset protection and insurance, buyback and trade-in and omnichannel retail, and mobile digital products within the wireless telecommunications industry.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti//file/bugatti.svg</url><title>Bugatti Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bugatti</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</guid><description turbo="true"> Automobiles Ettore Bugatti was a French car manufacturer of high-performance automobiles, founded in 1909 in the then-German city of Molsheim, Alsace by the Italian-born industrial designer Ettore Bugatti. The cars were known for their design beauty and for their many race victories. Famous Bugattis include the Type 35 Grand Prix cars, the Type 41 &amp;ldquo;Royale&amp;rdquo;, the Type 57 &amp;ldquo;Atlantic&amp;rdquo; and the Type 55 sports car.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle//file/crown-castle.svg</url><title>Crown Castle Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Crown Castle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/crown-castle/</guid><description turbo="true">Crown Castle is a real estate investment trust and the largest provider of shared communications infrastructure in the United States, with more than 40,000 cell towers and approximately 70,000 route miles of fiber supporting small cells and fiber solutions.
Source s</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/didi//file/didi.svg</url><title>DiDi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">DiDi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/didi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/didi/</guid><description turbo="true">Didi Chuxing Technology Co., formerly Didi Kuaidi (Chinese: 滴滴快的), is a transportation company headquartered in Beijing. The company provides app-based transportation services, including taxi hailing, private car hailing, social ride-sharing and bike sharing; on-demand delivery services; and automobile services, including sales, leasing, financing, maintenance, fleet operation, electric vehicle charging and co-development of vehicles with automakers. In 2018, DiDi&amp;rsquo;s platform had more than 550 million users and tens of millions of drivers.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus//file/lotus.svg</url><title>Lotus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lotus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lotus/</guid><description turbo="true">Lotus Cars Limited is a British automotive company that manufactures sports cars and racing cars with headquarters in Hethel, England. Lotus cars include the Esprit, Elan, Europa, Elise, Exige, Evora and Evija sports cars and it had motor racing success with Team Lotus in Formula One. Lotus Cars are based at the former site of RAF Hethel, a World War II airfield in Norfolk. The company designs and builds race and production automobiles of light weight and fine handling characteristics.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mufg//file/mufg.svg</url><title>MUFG Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MUFG</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mufg/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mufg/</guid><description turbo="true"> Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group, Inc. (MUFG; 株式会社三菱UFJフィナンシャル・グループ, Kabushiki gaisha Mitsubishi Yūefujei Finansharu Gurūpu) is a Japanese bank holding and financial services company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/spine-rx//file/spine-rx.svg</url><title>Spine RX Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Spine RX</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/spine-rx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spine-rx/</guid><description turbo="true">When you visit SPINE/RX, you’ll see the difference right away. At your first consultation, Spine RX surgical team will explain how modern spine surgery solutions are different from traditional spine surgery. They will take the time to understand your pain, evaluate your condition, and explain your options for more definitive pain relief. Many of Spine RX procedures are same day, minimally-invasive, and have shorter recovery times - getting you back on track fast.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/waves//file/waves.svg</url><title>Waves Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Waves</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/waves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/waves/</guid><description turbo="true"> Waves Platform is a cryptocurrency project launched by the Russian entrepreneur Alexander Ivanov in 2016. The blockchain platform launch campaign raised $16 million, becoming one of the largest in terms of funds raised through crowdfunding. In June 2017, the Waves platform reported the integration of the dollar payment gateway into the Lite Client, which allows users of the wallet to replenish the account in US dollars.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin//file/bitcoin.svg</url><title>Bitcoin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bitcoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash//file/bitcoin-cash.svg</url><title>Bitcoin Cash Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bitcoin Cash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017. In 2018 Bitcoin Cash subsequently split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash, and Bitcoin SV. Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dribbble//file/dribbble.svg</url><title>Dribbble Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dribbble</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dribbble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dribbble/</guid><description turbo="true"> Dribbble is a self-promotion and networking platform for digital designers of various disciplines, including graphic design, web design, UX/UI, web design, illustration, and branding.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum//file/ethereum.svg</url><title>Ethereum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ethereum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ethereum is an open source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform and operating system featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It supports a modified version of Nakamoto consensus via transaction-based state transitions. Ether is a cryptocurrency generated by the Ethereum platform and used to compensate mining nodes for computations performed. Each Ethereum account has an ether balance and ether may be transferred from one account to another.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh//file/hmh.svg</url><title>HMH Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HMH</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hmh/</guid><description turbo="true"> Houghton Mifflin Harcourt is a publisher of textbooks, instructional technology materials, assessments, reference works, and fiction and non-fiction for both young readers and adults.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot//file/hubspot.svg</url><title>HubSpot Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">HubSpot</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hubspot/</guid><description turbo="true"> HubSpot is a developer and marketer of software products for inbound marketing and sales. It was founded by Brian Halligan and Dharmesh Shah in 2006. Its products and services aim to provide tools for social media marketing, content management, web analytics and search engine optimization.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero//file/monero.svg</url><title>Monero Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Monero</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</guid><description turbo="true"> Monero is an open-source cryptocurrency created in April 2014 that focuses on fungibility, privacy and decentralization. Monero uses an obfuscated public ledger, meaning anybody can broadcast or send transactions, but no outside observer can tell the source, amount or destination. Monero uses a Proof of Work mechanism to issue new coins and incentivize miners to secure the network and validate transactions.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov//file/nov.svg</url><title>NOV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NOV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</guid><description turbo="true">National Oilwell Varco (NOV) is an American multinational corporation based in Houston, Texas. It is a leading worldwide provider of equipment and components used in oil and gas drilling and production operations, oilfield services, and supply chain integration services to the upstream oil and gas industry. The company conducts operations in more than 600 locations across six continents, operating through three reporting segments: Rig Technologies, Wellbore Technologies, and Completion &amp;amp; Production Solutions.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/revel//file/revel.svg</url><title>Revel Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Revel</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/revel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/revel/</guid><description turbo="true"> Revel is an American manufacturer and distributor of high-end luxury audio loudspeakers. It is owned by Harman International Industries, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics. The company is based in Stamford, Connecticut, United States.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple//file/ripple.svg</url><title>Ripple Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ripple</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple/</guid><description turbo="true">Ripple is a real-time gross settlement system, currency exchange and remittance network created by Ripple Labs Inc., a US-based technology company. Released in 2012, Ripple is built upon a distributed open source protocol, and supports tokens representing fiat currency, cryptocurrency, commodities, or other units of value such as frequent flier miles or mobile minutes. Ripple purports to enable &amp;ldquo;secure, instantly and nearly free global financial transactions of any size with no chargebacks.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft//file/soundcraft.svg</url><title>Soundcraft Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Soundcraft</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/soundcraft/</guid><description turbo="true"> Soundcraft is a British designer and importer (formerly a manufacturer) of mixing consoles and other professional audio equipment. It is a subsidiary of Harman International Industries, which is owned by South Korean company Samsung Electronics. It was founded by sound engineer Phil Dudderidge and electronics designer Graham Blyth in 1973.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether//file/tether.svg</url><title>Tether Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tether</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</guid><description turbo="true"> Tether is a controversial cryptocurrency with tokens issued by Tether Limited. It formerly claimed that each token was backed by one United States dollar, but on 14 March 2019 changed the backing to include loans to affiliate companies. The Bitfinex exchange was accused by the New York Attorney General of using Tether&amp;rsquo;s funds to cover up $850 million in funds missing since mid-2018.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/basf//file/basf.svg</url><title>BASF Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">BASF</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/basf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/basf/</guid><description turbo="true">BASF SE is a German chemical company and the largest chemical producer in the world. The BASF Group comprises subsidiaries and joint ventures in more than 80 countries and operates six integrated production sites and 390 other production sites in Europe, Asia, Australia, the Americas and Africa. Its headquarters is located in Ludwigshafen, Germany. BASF has customers in over 190 countries and supplies products to a wide variety of industries.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute//file/cfa-institute.svg</url><title>CFA Institute Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CFA Institute</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cfa-institute/</guid><description turbo="true"> The organization offers the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) designation, the Certificate in Investment Performance Measurement (CIPM) designation, and the Investment Foundations Certificate. It provides continuing education conferences, seminars, webcasts, and publications to allow members and other participants to stay current on developments in the investment industry. CFA Institute also oversees the CFA Institute Research Challenge for university students and the Research Foundation of CFA Institute.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus//file/cnnplus.svg</url><title>CNNplus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">CNNplus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cnnplus/</guid><description turbo="true"> CNN+ (CNN Plus) was a Spanish 24-hour television news channel. Launched in 1999 as a joint venture by Sogecable and Turner Broadcasting, a unit of Time Warner that owns CNN, it went off the air at the end of 28 December 2010. The management announced that CNN+ would be closed on 31 December 2010.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv//file/fox-tv.svg</url><title>Fox TV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Fox TV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fox-tv/</guid><description turbo="true"> Fox Television Stations, LLC (FTS; alternately Fox Television Stations Group, LLC), is a group of television stations located within the United States which are owned-and-operated by the Fox Broadcasting Company, a subsidiary of the Fox Corporation.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/magirus//file/magirus.svg</url><title>Magirus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Magirus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/magirus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/magirus/</guid><description turbo="true"> Magirus GmbH is a truck manufacturer based in Ulm, Germany, founded by Conrad Dietrich Magirus (1824–1895). The parent company was Klöckner Humboldt Deutz AG, maker of the well-known Deutz engines, so the brand commonly used was Magirus Deutz, and for a short time Klöckner. The logo of Magirus Deutz was a stylised M with a sharp, long centre point to represent the spire of Ulm Cathedral.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mit//file/mit.svg</url><title>MIT Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MIT</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mit/</guid><description turbo="true">The Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) is a private research university in Cambridge, Massachusetts. The Institute is a land-grant, sea-grant, and space-grant university, with an urban campus that extends more than a mile (1.6 km) alongside the Charles River. The Institute also encompasses a number of major off-campus facilities such as the MIT Lincoln Laboratory, the Bates Center, and the Haystack Observatory, as well as affiliated laboratories such as the Broad and Whitehead Institutes.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv//file/mynetworktv.svg</url><title>MyNetworkTV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MyNetworkTV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mynetworktv/</guid><description turbo="true">MyNetworkTV (unofficially abbreviated as MyTV, MyNet, MNT or MNTV), is an American television network/syndication service that is owned by Fox Corporation, operated by its Fox Television Stations division, and distributed through the syndication structure of 20th Television. MyNetworkTV began operations on September 5, 2006 with an initial affiliate lineup covering about 96% of the country, most of which consisted of stations that were former affiliates of The WB and UPN that did not join the successor of those two networks, The CW.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk//file/nhk.svg</url><title>NHK Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NHK</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk/</guid><description turbo="true"> NHK World-Japan is the international broadcasting service of NHK (Nippon Hōsō Kyōkai - Japan Broadcasting Corporation), Japan&amp;rsquo;s public broadcaster. The service is aimed at the overseas market, similar to BBC World News, DW, France 24, CGTN, and RT, and broadcast through satellite and cable operators throughout the world as well as online and through its mobile apps. The channel is based in Tokyo, Japan.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines//file/siberia-airlines.svg</url><title>Siberia Airlines Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Siberia Airlines</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</guid><description turbo="true"> S7 Airlines, legally JSC Siberia Airlines (Russian: АО «Авиакомпания &amp;ldquo;Сибирь&amp;rdquo;», &amp;ldquo;АО Aviakompania Sibir&amp;rdquo;), is an airline headquartered in Ob, Novosibirsk Oblast, Russia, with offices in Moscow. As of 2008, it is Russia&amp;rsquo;s biggest domestic airline, with its main bases at Domodedovo International Airport and Tolmachevo Airport
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts//file/tufts.svg</url><title>Tufts Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tufts</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tufts/</guid><description turbo="true">Tufts University is a private research university in Medford and Somerville, Massachusetts. A charter member of the New England Small College Athletic Conference (NESCAC), Tufts College was founded in 1852 by Christian universalists who worked for years to open a nonsectarian institution of higher learning. It was a small New England liberal arts college until its transformation into a larger research university in the 1970s. The university emphasizes active citizenship and public service in all its disciplines, and is known for its internationalism and study abroad programs</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets//file/charlotte-hornets.svg</url><title>Charlotte Hornets Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Charlotte Hornets</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/charlotte-hornets/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Charlotte Hornets are an American professional basketball team based in Charlotte, North Carolina. The Hornets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Southeast Division. The team is largely owned by retired NBA player Michael Jordan, who acquired controlling interest in the team in 2010. The Hornets play their home games at the Spectrum Center in Uptown Charlotte.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc//file/chicago-fire-fc.svg</url><title>Chicago Fire FC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago Fire FC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc/</guid><description turbo="true">Chicago Fire Football Club is an American professional soccer club based in Chicago, Illinois. The team competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the league’s Eastern Conference, having moved to the conference in 2002. The franchise is named after the Great Chicago Fire of 1871, and was founded as the Chicago Fire Soccer Club on October 8, 1997, the event’s 126th anniversary. The team began play in 1998 as one of the league’s first expansion teams.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-pacers//file/indiana-pacers.svg</url><title>Indiana Pacers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Indiana Pacers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-pacers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/indiana-pacers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Indiana Pacers are an American professional basketball team based in Indianapolis, Indiana. The Pacers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Central Division. The Pacers were first established in 1967 as a member of the American Basketball Association (ABA) and became a member of the NBA in 1976 as a result of the ABA–NBA merger. They play their home games at Bankers Life Fieldhouse.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/memphis-grizzlies//file/memphis-grizzlies.svg</url><title>Memphis Grizzlies Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Memphis Grizzlies</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/memphis-grizzlies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/memphis-grizzlies/</guid><description turbo="true">The Memphis Grizzlies are an American professional basketball team based in Memphis, Tennessee. The Grizzlies compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member team of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The Grizzlies play their home games at FedExForum. The team is owned by Robert Pera. The Grizzlies are currently the only team in the major professional North American sports leagues based in the city of Memphis.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sacramento-kings//file/sacramento-kings.svg</url><title>Sacramento Kings Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sacramento Kings</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sacramento-kings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sacramento-kings/</guid><description turbo="true">The Sacramento Kings are an American professional basketball team based in Sacramento, California. The Kings compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the Western Conference&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Division. The Kings are the only team in the major professional North American sports leagues located in Sacramento. The team plays its home games at the Golden 1 Center. Their best seasons to date in the city were in the early 2000s, including the 2001–02 season when they had the best record in the NBA at 61–21 (a winning percentage of .</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc//file/sporting-kc.svg</url><title>Sporting KC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sporting KC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sporting-kc/</guid><description turbo="true"> Sporting Kansas City is an American professional soccer club in Kansas City, Kansas, with its main office and historic location in Kansas City, Missouri. The club competes as a member of the Western Conference in Major League Soccer (MLS), having returned in 2015 after spending ten seasons in the Eastern Conference.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/spurs//file/spurs.svg</url><title>Spurs Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Spurs</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/spurs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spurs/</guid><description turbo="true"> The San Antonio Spurs are an American professional basketball team based in San Antonio, Texas. The Spurs compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference Southwest Division. The team plays its home games at the AT&amp;amp;T Center in San Antonio.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-fc//file/toronto-fc.svg</url><title>Toronto FC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Toronto FC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-fc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-fc/</guid><description turbo="true"> Toronto Football Club is a Canadian professional soccer team based in Toronto, Ontario. The team competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the Eastern Conference. The team plays its home matches at BMO Field, located at Exhibition Place on Toronto&amp;rsquo;s shoreline. Toronto FC joined MLS in 2007 as an expansion team and was the first Canadian-based franchise in the league.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-raptors//file/toronto-raptors.svg</url><title>Toronto Raptors Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Toronto Raptors</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-raptors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toronto-raptors/</guid><description turbo="true">The Toronto Raptors are a Canadian professional basketball team based in Toronto, Ontario. The Raptors compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Atlantic Division. They play their home games at the Scotiabank Arena, which they share with the Toronto Maple Leafs of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was founded in 1995 as part of the NBA&amp;rsquo;s expansion into Canada, along with the Vancouver Grizzlies.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/vegas-golden-knights//file/vegas-golden-knights.svg</url><title>Vegas Golden Knights Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Vegas Golden Knights</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/vegas-golden-knights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vegas-golden-knights/</guid><description turbo="true">The Vegas Golden Knights are a professional ice hockey team based in the Las Vegas metropolitan area that competes in the National Hockey League (NHL). They are members of the Pacific Division of the league&amp;rsquo;s Western Conference, and began play in the 2017–18 NHL season. The team is owned by Black Knight Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment, a consortium led by Bill Foley and the Maloof family. The team plays its home games at T-Mobile Arena on the Las Vegas Strip in Paradise, Nevada.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-falcons//file/atlanta-falcons.svg</url><title>Atlanta Falcons Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Atlanta Falcons</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-falcons/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/atlanta-falcons/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Atlanta Falcons are a professional American football team based in Atlanta, Georgia. The Falcons compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The Falcons joined the NFL in 1965[5] as an expansion team, after the NFL offered then-owner Rankin Smith a franchise to keep him from joining the rival American Football League (AFL).
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-panthers//file/carolina-panthers.svg</url><title>Carolina Panthers Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Carolina Panthers</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-panthers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/carolina-panthers/</guid><description turbo="true">The Carolina Panthers are a professional American football team based in Charlotte, North Carolina. The Panthers compete in the National Football League (NFL), as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The team is headquartered in Bank of America Stadium in uptown Charlotte; the stadium also serves as the team&amp;rsquo;s home field. They are one of the few NFL teams to own the stadium they play in, which is legally registered as Panthers Stadium, LLC.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox//file/chicago-white-sox.svg</url><title>Chicago White Sox Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chicago White Sox</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-white-sox/</guid><description turbo="true">The Chicago White Sox are an American professional baseball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The White Sox compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) Central division. The White Sox are owned by Jerry Reinsdorf, and play their home games at Guaranteed Rate Field, located on the city&amp;rsquo;s South Side. They are one of two major league clubs in Chicago; the other is the Chicago Cubs, who are a member of the National League (NL) Central division.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-lions//file/detroit-lions.svg</url><title>Detroit Lions Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Detroit Lions</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-lions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/detroit-lions/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Detroit Lions are a professional American football team based in Detroit, Michigan. The Lions compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) North division. The team plays its home games at Ford Field in Downtown Detroit.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-angels//file/la-angels.svg</url><title>LA Angels Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">LA Angels</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/la-angels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/la-angels/</guid><description turbo="true">The Los Angeles Angels are an American professional baseball franchise based in Anaheim, California. The Angels compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) West division. The Angels have played home games at Angel Stadium since 1966. The current MLB franchise was established as an expansion team in 1961 by Gene Autry (1907–1998), the team&amp;rsquo;s first owner. Autry was a famous singing cowboy actor in a series of films in the 1930s to 1950s, and later was the subject of the Gene Autry Western Heritage Museum.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots//file/new-england-patriots.svg</url><title>New England Patriots Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">New England Patriots</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots/</guid><description turbo="true">The New England Patriots are a professional American football team based in the Greater Boston area. The Patriots compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team plays its home games at Gillette Stadium in the town of Foxborough, Massachusetts, which is located 21 miles (34 km) southwest of downtown Boston, Massachusetts and 20 miles (32 km) northeast of downtown Providence, Rhode Island.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees//file/new-york-yankees.svg</url><title>New York Yankees Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">New York Yankees</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees/</guid><description turbo="true">The New York Yankees are an American professional baseball team based in the New York City borough of the Bronx. The Yankees compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) East division. They are one of two major league clubs based in New York City; the other club is the National League (NL)&amp;rsquo;s New York Mets. In the 1901 season, the club began play in the AL as the Baltimore Orioles (no relation to the modern Baltimore Orioles).</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhl//file/nhl.svg</url><title>NHL Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NHL</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nhl/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhl/</guid><description turbo="true">The National Hockey League (NHL; French: Ligue nationale de hockey—LNH) is a professional ice hockey league in North America, currently comprising 31 teams: 24 in the United States and 7 in Canada. The NHL is considered to be the premier professional ice hockey league in the world, and one of the major professional sports leagues in the United States and Canada. The Stanley Cup, the oldest professional sports trophy in North America, is awarded annually to the league playoff champion at the end of each season.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/oakland-raiders//file/oakland-raiders.svg</url><title>Oakland Raiders Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Oakland Raiders</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/oakland-raiders/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/oakland-raiders/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Oakland Raiders are a professional American football franchise based in Oakland, California. The Raiders compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) West division. Founded on January 30, 1960, they played their first regular season game on September 11, 1960, as a charter member of the American Football League (AFL) which merged with the NFL in 1970.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-seahawks//file/seattle-seahawks.svg</url><title>Seattle Seahawks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Seattle Seahawks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-seahawks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seattle-seahawks/</guid><description turbo="true">The Seattle Seahawks are a professional American football franchise based in Seattle, Washington. The Seahawks compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) West division. They joined the NFL in 1976 as an expansion team. The Seahawks are coached by Pete Carroll. Since 2002, they have played their home games at CenturyLink Field (formerly Qwest Field), located south of downtown Seattle.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens-boots-alliance//file/walgreens-boots-alliance.svg</url><title>Walgreens Boots Alliance Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Walgreens Boots Alliance</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens-boots-alliance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens-boots-alliance/</guid><description turbo="true">Walgreens Boots Alliance, Inc. is an American holding company headquartered in Deerfield, Illinois, that owns Walgreens, Boots, and a number of pharmaceutical manufacturing, wholesale, and distribution companies. The company was formed on December 31, 2014, after Walgreens purchased the 55% stake in UK and Switzerland-based Alliance Boots that it did not already own. The total price of the acquisition was $4.9 billion in cash and 144.3 million common shares with fair value of $10.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox//file/21st-century-fox.svg</url><title>21st Century Fox Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">21st Century Fox</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</guid><description turbo="true"> Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc., doing business as 21st Century Fox (21CF), was an American multinational mass media corporation that was based in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was one of the two companies formed from the 2013 spin-off of the publishing assets of News Corporation, as founded by Rupert Murdoch in 1980.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good//file/fashion-for-good.svg</url><title>Fashion For Good Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Fashion For Good</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fashion-for-good/</guid><description turbo="true"> Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi//file/hitachi.svg</url><title>Hitachi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Hitachi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hitachi/</guid><description turbo="true">Hitachi, Ltd. is a Japanese multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan. It is the parent company of the Hitachi Group (Hitachi Gurūpu) and forms part of the DKB Group of companies. Hitachi is a highly diversified company that operates eleven business segments: Information &amp;amp; Telecommunication Systems, Social Infrastructure, High Functional Materials &amp;amp; Components, Financial Services, Power Systems, Electronic Systems &amp;amp; Equipment, Automotive Systems, Railway &amp;amp; Urban Systems, Digital Media &amp;amp; Consumer Products, Construction Machinery and Other Components &amp;amp; Systems.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/katerra//file/katerra.svg</url><title>Katerra Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Katerra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/katerra/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/katerra/</guid><description turbo="true"> Katerra is a technology-driven offsite construction company. It was founded in 2015 by Michael Marks, former CEO of Flextronics and former Tesla interim CEO, along with Fritz Wolff, the executive chairman of The Wolff Co. It has raised US$1.1 billion in venture capital banking &amp;amp; finances and has more than $1 billion in project backlog. Katerra was listed on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Top Startup Companies&amp;rdquo; to work for in 2017.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/star-alliance//file/star-alliance.svg</url><title>Star Alliance Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Star Alliance</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/star-alliance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/star-alliance/</guid><description turbo="true"> Star Alliance is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest global airline alliances. Founded on 14 May 1997, its current CEO is Jeffrey Goh and its headquarters is located in Frankfurt am Main, Germany. As of April 2018, Star Alliance is the second largest global alliance by passenger count with 728 million, behind SkyTeam (730 million) and ahead of Oneworld (528 million). Its slogan is &amp;ldquo;The Way The Earth Connects&amp;rdquo;.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens//file/walgreens.svg</url><title>Walgreens Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Walgreens</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walgreens/</guid><description turbo="true">Walgreen Company or simply Walgreens is an American company that operates as the second-largest pharmacy store chain in the United States behind CVS Health. It specializes in filling prescriptions, health and wellness products, health information, and photo services. As of August 31, 2018, the company operated 9,560 stores in all 50 states, the District of Columbia and the US territories of Puerto Rico and the U.S. Virgin Islands. It was founded in Chicago, Illinois, in 1901.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen//file/citroen.svg</url><title>Citroen Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Citroen</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citroen/</guid><description turbo="true"> Citroën is a French automobile manufacturer, part of the PSA Peugeot Citroën group since 1976, founded in 1919 by French industrialist André-Gustave Citroën (1878–1935). In 1934, the firm established its reputation for innovative technology with the Traction Avant. This car was the world&amp;rsquo;s first mass-produced front wheel drive car, and also one of the first to feature a unitary type body, with no chassis supporting the mechanical components.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz//file/mercedes-benz.svg</url><title>Mercedes-Benz Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Mercedes-Benz</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mercedes-benz/</guid><description turbo="true"> Mercedes-Benz is a German global automobile marque and a division of Daimler AG. The brand is known for luxury vehicles, buses, coaches, and trucks. The headquarters is in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg. The name first appeared in 1926 under Daimler-Benz. In 2018, Mercedes-Benz was the biggest selling premium vehicle brand in the world, having sold 2.31 million passenger cars.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany//file/sany.svg</url><title>Sany Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sany</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sany/</guid><description turbo="true"> Sany Heavy Industry Co., Ltd. is a Chinese multinational heavy equipment manufacturing company headquartered in Changsha, Hunan Province. It is the sixth-largest heavy equipment manufacturer in the world, and the first in its industry in China to enter the FT Global 500 and the Forbes Global 2000 rankings. Its founder and main shareholder is Liang Wengen.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart//file/smart.svg</url><title>Smart Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Smart</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smart/</guid><description turbo="true"> Smart (stylized as smart) is a German automotive brand and division of Daimler AG. The company is based in Böblingen, Germany. It produces microcars and subcompacts, primarily the Fortwo and Forfour. The primary assembly plants is the Smartville in Hambach, France. A second plant exists in Novo Mesto, Slovenia. Marketed in 46 countries around the world, production of the Fortwo had surpassed 1.7 million units by early 2015.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health//file/versant-health.svg</url><title>Versant Health Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Versant Health</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/versant-health/</guid><description turbo="true"> Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper//file/prosper.svg</url><title>Prosper Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Prosper</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</guid><description turbo="true">About Prosper (from prosper.com)
Prosper was founded in 2005 as the first peer-to-peer lending marketplace in the United States. Since then, Prosper has facilitated more than $15 billion in loans to more than 910,000 people.
Through Prosper, people can invest in each other in a way that is financially and socially rewarding. Borrowers apply online for a fixed-rate, fixed-term loan between $2,000 and $40,000. Individuals and institutions can invest in the loans and earn attractive returns.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare//file/prosper-healthcare.svg</url><title>Prosper healthcare Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Prosper healthcare</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper-healthcare/</guid><description turbo="true">About Prosper healthcare (from prosperhealthcare.com)
Prosper healthcare Lending is a patient financing marketplace company headquartered in Salt Lake City, Utah at the heart of the “Silicon Slopes”. Prosper healthcare sit at the intersection of the healthcare, technology, and financial services markets and Prosper healthcare are using technology to bring innovative financial services solutions to a massive healthcare problem. Prosper healthcare patient financing platform allows healthcare providers nationwide to help Make healthcare Affordable™ for patients every day by referring patients with good credit to affordable installment loans offered through Prosper.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood//file/path2parenthood.svg</url><title>Path2Parenthood Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Path2Parenthood</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:01 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/path2parenthood/</guid><description turbo="true">About Path2Parenthoods Path2Parenthood (P2P) is an inclusive organization committed to helping people create their families by providing leading-edge outreach programs and timely educational information. The scope of Path2Parenthood work encompasses reproductive health, infertility prevention and treatment, and family-building options including adoption and third party solutions. P2P is a national, not-for-profit 501(c)(3) charitable organization headquartered in New York City.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/patients-choice-award//file/patients-choice-award.svg</url><title>Patients Choice Award Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Patients Choice Award</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/patients-choice-award/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:51 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/patients-choice-award/</guid><description turbo="true"/></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists//file/college-of-american-pathologists.svg</url><title>College of American Pathologists Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">College of American Pathologists</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:21:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/college-of-american-pathologists/</guid><description turbo="true"> The College of American Pathologists is a member-based physician organization founded in 1946 comprising approximately 18,000 board-certified pathologists. It serves patients, pathologists, and the public by fostering and advocating best practices in pathology and laboratory medicine.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors//file/best-doctors.svg</url><title>Best Doctors Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Best Doctors</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:47 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors/</guid><description turbo="true"/></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/pocket//file/pocket.svg</url><title>Pocket Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Pocket</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/pocket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pocket/</guid><description turbo="true">About Pocket (from getpocket.com)
Pocket was founded in 2007 by Nate Weiner to help people save interesting articles, videos and more from the web for later enjoyment. Once saved to Pocket, the list of content is visible on any device — phone, tablet or computer. It can be viewed while waiting in line, on the couch, during commutes or travel — even offline.
The world&amp;rsquo;s leading save-for-later service currently has more than 30 million registered users and is integrated into more than 1500 apps including Flipboard, Twitter and Zite.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists//file/houston-fertility-specialists.svg</url><title>Houston Fertility Specialists Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Houston Fertility Specialists</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:20:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/houston-fertility-specialists/</guid><description turbo="true"/></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1//file/toyota-f1.svg</url><title>Toyota F1 Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Toyota F1</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota-f1/</guid><description turbo="true"/></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive//file/iv-interactive.svg</url><title>IV Interactive Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">IV Interactive</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iv-interactive/</guid><description turbo="true">About IV interactive IV Interactive is a full-service interactive agency specializing in the four elements required for success in an increasingly digital world: innovative design, interactive marketing, technology implementation and strategic consulting. Using this multidisciplinary approach, IV Interactive provide results-driven, award-winning solutions to organizations of all sizes and disciplines. From Jones Apparel Group to Thomson Reuters, IV Interactive have helped IV Interactive clients identify and implement the elements necessary for success.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-news//file/opera-news.svg</url><title>Opera News Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Opera News</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-news/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/opera-news/</guid><description turbo="true"/></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo//file/wells-fargo.svg</url><title>Wells Fargo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Wells Fargo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</guid><description turbo="true">About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy Wells Fargo customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content/></rss>