<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>N on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/n/</link>
    <description>Recent content in N on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/n/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NC Dinos</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nc-dinos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nc-dinos/</guid>
      <description> NC Dinos (Korean: 엔씨 다이노스) are a South Korean professional baseball team based in Changwon. They have competed in KBO League since 2013. Their home stadium is Changwon NC Park since 2019. NC Dinos are owned by a video game developer NCSoft Corporation, and named after that company.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nexen Heroes</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexen-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexen-heroes/</guid>
      <description>Kiwoom Heroes (Korean: 키움 히어로즈) is a South Korean professional baseball team based in Seoul. They are a member of the KBO League. The Heroes mascot is Teokdori (턱돌이; Mr. Jaw). Like other baseball teams in South Korea, the team is known primarily by the name of the sponsor, occasionally as their nickname, and never as the city in which they are based. The Heroes play their home games at Gocheok Sky Dome in Gocheok-dong, a neighborhood located in the southwestern part of Seoul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New York Times</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-new-york-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-new-york-times/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times (NYT), is an American newspaper based in New York City with worldwide influence and readership. Nicknamed &amp;ldquo;the Gray Lady&amp;rdquo;, the Times has long been regarded within the industry as a national &amp;ldquo;newspaper of record&amp;rdquo;. The paper&amp;rsquo;s motto, &amp;ldquo;All the News That&amp;rsquo;s Fit to Print&amp;rdquo;, appears in the upper left-hand corner of the front page. Founded in 1851, the paper has won 130 Pulitzer Prizes, more than any other newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nasa/</guid>
      <description>The National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA; /ˈnæsə/) is an independent agency of the United States Federal Government responsible for the civilian space program, as well as aeronautics and space research. NASA was established in 1958, succeeding the National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics (NACA). The new agency was to have a distinctly civilian orientation, encouraging peaceful applications in space science. Since its establishment, most US space exploration efforts have been led by NASA, including the Apollo Moon landing missions, the Skylab space station, and later the Space Shuttle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nascar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nascar/</guid>
      <description>The National Association for Stock Car Auto Racing (NASCAR) is an American auto racing sanctioning and operating company that is best known for stock-car racing. The privately owned company was founded by Bill France Sr. in 1948,xx` and his son, Jim France, has been the CEO since August 6, 2018. The company is headquartered in Daytona Beach, Florida. Each year, NASCAR sanctions over 1,500 races at over 100 tracks in 48 US states as well as in Canada, Mexico, and Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nat Geo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nat-geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nat-geo/</guid>
      <description>National Geographic (formerly the National Geographic Magazine and branded also as NAT GEO) is the official magazine of the National Geographic Society. It has been published continuously since its first issue in 1888, nine months after the Society itself was founded. It primarily contains articles about science, geography, history, and world culture. The magazine is known for its thick square-bound glossy format with a yellow rectangular border and its extensive use of dramatic photographs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NetEase</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/netease/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/netease/</guid>
      <description>NetEase, Inc. (simplified Chinese: 网易; traditional Chinese: 網易; pinyin: WǎngYì) is a Chinese Internet technology company providing online services centered on content, community, communications and commerce. The company was founded in 1997 by Ding Lei. NetEase develops and operates online PC and mobile games, advertising services, email services and e-commerce platforms in China. It is one of the largest Internet and video game companies in the world. The company also owns several pig farms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick Jr</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr/</guid>
      <description>Nick Jr. is an American pay television channel run by Nickelodeon Group, a unit of the ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division of ViacomCBS, the channel&amp;rsquo;s ultimate owner headquartered in New York City. It launched on September 28, 2009 as a spin-off of Nickelodeon&amp;rsquo;s long-running preschool programming block of the same name, which had aired since 1988. The channel, which is aimed at children under 6, features a mix of originally-produced programming, and series previously and concurrently aired on the Nick Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nickelodeon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon/</guid>
      <description>Nickelodeon (often shortened to Nick) is an American pay television channel which was first tested on December 1, 1977, before relaunching on April 1, 1979 as the first cable channel for children. It is owned by ViacomCBS through its domestic networks division and is based in New York City. The network&amp;rsquo;s programming is primarily aimed at children and adolescents aged 2–17, while some of its program blocks target a broader family audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nissan</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissan/</guid>
      <description>Nissan Motor Co., Ltd. (Japanese: 日産自動車株式会社, Hepburn: Nissan Jidōsha Kabushiki-gaisha), usually shortened to Nissan is a Japanese multinational automobile manufacturer headquartered in Nishi-ku, Yokohama. The company sells its cars under the Nissan, Infiniti, and Datsun brands with in-house performance tuning products labelled Nismo. The company traces its name to the Nissan zaibatsu, now called Nissan Group.
 Since 1999, Nissan has been part of the Renault–Nissan–Mitsubishi Alliance (Mitsubishi joining in 2016), a partnership between Nissan of Japan, Mitsubishi Motors of Japan and Renault of France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nok Air</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nok-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nok-air/</guid>
      <description>Nok Air (SET: NOK, Thai: นกแอร์, derived from nok (นก), the Thai word for bird) is a low-cost airline in Thailand operating mostly domestic services out of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Don Mueang International Airport. Thai Airways owns the second-largest stake in the airline.
  Source About Nok Air Nok Air aspire to deliver the best customer experience to Nok Air passengers Nok Air is a budget carrier under the management of Nok Airlines Public Company Limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget Markets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nugget-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nugget-markets/</guid>
      <description>Nugget Markets is a family-owned upscale supermarket chain operating within the greater Sacramento metropolitan area. It is headquartered in Woodland, California. As of October 2019, the company operates twelve of its flagship Nugget Markets-brand stores, as well as Sonoma Market in Sonoma, Fork Lift by Nugget Markets in Cameron Park and Food 4 Less in Woodland.
  Source Nugget Markets Nugget Markets is a family-owned-and-operated company based in Northern California dedicated to creating an extraordinary grocery experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</guid>
      <description> NEM is a peer-to-peer blockchain platform for app developers. Its native cryptocurrency is the XEM. Its code was created from scratch in Java by the New Economy Movement (NEM), which seeks to build &amp;ldquo;a new economy based on the principles of financial freedom, decentralization, equality and solidarity&amp;rdquo;.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEO</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/neo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/neo/</guid>
      <description>NEO (formerly known as Antshares) is a smart economy platform and the first Chinese blockchain project. The project was founded in 2014 and was a real-time open source on GitHub in June 2015. NEO coin and the platform aims to develop a &amp;ldquo;smart economy&amp;rdquo; with a distributed network by utilizing blockchain technology and digital identity to digitize assets and automating the management of digital assets using smart contracts. NEO coin is currently traded on Bittrex, Cryptopia and Binance among other exchanges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nomura</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nomura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nomura/</guid>
      <description> Nomura Holdings, Inc. is a Japanese financial holding company and a principal member of the Nomura Group. It, along with its broker-dealer, banking and other financial services subsidiaries, provides investment, financing and related services to individual, institutional and government customers on a global basis with an emphasis on securities businesses.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nexford</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nexford/</guid>
      <description> Nexford University is a private for-profit online university headquartered in Washington, DC. It was founded in 2018 by Fadl Al Tarzi. The University offers programs through the process of online distance learning. Nexford is licensed to issue degrees by the Higher Education Licensure Commission (HELC) in Washington DC. Nexford is accredited by ASIC, an UK-based International accreditation agency operating in 60+ countries.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nov/</guid>
      <description>National Oilwell Varco (NOV) is an American multinational corporation based in Houston, Texas. It is a leading worldwide provider of equipment and components used in oil and gas drilling and production operations, oilfield services, and supply chain integration services to the upstream oil and gas industry. The company conducts operations in more than 600 locations across six continents, operating through three reporting segments: Rig Technologies, Wellbore Technologies, and Completion &amp;amp; Production Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N26</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/n26/</guid>
      <description> N26 (known as Number 26 until July 2016) is a German direct bank, headquartered in Berlin, Germany. N26 offers its services throughout most of the Eurozone, UK, Switzerland and US. It is expected to start operating in Brazil soon.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanotronics Imaging</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nanotronics-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nanotronics-imaging/</guid>
      <description> Nanotronics Imaging is a nanotechnology startup in Cuyahoga Falls, Ohio. It has an office in Brooklyn, New York at New Lab and manufactures its devices in California.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbc-news/</guid>
      <description> NBC News is the news division of the American broadcast television network NBC. The division operates under NBCUniversal Broadcast, Cable, Sports and News, a subsidiary of NBCUniversal, in turn a subsidiary of Comcast. The group&amp;rsquo;s various operations report to the president of NBC News, Noah Oppenheim.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBCUniversal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbcuniversal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nbcuniversal/</guid>
      <description> NBCUniversal Media, LLC, d/b/a NBCUniversal, is an American worldwide mass media conglomerate owned by Comcast and headquartered at Rockefeller Plaza&amp;rsquo;s Comcast Building in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It is one of two successor companies to MCA Inc., the other being Vivendi through its subsidiary Universal Music Group.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Visions</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-visions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-visions/</guid>
      <description>Launched in 1989, New Visions for Public Schools has become one of New York City’s largest educational nonprofits, supporting schools, training teachers, and operating a growing network of charter schools. The three bars of the new visual identity suggest growth, dynamism, the letter V, and climbing steps. It is simple enough to work everywhere, while standing out from the field of educational logos. To underscore the organization’s commitment to working within the public school system, Chermayeff &amp;amp; Geismar &amp;amp; Haviv gave all the words in the name equal emphasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News 12 Networks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/news-12-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/news-12-networks/</guid>
      <description> The News 12 Networks are a group of regional cable news television channels in the New York metropolitan area that are owned by Altice USA. All channels provide rolling news coverage 24-hours a day, focusing primarily on regions of the metro area outside Manhattan, Queens, and Staten Island.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsday</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/newsday/</guid>
      <description> Newsday is an American daily newspaper that primarily serves Nassau and Suffolk counties and the New York City borough of Queens on Long Island, although it is also sold throughout the New York metropolitan area. In 2012, Newsday expanded to include Rockland and Westchester county news on its website.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ng/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ng/</guid>
      <description>National Geographic (formerly the National Geographic Magazine and branded also as NAT GEO) is the official magazine of the National Geographic Society. It has been published continuously since its first issue in 1888, nine months after the Society itself was founded. It primarily contains articles about science, geography, history, and world culture. The magazine is known for its thick square-bound glossy format with a yellow rectangular border and its extensive use of dramatic photographs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhk/</guid>
      <description> NHK World-Japan is the international broadcasting service of NHK (Nippon Hōsō Kyōkai - Japan Broadcasting Corporation), Japan&amp;rsquo;s public broadcaster. The service is aimed at the overseas market, similar to BBC World News, DW, France 24, CGTN, and RT, and broadcast through satellite and cable operators throughout the world as well as online and through its mobile apps. The channel is based in Tokyo, Japan.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nissay</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nissay/</guid>
      <description> Nippon Life Insurance Company is the largest Japanese life insurance company by revenue. The company was founded in 1889 as the Nippon Life Assurance Co., Inc. In structure it is a mutual company. It first paid policyholder dividends in 1898.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northface</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/northface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/northface/</guid>
      <description> The North Face is an American outdoor recreation product company. The North Face produces clothing, footwear, and outdoor equipment.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novartis</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/novartis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/novartis/</guid>
      <description> Novartis International AG is a Swiss multinational pharmaceutical company based in Basel, Switzerland. It is one of the largest pharmaceutical companies by both market capitalization and sales.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Post</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-post/</guid>
      <description> The New York Post (sometimes abbreviated as NY Post) is a daily newspaper in New York City. The Post also operates the celebrity gossip site PageSix.com, the entertainment site Decider.com, and co-produces the television show Page Six TV.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYU</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyu/</guid>
      <description> New York University (NYU) is a private research university based in New York City. Founded in 1831, NYU&amp;rsquo;s historical campus is in Greenwich Village, Lower Manhattan. NYU also has degree-granting campuses in Abu Dhabi and Shanghai, and academic centers in Accra, Berlin, Buenos Aires, Florence, London, Los Angeles, Madrid, Paris, Prague, Sydney, Tel Aviv, and Washington, D.C.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Predators</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-predators/</guid>
      <description> The Nashville Predators are a professional ice hockey team based in Nashville, Tennessee. They are members of the Central Division of the Western Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The Predators&amp;rsquo; television broadcasting rights are held by Fox Sports Tennessee, whereas radio broadcasting rights are held by WPRT-FM. The Predators have played their home games at Bridgestone Arena since 1998.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville SC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-sc/</guid>
      <description> Nashville Soccer Club is an American professional soccer team based in Nashville, Tennessee. Founded in 2016, the team made its debut in the United Soccer League in 2018.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NE Revolution</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ne-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ne-revolution/</guid>
      <description> The New England Revolution is an American professional soccer club based in the Greater Boston area that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), in the Eastern Conference of the league. It is one of the ten charter clubs of MLS, having competed in the league since its inaugural season.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey Devils</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-jersey-devils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-jersey-devils/</guid>
      <description>The New Jersey Devils are a professional ice hockey team based in Newark, New Jersey. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The club was founded as the Kansas City Scouts in Kansas City, Missouri, in 1974. The Scouts moved to Denver, Colorado in 1976 and became the Colorado Rockies. In 1982, they moved to East Rutherford, New Jersey and took their current name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Islanders</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-islanders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-islanders/</guid>
      <description>The New York Islanders are a professional ice hockey team based in the New York metropolitan area. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team splits its home games between Barclays Center in the borough of Brooklyn and Nassau Coliseum in Uniondale, New York. The Islanders are one of three NHL franchises in the New York metropolitan area, along with the New Jersey Devils and New York Rangers, and their fan base resides primarily on Long Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Rangers</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-rangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-rangers/</guid>
      <description>The New York Rangers are a professional ice hockey team based in New York City. They are members of the Metropolitan Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team plays its home games at Madison Square Garden in the borough of Manhattan, an arena they share with the New York Knicks of the National Basketball Association (NBA). They are one of three NHL teams located in the New York metropolitan area; the others being the New Jersey Devils and New York Islanders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Red Bulls</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-red-bulls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ny-red-bulls/</guid>
      <description>The New York Red Bulls are an American professional soccer club based in Harrison, New Jersey. The Red Bulls compete as a member of the Eastern Conference of Major League Soccer (MLS). The club was established in October 1994 and began play in the league&amp;rsquo;s inaugural season in 1996 as the New York/New Jersey MetroStars. In 2006, the team was sold to Red Bull GmbH and re-branded as part of the company&amp;rsquo;s global network of football clubs, leading to the team&amp;rsquo;s current name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-fc/</guid>
      <description> New York City Football Club is an American professional soccer club based in New York City that competes in Major League Soccer (MLS), the highest level of American soccer, as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nba/</guid>
      <description> The National Basketball Association (NBA) is a men&amp;rsquo;s professional basketball league in North America, composed of 30 teams (29 in the United States and 1 in Canada). It is one of the four major professional sports leagues in the United States and Canada, and is widely considered to be the premier men&amp;rsquo;s professional basketball league in the world.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</guid>
      <description>Netflix, Inc. is an American media-services provider headquartered in Los Gatos, California, founded in 1997 by Reed Hastings and Marc Randolph in Scotts Valley, California. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its subscription-based streaming OTT service which offers online streaming of a library of films and television programs, including those produced in-house. As of April 2019, Netflix had over 148 million paid subscriptions worldwide, including 60 million in the United States, and over 154 million subscriptions total including free trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Patriots</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-patriots/</guid>
      <description>The New England Patriots are a professional American football team based in the Greater Boston area. The Patriots compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team plays its home games at Gillette Stadium in the town of Foxborough, Massachusetts, which is located 21 miles (34 km) southwest of downtown Boston, Massachusetts and 20 miles (32 km) northeast of downtown Providence, Rhode Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Saints</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-orleans-saints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-orleans-saints/</guid>
      <description> The New Orleans Saints are a professional American football team based in New Orleans, Louisiana. The Saints currently compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) South division. The team was founded by John W. Mecom Jr., David Dixon, and the city of New Orleans on November 1, 1966. The Saints began play in Tulane Stadium in 1967.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Giants</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-giants/</guid>
      <description>The New York Giants are a professional American football team based in the New York metropolitan area. The Giants compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s National Football Conference (NFC) East division. The team plays its home games at MetLife Stadium in East Rutherford, New Jersey, which it shares with the New York Jets in a unique arrangement. The Giants hold their summer training camp at the Quest Diagnostics Training Center at the Meadowlands Sports Complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Jets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-jets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-jets/</guid>
      <description>The New York Jets are a professional American football team located in the New York metropolitan area. The Jets compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team is headquartered in Florham Park, New Jersey. In a unique arrangement for the league, the Jets share MetLife Stadium in East Rutherford, New Jersey with the New York Giants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Mets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-mets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-mets/</guid>
      <description> The New York Mets are an American professional baseball team based in the New York City borough of Queens. The Mets compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the National League (NL) East division. The Mets are one of two Major League clubs based in New York City; the other is the New York Yankees of the American League East.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Yankees</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-york-yankees/</guid>
      <description>The New York Yankees are an American professional baseball team based in the New York City borough of the Bronx. The Yankees compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) East division. They are one of two major league clubs based in New York City; the other club is the National League (NL)&amp;rsquo;s New York Mets. In the 1901 season, the club began play in the AL as the Baltimore Orioles (no relation to the modern Baltimore Orioles).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nfl/</guid>
      <description>The National Football League (NFL) is a professional American football league consisting of 32 teams, divided equally between the National Football Conference (NFC) and the American Football Conference (AFC). The NFL is one of the four major professional sports leagues in North America, and the highest professional level of American football in the world. The NFL&amp;rsquo;s 17-week regular season runs from early September to late December, with each team playing 16 games and having one bye week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHL</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nhl/</guid>
      <description>The National Hockey League (NHL; French: Ligue nationale de hockey—LNH) is a professional ice hockey league in North America, currently comprising 31 teams: 24 in the United States and 7 in Canada. The NHL is considered to be the premier professional ice hockey league in the world, and one of the major professional sports leagues in the United States and Canada. The Stanley Cup, the oldest professional sports trophy in North America, is awarded annually to the league playoff champion at the end of each season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NJPAC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</guid>
      <description> The New Jersey Performing Arts Center (NJPAC), in downtown Newark, New Jersey, United States, is one of the largest performing arts centers in the United States. Home to the New Jersey Symphony Orchestra (NJSO), more than nine million visitors (including more than one million children) have visited the center since it opened in October 1997 on the site of the former Military Park Hotel.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC Parks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks/</guid>
      <description> The New York City Department of Parks and Recreation, also called the Parks Department or NYC Parks, is the department of the government of New York City responsible for maintaining the city&amp;rsquo;s parks system, preserving and maintaining the ecological diversity of the city&amp;rsquo;s natural areas, and furnishing recreational opportunities for city&amp;rsquo;s residents and visitors.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nescafe</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nescafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nescafe/</guid>
      <description> Nescafé is a brand of coffee made by Nestlé. It comes in many different forms. The name is a portmanteau of the words &amp;ldquo;Nestlé&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;café&amp;rdquo;. Nestlé first introduced their flagship coffee brand in Switzerland on 1 April 1938.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nestle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</guid>
      <description> Nestlé S.A. is a Swiss multinational food and drink company headquartered in Vevey, Vaud, Switzerland. It is the largest food company in the world, measured by revenues and other metrics, since 2014. It ranked No. 64 on the Fortune Global 500 in 2017 and No. 33 on the 2016 edition of the Forbes Global 2000 list of largest public companies.[
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nike/</guid>
      <description>Nike, Inc. is an American multinational corporation that is engaged in the design, development, manufacturing, and worldwide marketing and sales of footwear, apparel, equipment, accessories, and services. The company is headquartered near Beaverton, Oregon, in the Portland metropolitan area. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest supplier of athletic shoes and apparel and a major manufacturer of sports equipment, with revenue in excess of US$24.1 billion in its fiscal year 2012 (ending May 31, 2012).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</guid>
      <description> Nikon Corporation is a Japanese multinational corporation headquartered in Tokyo, Japan, specializing in optics and imaging products.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</guid>
      <description> Nintendo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese multinational consumer electronics and video game company headquartered in Kyoto. Nintendo is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest video game companies by market capitalization, creating some of the best-known and top-selling video game franchises, such as Mario, The Legend of Zelda, and Pokémon.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nokia/</guid>
      <description>Nokia Corporation is a Finnish multinational telecommunications, information technology, and consumer electronics company, founded in 1865. Nokia&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Espoo, in the greater Helsinki metropolitan area. In 2018, Nokia employed approximately 103,000 people across over 100 countries, did business in more than 130 countries, and reported annual revenues of around €23 billion. Nokia is a public limited company listed on the Helsinki Stock Exchange and New York Stock Exchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern University</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Journal of Medicine</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine/</guid>
      <description>About NEJM The New England Journal of Medicine is a weekly medical journal published by the Massachusetts Medical Society. It is among the most prestigious peer-reviewed medical journals as well as the oldest continuously published one.
 The New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM) is the world’s leading medical journal and website. Published continuously for over 200 years, NEJM delivers high-quality, peer-reviewed research and interactive clinical content to physicians, educators, and the global medical community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nova Research Labs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nova-research-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 19:19:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nova-research-labs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>