<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>N on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/n/</link>
    <description>Recent content in N on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/n/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NJPAC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/njpac/</guid>
      <description> The New Jersey Performing Arts Center (NJPAC), in downtown Newark, New Jersey, United States, is one of the largest performing arts centers in the United States. Home to the New Jersey Symphony Orchestra (NJSO), more than nine million visitors (including more than one million children) have visited the center since it opened in October 1997 on the site of the former Military Park Hotel.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC Parks</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nyc-parks/</guid>
      <description> The New York City Department of Parks and Recreation, also called the Parks Department or NYC Parks, is the department of the government of New York City responsible for maintaining the city&amp;rsquo;s parks system, preserving and maintaining the ecological diversity of the city&amp;rsquo;s natural areas, and furnishing recreational opportunities for city&amp;rsquo;s residents and visitors.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nescafe</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nescafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nescafe/</guid>
      <description> Nescafé is a brand of coffee made by Nestlé. It comes in many different forms. The name is a portmanteau of the words &amp;ldquo;Nestlé&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;café&amp;rdquo;. Nestlé first introduced their flagship coffee brand in Switzerland on 1 April 1938.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nestle</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nestle/</guid>
      <description> Nestlé S.A. is a Swiss multinational food and drink company headquartered in Vevey, Vaud, Switzerland. It is the largest food company in the world, measured by revenues and other metrics, since 2014. It ranked No. 64 on the Fortune Global 500 in 2017 and No. 33 on the 2016 edition of the Forbes Global 2000 list of largest public companies.[
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nike/</guid>
      <description>Nike, Inc. is an American multinational corporation that is engaged in the design, development, manufacturing, and worldwide marketing and sales of footwear, apparel, equipment, accessories, and services. The company is headquartered near Beaverton, Oregon, in the Portland metropolitan area. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest supplier of athletic shoes and apparel and a major manufacturer of sports equipment, with revenue in excess of US$24.1 billion in its fiscal year 2012 (ending May 31, 2012).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</guid>
      <description> Nikon Corporation is a Japanese multinational corporation headquartered in Tokyo, Japan, specializing in optics and imaging products.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</guid>
      <description> Nintendo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese multinational consumer electronics and video game company headquartered in Kyoto. Nintendo is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest video game companies by market capitalization, creating some of the best-known and top-selling video game franchises, such as Mario, The Legend of Zelda, and Pokémon.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nokia/</guid>
      <description>Nokia Corporation is a Finnish multinational telecommunications, information technology, and consumer electronics company, founded in 1865. Nokia&amp;rsquo;s headquarters are in Espoo, in the greater Helsinki metropolitan area. In 2018, Nokia employed approximately 103,000 people across over 100 countries, did business in more than 130 countries, and reported annual revenues of around €23 billion. Nokia is a public limited company listed on the Helsinki Stock Exchange and New York Stock Exchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern University</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/northwestern-university/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Journal of Medicine</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:24:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-journal-of-medicine/</guid>
      <description>About NEJM The New England Journal of Medicine is a weekly medical journal published by the Massachusetts Medical Society. It is among the most prestigious peer-reviewed medical journals as well as the oldest continuously published one.
 The New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM) is the world’s leading medical journal and website. Published continuously for over 200 years, NEJM delivers high-quality, peer-reviewed research and interactive clinical content to physicians, educators, and the global medical community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nova Research Labs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nova-research-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 19:19:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nova-research-labs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 23:04:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nevada-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New England Fertility Institute</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/new-england-fertility-institute/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>