<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>crypto on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/crypto/</link><description>Recent content in crypto on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/kryptex//file/kryptex.svg</url><title>Kryptex Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Kryptex</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/kryptex/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kryptex/</guid><description turbo="true">The word cryptex is a neologism coined by the author Dan Brown for his 2003 novel The Da Vinci Code, denoting a portable vault used to hide secret messages. It is a word formed from Greek κρυπτός kryptós, &amp;ldquo;hidden, secret&amp;rdquo; and Latin codex; &amp;ldquo;an apt title for this device&amp;rdquo; since it uses &amp;ldquo;the science of cryptology to protect information written on the contained scroll or codex&amp;rdquo;. The first physical cryptex was created by Justin Kirk Nevins in 2004.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate//file/minergate.svg</url><title>MinerGate Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MinerGate</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate/</guid><description turbo="true"> MinerGate is one of the largest multicurrency mining pools, where users join resources to get a share of profits. The project was started in 2014 by a group of blockchain enthusiasts, led by Claude Lecomte. MinerGate operates with 10 coins and supports 4 major mining algorithms.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/decred//file/decred.svg</url><title>Decred Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Decred</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/decred/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/decred/</guid><description turbo="true"> Decred (DCR) is an open-source, community-based cryptocurrency, similar to Bitcoin. Decred was launched in February 2016 by the bitcoin developers that engineered btcsuite, an alternative full-node Bitcoin implementation written in the Go (golang) programming language and is used by development projects such as Ethereum, Factom, BitGo, OpenBazaar, and the Lightning Network.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus//file/exodus.svg</url><title>Exodus Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Exodus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus/</guid><description turbo="true"> Exodus is a multi-cryptocurrency wallet that boasts an easy-to-use UI. You can keep your Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), DASH, Decred (DCR), Ethereum Classic (ETC), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Bitcoin Gold (BTG) and Vertcoin (VTC), along with a continuously increasing number of Ethereum tokens, all in one place and easily calculate and organize your savings with their pie chart portfolio.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/iota//file/iota.svg</url><title>Iota Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Iota</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/iota/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iota/</guid><description turbo="true">IOTA is an open-source distributed ledger (cryptocurrency) focused on providing secure communications and payments between machines on the Internet of Things. Using directed acyclic graph (DAG) technology instead of the traditional blockchain, IOTA&amp;rsquo;s transactions are free regardless of the size of the transaction, confirmations times are fast, the number of transactions the system can handle simultaneously is unlimited, and the system can easily scale. IOTA was founded in 2015 by David Sonstebo, Sergey Ivancheglo, Dominik Schiener, and Dr.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem//file/nem.svg</url><title>NEM Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NEM</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</guid><description turbo="true"> NEM is a peer-to-peer blockchain platform for app developers. Its native cryptocurrency is the XEM. Its code was created from scratch in Java by the New Economy Movement (NEM), which seeks to build &amp;ldquo;a new economy based on the principles of financial freedom, decentralization, equality and solidarity&amp;rdquo;.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/neo//file/neo.svg</url><title>NEO Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NEO</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/neo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/neo/</guid><description turbo="true">NEO (formerly known as Antshares) is a smart economy platform and the first Chinese blockchain project. The project was founded in 2014 and was a real-time open source on GitHub in June 2015. NEO coin and the platform aims to develop a &amp;ldquo;smart economy&amp;rdquo; with a distributed network by utilizing blockchain technology and digital identity to digitize assets and automating the management of digital assets using smart contracts. NEO coin is currently traded on Bittrex, Cryptopia and Binance among other exchanges.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/status//file/status.svg</url><title>Status Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Status</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/status/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/status/</guid><description turbo="true"> Status (SNT) is a cryptocurrency and an open source messaging platform and mobile interface to interact with decentralized applications that run on the Ethereum blockchain.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/waves//file/waves.svg</url><title>Waves Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Waves</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/waves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/waves/</guid><description turbo="true"> Waves Platform is a cryptocurrency project launched by the Russian entrepreneur Alexander Ivanov in 2016. The blockchain platform launch campaign raised $16 million, becoming one of the largest in terms of funds raised through crowdfunding. In June 2017, the Waves platform reported the integration of the dollar payment gateway into the Lite Client, which allows users of the wallet to replenish the account in US dollars.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/binance//file/binance.svg</url><title>Binance Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Binance</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/binance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/binance/</guid><description turbo="true"> Binance is a global cryptocurrency exchange that provides a platform for trading more than 100 cryptocurrencies. Since early 2018, Binance is considered as the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world in terms of trading volume.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin//file/bitcoin.svg</url><title>Bitcoin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bitcoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash//file/bitcoin-cash.svg</url><title>Bitcoin Cash Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bitcoin Cash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017. In 2018 Bitcoin Cash subsequently split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash, and Bitcoin SV. Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano//file/cardano.svg</url><title>Cardano Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cardano</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cardano is een open source cryptovaluta blockchain platform waarop slimme contracten kunnen draaien.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/circle//file/circle.svg</url><title>Circle Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Circle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/circle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/circle/</guid><description turbo="true">Circle is a peer-to-peer payments technology company. It was founded by Jeremy Allaire and Sean Neville in October 2013. Circle&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment platform, Circle Pay, allows users to hold, send, and receive traditional fiat currencies . In September 2015, Circle received the first BitLicense issued from the New York State Department of Financial Services. In April 2016, the British government approved the first virtual currency licensure to Circle. Circle is headquartered in Boston, Massachusetts.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase//file/coinbase.svg</url><title>Coinbase Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coinbase</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coinbase is a digital currency exchange headquartered in San Francisco, California. They broker exchanges of Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic, and Litecoin with fiat currencies in approximately 32 countries, and bitcoin transactions and storage in 190 countries worldwide.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi//file/coinomi.svg</url><title>Coinomi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coinomi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coinomi – is one of the first, and most trusted, cryptocurrency multiwallets. Coinomi is a non-custodial multiwallet and your private keys are stored securely encrypted on your device at all times. The wallet is available on all platforms and the only official download sources are listed on the Coinomi website. Coinomi currently supports more than 125 blockchains and has FULL support for all Ethereum Tokens.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dash//file/dash.svg</url><title>Dash Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Dash is an open source cryptocurrency and is a form of decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) run by a subset of users, called &amp;ldquo;masternodes&amp;rdquo;. It is an altcoin that was forked from the Bitcoin protocol. The currency permits fast transactions that can be untraceable.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/eos//file/eos.svg</url><title>EOS Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">EOS</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/eos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eos/</guid><description turbo="true"> EOS.IO is a blockchain protocol powered by the native cryptocurrency EOS. The smart contract platform claims to eliminate transaction fees and also conduct millions of transactions per second.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum//file/ethereum.svg</url><title>Ethereum Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ethereum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ethereum is an open source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform and operating system featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It supports a modified version of Nakamoto consensus via transaction-based state transitions. Ether is a cryptocurrency generated by the Ethereum platform and used to compensate mining nodes for computations performed. Each Ethereum account has an ether balance and ether may be transferred from one account to another.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic//file/ethereum-classic.svg</url><title>Ethereum Classic Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ethereum Classic</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic/</guid><description turbo="true">Ethereum Classic is an open-source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It provides a decentralized Turing-complete virtual machine, the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), which can execute scripts using an international network of public nodes. Ethereum Classic and Ethereum have a value token called &amp;ldquo;ether&amp;rdquo;, which can be transferred between participants, stored in a cryptocurrency wallet and is used to compensate participant nodes for computations performed in the Ethereum Platform.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi//file/huobi.svg</url><title>Huobi Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Huobi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi/</guid><description turbo="true"> Huobi (Chinese: 火币网; pinyin: Huǒbìwǎng) is a Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange. Founded in China, the company now has offices in Hong Kong, Korea, Japan and the United States. In August 2018 it became a publicly listed Hong Kong company.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger//file/ledger.svg</url><title>Ledger Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ledger</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ledger is a fast paced, growing company developing security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies as well as blockchain applications for individuals and companies, by leveraging a distinctive, proprietary technology.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin//file/litecoin.svg</url><title>Litecoin Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Litecoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Litecoin (LTC or Ł) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency and open-source software project released under the MIT/X11 license. Creation and transfer of coins is based on an open source cryptographic protocol and is not managed by any central authority.[citation needed] Litecoin was an early bitcoin spinoff or altcoin, starting in October 2011. In technical details, litecoin is nearly identical to Bitcoin.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero//file/monero.svg</url><title>Monero Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Monero</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</guid><description turbo="true"> Monero is an open-source cryptocurrency created in April 2014 that focuses on fungibility, privacy and decentralization. Monero uses an obfuscated public ledger, meaning anybody can broadcast or send transactions, but no outside observer can tell the source, amount or destination. Monero uses a Proof of Work mechanism to issue new coins and incentivize miners to secure the network and validate transactions.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple//file/ripple.svg</url><title>Ripple Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ripple</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple/</guid><description turbo="true">Ripple is a real-time gross settlement system, currency exchange and remittance network created by Ripple Labs Inc., a US-based technology company. Released in 2012, Ripple is built upon a distributed open source protocol, and supports tokens representing fiat currency, cryptocurrency, commodities, or other units of value such as frequent flier miles or mobile minutes. Ripple purports to enable &amp;ldquo;secure, instantly and nearly free global financial transactions of any size with no chargebacks.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar//file/stellar.svg</url><title>Stellar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Stellar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar/</guid><description turbo="true"> Stellar is an open source, decentralized protocol for digital currency to fiat money transfers which allows cross-border transactions between any pair of currencies. The Stellar protocol is supported by a 501(c)3 nonprofit, the Stellar Development Foundation.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether//file/tether.svg</url><title>Tether Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tether</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</guid><description turbo="true"> Tether is a controversial cryptocurrency with tokens issued by Tether Limited. It formerly claimed that each token was backed by one United States dollar, but on 14 March 2019 changed the backing to include loans to affiliate companies. The Bitfinex exchange was accused by the New York Attorney General of using Tether&amp;rsquo;s funds to cover up $850 million in funds missing since mid-2018.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash//file/zcash.svg</url><title>Zcash Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Zcash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Zcash is a cryptocurrency aimed at using cryptography to provide enhanced privacy for its users compared to other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin.
Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra//file/calibra.svg</url><title>Calibra Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Calibra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</guid><description turbo="true">About Calibra Calibra is from Facebook. Making it easy to use in your favorite apps. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency that will make money work better for all of us.
Calibra was founded in 2019 with the mission of making money work for everyone. Calibra believe that all people, all over the world should have equal, easy and educated access to financial services. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra//file/libra.svg</url><title>Libra Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Libra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</guid><description turbo="true">About Libra Libra is a new global cryptocurrency. Libra is built on a secure, scalable, and reliable blockchain and is designed to help bring people everywhere equal access to financial services. Libra is backed by a reserve of assets so that its value stays stable. Libra is reinventing money so it can be used in countries around the world. It can easily be sent to anyone and exchanged into local currencies.</description></item></channel></rss>