<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>crypto on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/crypto/</link><description>Recent content in crypto on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Aave Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/aave.svg"/></figure></header>
Aave is a non-custodial money market protocol Users of the Aave protocol can participate as both depositors and borrowers. Depositors provide liquidity to the market to earn passive income, while borrowers are able to borrow using either a stable or variable interest rate. Holders of the AAVE token can participate in governance of the protocol. Check out the chart above to get historical and live Aave price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.<p>You can download theAavelogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/aave.svg</url><title>AaveLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Aave</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/aave/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aave/</guid><description turbo="true">Aave is a non-custodial money market protocol Users of the Aave protocol can participate as both depositors and borrowers. Depositors provide liquidity to the market to earn passive income, while borrowers are able to borrow using either a stable or variable interest rate. Holders of the AAVE token can participate in governance of the protocol. Check out the chart above to get historical and live Aave price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Algorand Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/algorand.svg"/></figure></header>
Algorand is a proof-of-stake blockchain that eliminates the possibility of hard forks The Algorand platform allows users to create tokens and dApps using a unique &amp;ldquo;pure proof-of-stake&amp;rdquo; consensus mechanism that, unlike other PoS systems, requires no &amp;ldquo;bonding&amp;rdquo; period. Algorand is also the first blockchain to provide immediate transaction finality, removing the risk of forking. Source<p>You can download theAlgorandlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/algorand.svg</url><title>AlgorandLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Algorand</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/algorand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/algorand/</guid><description turbo="true"> Algorand is a proof-of-stake blockchain that eliminates the possibility of hard forks The Algorand platform allows users to create tokens and dApps using a unique &amp;ldquo;pure proof-of-stake&amp;rdquo; consensus mechanism that, unlike other PoS systems, requires no &amp;ldquo;bonding&amp;rdquo; period. Algorand is also the first blockchain to provide immediate transaction finality, removing the risk of forking. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Augur Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/augur.svg"/></figure></header>
Augur is a decentralized prediction market platform built on the Ethereum blockchain. Augur is developed by Forecast Foundation, which was founded in 2014 by Jack Peterson, Joey Krug, and Jeremy Gardner. Forecast Foundation is advised by Ron Bernstein, founder of now-defunct company Intrade, and Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin. Source<p>You can download theAugurlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/augur.svg</url><title>AugurLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Augur</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/augur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/augur/</guid><description turbo="true"> Augur is a decentralized prediction market platform built on the Ethereum blockchain. Augur is developed by Forecast Foundation, which was founded in 2014 by Jack Peterson, Joey Krug, and Jeremy Gardner. Forecast Foundation is advised by Ron Bernstein, founder of now-defunct company Intrade, and Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Basic Attention Token Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/basic-attention-token.svg"/></figure></header>
Basic Attention Token powers the first blockchain based digital advertising platform Basic Attention Token (BAT) is an Ethereum-based cryptocurrency that is exchanged between publishers, advertisers and consumers in an effort to improve digital marketing efficiency and prevent billions of dollars worth of fraud that takes place each year. The Basic Attention Token is used on the Brave browser (brave.com) to reward users for viewing ads. Publishers also receive BAT in the form of ad revenue for users consuming their content.<p>You can download theBasic Attention Tokenlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/basic-attention-token.svg</url><title>Basic Attention TokenLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Basic Attention Token</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/basic-attention-token/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/basic-attention-token/</guid><description turbo="true">Basic Attention Token powers the first blockchain based digital advertising platform Basic Attention Token (BAT) is an Ethereum-based cryptocurrency that is exchanged between publishers, advertisers and consumers in an effort to improve digital marketing efficiency and prevent billions of dollars worth of fraud that takes place each year. The Basic Attention Token is used on the Brave browser (brave.com) to reward users for viewing ads. Publishers also receive BAT in the form of ad revenue for users consuming their content.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Bitcoin Cash Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/bitcoin-cash.svg"/></figure></header>
Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is a fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017.
In November 2018, Bitcoin Cash split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV.
Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash. Source<p>You can download theBitcoin Cashlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/bitcoin-cash.svg</url><title>Bitcoin CashLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bitcoin Cash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is a fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017.
In November 2018, Bitcoin Cash split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV.
Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Chainlink Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/chainlink.svg"/></figure></header>
Chainlink is a decentralized oracle that provides external data to smart contracts Using reputation and validation systems to reward honest behavior among tamper-proof oracles, the Chainlink network connects smart contracts to real world data, events and payments. The cryptocurrency that powers the network is LINK, an ERC-20 token that incentivizes oracles - third party blockchain data sources - to maintain service level agreement (SLA) standards. Check out the chart above to get historical and live Chainlink price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.<p>You can download theChainlinklogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/chainlink.svg</url><title>ChainlinkLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Chainlink</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/chainlink/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chainlink/</guid><description turbo="true">Chainlink is a decentralized oracle that provides external data to smart contracts Using reputation and validation systems to reward honest behavior among tamper-proof oracles, the Chainlink network connects smart contracts to real world data, events and payments. The cryptocurrency that powers the network is LINK, an ERC-20 token that incentivizes oracles - third party blockchain data sources - to maintain service level agreement (SLA) standards. Check out the chart above to get historical and live Chainlink price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Compound Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/compound.svg"/></figure></header>
Compound lets you earn interest on various cryptocurrencies Built on the Ethereum blockchain, the Compound protocol establishes money markets which algorithmically derive interest rates based on the supply and demand of different cryptocurrencies. This allows suppliers and borrowers of a given asset to earn or pay a floating interest rate without having to negotiate terms with a peer or counterparty. Source<p>You can download theCompoundlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/compound.svg</url><title>CompoundLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Compound</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/compound/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/compound/</guid><description turbo="true"> Compound lets you earn interest on various cryptocurrencies Built on the Ethereum blockchain, the Compound protocol establishes money markets which algorithmically derive interest rates based on the supply and demand of different cryptocurrencies. This allows suppliers and borrowers of a given asset to earn or pay a floating interest rate without having to negotiate terms with a peer or counterparty. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> ATOM Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/cosmos.svg"/></figure></header>
Cosmos is the internet of blockchains Cosmos is a decentralized ecosystem of blockchains that can scale and interoperate. The goal of Cosmos is to make it easy for developers to build separate blockchains that can interact with each other - essentially forming an internet of blockchains that are networked together. ATOM is the native staking token associated with Cosmos Hub, the first of thousands of interconnected blockchains. Check out the chart above to get historical and live Cosmos price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.<p>You can download theCosmoslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/cosmos.svg</url><title>CosmosLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cosmos</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cosmos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cosmos/</guid><description turbo="true">Cosmos is the internet of blockchains Cosmos is a decentralized ecosystem of blockchains that can scale and interoperate. The goal of Cosmos is to make it easy for developers to build separate blockchains that can interact with each other - essentially forming an internet of blockchains that are networked together. ATOM is the native staking token associated with Cosmos Hub, the first of thousands of interconnected blockchains. Check out the chart above to get historical and live Cosmos price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Curve DAO Token Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/curve-dao.svg"/></figure></header>
Curve is a liquidity pool for stable coins Curve awards the CRV token to users who provide liquidity to their pools. Traders then use the pooled funds to exchange different stable coins, avoiding slippage and high fees. Source<p>You can download theCurve DAOlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/curve-dao.svg</url><title>Curve DAOLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Curve DAO</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/curve-dao/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/curve-dao/</guid><description turbo="true"> Curve is a liquidity pool for stable coins Curve awards the CRV token to users who provide liquidity to their pools. Traders then use the pooled funds to exchange different stable coins, avoiding slippage and high fees. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Dai Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/dai.svg"/></figure></header>
Dai (or DAI) is a stablecoin cryptocurrency which aims to keep its value as close to one United States dollar (USD) as possible through an automated system of smart contracts on the Ethereum blockchain. Dai is maintained and regulated by MakerDAO, a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) composed of the owners of its governance token, MKR, who may vote on changes to certain parameters in its smart contracts in order to ensure the stability of Dai.<p>You can download theDailogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/dai.svg</url><title>DaiLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dai</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dai/</guid><description turbo="true">Dai (or DAI) is a stablecoin cryptocurrency which aims to keep its value as close to one United States dollar (USD) as possible through an automated system of smart contracts on the Ethereum blockchain. Dai is maintained and regulated by MakerDAO, a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) composed of the owners of its governance token, MKR, who may vote on changes to certain parameters in its smart contracts in order to ensure the stability of Dai.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Filecoin Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/filecoin.svg"/></figure></header>
Filecoin (⨎) is an open-source, public, cryptocurrency and digital payment system intended to be a blockchain-based cooperative digital storage and data retrieval method. It is made by Protocol Labs and builds on top of InterPlanetary File System, allowing users to rent unused hard drive space. A blockchain mechanism is used to register the deals. Source<p>You can download theFilecoinlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/filecoin.svg</url><title>FilecoinLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Filecoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/filecoin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/filecoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Filecoin (⨎) is an open-source, public, cryptocurrency and digital payment system intended to be a blockchain-based cooperative digital storage and data retrieval method. It is made by Protocol Labs and builds on top of InterPlanetary File System, allowing users to rent unused hard drive space. A blockchain mechanism is used to register the deals. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Gnosis Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/gnosis.svg"/></figure></header>
Gnosis is an Ethereum-based prediction market protocol Gnosis enables users to trade cryptocurrencies that are representative of events. As the outcome of these events become clear, Gnosis tokens gain or lose value depending on what was predicted by the user. GNO tokens are staked in order to pay the fees associated with the platform. Source<p>You can download theGnosislogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/gnosis.svg</url><title>GnosisLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Gnosis</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/gnosis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gnosis/</guid><description turbo="true"> Gnosis is an Ethereum-based prediction market protocol Gnosis enables users to trade cryptocurrencies that are representative of events. As the outcome of these events become clear, Gnosis tokens gain or lose value depending on what was predicted by the user. GNO tokens are staked in order to pay the fees associated with the platform. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>ICON Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/icon.svg"/></figure></header>
The ICON network connects blockchain products with established institutions in the real world ICON is a decentralized network seeking to connect blockchain communities that were previously independent. Anyone in the world can now create a blockchain project, participate in the ICON network and interact with existing communities comprised of reputable institutions like banks, securities, hospitals, universities and more. The cryptocurrency used for real-time payments within the ICON network is ICX.<p>You can download theICONlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/icon.svg</url><title>ICONLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">ICON</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/icon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/icon/</guid><description turbo="true">The ICON network connects blockchain products with established institutions in the real world ICON is a decentralized network seeking to connect blockchain communities that were previously independent. Anyone in the world can now create a blockchain project, participate in the ICON network and interact with existing communities comprised of reputable institutions like banks, securities, hospitals, universities and more. The cryptocurrency used for real-time payments within the ICON network is ICX.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Kusama Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/kusama.svg"/></figure></header>
Kusama is an experimental test environment based on Polkadot&amp;rsquo;s codebase Created by the same team that deployed Polkadot, Kusama is a testing ground for developers that hold the KSM token and want to build and deploy a parachain or try out Polkadot&amp;rsquo;s governance, staking, nomination and validation functionality in a real environment. Source<p>You can download theKusamalogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/kusama.svg</url><title>KusamaLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Kusama</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/kusama/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kusama/</guid><description turbo="true"> Kusama is an experimental test environment based on Polkadot&amp;rsquo;s codebase Created by the same team that deployed Polkadot, Kusama is a testing ground for developers that hold the KSM token and want to build and deploy a parachain or try out Polkadot&amp;rsquo;s governance, staking, nomination and validation functionality in a real environment. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Kyber Network Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/kyber-network.svg"/></figure></header>
Kyber Network is a decentralized liquidity protocol used for token swaps Kyber allows for instant token exchanges for any decentralized application (dapp) without the need for an intermediary. Kyber Network Crystal (KNC), the first deflationary staking token, plays a critical role in the network, allowing owners to earn staking rewards and voting rights on the protocol. Source<p>You can download theKyber Networklogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/kyber-network.svg</url><title>Kyber NetworkLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Kyber Network</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/kyber-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kyber-network/</guid><description turbo="true"> Kyber Network is a decentralized liquidity protocol used for token swaps Kyber allows for instant token exchanges for any decentralized application (dapp) without the need for an intermediary. Kyber Network Crystal (KNC), the first deflationary staking token, plays a critical role in the network, allowing owners to earn staking rewards and voting rights on the protocol. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Nano Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/nano.svg"/></figure></header>
Nano (NANO), formerly RaiBlocks (XRB), is a peer-to-peer digital currency. It is a decentralized, open-source cryptocurrency based on directed acyclic graph (DAG) architecture, and released under the FreeBSD License. It operates without intermediaries by utilizing a distributed ledger with a block-lattice data structure.
Nano was launched in October 2015 by Colin LeMahieu, with the aim of addressing blockchain scalability limitations that can result in restrictive fees and increased transaction confirmation times under load.<p>You can download theNanologo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/nano.svg</url><title>NanoLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nano</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nano/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nano/</guid><description turbo="true">Nano (NANO), formerly RaiBlocks (XRB), is a peer-to-peer digital currency. It is a decentralized, open-source cryptocurrency based on directed acyclic graph (DAG) architecture, and released under the FreeBSD License. It operates without intermediaries by utilizing a distributed ledger with a block-lattice data structure.
Nano was launched in October 2015 by Colin LeMahieu, with the aim of addressing blockchain scalability limitations that can result in restrictive fees and increased transaction confirmation times under load.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>OmiseGO Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/omisego.svg"/></figure></header>
The OmiseGo network enables instant transactions in real-time for financial services OmiseGO (OMG) is a global platform for open financial services that enables transparent, peer-to-peer transactions in real-time across multiple blockchains, geographies and applications. The cryptocurrency that powers OmiseGO is the OMG token, which is based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ERC-20 standard. OmiseGO also provides a white labeled eWallet designed for businesses that can be used to digitize and store assets, pay for goods and services or receive payments from customers.<p>You can download theOmiseGOlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/omisego.svg</url><title>OmiseGOLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">OmiseGO</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/omisego/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/omisego/</guid><description turbo="true">The OmiseGo network enables instant transactions in real-time for financial services OmiseGO (OMG) is a global platform for open financial services that enables transparent, peer-to-peer transactions in real-time across multiple blockchains, geographies and applications. The cryptocurrency that powers OmiseGO is the OMG token, which is based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ERC-20 standard. OmiseGO also provides a white labeled eWallet designed for businesses that can be used to digitize and store assets, pay for goods and services or receive payments from customers.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Polkadot Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/polkadot.svg"/></figure></header>
Polkadot is a heterogeneous multi-chain interchange and translation architecture which enables customised side-chains to connect with public blockchains. Blockchains can exchange messages in a secure and trust-free manner with Polkadot.
The protocol was created by the Ethereum co-founder Gavin Wood, and raised $144.3 million in its Initial Coin Offering in October 2017. Source<p>You can download thePolkadotlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/polkadot.svg</url><title>PolkadotLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Polkadot</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/polkadot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/polkadot/</guid><description turbo="true"> Polkadot is a heterogeneous multi-chain interchange and translation architecture which enables customised side-chains to connect with public blockchains. Blockchains can exchange messages in a secure and trust-free manner with Polkadot.
The protocol was created by the Ethereum co-founder Gavin Wood, and raised $144.3 million in its Initial Coin Offering in October 2017. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Qtum Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/qtum.svg"/></figure></header>
Qtum is a hybrid platform that combines elements of both Bitcoin and Ethereum Qtum was the first to combine the value transfer functionality of Bitcoin (BTC) and the smart contract support of Ethereum (ETH) into a single platform. This allows users to build applications running on a blockchain, while also allowing their creations to transact in a way that&amp;rsquo;s similar to Bitcoin. The QTUM cryptocurrency is used to pay fees and provide governance on the platform.<p>You can download theQtumlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/qtum.svg</url><title>QtumLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Qtum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/qtum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/qtum/</guid><description turbo="true">Qtum is a hybrid platform that combines elements of both Bitcoin and Ethereum Qtum was the first to combine the value transfer functionality of Bitcoin (BTC) and the smart contract support of Ethereum (ETH) into a single platform. This allows users to build applications running on a blockchain, while also allowing their creations to transact in a way that&amp;rsquo;s similar to Bitcoin. The QTUM cryptocurrency is used to pay fees and provide governance on the platform.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Siacoin Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/siacoin.svg"/></figure></header>
Sia is an affordable, blockchain-based cloud storage marketplace Sia is a decentralized cloud storage platform that requires no signups, no servers and no third party providers. Sia is completely private, and uses blockchain technology to encrypt and distribute all files stored there across a decentralized network. In order to store files, users must rent storage space using Siacoin (SC), a cryptocurrency that can also be mined and traded. Source<p>You can download theSiacoinlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/siacoin.svg</url><title>SiacoinLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Siacoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/siacoin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siacoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Sia is an affordable, blockchain-based cloud storage marketplace Sia is a decentralized cloud storage platform that requires no signups, no servers and no third party providers. Sia is completely private, and uses blockchain technology to encrypt and distribute all files stored there across a decentralized network. In order to store files, users must rent storage space using Siacoin (SC), a cryptocurrency that can also be mined and traded. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> synthetix.io Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/synthetix.svg"/></figure></header>
Synthetix is an alternative way to invest in fiat currencies, cryptocurrencies and commodities Synthetix is a decentralized protocol built on Ethereum that allows users to gain exposure to assets (cryptocurrencies, gold, stocks) without actually holding the underlying resource. These synthetic assets (Synths) are backed by the platform&amp;rsquo;s cryptocurrency, Synthetix Network Token (SNX), which is staked as collateral in order to generate rewards. Source<p>You can download theSynthetixlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/synthetix.svg</url><title>SynthetixLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Synthetix</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/synthetix/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/synthetix/</guid><description turbo="true"> Synthetix is an alternative way to invest in fiat currencies, cryptocurrencies and commodities Synthetix is a decentralized protocol built on Ethereum that allows users to gain exposure to assets (cryptocurrencies, gold, stocks) without actually holding the underlying resource. These synthetic assets (Synths) are backed by the platform&amp;rsquo;s cryptocurrency, Synthetix Network Token (SNX), which is staked as collateral in order to generate rewards. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Tezos Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/tezos.svg"/></figure></header>
Tezos is a decentralized, open-source blockchain network that can execute peer-to-peer transactions and serve as a platform for deploying smart contracts. The native cryptocurrency for the Tezos blockchain is the tez or tezzie, which has the symbol XTZ. As of January 2021, there are over 400 block validating nodes (bakers) on the Tezos network. The vast majority of transactions currently happening on Tezos today though are mostly to maintain consensus and are not for more substantive operations, such as executing smart contracts, even though the network has the capacity to handle many more transactions.<p>You can download theTezoslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/tezos.svg</url><title>TezosLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tezos</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tezos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tezos/</guid><description turbo="true">Tezos is a decentralized, open-source blockchain network that can execute peer-to-peer transactions and serve as a platform for deploying smart contracts. The native cryptocurrency for the Tezos blockchain is the tez or tezzie, which has the symbol XTZ. As of January 2021, there are over 400 block validating nodes (bakers) on the Tezos network. The vast majority of transactions currently happening on Tezos today though are mostly to maintain consensus and are not for more substantive operations, such as executing smart contracts, even though the network has the capacity to handle many more transactions.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>The Graph Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/the-graph.svg"/></figure></header>
The Graph makes it possible to index and query data from blockchains With The Graph, anyone can build and publish open APIs, called subgraphs, that make data from blockchains easily accessible. The data from these subgraphs can then be transformed, organized and shared across decentralized applications (dapps) for anyone to query. GRT is the token that powers the economics of The Graph protocol. Source<p>You can download theThe Graphlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/the-graph.svg</url><title>The GraphLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">The Graph</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/the-graph/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/the-graph/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Graph makes it possible to index and query data from blockchains With The Graph, anyone can build and publish open APIs, called subgraphs, that make data from blockchains easily accessible. The data from these subgraphs can then be transformed, organized and shared across decentralized applications (dapps) for anyone to query. GRT is the token that powers the economics of The Graph protocol. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>TRON Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/tron.svg"/></figure></header>
TRON is a blockchain platform where developers can deploy their own decentralized apps (dapps) TRON is powered by delegated proof-of-stake (DPoS), allowing anyone who buys TRX to vote on who can earn rewards for validating transactions on the blockchain. TRON&amp;rsquo;s vision is to create a decentralized version of the internet. Check out the chart above to get historical and live TRON price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.<p>You can download theTRONlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/tron.svg</url><title>TRONLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">TRON</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tron/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tron/</guid><description turbo="true">TRON is a blockchain platform where developers can deploy their own decentralized apps (dapps) TRON is powered by delegated proof-of-stake (DPoS), allowing anyone who buys TRX to vote on who can earn rewards for validating transactions on the blockchain. TRON&amp;rsquo;s vision is to create a decentralized version of the internet. Check out the chart above to get historical and live TRON price data, then use the buy/sell button to start trading.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Uniswap Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/uniswap.svg"/></figure></header>
Uniswap is a decentralized cryptocurrency exchange which facilitates automated transactions between cryptocurrency tokens on the Ethereum blockchain through the use of smart contracts. As of October 2020, Uniswap is estimated to be the largest decentralized exchange and the fourth-largest cryptocurrency exchange overall by daily trading volume. Source<p>You can download theUniswaplogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/uniswap.svg</url><title>UniswapLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Uniswap</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/uniswap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/uniswap/</guid><description turbo="true"> Uniswap is a decentralized cryptocurrency exchange which facilitates automated transactions between cryptocurrency tokens on the Ethereum blockchain through the use of smart contracts. As of October 2020, Uniswap is estimated to be the largest decentralized exchange and the fourth-largest cryptocurrency exchange overall by daily trading volume. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Yearn Finance Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/yearn.svg"/></figure></header>
Yearn.Finance is a decentralized yield aggregator running on the Ethereum blockchain Cryptocurrency deposited on Yearn.Finance is automatically lended out at the highest lending rate possible across a number of other platforms. YFI is the token for Yearn Finance. Holders of YFI can participate in the protocol&amp;rsquo;s governance and earn a percentage of the fees generated on the various Yearn Finance products through staking. Source<p>You can download theYearnlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/yearn.svg</url><title>YearnLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Yearn</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/yearn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yearn/</guid><description turbo="true"> Yearn.Finance is a decentralized yield aggregator running on the Ethereum blockchain Cryptocurrency deposited on Yearn.Finance is automatically lended out at the highest lending rate possible across a number of other platforms. YFI is the token for Yearn Finance. Holders of YFI can participate in the protocol&amp;rsquo;s governance and earn a percentage of the fees generated on the various Yearn Finance products through staking. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Kryptex Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/kryptex.svg"/></figure></header>
The word cryptex is a neologism coined by the author Dan Brown for his 2003 novel The Da Vinci Code, denoting a portable vault used to hide secret messages. It is a word formed from Greek κρυπτός kryptós, &amp;ldquo;hidden, secret&amp;rdquo; and Latin codex; &amp;ldquo;an apt title for this device&amp;rdquo; since it uses &amp;ldquo;the science of cryptology to protect information written on the contained scroll or codex&amp;rdquo;. The first physical cryptex was created by Justin Kirk Nevins in 2004.<p>You can download theKryptexlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/kryptex.svg</url><title>KryptexLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Kryptex</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/kryptex/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kryptex/</guid><description turbo="true">The word cryptex is a neologism coined by the author Dan Brown for his 2003 novel The Da Vinci Code, denoting a portable vault used to hide secret messages. It is a word formed from Greek κρυπτός kryptós, &amp;ldquo;hidden, secret&amp;rdquo; and Latin codex; &amp;ldquo;an apt title for this device&amp;rdquo; since it uses &amp;ldquo;the science of cryptology to protect information written on the contained scroll or codex&amp;rdquo;. The first physical cryptex was created by Justin Kirk Nevins in 2004.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>MinerGate Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/minergate.svg"/></figure></header>
MinerGate is one of the largest multicurrency mining pools, where users join resources to get a share of profits. The project was started in 2014 by a group of blockchain enthusiasts, led by Claude Lecomte. MinerGate operates with 10 coins and supports 4 major mining algorithms. Source<p>You can download theMinerGatelogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/minergate.svg</url><title>MinerGateLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MinerGate</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/minergate/</guid><description turbo="true"> MinerGate is one of the largest multicurrency mining pools, where users join resources to get a share of profits. The project was started in 2014 by a group of blockchain enthusiasts, led by Claude Lecomte. MinerGate operates with 10 coins and supports 4 major mining algorithms. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Decred (DCR) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/decred.svg"/></figure></header>
Decred (DCR) is an open-source, community-based cryptocurrency, similar to Bitcoin. Decred was launched in February 2016 by the bitcoin developers that engineered btcsuite, an alternative full-node Bitcoin implementation written in the Go (golang) programming language and is used by development projects such as Ethereum, Factom, BitGo, OpenBazaar, and the Lightning Network. Source<p>You can download theDecredlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/decred.svg</url><title>DecredLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Decred</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/decred/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/decred/</guid><description turbo="true"> Decred (DCR) is an open-source, community-based cryptocurrency, similar to Bitcoin. Decred was launched in February 2016 by the bitcoin developers that engineered btcsuite, an alternative full-node Bitcoin implementation written in the Go (golang) programming language and is used by development projects such as Ethereum, Factom, BitGo, OpenBazaar, and the Lightning Network. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Dogecoin (DOGE) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/dogecoin.svg"/></figure></header>
Dogecoin (DOGE, symbol: Ð and D) is a Litecoin-derived cryptocurrency featuring a Shiba Inu from the Doge Internet meme on its logo. The users themselves call it “joky”. One of the most popular uses of the coin is the reward of Internet users for interesting and quality content created or shared by them. It was introduced on December 8, 2013. Source<p>You can download theDogecoinlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/dogecoin.svg</url><title>DogecoinLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dogecoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dogecoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dogecoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Dogecoin (DOGE, symbol: Ð and D) is a Litecoin-derived cryptocurrency featuring a Shiba Inu from the Doge Internet meme on its logo. The users themselves call it “joky”. One of the most popular uses of the coin is the reward of Internet users for interesting and quality content created or shared by them. It was introduced on December 8, 2013. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Exodus Wallet Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/exodus.svg"/></figure></header>
Exodus is a multi-cryptocurrency wallet that boasts an easy-to-use UI. You can keep your Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), DASH, Decred (DCR), Ethereum Classic (ETC), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Bitcoin Gold (BTG) and Vertcoin (VTC), along with a continuously increasing number of Ethereum tokens, all in one place and easily calculate and organize your savings with their pie chart portfolio. Source<p>You can download theExoduslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/exodus.svg</url><title>ExodusLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Exodus</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/exodus/</guid><description turbo="true"> Exodus is a multi-cryptocurrency wallet that boasts an easy-to-use UI. You can keep your Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), DASH, Decred (DCR), Ethereum Classic (ETC), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Bitcoin Gold (BTG) and Vertcoin (VTC), along with a continuously increasing number of Ethereum tokens, all in one place and easily calculate and organize your savings with their pie chart portfolio. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Iota (MIOTA) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/iota.svg"/></figure></header>
IOTA is an open-source distributed ledger (cryptocurrency) focused on providing secure communications and payments between machines on the Internet of Things. Using directed acyclic graph (DAG) technology instead of the traditional blockchain, IOTA&amp;rsquo;s transactions are free regardless of the size of the transaction, confirmations times are fast, the number of transactions the system can handle simultaneously is unlimited, and the system can easily scale. IOTA was founded in 2015 by David Sonstebo, Sergey Ivancheglo, Dominik Schiener, and Dr.<p>You can download theIotalogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/iota.svg</url><title>IotaLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Iota</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/iota/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/iota/</guid><description turbo="true">IOTA is an open-source distributed ledger (cryptocurrency) focused on providing secure communications and payments between machines on the Internet of Things. Using directed acyclic graph (DAG) technology instead of the traditional blockchain, IOTA&amp;rsquo;s transactions are free regardless of the size of the transaction, confirmations times are fast, the number of transactions the system can handle simultaneously is unlimited, and the system can easily scale. IOTA was founded in 2015 by David Sonstebo, Sergey Ivancheglo, Dominik Schiener, and Dr.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> NEM (XEM) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/nem.svg"/></figure></header>
NEM is a peer-to-peer blockchain platform for app developers. Its native cryptocurrency is the XEM. Its code was created from scratch in Java by the New Economy Movement (NEM), which seeks to build &amp;ldquo;a new economy based on the principles of financial freedom, decentralization, equality and solidarity&amp;rdquo;. Source<p>You can download theNEMlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/nem.svg</url><title>NEMLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NEM</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nem/</guid><description turbo="true"> NEM is a peer-to-peer blockchain platform for app developers. Its native cryptocurrency is the XEM. Its code was created from scratch in Java by the New Economy Movement (NEM), which seeks to build &amp;ldquo;a new economy based on the principles of financial freedom, decentralization, equality and solidarity&amp;rdquo;. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> NEO (NEO) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/neo.svg"/></figure></header>
NEO (formerly known as Antshares) is a smart economy platform and the first Chinese blockchain project. The project was founded in 2014 and was a real-time open source on GitHub in June 2015. NEO coin and the platform aims to develop a &amp;ldquo;smart economy&amp;rdquo; with a distributed network by utilizing blockchain technology and digital identity to digitize assets and automating the management of digital assets using smart contracts. NEO coin is currently traded on Bittrex, Cryptopia and Binance among other exchanges.<p>You can download theNEOlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/neo.svg</url><title>NEOLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NEO</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/neo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/neo/</guid><description turbo="true">NEO (formerly known as Antshares) is a smart economy platform and the first Chinese blockchain project. The project was founded in 2014 and was a real-time open source on GitHub in June 2015. NEO coin and the platform aims to develop a &amp;ldquo;smart economy&amp;rdquo; with a distributed network by utilizing blockchain technology and digital identity to digitize assets and automating the management of digital assets using smart contracts. NEO coin is currently traded on Bittrex, Cryptopia and Binance among other exchanges.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Status (SNT) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/status.svg"/></figure></header>
Status (SNT) is a cryptocurrency and an open source messaging platform and mobile interface to interact with decentralized applications that run on the Ethereum blockchain. Source<p>You can download theStatuslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/status.svg</url><title>StatusLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Status</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/status/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/status/</guid><description turbo="true"> Status (SNT) is a cryptocurrency and an open source messaging platform and mobile interface to interact with decentralized applications that run on the Ethereum blockchain. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Waves Platform (WAVES) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/waves.svg"/></figure></header>
Waves Platform is a cryptocurrency project launched by the Russian entrepreneur Alexander Ivanov in 2016. The blockchain platform launch campaign raised $16 million, becoming one of the largest in terms of funds raised through crowdfunding. In June 2017, the Waves platform reported the integration of the dollar payment gateway into the Lite Client, which allows users of the wallet to replenish the account in US dollars. Source<p>You can download theWaveslogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/waves.svg</url><title>WavesLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Waves</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/waves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/waves/</guid><description turbo="true"> Waves Platform is a cryptocurrency project launched by the Russian entrepreneur Alexander Ivanov in 2016. The blockchain platform launch campaign raised $16 million, becoming one of the largest in terms of funds raised through crowdfunding. In June 2017, the Waves platform reported the integration of the dollar payment gateway into the Lite Client, which allows users of the wallet to replenish the account in US dollars. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Binance coin Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/binance.svg"/></figure></header>
Binance is a global cryptocurrency exchange that provides a platform for trading more than 100 cryptocurrencies. Since early 2018, Binance is considered as the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world in terms of trading volume. Source<p>You can download theBinancelogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/binance.svg</url><title>BinanceLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Binance</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/binance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/binance/</guid><description turbo="true"> Binance is a global cryptocurrency exchange that provides a platform for trading more than 100 cryptocurrencies. Since early 2018, Binance is considered as the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world in terms of trading volume. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Bitcoin (BTC) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/bitcoin.svg"/></figure></header>
Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries. Source<p>You can download theBitcoinlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/bitcoin.svg</url><title>BitcoinLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bitcoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Cardano (ADA) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/cardano.svg"/></figure></header>
Cardano is een open source cryptovaluta blockchain platform waarop slimme contracten kunnen draaien. Source<p>You can download theCardanologo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/cardano.svg</url><title>CardanoLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cardano</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cardano/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cardano is een open source cryptovaluta blockchain platform waarop slimme contracten kunnen draaien. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Circle Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/circle.svg"/></figure></header>
Circle is a peer-to-peer payments technology company. It was founded by Jeremy Allaire and Sean Neville in October 2013. Circle&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment platform, Circle Pay, allows users to hold, send, and receive traditional fiat currencies . In September 2015, Circle received the first BitLicense issued from the New York State Department of Financial Services. In April 2016, the British government approved the first virtual currency licensure to Circle. Circle is headquartered in Boston, Massachusetts.<p>You can download theCirclelogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/circle.svg</url><title>CircleLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Circle</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/circle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/circle/</guid><description turbo="true">Circle is a peer-to-peer payments technology company. It was founded by Jeremy Allaire and Sean Neville in October 2013. Circle&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment platform, Circle Pay, allows users to hold, send, and receive traditional fiat currencies . In September 2015, Circle received the first BitLicense issued from the New York State Department of Financial Services. In April 2016, the British government approved the first virtual currency licensure to Circle. Circle is headquartered in Boston, Massachusetts.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Coinbase Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/coinbase.svg"/></figure></header>
Coinbase is a digital currency exchange headquartered in San Francisco, California. They broker exchanges of Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic, and Litecoin with fiat currencies in approximately 32 countries, and bitcoin transactions and storage in 190 countries worldwide. Source<p>You can download theCoinbaselogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/coinbase.svg</url><title>CoinbaseLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coinbase</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinbase/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coinbase is a digital currency exchange headquartered in San Francisco, California. They broker exchanges of Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic, and Litecoin with fiat currencies in approximately 32 countries, and bitcoin transactions and storage in 190 countries worldwide. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Coinomi Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/coinomi.svg"/></figure></header>
Coinomi – is one of the first, and most trusted, cryptocurrency multiwallets. Coinomi is a non-custodial multiwallet and your private keys are stored securely encrypted on your device at all times. The wallet is available on all platforms and the only official download sources are listed on the Coinomi website. Coinomi currently supports more than 125 blockchains and has FULL support for all Ethereum Tokens. Source<p>You can download theCoinomilogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/coinomi.svg</url><title>CoinomiLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Coinomi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/coinomi/</guid><description turbo="true"> Coinomi – is one of the first, and most trusted, cryptocurrency multiwallets. Coinomi is a non-custodial multiwallet and your private keys are stored securely encrypted on your device at all times. The wallet is available on all platforms and the only official download sources are listed on the Coinomi website. Coinomi currently supports more than 125 blockchains and has FULL support for all Ethereum Tokens. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Dash (DASH) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/dash.svg"/></figure></header>
Dash is an open source cryptocurrency and is a form of decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) run by a subset of users, called &amp;ldquo;masternodes&amp;rdquo;. It is an altcoin that was forked from the Bitcoin protocol. The currency permits fast transactions that can be untraceable. Source<p>You can download theDashlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/dash.svg</url><title>DashLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Dash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Dash is an open source cryptocurrency and is a form of decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) run by a subset of users, called &amp;ldquo;masternodes&amp;rdquo;. It is an altcoin that was forked from the Bitcoin protocol. The currency permits fast transactions that can be untraceable. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> EOS (EOS) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/eos.svg"/></figure></header>
EOS.IO is a blockchain protocol powered by the native cryptocurrency EOS. The smart contract platform claims to eliminate transaction fees and also conduct millions of transactions per second. Source<p>You can download theEOSlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/eos.svg</url><title>EOSLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">EOS</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/eos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eos/</guid><description turbo="true"> EOS.IO is a blockchain protocol powered by the native cryptocurrency EOS. The smart contract platform claims to eliminate transaction fees and also conduct millions of transactions per second. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Ethereum (ETH) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/ethereum.svg"/></figure></header>
Ethereum is an open source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform and operating system featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It supports a modified version of Nakamoto consensus via transaction-based state transitions. Ether is a cryptocurrency generated by the Ethereum platform and used to compensate mining nodes for computations performed. Each Ethereum account has an ether balance and ether may be transferred from one account to another. Source<p>You can download theEthereumlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/ethereum.svg</url><title>EthereumLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ethereum</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ethereum is an open source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform and operating system featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It supports a modified version of Nakamoto consensus via transaction-based state transitions. Ether is a cryptocurrency generated by the Ethereum platform and used to compensate mining nodes for computations performed. Each Ethereum account has an ether balance and ether may be transferred from one account to another. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Ethereum Classic (ETC) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/ethereum-classic.svg"/></figure></header>
Ethereum Classic is an open-source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It provides a decentralized Turing-complete virtual machine, the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), which can execute scripts using an international network of public nodes. Ethereum Classic and Ethereum have a value token called &amp;ldquo;ether&amp;rdquo;, which can be transferred between participants, stored in a cryptocurrency wallet and is used to compensate participant nodes for computations performed in the Ethereum Platform.<p>You can download theEthereum Classiclogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/ethereum-classic.svg</url><title>Ethereum ClassicLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ethereum Classic</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ethereum-classic/</guid><description turbo="true">Ethereum Classic is an open-source, public, blockchain-based distributed computing platform featuring smart contract (scripting) functionality. It provides a decentralized Turing-complete virtual machine, the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), which can execute scripts using an international network of public nodes. Ethereum Classic and Ethereum have a value token called &amp;ldquo;ether&amp;rdquo;, which can be transferred between participants, stored in a cryptocurrency wallet and is used to compensate participant nodes for computations performed in the Ethereum Platform.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Huobi token Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/huobi.svg"/></figure></header>
Huobi (Chinese: 火币网; pinyin: Huǒbìwǎng) is a Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange. Founded in China, the company now has offices in Hong Kong, Korea, Japan and the United States. In August 2018 it became a publicly listed Hong Kong company. Source<p>You can download theHuobilogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/huobi.svg</url><title>HuobiLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Huobi</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/huobi/</guid><description turbo="true"> Huobi (Chinese: 火币网; pinyin: Huǒbìwǎng) is a Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange. Founded in China, the company now has offices in Hong Kong, Korea, Japan and the United States. In August 2018 it became a publicly listed Hong Kong company. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Ledger Wallet Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/ledger.svg"/></figure></header>
Ledger is a fast paced, growing company developing security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies as well as blockchain applications for individuals and companies, by leveraging a distinctive, proprietary technology. Source<p>You can download theLedgerlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/ledger.svg</url><title>LedgerLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ledger</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ledger/</guid><description turbo="true"> Ledger is a fast paced, growing company developing security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies as well as blockchain applications for individuals and companies, by leveraging a distinctive, proprietary technology. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Litecoin (LTC) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/litecoin.svg"/></figure></header>
Litecoin (LTC or Ł) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency and open-source software project released under the MIT/X11 license. Creation and transfer of coins is based on an open source cryptographic protocol and is not managed by any central authority.[citation needed] Litecoin was an early bitcoin spinoff or altcoin, starting in October 2011. In technical details, litecoin is nearly identical to Bitcoin. Source<p>You can download theLitecoinlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/litecoin.svg</url><title>LitecoinLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Litecoin</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/litecoin/</guid><description turbo="true"> Litecoin (LTC or Ł) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency and open-source software project released under the MIT/X11 license. Creation and transfer of coins is based on an open source cryptographic protocol and is not managed by any central authority.[citation needed] Litecoin was an early bitcoin spinoff or altcoin, starting in October 2011. In technical details, litecoin is nearly identical to Bitcoin. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Monero (XMR) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/monero.svg"/></figure></header>
Monero is an open-source cryptocurrency created in April 2014 that focuses on fungibility, privacy and decentralization. Monero uses an obfuscated public ledger, meaning anybody can broadcast or send transactions, but no outside observer can tell the source, amount or destination. Monero uses a Proof of Work mechanism to issue new coins and incentivize miners to secure the network and validate transactions. Source<p>You can download theMonerologo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/monero.svg</url><title>MoneroLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Monero</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/monero/</guid><description turbo="true"> Monero is an open-source cryptocurrency created in April 2014 that focuses on fungibility, privacy and decentralization. Monero uses an obfuscated public ledger, meaning anybody can broadcast or send transactions, but no outside observer can tell the source, amount or destination. Monero uses a Proof of Work mechanism to issue new coins and incentivize miners to secure the network and validate transactions. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Ripple XRP (XRP) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/ripple.svg"/></figure></header>
Ripple is a real-time gross settlement system, currency exchange and remittance network created by Ripple Labs Inc., a US-based technology company. Released in 2012, Ripple is built upon a distributed open source protocol, and supports tokens representing fiat currency, cryptocurrency, commodities, or other units of value such as frequent flier miles or mobile minutes. Ripple purports to enable &amp;ldquo;secure, instantly and nearly free global financial transactions of any size with no chargebacks.<p>You can download theRipplelogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/ripple.svg</url><title>RippleLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ripple</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ripple/</guid><description turbo="true">Ripple is a real-time gross settlement system, currency exchange and remittance network created by Ripple Labs Inc., a US-based technology company. Released in 2012, Ripple is built upon a distributed open source protocol, and supports tokens representing fiat currency, cryptocurrency, commodities, or other units of value such as frequent flier miles or mobile minutes. Ripple purports to enable &amp;ldquo;secure, instantly and nearly free global financial transactions of any size with no chargebacks.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Stellar (XLM) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/stellar.svg"/></figure></header>
Stellar is an open source, decentralized protocol for digital currency to fiat money transfers which allows cross-border transactions between any pair of currencies. The Stellar protocol is supported by a 501(c)3 nonprofit, the Stellar Development Foundation. Source<p>You can download theStellarlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/stellar.svg</url><title>StellarLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Stellar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/stellar/</guid><description turbo="true"> Stellar is an open source, decentralized protocol for digital currency to fiat money transfers which allows cross-border transactions between any pair of currencies. The Stellar protocol is supported by a 501(c)3 nonprofit, the Stellar Development Foundation. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Tether (USDT) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/tether.svg"/></figure></header>
Tether is a controversial cryptocurrency with tokens issued by Tether Limited. It formerly claimed that each token was backed by one United States dollar, but on 14 March 2019 changed the backing to include loans to affiliate companies. The Bitfinex exchange was accused by the New York Attorney General of using Tether&amp;rsquo;s funds to cover up $850 million in funds missing since mid-2018. Source<p>You can download theTetherlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/tether.svg</url><title>TetherLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tether</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tether/</guid><description turbo="true"> Tether is a controversial cryptocurrency with tokens issued by Tether Limited. It formerly claimed that each token was backed by one United States dollar, but on 14 March 2019 changed the backing to include loans to affiliate companies. The Bitfinex exchange was accused by the New York Attorney General of using Tether&amp;rsquo;s funds to cover up $850 million in funds missing since mid-2018. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1> Zcash (ZEC) Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/zcash.svg"/></figure></header>
Zcash is a cryptocurrency aimed at using cryptography to provide enhanced privacy for its users compared to other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin. Source<p>You can download theZcashlogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/zcash.svg</url><title>ZcashLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Zcash</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/zcash/</guid><description turbo="true"> Zcash is a cryptocurrency aimed at using cryptography to provide enhanced privacy for its users compared to other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin. Source</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Calibra Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/calibra.svg"/></figure></header>
About Calibra Calibra is from Facebook. Making it easy to use in your favorite apps. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency that will make money work better for all of us.
Calibra was founded in 2019 with the mission of making money work for everyone. Calibra believe that all people, all over the world should have equal, easy and educated access to financial services. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency.<p>You can download theCalibralogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/calibra.svg</url><title>CalibraLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Calibra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</guid><description turbo="true">About Calibra Calibra is from Facebook. Making it easy to use in your favorite apps. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency that will make money work better for all of us.
Calibra was founded in 2019 with the mission of making money work for everyone. Calibra believe that all people, all over the world should have equal, easy and educated access to financial services. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency.</description></item><item turbo="true"><turbo:content>
&lt;! [CDATA[<header><h1>Libra Logo</h1><figure><img src="https://logotyp.us/file/libra.svg"/></figure></header>
About Libra Libra is a new global cryptocurrency. Libra is built on a secure, scalable, and reliable blockchain and is designed to help bring people everywhere equal access to financial services. Libra is backed by a reserve of assets so that its value stays stable. Libra is reinventing money so it can be used in countries around the world. It can easily be sent to anyone and exchanged into local currencies.<p>You can download theLibralogo on full-version of the page.</p>
]] ></turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/file/libra.svg</url><title>LibraLogo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Libra</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</guid><description turbo="true">About Libra Libra is a new global cryptocurrency. Libra is built on a secure, scalable, and reliable blockchain and is designed to help bring people everywhere equal access to financial services. Libra is backed by a reserve of assets so that its value stays stable. Libra is reinventing money so it can be used in countries around the world. It can easily be sent to anyone and exchanged into local currencies.</description></item></channel></rss>