<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>G on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/g/</link>
    <description>Recent content in G on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/g/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gm/</guid>
      <description>General Motors Company, is an American multinational corporation headquartered in Detroit that designs, manufactures, markets, and distributes vehicles and vehicle parts, and sells financial services, with global headquarters in Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Renaissance Center. It was originally founded by William C. Durant on September 16, 1908 as a holding company. The company is the largest American automobile manufacturer, and one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest. As of 2018, General Motors is ranked #10 on the Fortune 500 rankings of the largest United States corporations by total revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/google/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/google/</guid>
      <description>About Google Google is an American multinational technology company that specializes in Internet-related services and products. These include online advertising technologies, search, cloud computing, software, and hardware. Google was founded in 1998 by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while they were Ph.D. students at Stanford University in California.
The current Google logo was released on Sept 1 2015. A sans serif logotype retains google’s distinct multi-color sequence, and a compact version of the Google icon works in small contexts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>