<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Russia on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/russia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Russia on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beeline</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beeline/</guid>
      <description>Beeline (Russian: Билайн), earlier Bee Line GSM (Russian: Би Лайн GSM) is a telecommunications brand by company PJSC VimpelCom, founded in Russia.
 PJSC VimpelCom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s third-largest wireless and second-largest telecommunications operator. Its headquarters is located in Moscow. Since 2009, PJSC VimpelCom has been a subsidiary of VimpelCom Ltd., which has become Veon in 2017. It is based in Amsterdam. VimpelCom&amp;rsquo;s main competitors in Russia are Mobile TeleSystems, MegaFon and Tele2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MegaFon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/megafon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/megafon/</guid>
      <description>MegaFon (Russian: МегаФон), previously known as North-West GSM, is the second largest mobile phone operator and the third largest telecom operator in Russia. It works in the GSM, UMTS and LTE standard. As of June 2012, the company serves 62.1 million subscribers in Russia and 1.6 million in Tajikistan. It is headquartered in Moscow.
 In 2002 the company changed its name from North-West GSM to MegaFon when it acquired several regional companies, becoming the first GSM company in Russia to cover all its territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tele2</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tele2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tele2/</guid>
      <description>Tele2 AB is a European telecommunications operator headquartered in the Kista Science City, Stockholm, Sweden. It is a major telephone operator in the Nordic and Baltic countries and an alternative provider in many others, with about 17 million customers in 8 countries and under franchise in 1 additional countries.
 Tele2 started as a telecommunications company in Sweden in 1993 by the company Investment AB Kinnevik.
Tele2 operates in Sweden, Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania, the Netherlands, Croatia, Russia and Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gazprom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/gazprom/</guid>
      <description>Public Joint Stock Company Gazprom is a large Russian company founded in 1989, which carries on the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of natural gas. The company is majority owned by the Government of Russia, via the Federal Agency for State Property Management and Rosneftegaz. The remaining shares are listed on public stock markets of Moscow, London and Frankfurt. The Gazprom name is a portmanteau of the Russian words Gazovaya Promyshlennost (Russian: га́зовая промы́шленность - gas industry).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lukoil</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lukoil/</guid>
      <description>The PJSC Lukoil Oil Company is a Russian multinational energy corporation headquartered in Moscow, specializing in the business of extraction, production, transport, and sale of petroleum, natural gas, and petroleum products. It was formed in 1991 when three state-run, western Siberian companies named after the respective town in Khanty–Mansi Autonomous Okrug that each was based in, Langepasneftegaz, Urayneftegaz, and Kogalymneftegaz, merged. Its name is the combination of the acronym LUK (initials of the oil-producing cities of Langepas, Uray, Kogalym) and the English word &amp;ldquo;oil&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBK TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbk-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbk-tv/</guid>
      <description> RBC TV (Russian: РБК) is the first (and so far only) 24-hour business news television channel in Russia. It is owned and operated by the RBC Group. The channel was launched in September 2003 in partnership with the CNBC and CNN television channels.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosneft</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rosneft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rosneft/</guid>
      <description>PJSC Rosneft Oil Company (Russian: Росне́фть, tr. Rosnéft&amp;rsquo;, IPA: stylized as ROSNEFT) is a Russian integrated energy company headquartered in the Russian capital of Moscow. It is specializing on exploration, extraction, production, refinement, transport, and sale of petroleum, natural gas, and petroleum products. The company is controlled by the Russian government through the Rosneftegaz holding company. Its name is a portmanteau of the Russian words Rossiyskaya neft&amp;rsquo; (Russian: Российская нефть - Russian oil).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RT</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rt/</guid>
      <description> RT (formerly Russia Today) is a Russian international television network funded by the Russian government. It operates pay television channels directed to audiences outside of Russia, as well as providing Internet content in English, Spanish, French, German, Arabic and Russian.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia 24</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/russia-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/russia-24/</guid>
      <description> Russia-24 is a state-owned Russian-language news channel from Russia. It covers major national and international events as well as focuses on domestic issues. It is owned by VGTRK
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siberia Airlines</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/siberia-airlines/</guid>
      <description> S7 Airlines, legally JSC Siberia Airlines (Russian: АО «Авиакомпания &amp;ldquo;Сибирь&amp;rdquo;», &amp;ldquo;АО Aviakompania Sibir&amp;rdquo;), is an airline headquartered in Ob, Novosibirsk Oblast, Russia, with offices in Moscow. As of 2008, it is Russia&amp;rsquo;s biggest domestic airline, with its main bases at Domodedovo International Airport and Tolmachevo Airport
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telegram</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</guid>
      <description> Telegram is a cloud-based instant messaging and voice over IP service. Telegram client apps are available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any type.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vk/</guid>
      <description> VK (short for its original name VKontakte; Russian: ВКонта́кте, meaning InContact) is a Russian online social media and social networking service based in Saint Petersburg. VK is available in numerous languages but it is especially used by Russian-speakers. VK allows users to message each other publicly or privately; create groups, public pages, and events; share and tag images, audio, and video; and play browser-based games.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2014 Sochi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi/</guid>
      <description>The 2014 Winter Olympics, officially called the XXII Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XXIIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver) (Russian: XXII Олимпийские зимние игры, tr. XXII Olimpiyskiye zimniye igry) and commonly known as Sochi 2014, was an international winter multi-sport event that was held from 7 to 23 February 2014 in Sochi, Krasnodar Krai, Russia, with opening rounds in certain events held on the eve of the opening ceremony, 6 February 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aeroflot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</guid>
      <description> Aeroflot – Russian Airlines is the flag carrier and largest airline of the Russian Federation. The carrier is an open joint stock company that operates domestic and international passenger and services, mainly from its hub at Sheremetyevo International Airport.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfa Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</guid>
      <description>Alfa Bank JSC, the corporate treasury of the Alfa Group, is one of the largest private commercial banks in Russia. It was founded by Russian businessman Mikhail Fridman, who is still the controlling owner today. It is headquartered in Moscow. It operates in seven countries, providing financial services to over 381,600 active corporate customers and 14.2 million retail clients. Alfa-Bank is particularly active in Russia and Ukraine, ranking among top 10 largest banks in terms of capital in both countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rambler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</guid>
      <description> Rambler (Russian: Рамблер) is a Russian search engine and one of the biggest Russian web portals. It is owned by the Rambler Media Group and Prof-Media since 2006. It was launched in 1996 by Stack Ltd, including Sergey Lysakov, Dmitry Kryukov, Vladimir Samoylov and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rostelecom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</guid>
      <description> Rostelecom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s leading long-distance telephony provider. Domestic long distance service provides about 50% of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue; and international long distance calls provide about 25%.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</guid>
      <description>Yandex N.V. is a Russian multinational corporation specializing in Internet-related products and services, including search and information services, eCommerce, transportation, navigation, mobile applications, and online advertising. Yandex provides over 70 services in total. Incorporated in the Netherlands, Yandex primarily serves audiences in Russia and the Commonwealth of Independent States. The company founders and most of the team members are located in Russia. The company has 18 commercial offices worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Alisa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-alisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-alisa/</guid>
      <description> Alice (Russian: Алиса (Alisa)) is a Russian intelligent personal assistant for Android, iOS and Windows operating systems developed by Yandex. Alice was officially introduced on 10 October 2017. Aside from common tasks, such as internet search or weather forecasts, it can also run applications and chit-chat. Alice is also the virtual assistant used for the Yandex Station smart speaker.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Browser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Browser (Яндекс браузер in Russian) is a freeware web browser developed by the Russian web search corporation Yandex that uses the Blink web browser engine and is based on the Chromium open source project. The browser checks webpage security with the Yandex security system and checks downloaded files with Kaspersky anti-virus. The browser also uses Opera Software&amp;rsquo;s Turbo technology to speed web browsing on slow connections.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Money</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</guid>
      <description> Yandex.Money is Russia’s largest electronic payment service according to a 2016 survey by TNS. It is an online payment service that works with two types of clients — individual users and merchants.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Music» is a music streaming service developed by Yandex. Users select musical compositions, albums, collections of musical tracks to stream to their device on demand and receive personalized recommendations. The service is also available as a mobile app with versions compatible with iOS, Android. Service is available in Russia, Belarus, Kyrgyzstan, Kazakhstan, Armenia, Israel. Paid subscription service is available in all the other countries of the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>