<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Russia on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/country/russia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Russia on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympics 2014 Sochi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2014-sochi/</guid>
      <description>The 2014 Winter Olympics, officially called the XXII Olympic Winter Games (French: Les XXIIes Jeux olympiques d&amp;rsquo;hiver) (Russian: XXII Олимпийские зимние игры, tr. XXII Olimpiyskiye zimniye igry) and commonly known as Sochi 2014, was an international winter multi-sport event that was held from 7 to 23 February 2014 in Sochi, Krasnodar Krai, Russia, with opening rounds in certain events held on the eve of the opening ceremony, 6 February 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aeroflot</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aeroflot/</guid>
      <description> Aeroflot – Russian Airlines is the flag carrier and largest airline of the Russian Federation. The carrier is an open joint stock company that operates domestic and international passenger and services, mainly from its hub at Sheremetyevo International Airport.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfa Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</guid>
      <description>Alfa Bank JSC, the corporate treasury of the Alfa Group, is one of the largest private commercial banks in Russia. It was founded by Russian businessman Mikhail Fridman, who is still the controlling owner today. It is headquartered in Moscow. It operates in seven countries, providing financial services to over 381,600 active corporate customers and 14.2 million retail clients. Alfa-Bank is particularly active in Russia and Ukraine, ranking among top 10 largest banks in terms of capital in both countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rambler</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rambler/</guid>
      <description> Rambler (Russian: Рамблер) is a Russian search engine and one of the biggest Russian web portals. It is owned by the Rambler Media Group and Prof-Media since 2006. It was launched in 1996 by Stack Ltd, including Sergey Lysakov, Dmitry Kryukov, Vladimir Samoylov and others.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rostelecom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rostelecom/</guid>
      <description> Rostelecom is Russia&amp;rsquo;s leading long-distance telephony provider. Domestic long distance service provides about 50% of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue; and international long distance calls provide about 25%.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex/</guid>
      <description>Yandex N.V. is a Russian multinational corporation specializing in Internet-related products and services, including search and information services, eCommerce, transportation, navigation, mobile applications, and online advertising. Yandex provides over 70 services in total. Incorporated in the Netherlands, Yandex primarily serves audiences in Russia and the Commonwealth of Independent States. The company founders and most of the team members are located in Russia. The company has 18 commercial offices worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Alisa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-alisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-alisa/</guid>
      <description> Alice (Russian: Алиса (Alisa)) is a Russian intelligent personal assistant for Android, iOS and Windows operating systems developed by Yandex. Alice was officially introduced on 10 October 2017. Aside from common tasks, such as internet search or weather forecasts, it can also run applications and chit-chat. Alice is also the virtual assistant used for the Yandex Station smart speaker.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Browser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-browser/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Browser (Яндекс браузер in Russian) is a freeware web browser developed by the Russian web search corporation Yandex that uses the Blink web browser engine and is based on the Chromium open source project. The browser checks webpage security with the Yandex security system and checks downloaded files with Kaspersky anti-virus. The browser also uses Opera Software&amp;rsquo;s Turbo technology to speed web browsing on slow connections.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Money</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</guid>
      <description> Yandex.Money is Russia’s largest electronic payment service according to a 2016 survey by TNS. It is an online payment service that works with two types of clients — individual users and merchants.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Music</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-music/</guid>
      <description> Yandex Music» is a music streaming service developed by Yandex. Users select musical compositions, albums, collections of musical tracks to stream to their device on demand and receive personalized recommendations. The service is also available as a mobile app with versions compatible with iOS, Android. Service is available in Russia, Belarus, Kyrgyzstan, Kazakhstan, Armenia, Israel. Paid subscription service is available in all the other countries of the world.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>