<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entertaiment on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/entertaiment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entertaiment on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/entertaiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</guid>
      <description> Animal Planet is an American pay television channel owned by Discovery, Inc. First established on October 1, 1996, the network is primarily devoted to series and documentaries about wild animals and domestic pets.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Ashe Stadium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</guid>
      <description> Arthur Ashe Stadium is a tennis stadium at Flushing Meadows-Corona Park in Queens, New York City. Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center, it is the main stadium of the US Open tennis tournament, and the largest tennis stadium in the world, with a capacity of 23,771.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>The National Aquarium - also known as National Aquarium in Baltimore and formerly known as Baltimore Aquarium - is a non-profit public aquarium located at 501 East Pratt Street on Pier 3 in the Inner Harbor area of downtown Baltimore, Maryland, in the United States. Constructed during a period of urban renewal in Baltimore, the aquarium opened on August 8, 1981. The aquarium has an annual attendance of 1.5 million visitors and is the largest tourism attraction in the State of Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cirque du Soleil</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil/</guid>
      <description> Cirque du Soleil (French: [sɪʁk dzy sɔ.lɛj], &amp;ldquo;Circus of the Sun&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Sun Circus&amp;rdquo;) is a Canadian (Quebecois) entertainment company and the largest theatrical producer in the world. Based in Montreal, Quebec, Canada, and located in the inner-city area of Saint-Michel, it was founded in Baie-Saint-Paul on 7 July 1984, by two former street performers, Guy Laliberté and Gilles Ste-Croix.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</guid>
      <description>Netflix, Inc. is an American media-services provider headquartered in Los Gatos, California, founded in 1997 by Reed Hastings and Marc Randolph in Scotts Valley, California. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its subscription-based streaming OTT service which offers online streaming of a library of films and television programs, including those produced in-house. As of April 2019, Netflix had over 148 million paid subscriptions worldwide, including 60 million in the United States, and over 154 million subscriptions total including free trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21st Century Fox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</guid>
      <description> Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc., doing business as 21st Century Fox (21CF), was an American multinational mass media corporation that was based in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was one of the two companies formed from the 2013 spin-off of the publishing assets of News Corporation, as founded by Rupert Murdoch in 1980.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</guid>
      <description> DC Comics, Inc. is an American comic book publisher. It is the publishing unit of DC Entertainment, a subsidiary of Warner Bros. since 1967. DC Comics is one of the largest and oldest American comic book companies, and produces material featuring numerous culturally iconic heroic characters including: Superman, Batman, Wonder Woman, The Flash, Green Lantern, Aquaman, Shazam, Martian Manhunter, Nightwing, Green Arrow, Hawkman, Cyborg and Supergirl.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</guid>
      <description>Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc. (formerly Warner Bros. Pictures, Inc.), commonly referred to as Warner Bros. and abbreviated as WB, is an American entertainment company headquartered in Burbank, California and a subsidiary of AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. Founded in 1923, it has operations in film, television and video games and is one of the &amp;ldquo;Big Five&amp;rdquo; major American film studios, as well as a member of the Motion Picture Association of America</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Company</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walt Disney Pictures</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures/</guid>
      <description>About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948  Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>