<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>entertaiment on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/industry/entertaiment/</link><description>Recent content in entertaiment on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/entertaiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sega//file/sega.svg</url><title>Sega Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sega</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sega/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sega/</guid><description turbo="true">Sega Corporation is a Japanese multinational video game developer and publisher headquartered in Shinagawa, Tokyo. Its international branches, Sega of America and Sega Europe, are respectively headquartered in Irvine, California, and London. Sega&amp;rsquo;s arcade division existed as Sega Interactive Co., Ltd. from 2015 to 2020 before it merged with Sega Games to create Sega Corporation with Sega Games as the surviving entity. Sega is a subsidiary of Sega Group Corporation, which is, in turn, a part of Sega Sammy Holdings.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony-pictures//file/sony-pictures.svg</url><title>Sony Pictures Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Sony Pictures</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/sony-pictures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony-pictures/</guid><description turbo="true">Sony Pictures Entertainment Inc. (Sony Pictures or SPE) is an American entertainment company that produces, acquires, and distributes filmed entertainment (theatrical motion pictures, television programs, and recorded videos) through multiple platforms. Through an intermediate holding company called Sony Film Holding Inc., it is operated as a subsidiary of Sony Entertainment Inc., which is itself a subsidiary of the Japanese multinational technology and media conglomerate Sony Corporation. Based at the former Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer lot in Culver City, California, it encompasses Sony&amp;rsquo;s motion picture, television production and distribution units.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/take-two//file/take-two.svg</url><title>Take-Two Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Take-Two</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/take-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/take-two/</guid><description turbo="true">Take-Two Interactive Software, Inc. is an American video game holding company based in New York City and founded by Ryan Brant in September 1993.
The company owns two major publishing labels, Rockstar Games and 2K, which operate internal game development studios. More recently, Take-Two created the Private Division label to support publishing from independent developers, and acquired the developer Social Point to establish itself in the mobile game market.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft//file/ubisoft.svg</url><title>Ubisoft Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Ubisoft</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubisoft/</guid><description turbo="true">Ubisoft Entertainment is a French video game company headquartered in Montreuil with several development studios across the world. It publishes games for several video game franchises, including Rayman, Raving Rabbids, Prince of Persia, Assassin&amp;rsquo;s Creed, Far Cry, Just Dance, and the Tom Clancy&amp;rsquo;s series. As of March 2018, Ubisoft is the fifth largest publicly traded game company in the Americas and Europe in terms of revenue and market capitalisation, after Activision Blizzard, Electronic Arts, Take-Two Interactive and CD Projekt.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/vh-1//file/vh-1.svg</url><title>VH-1 Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">VH-1</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/vh-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/vh-1/</guid><description turbo="true">VH1 (originally an initialism of Video Hits One) is an American basic cable television network based in New York City owned by ViacomCBS. It was created by Warner-Amex Satellite Entertainment, at the time a division of Warner Communications and the original owner of MTV, and launched on January 1, 1985, in the former space of Turner Broadcasting System&amp;rsquo;s short-lived Cable Music Channel.
The channel was originally conceived to build upon the success of sister channel MTV by playing music videos targeting a slightly older demographic than MTV by focusing on the lighter, softer side of popular music.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney-xd//file/disney-xd.svg</url><title>Disney XD Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Disney XD</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/disney-xd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/disney-xd/</guid><description turbo="true">Disney XD is an American pay television channel which is owned by the Walt Disney Television unit of The Walt Disney Company through Disney Channels Worldwide. Aimed primarily at children ages 6–15, its programming consists of original first-run television series, current and former original series and made-for-TV films from sister network Disney Channel, theatrically-released films, and acquired programs from other distributors, including Pokémon the Series: Sun &amp;amp; Moon and Beyblade Burst, along with a primetime block of programming involving competitive gaming.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamworks//file/dreamworks.svg</url><title>DreamWorks Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">DreamWorks</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamworks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dreamworks/</guid><description turbo="true">DreamWorks Animation LLC (also simply known as DreamWorks, and later rebranded as such since 2018) is an American animation studio that is a subsidiary of Universal Pictures, itself a subsidiary of NBCUniversal, which is owned by Comcast. It is based in Glendale, California, and produces animated feature films, television programs, and online virtual games. The studio has currently released a total of 38 feature films, beginning with Antz (1998); its most recent film was Trolls World Tour (2020).</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/electronic-arts//file/electronic-arts.svg</url><title>Electronic Arts Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Electronic Arts</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/electronic-arts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/electronic-arts/</guid><description turbo="true">Electronic Arts Inc. (EA) is an American video game company headquartered in Redwood City, California. It is the second-largest gaming company in the Americas and Europe by revenue and market capitalization after Activision Blizzard and ahead of Take-Two Interactive and Ubisoft as of March 2018.
Founded and incorporated on May 27, 1982, by Apple employee Trip Hawkins, the company was a pioneer of the early home computer games industry and was notable for promoting the designers and programmers responsible for its games.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games//file/epic-games.svg</url><title>Epic Games Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Epic Games</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/epic-games/</guid><description turbo="true">Epic Games, Inc. is an American video game and software developer and publisher based in Cary, North Carolina. The company was founded by Tim Sweeney as Potomac Computer Systems in 1991, originally located in his parents&amp;rsquo; house in Potomac, Maryland. Following his first commercial video game release, ZZT (1991), the company became Epic MegaGames, Inc. in early 1992 and brought on Mark Rein, who is the company&amp;rsquo;s vice president to date.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite//file/fortnite.svg</url><title>Fortnite Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Fortnite</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fortnite/</guid><description turbo="true">Fortnite is an online video game developed by Epic Games and released in 2017. It is available in three distinct game mode versions that otherwise share the same general gameplay and game engine: Fortnite: Save the World, a cooperative shooter-survival game for up to four players to fight off zombie-like creatures and defend objects with fortifications they can build; Fortnite Battle Royale, a free-to-play battle royale game where up to 100 players fight to be the last person standing; and Fortnite Creative, where players are given complete freedom to create worlds and battle arenas.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucasfilm//file/lucasfilm.svg</url><title>Lucasfilm Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Lucasfilm</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/lucasfilm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/lucasfilm/</guid><description turbo="true">Lucasfilm Ltd. LLC is an American film and television production company that is a subsidiary of The Walt Disney Studios, a division of The Walt Disney Company. The studio is best known for creating and producing the Star Wars and Indiana Jones franchises, as well as its leadership in developing special effects, sound and computer animation for films. Lucasfilm was founded by filmmaker George Lucas in 1971 in San Rafael, California; most of the company&amp;rsquo;s operations were moved to San Francisco in 2005.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/machine-zone//file/machine-zone.svg</url><title>Machine Zone Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Machine Zone</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/machine-zone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/machine-zone/</guid><description turbo="true">Machine Zone, Inc. (MZ) is a privately held technology company, founded in 2008 and based in Palo Alto, California. The company is best known for its widely advertised freemium mobile MMO strategy games Game of War: Fire Age and Mobile Strike, which have both simultaneously been ranked among the top ten highest-grossing mobile games.
Source About Machine Zone Ten years in and every day we’re finding new ways to break new ground.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-studios//file/marvel-studios.svg</url><title>Marvel Studios Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Marvel Studios</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-studios/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/marvel-studios/</guid><description turbo="true">Marvel Studios, LLC (originally known as Marvel Films from 1993 to 1996) is an American film and television studio that is a subsidiary of The Walt Disney Studios. Marvel Studios is known for the production of the Marvel Cinematic Universe films, based on characters that appear in Marvel Comics publications.
Marvel Studios has released 23 films since 2008 within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, from Iron Man (2008) to Spider-Man: Far From Home (2019).</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mpa//file/mpa.svg</url><title>MPA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MPA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mpa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mpa/</guid><description turbo="true">The Motion Picture Association (MPA) is an American trade association representing the five major film studios of the United States, as well as the video streaming service Netflix. Founded in 1922 as the Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America (MPPDA) and known as the Motion Picture Association of America (MPAA) from 1945 until September 2019, its original goal was to ensure the viability of the American film industry. In addition, the MPAA established guidelines for film content which resulted in the creation of the Production Code in 1930.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/mtv//file/mtv.svg</url><title>MTV Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">MTV</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/mtv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mtv/</guid><description turbo="true">MTV (originally an initialism of Music Television) is an American cable channel, launched on August 1, 1981. Based in New York City, it serves as the flagship property of the ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division of ViacomCBS, also headquartered in New York City.
MTV originally aired music videos as guided by television personalities known as &amp;ldquo;video jockeys&amp;rdquo; (VJs), but in the years since its inception, the network significantly toned down its focus on music in favor of original reality programming targeting teenagers and young adults.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr//file/nick-jr.svg</url><title>Nick Jr Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nick Jr</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nick-jr/</guid><description turbo="true">Nick Jr. is an American pay television channel run by Nickelodeon Group, a unit of the ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division of ViacomCBS, the channel&amp;rsquo;s ultimate owner headquartered in New York City. It launched on September 28, 2009 as a spin-off of Nickelodeon&amp;rsquo;s long-running preschool programming block of the same name, which had aired since 1988. The channel, which is aimed at children under 6, features a mix of originally-produced programming, and series previously and concurrently aired on the Nick Jr.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon//file/nickelodeon.svg</url><title>Nickelodeon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Nickelodeon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nickelodeon/</guid><description turbo="true">Nickelodeon (often shortened to Nick) is an American pay television channel which was first tested on December 1, 1977, before relaunching on April 1, 1979 as the first cable channel for children. It is owned by ViacomCBS through its domestic networks division and is based in New York City. The network&amp;rsquo;s programming is primarily aimed at children and adolescents aged 2–17, while some of its program blocks target a broader family audience.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount//file/paramount.svg</url><title>Paramount Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Paramount</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/paramount/</guid><description turbo="true">Paramount Pictures Corporation (also known simply as Paramount) is an American film studio and subsidiary of ViacomCBS. It is the fifth oldest film studio in the world, the second oldest film studio in the United States, and the sole member of the &amp;ldquo;Big Five&amp;rdquo; film studios still located in Los Angeles.
In 1916, film producer Adolph Zukor put 22 actors and actresses under contract and honored each with a star on the logo.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/playboy//file/playboy.svg</url><title>Playboy Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Playboy</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/playboy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/playboy/</guid><description turbo="true">Playboy is an American men&amp;rsquo;s lifestyle and entertainment magazine, formerly in print and currently online. It was founded in Chicago in 1953, by Hugh Hefner and his associates, and funded in part by a $1,000 loan from Hefner&amp;rsquo;s mother. Notable for its centerfolds of nude and semi-nude models (Playmates), Playboy played an important role in the sexual revolution and remains one of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known brands, having grown into Playboy Enterprises, Inc.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/pokemon//file/pokemon.svg</url><title>Pokemon Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Pokemon</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/pokemon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pokemon/</guid><description turbo="true">Pokémon (English: /ˈpoʊkɪˌmɒn, -ki-, -keɪ-/), also known as Pocket Monsters in Japan, is a Japanese media franchise managed by the Pokémon Company, a company founded and with shares divided between Nintendo, Game Freak, and Creatures. The franchise copyright and Japanese trademark is shared by all three companies, but Nintendo is the sole owner of the trademark in other countries. The franchise was created by Satoshi Tajiri in 1995, and is centered on fictional creatures called &amp;ldquo;Pokémon&amp;rdquo;, which humans, known as Pokémon Trainers, catch and train to battle each other for sport.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/riot-games//file/riot-games.svg</url><title>Riot Games Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Riot Games</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/riot-games/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/riot-games/</guid><description turbo="true">Riot Games, Inc. is an American video game developer, publisher, and esports tournament organizer based in West Los Angeles, California. The company was founded in September 2006 by University of Southern California roommates Brandon Beck and Marc Merrill, as they sought to create a company that continuously improves on an already released game, instead of commencing development on a new one. Riot Games was majority-acquired by Tencent in February 2011 and fully acquired in December 2015.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/rockstar//file/rockstar.svg</url><title>Rockstar Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Rockstar</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/rockstar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rockstar/</guid><description turbo="true">Rockstar Games, Inc. is an American video game publisher based in New York City. The company was established in December 1998 as a subsidiary of Take-Two Interactive, using the assets Take-Two had previously acquired from BMG Interactive. Founding members of the company were Sam and Dan Houser, Terry Donovan and Jamie King, who worked for Take-Two at the time, and of which the Houser brothers were previously executives at BMG Interactive.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/activision//file/activision.svg</url><title>Activision Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Activision</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/activision/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/activision/</guid><description turbo="true"> Activision Publishing, Inc. is an American video game publisher based in Santa Monica, California. It currently serves as the publishing business for its parent company, Activision Blizzard, and consists of several subsidiary studios. Activision is one of the largest third-party video game publishers in the world and was the top United States publisher in 2016.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc//file/bbc.svg</url><title>BBC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">BBC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</guid><description turbo="true">The British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) is a British public service broadcaster. Its headquarters are at Broadcasting House in Westminster, London. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest national broadcaster, and the largest broadcaster in the world by number of employees. It employs over 22,000 staff in total, more than 16,000 of whom are in public sector broadcasting. The total number of staff is 35,402 when part-time, flexible, and fixed-contract staff are included.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard//file/billboard.svg</url><title>Billboard Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Billboard</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard/</guid><description turbo="true">Billboard, stylized as billboard, is an American entertainment media brand owned by the Billboard-Hollywood Reporter Media Group, a division of Eldridge Industries. It publishes pieces involving news, video, opinion, reviews, events, and style, and is also known for its music charts, including the Hot 100 and Billboard 200, tracking the most popular songs and albums in different genres. It also hosts events, owns a publishing firm, and operates several TV shows.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-sky//file/blue-sky.svg</url><title>Blue Sky Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Blue Sky</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-sky/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-sky/</guid><description turbo="true">Blue Sky Studios, Inc. is an American computer animation film studio based in Greenwich, Connecticut. It is a subsidiary of 20th Century Fox Animation, a division of The Walt Disney Studios.
The studio was founded in 1987 by Chris Wedge, Michael Ferraro, Carl Ludwig, Alison Brown, David Brown, and Eugene Troubetzkoy after their employer MAGI, one of the visual effects studios behind Tron, shut down. Using its in-house rendering software, the studio had worked on visual effects for commercials and films before completely dedicating itself to animated film production.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo//file/bravo.svg</url><title>Bravo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Bravo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo/</guid><description turbo="true">Bravo is an American pay television network, launched on December 1, 1980. It is owned by NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast. The channel originally focused on programming related to fine arts and film. It currently broadcasts several reality television series targeted at 25–54-year-old women as well as the gay community, along with acquired and original dramas, and mainstream theatrically released feature films.
As of January 2016, approximately 89,824,000 American households (77.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network//file/cartoon-network.svg</url><title>Cartoon Network Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cartoon Network</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cartoon-network/</guid><description turbo="true">Cartoon Network is an American pay television channel owned by Warner Bros. Entertainment, a division of AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s WarnerMedia. The channel was launched on October 1, 1992, and primarily broadcasts animated television series, mostly children&amp;rsquo;s programming, ranging from action to animated comedy. It operates usually from 6:00 AM to 8:00 PM (ET/PT) and is targeted at children between ages 7 and 15. Its overnight daypart block Adult Swim is aimed at adults and is treated as a separate entity for promotional purposes and as a separate channel by Nielsen for ratings purposes.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/claro//file/claro.svg</url><title>Claro Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Claro</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/claro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/claro/</guid><description turbo="true"> Claro Americas is a Brazilian company part of América Móvil, a Mexican telecom group. Claro serves clients in Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, the Dominican Republic, Ecuador, El Salvador, Guatemala, Honduras, Nicaragua, Panama, Paraguay, Peru, Puerto Rico and Uruguay. The company&amp;rsquo;s name means &amp;ldquo;bright&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;clear&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo; in Portuguese and Spanish.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/comedy-central//file/comedy-central.svg</url><title>Comedy Central Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Comedy Central</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/comedy-central/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/comedy-central/</guid><description turbo="true"> Comedy Central is an American pay television channel owned by ViacomCBS through its ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks division&amp;rsquo;s Entertainment &amp;amp; Youth Group unit, based in Manhattan. The channel is geared for mature audiences and carries comedy programming in the form of both original, licensed, and syndicated series, stand-up comedy specials, and feature films.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros//file/warner-bros.svg</url><title>Warner Bros Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Warner Bros</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</guid><description turbo="true">New Logo and Identity for Warner Bros. by Pentagram Established in 1923, Warner Bros. is one of the most well-known entertainment companies with the creation, production, distribution, licensing, and marketing of content across feature films, television, home entertainment production, animation, comic books, video games, product and brand licensing, and broadcasting. Its library consists of more than 100,000 hours of programming that include over 8,600 feature films and 5,000 television programs.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet//file/animal-planet.svg</url><title>Animal Planet Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Animal Planet</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/animal-planet/</guid><description turbo="true"> Animal Planet is an American pay television channel owned by Discovery, Inc. First established on October 1, 1996, the network is primarily devoted to series and documentaries about wild animals and domestic pets.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium//file/arthur-ashe-stadium.svg</url><title>Arthur Ashe Stadium Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Arthur Ashe Stadium</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/arthur-ashe-stadium/</guid><description turbo="true"> Arthur Ashe Stadium is a tennis stadium at Flushing Meadows-Corona Park in Queens, New York City. Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center, it is the main stadium of the US Open tennis tournament, and the largest tennis stadium in the world, with a capacity of 23,771.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium//file/baltimore-aquarium.svg</url><title>Baltimore Aquarium Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Baltimore Aquarium</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</guid><description turbo="true">The National Aquarium - also known as National Aquarium in Baltimore and formerly known as Baltimore Aquarium - is a non-profit public aquarium located at 501 East Pratt Street on Pier 3 in the Inner Harbor area of downtown Baltimore, Maryland, in the United States. Constructed during a period of urban renewal in Baltimore, the aquarium opened on August 8, 1981. The aquarium has an annual attendance of 1.5 million visitors and is the largest tourism attraction in the State of Maryland.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil//file/cirque-du-soleil.svg</url><title>Cirque du Soleil Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Cirque du Soleil</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cirque-du-soleil/</guid><description turbo="true"> Cirque du Soleil (French: [sɪʁk dzy sɔ.lɛj], &amp;ldquo;Circus of the Sun&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Sun Circus&amp;rdquo;) is a Canadian (Quebecois) entertainment company and the largest theatrical producer in the world. Based in Montreal, Quebec, Canada, and located in the inner-city area of Saint-Michel, it was founded in Baie-Saint-Paul on 7 July 1984, by two former street performers, Guy Laliberté and Gilles Ste-Croix.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ng//file/ng.svg</url><title>NG Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">NG</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ng/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ng/</guid><description turbo="true">National Geographic (formerly the National Geographic Magazine and branded also as NAT GEO) is the official magazine of the National Geographic Society. It has been published continuously since its first issue in 1888, nine months after the Society itself was founded. It primarily contains articles about science, geography, history, and world culture. The magazine is known for its thick square-bound glossy format with a yellow rectangular border and its extensive use of dramatic photographs.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo//file/prague-zoo.svg</url><title>Prague Zoo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Prague Zoo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prague-zoo/</guid><description turbo="true">Prague Zoological Garden is a zoo in Prague, Czech Republic. It was opened in 1931 with the goal to &amp;ldquo;advance the study of zoology, protect wildlife, and educate the public&amp;rdquo; in the district of Troja in the north of Prague. In 2013, the zoo occupied 58 hectares (140 acres) with 50 hectares (120 acres) in use for exhibits, and housed around 5,000 animals from just 676 species, including 132 species listed as threatened.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac//file/ratpac.svg</url><title>RatPac Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">RatPac</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ratpac/</guid><description turbo="true"> RatPac Entertainment is an American motion picture production and financing company owned by producer-director Brett Ratner. RatPac was founded by Ratner and billionaire James Packer. RatPac is a partner in RatPac-Dune Entertainment with Dune Entertainment.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems//file/screen-gems.svg</url><title>Screen Gems Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Screen Gems</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/screen-gems/</guid><description turbo="true"> Screen Gems, Inc. is an American film production and distribution studio that is a division of Sony Pictures&amp;rsquo;s Motion Picture Group, a subsidiary of Japanese multinational conglomerate Sony.[1] It has served several different purposes for its parent companies over the decades since its incorporation. The label currently specializes in genre films, mainly horror.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime//file/showtime.svg</url><title>Showtime Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Showtime</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/showtime/</guid><description turbo="true"> Showtime Networks Inc. (SNI) is an American entertainment company that oversees the company&amp;rsquo;s premium cable television channels, including its flagship service Showtime. It is a subsidiary of media conglomerate CBS Corporation.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-aquarium//file/tennessee-aquarium.svg</url><title>Tennessee Aquarium Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Tennessee Aquarium</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-aquarium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tennessee-aquarium/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Tennessee Aquarium is a non-profit public aquarium located in Chattanooga, Tennessee, United States. It opened in 1992 on the banks of the Tennessee River in downtown Chattanooga, with a major expansion added in 2005. The Aquarium, which has been accredited by the Association of Zoos and Aquariums (AZA) since 1993, is home to more than 12,000 animals representing almost 800 species.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix//file/netflix.svg</url><title>Netflix Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Netflix</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/netflix/</guid><description turbo="true">Netflix, Inc. is an American media-services provider headquartered in Los Gatos, California, founded in 1997 by Reed Hastings and Marc Randolph in Scotts Valley, California. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its subscription-based streaming OTT service which offers online streaming of a library of films and television programs, including those produced in-house. As of April 2019, Netflix had over 148 million paid subscriptions worldwide, including 60 million in the United States, and over 154 million subscriptions total including free trials.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox//file/21st-century-fox.svg</url><title>21st Century Fox Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">21st Century Fox</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/21st-century-fox/</guid><description turbo="true"> Twenty-First Century Fox, Inc., doing business as 21st Century Fox (21CF), was an American multinational mass media corporation that was based in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was one of the two companies formed from the 2013 spin-off of the publishing assets of News Corporation, as founded by Rupert Murdoch in 1980.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc//file/dc.svg</url><title>DC Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">DC</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dc/</guid><description turbo="true"> DC Comics, Inc. is an American comic book publisher. It is the publishing unit of DC Entertainment, a subsidiary of Warner Bros. since 1967. DC Comics is one of the largest and oldest American comic book companies, and produces material featuring numerous culturally iconic heroic characters including: Superman, Batman, Wonder Woman, The Flash, Green Lantern, Aquaman, Shazam, Martian Manhunter, Nightwing, Green Arrow, Hawkman, Cyborg and Supergirl.
Source Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company//file/walt-disney-company.svg</url><title>Walt Disney Company Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Walt Disney Company</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-company/</guid><description turbo="true">About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948 Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures//file/walt-disney-pictures.svg</url><title>Walt Disney Pictures Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Walt Disney Pictures</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walt-disney-pictures/</guid><description turbo="true">About The Walt Disney Company 1937–1948 Disney was founded on October 16, 1923 – by brothers Walt Disney and Roy O. Disney – as the Disney Brothers Cartoon Studio, and established itself as a leader in the American animation industry before diversifying into live-action film production, television, and theme parks. The company also operated under the names The Walt Disney Studio and then Walt Disney Productions. Taking on its current name in 1986, it expanded its existing operations and also started divisions focused upon theater, radio, music, publishing, and online media.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content/></rss>