<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru"><channel><title>Sweden on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/country/sweden/</link><description>Recent content in Sweden on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/country/sweden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/scania//file/scania.svg</url><title>Scania Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Scania</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/scania/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/scania/</guid><description turbo="true">Scania is a major Swedish manufacturer of commercial vehicles – specifically heavy lorries and buses. It also manufactures diesel engines for heavy vehicles as well as marine and general industrial applications.
Scania was formed in 1911 through the merger of Södertälje-based Vabis and Malmö-based Maskinfabriks-aktiebolaget Scania. The company&amp;rsquo;s head office has been in Södertälje since 1912. Today, Scania has production facilities in Sweden, France, the Netherlands, India, Argentina, Brazil, Poland, Russia and Finland In addition, there are assembly plants in ten countries in Africa, Asia and Europe.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm//file/hm.svg</url><title>H&amp;M Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">H&amp;M</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hm/</guid><description turbo="true">Hennes &amp;amp; Mauritz AB is a Swedish multinational clothing-retail company known for its fast-fashion clothing for men, women, teenagers and children. H&amp;amp;M and its associated companies operate in 62 countries with over 4,500 stores and as of 2015 employed around 132,000 people. It is the second-largest global clothing Retail, just behind Spain-based Inditex (parent company of Zara). The company has a significant online presence, with online shopping available in 33 countries:</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea//file/ikea.svg</url><title>IKEA Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">IKEA</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</guid><description turbo="true">IKEA is a Swedish-founded multinational group that designs and sells ready-to-assemble furniture, kitchen appliances and home products, among other useful goods and occasionally home services. It has been the world&amp;rsquo;s largest furniture Retail since at least 2008. It was founded in Sweden in 1943 by 17-year-old carpenter Ingvar Kamprad, who was listed by Forbes in 2015 as one of the ten richest people in the world, worth more than $40 billion.</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify//file/spotify.svg</url><title>Spotify Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Spotify</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/spotify/</guid><description turbo="true"> Spotify Technology S.A. (/ˈspɒtɪfaɪ/) is a Swedish media-services provider founded in 2006. The company&amp;rsquo;s primary business is its audio streaming platform that provides DRM-protected music and podcasts from record labels and media companies. As a freemium service, basic features are free with advertisements or automatic music videos, while additional features, such as improved streaming quality, are offered via paid subscriptions.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content><item turbo="true"><turbo:content><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo//file/volvo.svg</url><title>Volvo Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Volvo</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/volvo/</guid><description turbo="true"> The Volvo Group (Swedish: Volvokoncernen; legally Aktiebolaget Volvo, shortened to AB Volvo) (stylized as VOLVO) is a Swedish multinational manufacturing company headquartered in Gothenburg. While its core activity is the production, distribution and sale of trucks, buses and construction equipment, Volvo also supplies marine and industrial drive systems and financial services. In 2016, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest manufacturer of heavy-duty trucks.
Source</description></turbo:content></item><turbo:content/></rss>