<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/year/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/skype/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/skype/</guid>
      <description>Skype (/skaɪp/) is a telecommunications application that specializes in providing video chat and voice calls between computers, tablets, mobile devices, the Xbox One console, and smartwatches over the Internet. Skype also provides instant messaging services. Users may transmit text, video, audio and images. Skype allows video conference calls.
 At the end of 2010, there were over 660 million worldwide users, with over 300 million estimated active each month as of August 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/android/</guid>
      <description> Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android is developed by a consortium of developers known as the Open Handset Alliance, with the main contributor and commercial marketer being Google.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DXT</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dxt/</guid>
      <description> DXC Technology is an American multinational corporation that provides B2B IT services.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macys</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/macys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/macys/</guid>
      <description>Macy&amp;rsquo;s (originally R. H. Macy &amp;amp; Co., stylized as macy*s) is an American department store chain founded in 1858 by Rowland Hussey Macy. It became a division of the Cincinnati-based Federated Department Stores in 1994 (later renamed as Macy&amp;rsquo;s, Inc. in 2007), as a Bloomingdale&amp;rsquo;s department store chain affiliate. As of 2015, Macy&amp;rsquo;s was the largest U.S. department store company by retail sales. As of February 2019, there were 584 full-line stores with the Macy&amp;rsquo;s nameplate in operation throughout the United States, Puerto Rico, and Guam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super 8</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/super-8/</guid>
      <description> With more than 2,800 hotels on four continents, the newly redesigned Super 8 offers affordable, innovative lodging on the open road. As your ultimate roadside companion, every location also offers free WiFi and a complimentary SuperStart Breakfast to get you recharged and refueled for the day ahead.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach First</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/teach-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/teach-first/</guid>
      <description> Teach First is a social enterprise registered as a charity which aims to address educational disadvantage in England and Wales. Teach First coordinates an employment-based teaching training programme whereby participants achieve Qualified Teacher Status through the participation in a two-year training programme that involves the completion of a PGDE along with wider leadership skills training and an optional master&amp;rsquo;s degree.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warner Bros</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/warner-bros/</guid>
      <description>New Logo and Identity for Warner Bros. by Pentagram  Established in 1923, Warner Bros. is one of the most well-known entertainment companies with the creation, production, distribution, licensing, and marketing of content across feature films, television, home entertainment production, animation, comic books, video games, product and brand licensing, and broadcasting. Its library consists of more than 100,000 hours of programming that include over 8,600 feature films and 5,000 television programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldmark</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/worldmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/worldmark/</guid>
      <description> WorldMark by Wyndham (formerly Trendwest) is the developer and marketer of WorldMark, The Club, a vacation ownership program and part of the Wyndham Worldwide Corporation. The original development partner of the Club was Trendwest International (TWI), a subsidiary of Jeld-Wenn Industries, a privately held door and window manufacturer.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yahoo/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! is an American web services provider headquartered in Sunnyvale, California, and owned by Verizon Media. The original Yahoo! company was founded by Jerry Yang and David Filo in January 1994 and was incorporated on March 2, 1995. Yahoo was one of the pioneers of the early Internet era in the 1990s.
 About new Yahoo! logo  With its new products, Yahoo will empower users to better sift out irrelevant parts of the digital world, giving them more control of what they see and when they see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC News is an operational business division of the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) responsible for the gathering and broadcasting of news and current affairs. The department is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest broadcast news organisation and generates about 120 hours of radio and television output each day, as well as online news coverage. The service maintains 50 foreign news bureaux with more than 250 correspondents around the world. Fran Unsworth has been Director of News and Current Affairs since January 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC World News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC World News is the BBC&amp;rsquo;s international news and current affairs television channel. It has the largest audience of any channel, with an estimated 121 million viewers weekly in 2016/2017, part of the estimated 372 million weekly audience of the BBC&amp;rsquo;s four main international news services. Launched on 11 March 1991 as BBC World Service Television outside Europe, its name was changed to BBC World on 16 January 1995 and to BBC World News on 21 April 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbc-news/</guid>
      <description>CBC News is the division of the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation responsible for the news gathering and production of news programs on the corporation&amp;rsquo;s English-language operations, namely CBC Television, CBC Radio, CBC News Network, and CBC.ca. Founded in 1941, CBC News is the largest news broadcaster in Canada and has local, regional and national broadcasts and stations. It frequently collaborates with its French-language counterpart, Radio-Canada Info, although the two are organizationally separate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RMA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rma/</guid>
      <description> Reproductive Medicine Associates of New York is dedicated to providing patients the highest quality care in a compassionate and supportive manner. Helping couples successfully achieve their family-building goals has been RMA of New York’s focus since 2001.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telegram</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/telegram/</guid>
      <description> Telegram is a cloud-based instant messaging and voice over IP service. Telegram client apps are available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any type.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Fire FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chicago-fire-fc/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Fire Football Club is an American professional soccer club based in Chicago, Illinois. The team competes in Major League Soccer (MLS) as a member of the league’s Eastern Conference, having moved to the conference in 2002. The franchise is named after the Great Chicago Fire of 1871, and was founded as the Chicago Fire Soccer Club on October 8, 1997, the event’s 126th anniversary. The team began play in 1998 as one of the league’s first expansion teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville SC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nashville-sc/</guid>
      <description> Nashville Soccer Club is an American professional soccer team based in Nashville, Tennessee. Founded in 2016, the team made its debut in the United Soccer League in 2018.
  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cvs/</guid>
      <description>CVS Pharmacy is a subsidiary of the American retail and health care company CVS Health, headquartered in Woonsocket, Rhode Island. It was also known as, and originally named, the Consumer Value Store and was founded in Lowell, Massachusetts, in 1963. The chain was owned by its original holding company Melville Corporation since its inception until its current parent company (CVS Health) was spun off into its own company in 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/linkedin/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn is an American business and employment-oriented service that operates via websites and mobile apps. Founded on December 28, 2002, and launched on May 5, 2003, it is mainly used for professional networking, including employers posting jobs and job seekers posting their CVs. As of 2015, most of the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue came from selling access to information about its members to recruiters and sales professionals. As of March 2019, LinkedIn had 610 million registered members in 200 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Hut</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pizza-hut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pizza-hut/</guid>
      <description>Pizza Hut is an American restaurant chain and international franchise which was founded in 1958 by Dan and Frank Carney. The company is known for its Italian-American cuisine menu, including pizza and pasta, as well as side dishes and desserts. Pizza Hut has 18,431 restaurants worldwide as of December 31, 2018, making it the world&amp;rsquo;s largest pizza chain in terms of locations. It is a subsidiary of Yum! Brands, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redhat</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/redhat/</guid>
      <description> Red Hat, Inc. is an American multinational software company providing open-source software products to the enterprise community. Founded in 1993, Red Hat has its corporate headquarters in Raleigh, North Carolina, with other offices worldwide.
  Source  Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aer Lungus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/aer-lungus/</guid>
      <description>Aer Lingus is the flag carrier airline of Ireland and the second-largest airline in the country after Ryanair. Founded by the Irish government, it was privatised between 2006 and 2015 and it is now a wholly owned subsidiary of International Airlines Group (IAG), the parent company of British Airways and Iberia. The airline&amp;rsquo;s head office is on the grounds of Dublin Airport in Cloghran, County Dublin, Ireland.
  Source Aer Lingus tasked Lippincott with creating a brand that would reflect the radically different airline it had become, yet preserve the emotional bond with Ireland that it has always had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunkin Donuts</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dunkin-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Dunkin&amp;rsquo; (formerly known as Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts from 1950 to 2019) is an American multinational coffee company and quick service restaurant. It was founded by William Rosenberg in Quincy, Massachusetts in 1950. The chain was acquired by Baskin-Robbins&amp;rsquo; holding company Allied Lyons in 1990; its acquisition of the Mister Donut chain and conversion to Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts facilitated the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth in North America that year. Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Donuts and Baskin-Robbins have been subsidiaries of Dunkin&amp;rsquo; Brands, headquartered in Canton, Massachusetts, since 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IKEA</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ikea/</guid>
      <description>IKEA is a Swedish-founded multinational group that designs and sells ready-to-assemble furniture, kitchen appliances and home products, among other useful goods and occasionally home services. It has been the world&amp;rsquo;s largest furniture Retail since at least 2008. It was founded in Sweden in 1943 by 17-year-old carpenter Ingvar Kamprad, who was listed by Forbes in 2015 as one of the ten richest people in the world, worth more than $40 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria, S.A. (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈbaŋko βilˈβao βiθˈkaʝa aɾxenˈtaɾja]), better known by its initialism BBVA, is a multinational Spanish banking group based in Madrid and Bilbao. It is one of the largest financial institutions in the world, and is present mainly in Spain, North America, South America and Turkey.
 The bank was founded as Banco de Bilbao, on May 28, 1857 in Bilbao, Biscay, where it has been headquartered since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/facebook/</guid>
      <description>New Facebook Logo  The company unveiled its new logo Tuesday, April 30, 2019. The new logo retains the distinctive “f” letter, but replaces the rounded square container with a circle. In addition, the new look moves the “f” to the center of the icon, rather than the right side like in the old version. The “Facebook” logotype that has the full name of the company is now relegated to use only for the company — but not its services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Firefox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mozilla-firefox/</guid>
      <description>New Firefor Logo  The “Firefox” you’ve always known as a browser is stretching to cover a family of products and services united by putting you and your privacy first. Firefox is a browser AND an encrypted service to send huge files. It’s an easy way to protect your passwords on every device AND an early warning if your email has been part of a data breach. Safe, private, eye-opening. That’s just the beginning of the new Firefox family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/toyota/</guid>
      <description>About the Toyota logo   The Toyota brand represents Toyota tenets of quality, reliability and durability. It also stands as a symbol to inspire people around the world to go to the places and do the things they’ve always dreamed of.
 The staging platform is how Toyota refer to the Toyota emblem when shown in the red surround. The staging platform allows the emblem to be anchored and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hsbc Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</guid>
      <description>About HSBC Bank  The HSBC brand is recognised worldwide. Hsbc Bank latest advertising illustrates Hsbc Bank role in helping people, businesses and communities to thrive.
 HSBC is one of the largest banking and financial services organisations in the world, with operations in 66 countries and territories. Hsbc Bank aim to be where the growth is, enabling businesses to thrive and economies to prosper, and, ultimately, helping people to fulfil their hopes and realise their ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calibra</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/calibra/</guid>
      <description>About Calibra  Calibra is from Facebook. Making it easy to use in your favorite apps. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency that will make money work better for all of us.
 Calibra was founded in 2019 with the mission of making money work for everyone. Calibra believe that all people, all over the world should have equal, easy and educated access to financial services. Calibra is designed for Libra, a new cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libra</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/libra/</guid>
      <description>About Libra  Libra is a new global cryptocurrency. Libra is built on a secure, scalable, and reliable blockchain and is designed to help bring people everywhere equal access to financial services. Libra is backed by a reserve of assets so that its value stays stable. Libra is reinventing money so it can be used in countries around the world. It can easily be sent to anyone and exchanged into local currencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fargo/</guid>
      <description>About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy Wells Fargo customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV Plus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv-plus/</guid>
      <description>About Apple TV+ (from apple.com)
Introducing Apple TV+, a new streaming service where the most creative minds in TV and film tell the kinds of stories only they can. Featuring original shows and movies across every genre, Apple TV+ is coming this fall. Exclusively on the Apple TV app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>