<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>B on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/b/</link>
    <description>Recent content in B on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/b/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Boss</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boss/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Boss AG, often styled as BOSS, is a German luxury fashion house headquartered in Metzingen. It was founded in 1924 by Hugo Boss and originally produced general purpose clothing. With the rise of the Nazi Party in the 1930s, Boss began to produce and sell Nazi uniforms. Boss would eventually supply the wartime German government with uniforms for organizations such as the Hitler Youth and Waffen-SS, resulting in a large boost in sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbie</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barbie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barbie/</guid>
      <description> Barbie is a fashion doll manufactured by the American toy company Mattel, Inc. and launched in March 1959. American businesswoman Ruth Handler is credited with the creation of the doll using a German doll called Bild Lilli as her inspiration.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona FC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barcelona-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barcelona-fc/</guid>
      <description> Futbol Club Barcelona (Catalan pronunciation: [fubˈbɔl ˈklub bəɾsəˈlonə] (About this soundlisten)), commonly referred to as Barcelona and colloquially known as Barça , is a Spanish professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc/</guid>
      <description>The British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) is a British public service broadcaster. Its headquarters are at Broadcasting House in Westminster, London. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest national broadcaster, and the largest broadcaster in the world by number of employees. It employs over 22,000 staff in total, more than 16,000 of whom are in public sector broadcasting. The total number of staff is 35,402 when part-time, flexible, and fixed-contract staff are included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berkshire Hathaway</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/berkshire-hathaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/berkshire-hathaway/</guid>
      <description>Berkshire Hathaway is an American multinational conglomerate holding company headquartered in Omaha, Nebraska, United States. The company wholly owns GEICO, Duracell, Dairy Queen, BNSF, Lubrizol, Fruit of the Loom, Helzberg Diamonds, Long &amp;amp; Foster, FlightSafety International, Pampered Chef, Forest River and NetJets, and also owns 38.6% of Pilot Flying J; 26.7% of the Kraft Heinz Company, and significant minority holdings in American Express (17.6%), Wells Fargo (9.9%), The Coca-Cola Company (9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bertelsmann Music Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bertelsmann-music-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bertelsmann-music-group/</guid>
      <description>Bertelsmann Music Group (BMG) was a division of German media company Bertelsmann before its completion of sale of the majority of its assets to Sony Corporation of America on 1 October 2008. Although it was established in 1987, the music company was formed as RCA/Ariola International in 1985 as a joint venture to combine the music label activities of RCA Corporation&amp;rsquo;s RCA Records division and Bertelsmann&amp;rsquo;s Ariola Records and its associated labels which include Arista Records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billboard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/billboard/</guid>
      <description>Billboard, stylized as billboard, is an American entertainment media brand owned by the Billboard-Hollywood Reporter Media Group, a division of Eldridge Industries. It publishes pieces involving news, video, opinion, reviews, events, and style, and is also known for its music charts, including the Hot 100 and Billboard 200, tracking the most popular songs and albums in different genres. It also hosts events, owns a publishing firm, and operates several TV shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bing</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bing/</guid>
      <description> Bing is a web search engine owned and operated by Microsoft. The service has its origins in Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s previous search engines: MSN Search, Windows Live Search and later Live Search. Bing provides a variety of search services, including web, video, image and map search products. It is developed using ASP.NET.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Sky</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-sky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-sky/</guid>
      <description>Blue Sky Studios, Inc. is an American computer animation film studio based in Greenwich, Connecticut. It is a subsidiary of 20th Century Fox Animation, a division of The Walt Disney Studios.
 The studio was founded in 1987 by Chris Wedge, Michael Ferraro, Carl Ludwig, Alison Brown, David Brown, and Eugene Troubetzkoy after their employer MAGI, one of the visual effects studios behind Tron, shut down. Using its in-house rendering software, the studio had worked on visual effects for commercials and films before completely dedicating itself to animated film production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmg/</guid>
      <description> BMG are an established medical practice with strong ties to St. Francis Hospital, California Pacific Medical Center, and UCSF Medical Center. BMG providers have completed their medical training at various prestigious universities. Bayspring has a long established reputation for being an excellent community medical practice that offers warm and personalized attention from a diverse group of medical providers.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boeing</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boeing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boeing/</guid>
      <description>The Boeing Company, commonly known as Boeing (/ˈboʊɪŋ/), is an American multinational corporation that designs, manufactures, and sells airplanes, rotorcraft, rockets, satellites, telecommunications equipment, and missiles worldwide. The company also provides leasing and product support services. Boeing is among the largest global aerospace manufacturers; it is the second-largest defense contractor in the world based on 2018 revenue, and is the largest exporter in the United States by dollar value. Boeing stock is included in the Dow Jones Industrial Average.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Booking</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/booking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/booking/</guid>
      <description> Booking.com is a travel metasearch engine for lodging reservations. It is owned and operated by and is the primary revenue source of United States-based Booking Holdings and is headquartered in Amsterdam.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-dynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-dynamics/</guid>
      <description> Boston Dynamics is an American engineering and robotics design company founded in 1992 as a spin-off from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Headquartered in Waltham, Massachusetts, Boston Dynamics is a wholly owned subsidiary of the Japanese conglomerate SoftBank Group.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bravo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bravo/</guid>
      <description>Bravo is an American pay television network, launched on December 1, 1980. It is owned by NBCUniversal, a subsidiary of Comcast. The channel originally focused on programming related to fine arts and film. It currently broadcasts several reality television series targeted at 25–54-year-old women as well as the gay community, along with acquired and original dramas, and mainstream theatrically released feature films.
 As of January 2016, approximately 89,824,000 American households (77.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridgestone</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bridgestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bridgestone/</guid>
      <description> Bridgestone Corporation is a Japanese multinational auto and truck parts manufacturer founded in 1931 by Shojiro Ishibashi (石橋正二郎, Ishibashi Shōjirō) in the city of Kurume, Fukuoka, Japan. The name Bridgestone comes from a calque translation and transposition of ishibashi, meaning &amp;ldquo;stone bridge&amp;rdquo; in Japanese.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightstar</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brightstar/</guid>
      <description>Brightstar Corp., an American privately held corporation founded in 1997, distributes mobile phones and other devices, serving more than 200 carriers, 40,000+ retailers, and 15,000+ enterprise customers in more than 100 countries. It provides specialized global wireless distribution and services, serving mobile device manufacturers, wireless operators and retailers. Brightstar offers value-added device and accessories distribution, supply chain, handset protection and insurance, buyback and trade-in and omnichannel retail, and mobile digital products within the wireless telecommunications industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcom</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/broadcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/broadcom/</guid>
      <description> Broadcom Inc. is an American designer, developer, manufacturer and global supplier of a wide range of semiconductor and infrastructure software products, Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio serves the data center, networking, software, broadband, wireless, and storage and industrial markets.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bugatti</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bugatti/</guid>
      <description> Automobiles Ettore Bugatti was a French car manufacturer of high-performance automobiles, founded in 1909 in the then-German city of Molsheim, Alsace by the Italian-born industrial designer Ettore Bugatti. The cars were known for their design beauty and for their many race victories. Famous Bugattis include the Type 35 Grand Prix cars, the Type 41 &amp;ldquo;Royale&amp;rdquo;, the Type 57 &amp;ldquo;Atlantic&amp;rdquo; and the Type 55 sports car.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bamboo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bamboo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bamboo/</guid>
      <description> Bamboo Server is the choice of professional teams for continuous integration, deployment, and delivery
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baymont</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baymont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baymont/</guid>
      <description> Baymont Inn &amp;amp; Suites is a hotel franchise owned by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and based in the United States. As of December 31, 2018, it has 513 properties with 40,541 rooms.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beats</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beats/</guid>
      <description> Beats Electronics LLC (also known as Beats by Dr. Dre, or simply Beats by Dre) is a subsidiary of Apple Inc. that produces audio products. Headquartered in Culver City, California, the company was founded by music producer and rapper Dr. Dre and Interscope Records co-founder Jimmy Iovine.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Western</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-western/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-western/</guid>
      <description> Best Western International, Inc. owns the Best Western Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts brand, which it licenses to over 4,500 hotels worldwide. The franchise, with its corporate headquarters in Phoenix, Arizona, includes more than 2,000 hotels in North America. The brand was founded by M.K. Guertin in 1946. As of May 2019, David Kong is the president and CEO of Best Western and Dorothy Dowling is the chief marketing officer.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Binance</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/binance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/binance/</guid>
      <description> Binance is a global cryptocurrency exchange that provides a platform for trading more than 100 cryptocurrencies. Since early 2018, Binance is considered as the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world in terms of trading volume.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitbucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitbucket/</guid>
      <description> Bitbucket is more than just Git code management. Bitbucket gives teams one place to plan projects, collaborate on code, test, and deploy.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin (₿) is a cryptocurrency. It is a decentralized digital currency without a central bank or single administrator that can be sent from user to user on the peer-to-peer bitcoin network without the need for intermediaries.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Cash</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bitcoin-cash/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin Cash is a cryptocurrency that is fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash is a spin-off or altcoin that was created in 2017. In 2018 Bitcoin Cash subsequently split into two cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin Cash, and Bitcoin SV. Bitcoin Cash is sometimes also referred to as Bcash.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackberry</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/blackberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blackberry/</guid>
      <description>BlackBerry Limited is a Canadian multinational company specialising in enterprise software and the Internet of things. Originally known as Research In Motion (RIM), it is best known to the general public as the former developer of the BlackBerry brand of smartphones, and tablets. It transitioned to an enterprise software and services company under CEO John S. Chen. Its products are used worldwide by various businesses, car makers, and government agencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Apron</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/blue-apron/</guid>
      <description> Blue Apron Inc. is an American ingredient-and-recipe meal kit service. It exclusively operates in the United States. The weekly boxes contain ingredients and also include suggested recipes that must be cooked by hand by the customer using the pre-ordered ingredients.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bose</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bose/</guid>
      <description> Bose Corporation is a manufacturing company which predominantly sells audio equipment. The company was established by Amar Bose in 1964 and is based in Framingham, Massachusetts. Bose is best known for its home audio systems and speakers, noise-cancelling headphones, professional audio products and automobile sound systems. Bose has a reputation for being particularly protective of its patents, trademarks, and brands.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/eos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/eos/</guid>
      <description> EOS.IO is a blockchain protocol powered by the native cryptocurrency EOS. The smart contract platform claims to eliminate transaction fees and also conduct millions of transactions per second.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Aquarium</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>The National Aquarium - also known as National Aquarium in Baltimore and formerly known as Baltimore Aquarium - is a non-profit public aquarium located at 501 East Pratt Street on Pier 3 in the Inner Harbor area of downtown Baltimore, Maryland, in the United States. Constructed during a period of urban renewal in Baltimore, the aquarium opened on August 8, 1981. The aquarium has an annual attendance of 1.5 million visitors and is the largest tourism attraction in the State of Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BASF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/basf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/basf/</guid>
      <description>BASF SE is a German chemical company and the largest chemical producer in the world. The BASF Group comprises subsidiaries and joint ventures in more than 80 countries and operates six integrated production sites and 390 other production sites in Europe, Asia, Australia, the Americas and Africa. Its headquarters is located in Ludwigshafen, Germany. BASF has customers in over 190 countries and supplies products to a wide variety of industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bayer/</guid>
      <description>Bayer AG is a German multinational pharmaceutical and life sciences company and one of the largest pharmaceutical companies in the world. Headquartered in Leverkusen, where its illuminated corporate logo, the Bayer cross, is a landmark, Bayer&amp;rsquo;s areas of business include human and veterinary pharmaceuticals; consumer healthcare products; agricultural chemicals, seeds and biotechnology products. The company is a component of the Euro Stoxx 50 stock market index. Werner Baumann has been CEO since 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC News is an operational business division of the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) responsible for the gathering and broadcasting of news and current affairs. The department is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest broadcast news organisation and generates about 120 hours of radio and television output each day, as well as online news coverage. The service maintains 50 foreign news bureaux with more than 250 correspondents around the world. Fran Unsworth has been Director of News and Current Affairs since January 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC World News</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbc-world-news/</guid>
      <description>BBC World News is the BBC&amp;rsquo;s international news and current affairs television channel. It has the largest audience of any channel, with an estimated 121 million viewers weekly in 2016/2017, part of the estimated 372 million weekly audience of the BBC&amp;rsquo;s four main international news services. Launched on 11 March 1991 as BBC World Service Television outside Europe, its name was changed to BBC World on 16 January 1995 and to BBC World News on 21 April 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beko</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beko/</guid>
      <description> Beko /bɛkoʊ/ (sometimes stylized as beko) is a Turkish domestic appliance and consumer electronics brand of Arçelik A.Ş. controlled by Koç Holding.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beme</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/beme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/beme/</guid>
      <description>Beme Inc. (/ˈbiːm/), stylized as beme, was a multimedia company founded by Matt Hackett and Casey Neistat, a vlogger and short film maker on YouTube. Beme Inc. was the creator of the mobile app, Beme. On November 28, 2016, CNN announced that it would acquire Beme. CNN intended to invest in the company and create a new brand focused on a young audience. The Beme app was officially shut down on January 31, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bemis Company</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bemis-company/</guid>
      <description> Bemis Company, Inc. is a global manufacturer of flexible packaging products (ranging from self-venting cook-in-bag packaging and retort packaging for shelf-stable products, to vacuum packaging for meat products and puncture-resistant, sterile medical packaging) and pressure-sensitive materials. Bemis is headquartered in Neenah, Wisconsin in the United States. Its divisions are located in 12 countries and its films for packaging products and adhesive materials are distributed worldwide.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bjs/</guid>
      <description> BJ&amp;rsquo;s Wholesale Club Holdings, Inc., commonly referred as BJ&amp;rsquo;s, is an American membership-only warehouse club chain operating on the East Coast of the United States and the state of Ohio.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bloomberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bloomberg/</guid>
      <description> Bloomberg L.P. is a privately held financial, software, data, and media company headquartered in Midtown Manhattan, New York City. It was founded by Michael Bloomberg in 1981, with the help of Thomas Secunda, Duncan MacMillan, Charles Zegar, and a 30% ownership investment by Merrill Lynch.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BP</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bp/</guid>
      <description>BP plc (formerly The British Petroleum Company plc and BP Amoco plc) is a British multinational oil and gas company headquartered in London, United Kingdom. It is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s seven oil and gas &amp;ldquo;supermajors&amp;rdquo;, whose performance in 2012 made it the world&amp;rsquo;s sixth-largest oil and gas company, the sixth-largest energy company by market capitalization and the company with the world&amp;rsquo;s 12th-largest revenue (turnover). It is a vertically integrated company operating in all areas of the oil and gas industry, including exploration and production, refining, distribution and marketing, petrochemicals, power generation and trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Council</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-council/</guid>
      <description> The British Council is a British organisation specialising in international cultural and educational opportunities. It works in over 100 countries: promoting a wider knowledge of the United Kingdom and the English language; encouraging cultural, scientific, technological and educational co-operation with the United Kingdom.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brown/</guid>
      <description> Brown University is a private Ivy League research university in Providence, Rhode Island. Founded in 1764 as the College in the English Colony of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, it is the seventh-oldest institution of higher education in the United States and one of the nine colonial colleges chartered before the American Revolution.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BU</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bu/</guid>
      <description> Boston University (commonly referred to as BU) is a private research university in Boston, Massachusetts. The university is nonsectarian, but has been historically affiliated with the United Methodist Church.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bellator</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bellator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bellator/</guid>
      <description>Bellator MMA is an American mixed martial arts promotion based in Santa Monica, California that is owned and operated as a subsidiary of Viacom. It is one of the largest MMA promotions in the world and features many of the upper echelon athletes in combat sports. Its first event was held in 2009, with 222 &amp;ldquo;numbered&amp;rdquo; events held as of June 2019. The word Bellator is Latin for &amp;ldquo;warrior&amp;rdquo;. The company was previously known as Bellator Fighting Championships</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Bruins</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-bruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-bruins/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Bruins are a professional ice hockey team based in Boston. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team has been in existence since 1924, and is the league&amp;rsquo;s third-oldest team overall and the oldest in the United States. It is also an Original Six franchise, along with the Chicago Blackhawks, Detroit Red Wings, Montreal Canadiens, New York Rangers and Toronto Maple Leafs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Celtics</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-celtics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-celtics/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Celtics are an American professional basketball team based in Boston, Massachusetts. The Celtics compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league&amp;rsquo;s Eastern Conference Atlantic Division. Founded in 1946 as one of the league&amp;rsquo;s original eight teams, the team play their home games at TD Garden, which they share with the National Hockey League (NHL)&amp;rsquo;s Boston Bruins. The Celtics are one of the most successful teams in NBA history; the franchise has won the most championships in the NBA with 17, accounting for 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braun</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/braun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/braun/</guid>
      <description>Braun GmbH is a German consumer products company based in Kronberg. From 1984 until 2007, Braun was a wholly owned subsidiary of The Gillette Company, which had purchased a controlling interest in the company in 1967. Braun is now a wholly owned subsidiary of Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, which acquired Gillette in 2005. On 16 April 2012, De&amp;rsquo;Longhi bought perpetual rights to manufacture Braun branded products from Procter &amp;amp; Gamble in the small appliance segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Nets</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brooklyn-nets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brooklyn-nets/</guid>
      <description>The Brooklyn Nets are an American professional basketball team based in the New York City borough of Brooklyn. The Nets compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference. The team plays its home games at Barclays Center. They are one of two NBA teams located in New York City; the other is the New York Knicks. The team was established in 1967 as a charter franchise of the NBA&amp;rsquo;s rival league, the American Basketball Association (ABA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sabres</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-sabres/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-sabres/</guid>
      <description>The Buffalo Sabres are a professional ice hockey team based in Buffalo, New York. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference of the National Hockey League (NHL). The team was established in 1970, along with the Vancouver Canucks, when the league expanded to 14 teams. They have played at KeyBank Center since 1996. Prior to that, the Buffalo Sabres played at the Buffalo Memorial Auditorium from the start of the franchise in 1970.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Orioles</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-orioles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-orioles/</guid>
      <description>The Baltimore Orioles are an American professional baseball team based in Baltimore, Maryland. As one of the American League&amp;rsquo;s eight charter teams in 1901, this particular franchise spent its first year as a major league club in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, as the Milwaukee Brewers (not related to the second current Brewers franchise there) before moving to St. Louis, Missouri, to become the St. Louis Browns. After 52 often-beleaguered years in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Ravens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-ravens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/baltimore-ravens/</guid>
      <description> The Baltimore Ravens are a professional American football team based in Baltimore, Maryland. The Ravens compete in the National Football League (NFL) as a member club of the American Football Conference (AFC) North division. The team plays its home games at M&amp;amp;T Bank Stadium and is headquartered in Owings Mills.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BHF</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bhf/</guid>
      <description> The British Heart Foundation (BHF) is a charity organisation in the United Kingdom. It funds research to beat heartbreak from heart and circulatory diseases and their risk factors.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boots UK</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boots-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boots-uk/</guid>
      <description> Boots UK Ltd., trading as Boots, is a health and beauty Retail and pharmacy chain in the United Kingdom and other territories including Ireland and Thailand
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Red Sox</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-red-sox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-red-sox/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Red Sox are an American professional baseball team based in Boston, Massachusetts. The Red Sox compete in Major League Baseball (MLB) as a member club of the American League (AL) East division. The Red Sox have won nine World Series championships, tied for the third-most of any MLB team, and they have played in 13. Their most recent appearance and win was in 2018. In addition, they won the 1904 American League pennant, but were not able to defend their 1903 World Series championship when the New York Giants refused to participate in the 1904 World Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Bills</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buffalo-bills/</guid>
      <description>The Buffalo Bills are a professional American football team based in the Buffalo–Niagara Falls metropolitan area. The Bills compete in the National Football League (NFL), as a member club of the league&amp;rsquo;s American Football Conference (AFC) East division. The team plays their home games at New Era Field in Orchard Park, New York. The Bills are the only NFL team that plays its home games in the state of New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burberry</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/burberry/</guid>
      <description> Burberry Group PLC is a British luxury fashion house headquartered in London, England. Its main fashion house focuses on and distributes trench coats (for which it is most famous), ready-to-wear outerwear, fashion accessories, fragrances, sunglasses, and cosmetics.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/brother/</guid>
      <description> Brother Industries, Ltd. is a Japanese multinational electronics and electrical equipment company headquartered in Nagoya, Japan. Its products include printers, multifunction printers, desktop computers, industrial sewing machines, large machine tools, label printers, typewriters, fax machines, and other computer-related electronics. Brother distributes its products both under its own name and under OEM agreements with other companies.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger King</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/burger-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/burger-king/</guid>
      <description> Burger King (BK) is an American global chain of hamburger fast food restaurants. Headquartered in the unincorporated area of Miami-Dade County, Florida, the company was founded in 1953 as Insta-Burger King, a Jacksonville, Florida–based restaurant chain. After Insta-Burger King ran into financial difficulties in 1954, its two Miami-based franchisees David Edgerton and James McLamore purchased the company and renamed it &amp;ldquo;Burger King&amp;rdquo;.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bain Capital</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</guid>
      <description> Bain Capital is a private investment firm based in Boston, Massachusetts. It specializes in private equity, venture capital, credit, public equity, impact investing, life sciences and real estate. Bain Capital invests across a range of industry sectors and geographic regions. As of 2018, the firm managed more than $105 billion of investor capital.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bentley</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bentley/</guid>
      <description> Bentley Motors Limited is a British manufacturer and marketer of luxury cars and SUVs—and a subsidiary of the Volkswagen Group since 1998.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-buy/</guid>
      <description> Best Buy Co., Inc. is an American multinational consumer electronics Retail headquartered in Richfield, Minnesota. It was originally founded by Richard M. Schulze and James Wheeler in 1966 as an audio specialty store called Sound of Music. In 1983, it was re-branded under its current name with an emphasis placed on consumer electronics.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMW</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</guid>
      <description> BMW AG (German originally an initialism for Bayerische Motoren Werke in German, or Bavarian Motor Works in English) is a German multinational company which currently produces automobiles and motorcycles, and also produced aircraft engines until 1945.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Airways</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-airways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/british-airways/</guid>
      <description>British Airways (BA) is the flag carrier airline of the United Kingdom, headquartered at Waterside, Harmondsworth. It is the second largest airline in the United Kingdom, based on fleet size and passengers carried, behind easyJet. The airline is based in Waterside near its main hub at London Heathrow Airport. In January 2011 BA merged with Iberia, creating the International Airlines Group (IAG), a holding company registered in Madrid, Spain. IAG is the world&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline group in terms of annual revenue and the second-largest in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budweiser</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/budweiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/budweiser/</guid>
      <description>Budweiser is an American-style pale lager produced by Anheuser-Busch, currently part of the transnational corporation Anheuser-Busch InBev and produced in various breweries around the world. There is an unrelated lager also called Budweiser, originating centuries ago in Budweis, Bohemia and made by Budweiser Budvar Brewery of České Budějovice, Czech Republic; this has given rise to a trademark dispute preventing Anheuser-Busch from using the &amp;ldquo;Budweiser&amp;rdquo; name in some regions, leading to the exclusive use of &amp;ldquo;Bud&amp;rdquo; in those markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buick</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/buick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/buick/</guid>
      <description>Buick is a division of the American automobile manufacturer General Motors (GM). It was among the first American marques of automobiles, and was the company that established General Motors in 1908. Before the establishment of General Motors, GM founder William C. Durant had served as Buick&amp;rsquo;s general manager and major investor. Buick was the first production automobile maker in the world to equip its cars with overhead valve engines, which it did in 1904.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria, S.A. (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈbaŋko βilˈβao βiθˈkaʝa aɾxenˈtaɾja]), better known by its initialism BBVA, is a multinational Spanish banking group based in Madrid and Bilbao. It is one of the largest financial institutions in the world, and is present mainly in Spain, North America, South America and Turkey.
 The bank was founded as Banco de Bilbao, on May 28, 1857 in Bilbao, Biscay, where it has been headquartered since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Compass</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-compass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-compass/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Compass BBVA Compass Bancshares, Inc. (formerly Compass Bancshares) is a bank holding company headquartered in Birmingham, Alabama. It has been a subsidiary of the Spanish multinational Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria since 2007 and operates chiefly in Alabama, Arizona, California, Colorado, Florida, New Mexico, and Texas.
The company is the 30th largest bank in the United States.
BBVA Compass is an official sponsor of the NBA and holds naming rights to BBVA Compass Stadium, a soccer venue in Houston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Magazine</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine/</guid>
      <description>About Boston Magazine Boston is a magazine concerning life in the Greater Boston area and has been in publication since the 1960s.
 Sophisticated, intellectual, and full of charm, Boston is a world center of higher education, medicine, finance, and biotechnology, with some of the nation’s leading cultural institutions, best restaurants, trendiest shopping, top universities, and smartest people. Then there’s the other Boston: a city of power struggles, politics, expensive real estate, and cutting-edge music and arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Top Docs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-top-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-top-docs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Doctors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBB</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbb/</guid>
      <description> The Better Business Bureau, founded in 1912, is an organization focused on advancing marketplace trust, consisting of 106 independently incorporated local BBB organizations in the United States and Canada, coordinated under the Council of Better Business Bureaus in Arlington, Virginia.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barclays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:42:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</guid>
      <description>History of the Bank of America logo (from Bank of America press release)
Bank of America today announced a new brand positioning focused on the question, “What would you like the power to do?” The positioning reflects the impact clients and communities can have when they have the power to achieve their goals, and the company’s role as a partner invested in their success. […]
The Flagscape logo is also getting its first update since being introduced in 1998, reflecting a more modern brand that delivers both cutting-edge technology and high-touch solutions for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>