<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>B on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/a-z/b/</link>
    <description>Recent content in B on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/a-z/b/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BMW</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bmw/</guid>
      <description> BMW AG (German originally an initialism for Bayerische Motoren Werke in German, or Bavarian Motor Works in English) is a German multinational company which currently produces automobiles and motorcycles, and also produced aircraft engines until 1945.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria, S.A. (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈbaŋko βilˈβao βiθˈkaʝa aɾxenˈtaɾja]), better known by its initialism BBVA, is a multinational Spanish banking group based in Madrid and Bilbao. It is one of the largest financial institutions in the world, and is present mainly in Spain, North America, South America and Turkey.
 The bank was founded as Banco de Bilbao, on May 28, 1857 in Bilbao, Biscay, where it has been headquartered since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Compass</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-compass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-compass/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Compass BBVA Compass Bancshares, Inc. (formerly Compass Bancshares) is a bank holding company headquartered in Birmingham, Alabama. It has been a subsidiary of the Spanish multinational Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria since 2007 and operates chiefly in Alabama, Arizona, California, Colorado, Florida, New Mexico, and Texas.
The company is the 30th largest bank in the United States.
BBVA Compass is an official sponsor of the NBA and holds naming rights to BBVA Compass Stadium, a soccer venue in Houston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Magazine</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-magazine/</guid>
      <description>About Boston Magazine Boston is a magazine concerning life in the Greater Boston area and has been in publication since the 1960s.
 Sophisticated, intellectual, and full of charm, Boston is a world center of higher education, medicine, finance, and biotechnology, with some of the nation’s leading cultural institutions, best restaurants, trendiest shopping, top universities, and smartest people. Then there’s the other Boston: a city of power struggles, politics, expensive real estate, and cutting-edge music and arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Top Docs</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-top-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/boston-top-docs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Doctors</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/best-doctors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBB</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbb/</guid>
      <description> The Better Business Bureau, founded in 1912, is an organization focused on advancing marketplace trust, consisting of 106 independently incorporated local BBB organizations in the United States and Canada, coordinated under the Council of Better Business Bureaus in Arlington, Virginia.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barclays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:42:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</guid>
      <description>History of the Bank of America logo (from Bank of America press release)
Bank of America today announced a new brand positioning focused on the question, “What would you like the power to do?” The positioning reflects the impact clients and communities can have when they have the power to achieve their goals, and the company’s role as a partner invested in their success. […]
The Flagscape logo is also getting its first update since being introduced in 1998, reflecting a more modern brand that delivers both cutting-edge technology and high-touch solutions for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>