<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>electronics on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/electronics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in electronics on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/electronics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/canon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/canon/</guid>
      <description> Canon Inc. (キヤノン株式会社 Kiyanon Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese multinational corporation specializing in the manufacture of imaging and optical products, including cameras, camcorders, photocopiers, steppers, computer printers and medical equipment. It&amp;rsquo;s headquartered in Ōta, Tokyo, Japan.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fujitsu</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujitsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fujitsu/</guid>
      <description> Fujitsu Ltd. is a Japanese multinational information technology equipment and services company headquartered in Tokyo, Japan. In 2015, it was the world&amp;rsquo;s fourth-largest IT services provider measured by IT services revenue (after IBM, HP and Accenture). Fortune named Fujitsu as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most admired companies and a Global 500 company.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikon</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nikon/</guid>
      <description> Nikon Corporation is a Japanese multinational corporation headquartered in Tokyo, Japan, specializing in optics and imaging products.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nintendo/</guid>
      <description> Nintendo Co., Ltd. is a Japanese multinational consumer electronics and video game company headquartered in Kyoto. Nintendo is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest video game companies by market capitalization, creating some of the best-known and top-selling video game franchises, such as Mario, The Legend of Zelda, and Pokémon.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympus/</guid>
      <description> Olympus Corporation (オリンパス株式会社 Orinpasu Kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese manufacturer of optics and reprography products. Olympus was established on 12 October 1919, initially specializing in microscopes and thermometers. Olympus holds roughly a 70-percent share of the global endoscope market, estimated to be worth approximately US\$2.5 billion. Its global headquarters are located in Shinjuku, Tokyo, Japan.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panasonic</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/panasonic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/panasonic/</guid>
      <description> Panasonic Corporation is a Japanese multinational electronics corporation headquartered in Kadoma, Osaka, Japan.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentax</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pentax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pentax/</guid>
      <description> Pentax (ペンタックス Pentakkusu) is a brand name used primarily by Japanese multinational imaging and electronics company Ricoh for cameras, sport optics (including binoculars and rifle scopes), and CCTV optics. The brand was also used by Hoya Corporation for medical products &amp;amp; services, TI Asahi for surveying instruments, and Seiko Optical Products for certain optical lenses.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pioneer</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/pioneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/pioneer/</guid>
      <description> Pioneer Corporation (パイオニア株式会社 Paionia Kabushiki-kaisha) commonly referred to as Pioneer, is a Japanese multinational corporation based in Tokyo, Japan, that specializes in digital entertainment products. The company was founded by Nozomu Matsumoto in 1938 in Tokyo as a radio and speaker repair shop, and its current president is Susumu Kotani.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SONY</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sony/</guid>
      <description>Sony Corporation is a Japanese multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Kōnan, Minato, Tokyo. Its diversified business includes consumer and professional electronics, gaming, entertainment and financial services. The company owns the largest music entertainment business in the world the largest video game console business and one of the largest video game publishing businesses, and is one of the leading manufacturers of electronic products for the consumer and professional markets, and a leading player in the film and television entertainment industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanyo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/sanyo/</guid>
      <description> Sanyo Electric Co., Ltd. (三洋電機株式会社 San&amp;rsquo;yō Denki Kabushiki-gaisha) (stylized as SANYO) was a Japanese major electronics company and formerly a member of the Fortune Global 500 whose headquarters was located in Moriguchi, Osaka prefecture, Japan. Sanyo had over 230 subsidiaries and affiliates. Sanyo was founded by Toshio Iue.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seiko</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/seiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/seiko/</guid>
      <description> Seiko Holdings Corporation is a Japanese holding company that has subsidiaries which manufactures and sells watches, clocks, electronic devices, semiconductors, jewelries, and optical products.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Fire</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/kindle-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:04:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/kindle-fire/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ibm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Echo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-echo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:13:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amazon-echo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple/</guid>
      <description>History of Apple logo (from RobJanoff.com)
At the time of his initial meeting with Steve Jobs in early 1977, Apple Computer was still very much in its infancy, having been incorporated for less than a year. Apple’s offices were in a local strip mall, and consisted of just the three partners – Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Mike Markkula.
The initial identity development was to coincide with the introduction of the brand’s first personal computer, the Apple II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-tv/</guid>
      <description>History of Apple logo (from RobJanoff.com)
At the time of his initial meeting with Steve Jobs in early 1977, Apple Computer was still very much in its infancy, having been incorporated for less than a year. Apple’s offices were in a local strip mall, and consisted of just the three partners – Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Mike Markkula.
The initial identity development was to coincide with the introduction of the brand’s first personal computer, the Apple II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Watch</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/apple-watch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>