<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru" version="2.0"><channel><title>2008 on Logotyp.us</title><link>https://logotyp.us/year/2008/</link><description>Recent content in 2008 on Logotyp.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0019</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/year/2008/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart//file/walmart.svg</url><title>Walmart Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Walmart</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0019</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/walmart/</guid><description turbo="true">Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets, discount department stores, and grocery stores.
Source The Walmart History Walmart as Walmart know it today evolved from Sam Walton’s goals for great value and great customer service. “Mr. Sam,” as he was known, believed in leadership through service. This belief that true leadership depends on willing service was the principle on which Walmart was built, and drove the decisions the company has made for the past 50 years.</description></item><item turbo="true"><image turbo="true"><url>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing//file/olympics-2008-beijing.svg</url><title>Olympics 2008 Beijing Logo</title><link>https://www.w3schools.com</link></image><title turbo="true">Olympics 2008 Beijing</title><link turbo="true">https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:55 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/olympics-2008-beijing/</guid><description turbo="true">About Olympic Games The Olympic flag The modern Olympic Games or Olympics (French: Jeux olympiques) are leading international sporting events featuring summer and winter sports competitions in which thousands of athletes from around the world participate in a variety of competitions. The Olympic Games are considered the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost sports competition with more than 200 nations participating. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the Summer and Winter Games alternating by occurring every four years but two years apart.</description></item></channel></rss>