<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfa Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/alfa-bank/</guid>
      <description>Alfa Bank JSC, the corporate treasury of the Alfa Group, is one of the largest private commercial banks in Russia. It was founded by Russian businessman Mikhail Fridman, who is still the controlling owner today. It is headquartered in Moscow. It operates in seven countries, providing financial services to over 381,600 active corporate customers and 14.2 million retail clients. Alfa-Bank is particularly active in Russia and Ukraine, ranking among top 10 largest banks in terms of capital in both countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bain Capital</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bain-capital/</guid>
      <description> Bain Capital is a private investment firm based in Boston, Massachusetts. It specializes in private equity, venture capital, credit, public equity, impact investing, life sciences and real estate. Bain Capital invests across a range of industry sectors and geographic regions. As of 2018, the firm managed more than $105 billion of investor capital.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principal</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/principal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/principal/</guid>
      <description>The Principal Financial Group is a global financial investment management and insurance company headquartered in Des Moines, Iowa
 Source Enter Lippincott, who, through leadership workshops, gained clarity on the vision and business objectives. We then conducted a global study of 1,200 employees to mine for perceived strengths and desired shifts in the brand evolution. Whether by geography, business unit or tenure, employees were calling for a strong signal about and recognition of the company’s next era — one that was already global, bolder, more collaborative, and more humanly and intellectually inclusive than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santander</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/santander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/santander/</guid>
      <description>Banco Santander, S.A., doing business as Santander Group (/ˌsɑːntɑːnˈdɛər/), is a Spanish multinational commercial bank and financial services company founded and based in Santander, Spain. In addition to hubs in Madrid and Barcelona, Santander maintains a presence in all global financial centres as the largest Spanish banking institution in the world. Although known for its European banking operations, it has extended operations across North and South America, and more recently in continental Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Money</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/yandex-money/</guid>
      <description> Yandex.Money is Russia’s largest electronic payment service according to a 2016 survey by TNS. It is an online payment service that works with two types of clients — individual users and merchants.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-bank/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria, S.A. (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈbaŋko βilˈβao βiθˈkaʝa aɾxenˈtaɾja]), better known by its initialism BBVA, is a multinational Spanish banking group based in Madrid and Bilbao. It is one of the largest financial institutions in the world, and is present mainly in Spain, North America, South America and Turkey.
 The bank was founded as Banco de Bilbao, on May 28, 1857 in Bilbao, Biscay, where it has been headquartered since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBVA Compass</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-compass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bbva-compass/</guid>
      <description>About BBVA Compass BBVA Compass Bancshares, Inc. (formerly Compass Bancshares) is a bank holding company headquartered in Birmingham, Alabama. It has been a subsidiary of the Spanish multinational Banco Bilbao Vizcaya Argentaria since 2007 and operates chiefly in Alabama, Arizona, California, Colorado, Florida, New Mexico, and Texas.
The company is the 30th largest bank in the United States.
BBVA Compass is an official sponsor of the NBA and holds naming rights to BBVA Compass Stadium, a soccer venue in Houston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commercial Bank of Kuwait</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/commercial-bank-of-kuwait/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:58:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/commercial-bank-of-kuwait/</guid>
      <description>History of the Commercial Bank of Kuwait logo   The new Commercial Bank symbol is an amalgamation of calligraphy and image. the words commercial and bank are rendered in kufic, a geometric script, to make a decorative star, recognizable by anyone as a distinctive pattern and, additionally, readable to an Arab. The dual language identity has English type in Paul Renner’s Futura with a compatible Arabic script especially drawn by Ahmed Mustafa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosper</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/prosper/</guid>
      <description>About Prosper (from prosper.com)
Prosper was founded in 2005 as the first peer-to-peer lending marketplace in the United States. Since then, Prosper has facilitated more than $15 billion in loans to more than 910,000 people.
Through Prosper, people can invest in each other in a way that is financially and socially rewarding. Borrowers apply online for a fixed-rate, fixed-term loan between $2,000 and $40,000. Individuals and institutions can invest in the loans and earn attractive returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital One</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:42:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one/</guid>
      <description>About Capital One (from capitalone.com)
Capital One Financial Corporation is a financial holding company whose subsidiaries, which include Capital One, N.A., and Capital One Bank (USA), N.A., had $249.8 billion in deposits and $372.5 billion in total assets as of December 31, 2018. Headquartered in McLean, Virginia, Capital One offers a broad spectrum of financial products and services to consumers, small businesses and commercial clients through a variety of channels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amalgamated Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:52:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Amalgamated Bank logo Amalgamated Bank is the leading financial institution dedicated to providing affordable banking services to working people, unions, and progressive organizations and businesses. Established in 1923 as New York City’s first labor bank, Amalgamated is now the largest union-owned bank in the United States, with locations across the city, as well as in Washington DC, New Jersey, Nevada and California. Pentagram has designed a new brand identity for the bank that updates its look while also honoring its legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Royal Bank of Canada</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 21:39:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/visa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBS Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Maestro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Cirrus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</guid>
      <description>History of the MasterCard logo (from pentagram.com)
The iconic red and yellow intersecting circles of Mastercard are one of the world’s most recognized brands. Today the company launches an evolution of its brand identity featuring a new mark that highlights the connectivity and seamlessness of Mastercard and its payment systems. Designed by Pentagram, the identity brings simplicity and clarity with an increased emphasis on the interlocking circles, and is optimized for use in digital contexts, an increasingly important part of Mastercard’s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hsbc Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/hsbc-bank/</guid>
      <description>About HSBC Bank  The HSBC brand is recognised worldwide. Our latest advertising illustrates our role in helping people, businesses and communities to thrive.
 HSBC is one of the largest banking and financial services organisations in the world, with operations in 66 countries and territories. We aim to be where the growth is, enabling businesses to thrive and economies to prosper, and, ultimately, helping people to fulfil their hopes and realise their ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Group logo (from pentagram.com and medium.com)
Citi Group  In Spring of 1998, Citi announced a merger with Travelers Insurance. At the time, it was the largest merger in the world and the brands needed to be unified to reflect that.
After a brief negotiation the budget for the brand overhaul was pegged at almost $10m, with the design of the logo itself making up $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citibank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
In 1998 financial giants Citicorp and Travelers Group merged to create Citigroup, the largest financial company in the world. After having designed the now ubiquitous identity for the newly formed entity, a three dimensional extension of the brand in the form of Citibank branch interiors and fascias was developed and implemented worldwide.
A visual language and colors and materials palette were developed to represent the new brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chase</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barclays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:42:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Express</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</guid>
      <description>History of the American Express logo (from pentagram.com)
American Express is one of the world’s most trusted and recognized brands. Pentagram has refreshed the American Express visual identity, reasserting and amplifying the brand’s visual expression. The project sought to retool the iconic Blue Box logo, introduced in 1975, and to derive a typographic language that could also live outside the Blue Box, providing a bolder, more confident expression of the brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</guid>
      <description>History of the Bank of America logo (from Bank of America press release)
Bank of America today announced a new brand positioning focused on the question, “What would you like the power to do?” The positioning reflects the impact clients and communities can have when they have the power to achieve their goals, and the company’s role as a partner invested in their success. […]
The Flagscape logo is also getting its first update since being introduced in 1998, reflecting a more modern brand that delivers both cutting-edge technology and high-touch solutions for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fagro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fagro/</guid>
      <description>About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>