<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:42:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital One</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:42:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/capital-one/</guid>
      <description>About Capital One (from capitalone.com)
Capital One Financial Corporation is a financial holding company whose subsidiaries, which include Capital One, N.A., and Capital One Bank (USA), N.A., had $249.8 billion in deposits and $372.5 billion in total assets as of December 31, 2018. Headquartered in McLean, Virginia, Capital One offers a broad spectrum of financial products and services to consumers, small businesses and commercial clients through a variety of channels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amalgamated Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:52:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/amalgamated-bank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Amalgamated Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
Amalgamated Bank is the leading financial institution dedicated to providing affordable banking services to working people, unions, and progressive organizations and businesses. Established in 1923 as New York City’s first labor bank, Amalgamated is now the largest union-owned bank in the United States, with locations across the city, as well as in Washington DC, New Jersey, Nevada and California. Pentagram has designed a new brand identity for the bank that updates its look while also honoring its legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Royal Bank of Canada</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 21:39:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/royal-bank-of-canada/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visa</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/visa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:08:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/ubs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBS Group</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/rbs-group/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Maestro</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-maestro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Cirrus</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard-cirrus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mastercard/</guid>
      <description>History of the MasterCard logo (from pentagram.com)
The iconic red and yellow intersecting circles of Mastercard are one of the world’s most recognized brands. Today the company launches an evolution of its brand identity featuring a new mark that highlights the connectivity and seamlessness of Mastercard and its payment systems. Designed by Pentagram, the identity brings simplicity and clarity with an increased emphasis on the interlocking circles, and is optimized for use in digital contexts, an increasingly important part of Mastercard’s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:45:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deutsche-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citi</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citi/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Group logo (from pentagram.com and medium.com)
Citi Group  In Spring of 1998, Citi announced a merger with Travelers Insurance. At the time, it was the largest merger in the world and the brands needed to be unified to reflect that.
After a brief negotiation the budget for the brand overhaul was pegged at almost $10m, with the design of the logo itself making up $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citibank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citibank/</guid>
      <description>History of the Citi Bank logo (from pentagram.com)
In 1998 financial giants Citicorp and Travelers Group merged to create Citigroup, the largest financial company in the world. After having designed the now ubiquitous identity for the newly formed entity, a three dimensional extension of the brand in the form of Citibank branch interiors and fascias was developed and implemented worldwide.
A visual language and colors and materials palette were developed to represent the new brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chase</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:44:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/chase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barclays</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 01:42:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/barclays/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Express</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/american-express/</guid>
      <description>History of the American Express logo (from pentagram.com)
American Express is one of the world’s most trusted and recognized brands. Pentagram has refreshed the American Express visual identity, reasserting and amplifying the brand’s visual expression. The project sought to retool the iconic Blue Box logo, introduced in 1975, and to derive a typographic language that could also live outside the Blue Box, providing a bolder, more confident expression of the brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-america/</guid>
      <description>History of the Bank of America logo (from Bank of America press release)
Bank of America today announced a new brand positioning focused on the question, “What would you like the power to do?” The positioning reflects the impact clients and communities can have when they have the power to achieve their goals, and the company’s role as a partner invested in their success. […]
The Flagscape logo is also getting its first update since being introduced in 1998, reflecting a more modern brand that delivers both cutting-edge technology and high-touch solutions for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of China</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/bank-of-china/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wells Fargo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fagro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 23:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/wells-fagro/</guid>
      <description>About Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (from Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company press release)
Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company is a diversified, community-based financial services company with $1.9 trillion in assets. Wells Fargo’s vision is to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. Founded in 1852 and headquartered in San Francisco, Wells Fargo provides banking, investment and mortgage products and services, as well as consumer and commercial finance, through 7,800 locations, more than 13,000 ATMs, the internet (wellsfargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>