<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/deloitte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/deloitte/</guid>
      <description>Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu Limited /dəˈlɔɪt ˈtuːʃ toʊˈmɑːtsuː/, commonly referred to as Deloitte, is a multinational professional services network. Deloitte is one of the &amp;ldquo;Big Four&amp;rdquo; accounting organizations and the largest professional services network in the world by revenue and number of professionals with headquarters in London, United Kingdom.
 Source About Deloitte “Deloitte” is the brand under which approximately 286,000 dedicated professionals in independent firms throughout the world collaborate to provide audit &amp;amp; assurance, consulting, financial advisory, risk advisory, tax and related services to select clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity Investments</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/fidelity-investments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/fidelity-investments/</guid>
      <description>Fidelity Investments Inc., commonly referred to as Fidelity, earlier as Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research or FMR, is an American multinational financial services corporation based in Boston, Massachusetts.
 It is one of the largest asset managers in the world with $2.46 trillion in assets under management as of March 2018 and a combined total customer asset value number of $6.7 trillion. Fidelity Investments operates a brokerage firm, manages a large family of mutual funds, provides fund distribution and investment advice, retirement services, Index funds, wealth management, cryptocurrency, securities execution and clearance, and life insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBS Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/dbs-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/dbs-bank/</guid>
      <description> DBS Bank is a Singaporean multinational banking and financial services corporation headquartered in Marina Bay Financial Centre Tower 3, Marina Bay, Singapore. The company was known as The Development Bank of Singapore Limited, before the present name was adopted on 21 July 2003 to reflect its changing role as a regional bank.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/jefferies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/jefferies/</guid>
      <description>Jefferies Group LLC is an American multinational independent investment bank and financial services company that is headquartered in New York City. The firm provides clients with capital markets and financial advisory services, institutional brokerage, securities research, and asset management. This includes mergers and acquisitions, restructuring, and other financial advisory services. The Capital Markets segment also includes its securities trading (including the results of its indirectly partially owned subsidiary, Jefferies High Yield Trading, LLC) and investment banking activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mizuho</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mizuho/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mizuho/</guid>
      <description> Mizuho Financial Group, Inc. ,abbreviated as MHFG, or simply called Mizuho, is a banking holding company headquartered in the Ōtemachi district of Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan. The name &amp;ldquo;mizuho (瑞穂)&amp;rdquo; literally means &amp;ldquo;abundant rice&amp;rdquo; in Japanese and &amp;ldquo;harvest&amp;rdquo; in the figurative sense. Upon its founding, it was the largest bank in the world by assets.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MUFG</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mufg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mufg/</guid>
      <description> Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group, Inc. (MUFG; 株式会社三菱UFJフィナンシャル・グループ, Kabushiki gaisha Mitsubishi Yūefujei Finansharu Gurūpu) is a Japanese bank holding and financial services company headquartered in Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nomura</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/nomura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/nomura/</guid>
      <description> Nomura Holdings, Inc. is a Japanese financial holding company and a principal member of the Nomura Group. It, along with its broker-dealer, banking and other financial services subsidiaries, provides investment, financing and related services to individual, institutional and government customers on a global basis with an emphasis on securities businesses.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMBC</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/smbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/smbc/</guid>
      <description>Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation is a Japanese multinational banking and financial services company headquartered in Yurakucho, Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan. It is the second largest bank in Japan by assets and market capitalization (as of 2019). Along with MUFG and Mizuho, SMBC is referred to as a Japanese megabank, one of the three largest banks who dominate market share in Japan&amp;rsquo;s financial system. The bank is closely affiliated with Sumitomo and Mitsui keiretsu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suite</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/suite/</guid>
      <description> Founded in 2001, Suite delivers industry grade software and services to the financial services community. Our customers include top-tier banks, data-providers, ECN&amp;rsquo;s/online trading platforms, outsourced service providers, hedge funds, and small community banks. We provide analytics for the pricing and risk management of fixed income cash products, fixed income derivatives and credit derivatives. Suite also provides customized software implementations, independent valuation services and portfolio stress testing.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truist</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/truist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/truist/</guid>
      <description>Truist Financial Corp. is an American bank holding company headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina. The company was formed in December 2019 as the result of the merger of BB&amp;amp;T (Branch Banking and Trust Company) and SunTrust Banks. Its bank operates 2,049 branches in 15 states and Washington, D.C., and offers consumer and commercial banking, securities brokerage, asset management, mortgage, and insurance products and services. It is on the list of largest banks in the United States by assets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBRE</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/cbre/</guid>
      <description> CBRE Group, Inc., is an American commercial real estate services and investment firm. The abbreviation CBRE stands for Coldwell Banker Richard Ellis. As of 2018, it is the largest commercial real estate services company in the world.
 Source Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizens</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/citizens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/citizens/</guid>
      <description> Citizens Financial Group, Inc. is an American bank headquartered in Providence, Rhode Island, which operates in the states of Connecticut, Delaware, Maine, Massachusetts, Michigan, New Hampshire, New Jersey, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island and Vermont.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N26</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/n26/</guid>
      <description> N26 (known as Number 26 until July 2016) is a German direct bank, headquartered in Berlin, Germany. N26 offers its services throughout most of the Eurozone, UK, Switzerland and US. It is expected to start operating in Brazil soon.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mizuho</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/mizuho-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/mizuho-2/</guid>
      <description> Mizuho Financial Group, Inc. ,abbreviated as MHFG, or simply called Mizuho, is a banking holding company headquartered in the Ōtemachi district of Chiyoda, Tokyo, Japan. The name &amp;ldquo;mizuho (瑞穂)&amp;rdquo; literally means &amp;ldquo;abundant rice&amp;rdquo; in Japanese and &amp;ldquo;harvest&amp;rdquo; in the figurative sense. Upon its founding, it was the largest bank in the world by assets.
 Source </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>