<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</title>
    <link>https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in banking &amp; finance on Logotyp.us</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logotyp.us/industry/banking-finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Commonwealth Bank</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/commonwealth-bank/</guid>
      <description>The Commonwealth Bank of Australia (CBA), or CommBank, is an Australian multinational bank with businesses across New Zealand, Asia, the United States and the United Kingdom. It provides a variety of financial services including retail, business and institutional banking, funds management, superannuation, insurance, investment and broking services. The Commonwealth Bank is the largest Australian listed company on the Australian Securities Exchange as of August 2015 with brands including Bankwest, Colonial First State Investments, ASB Bank (New Zealand), Commonwealth Securities (CommSec) and Commonwealth Insurance (CommInsure).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TPG Capital</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/tpg-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/tpg-capital/</guid>
      <description>TPG Capital, previously known as Texas Pacific Group, is an American investment company. The private equity firm is focused on leveraged buyouts and growth capital. TPG manages investment funds in growth capital, venture capital, public equity, and debt investments. The firm invests in a range of industries including consumer/retail, media and telecommunications, industrials, technology, travel, leisure, and health care.
 The firm was founded in 1992 by David Bonderman, James Coulter, and William S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Technologies</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/united-technologies/</guid>
      <description>United Technologies Corporation (UTC) was an American multinational conglomerate headquartered in Farmington, Connecticut. It merged with the Raytheon Company in April 2020 to form Raytheon Technologies. It researched, developed, and manufactured products in numerous areas, including aircraft engines, aerospace systems, HVAC, elevators and escalators, fire and security, building automation, and industrial products, among others. UTC was also a large military contractor, getting about 10% of its revenue from the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venmo</title>
      <link>https://logotyp.us/logo/venmo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logotyp.us/logo/venmo/</guid>
      <description>Venmo is a mobile payment service owned by PayPal. Venmo account holders can transfer funds to others via a mobile phone app; both the sender and receiver have to live in the U.S. It handled $12 billion in transactions in the first quarter of 2018. Venmo was launched in 2009 targeting the use case of friends splitting bills, e.g. for movies, dinner, rent, tickets, etc.
 By default, Venmo publishes every peer-to-peer transaction (excluding the amount), a feature which was shown by researchers to reveal sensitive details about users&amp;rsquo; lives in some situations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>